Chapter 1328: The Stage on Sky Arena

After the individual competitions, Happy temporarily held a 3-2 lead. But Wang Jiexi's performance during the group arena had completely changed the atmosphere of the entire stadium. Even if Team Tiny Herb had a 5-0 lead, the fans might not be as excited as they were now.

This kind of atmosphere once again put Chen Guo in a bad mood.

Clearly, Happy was still in the lead, and clearly, the team competition had yet to be played, but the fans of Tiny Herb looked as though they had already won the final victorymatch.

Was this because of Wang Jiexi?

Looking at the Tiny Herb fans around her, Chen Guo noticed that their gazes were indeed fixated on one point - their team's captain, Wang Jiexi. Because Wang Jiexi had appeared in the group arena, and because Wang Jiexi would definitely appear in the team competition, they immediately had a different level of confidence in their team. To Chen Guo, this was a kind of blind faith. Tiny Herb performed very well during the group arena, but it wasn't certain how strong their performance would be during the team competition.

With such a ruckus in the crowd, the downside was that it filled the entire break between the individual rounds and the group competition, making it extremely difficult for Team Happy's members to communicate. If this was always the case, it would almost be a necessity for the teams to have a seperate room to prepare in.

"These guys are acting like they've already won, we need to make them shut up!" Fang Rui expressed, with everyone understanding what he was referring to.

"There's no need to be influenced by the atmosphere, think about how calm we were when playing at Tyranny's home stadium," Ye Xiu said.

"Do you have to say these kinds of things on our behalf?" Chen Guo said.

"It's an objective matter of fact! Isn't it the same no matter who says it?" Ye Xiu asked.

"But now that you say that, there's no motivation for anyone to learn. If you don't believe me, just ask them," Chen Guo said.

"None at all," Fang Rui replied.

"Haha," Tang Rou laughed.

"Steamed Bun you shut up!" Seeing that Steamed Bun was about to say something, Chen Guo hurriedly stopped him.

"Alright then, since everyone is so unhappy about their arrogance, let's strike them a ruthless blow during the team competition! We'll focus on Wang Jiexi," Ye Xiu replied.

"Have you also lost all your rationality!" Chen Guo yelled.

At this moment, Qiao Yifan meekly raised his hand and asked, "When we were preparing for this round, didn't we practice to focus on Wang Jiexi in the first place?"

"Ah?" Chen Guo was startled and realized that she had been tricked once again…...

"Let's get ready to go onstage!" Ye Xiu called.

Team Happy's away game against Team Tiny Herb had finally reached the deciding tiebreaker round. The participants in the team competition walked onto the stage in succession.

Team Happy: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Tang Rou, An Wenyi, Qiao Yifan.

Team Tiny Herb: Wang Jiexi, Xu Bin, Gao Yingjie, Liu Xiaobie, Yuan Baiqing, Liang Fang.

"Ah, it seems that the lineup for both teams haven't changed very much, it's still the usual lineup for the team competition," commentator Pan Lin explained after seeing the list of names for both teams.

"Happy did make one change, Tang Rou is part of the original lineup, while Qiao Yifan is the sixth player," Li Yibo replied.

"This should indicate that they want to play a more aggressive style!" Pan Lin replied.

"It does seem to be the case," Li Yibo nodded his head.

"Hahaha, playing an aggressive style in their away game, how bold," Ruan Cheng laughed, but anyone could hear the mockery in his laughter, looking down on Happy for not knowing their own limits.

"On the side of Team Tiny Herb, Yuan Baiqing is playing his Cleric, Aweto, this should also mean that they want to play a more aggressive game!" Pan Lin said. Team Tiny Herb's healer was very unique, their player could play two different characters and could choose to use either the Cleric or the Paladin in different competitions, and from this decision, one could roughly tell what Tiny Herb wanted to do in the team battle.

"Tiny Herb is playing a home game, there's no reason for them to focus on defense." Ruan Cheng replied.

"Yes, it looks like this is going to be a very intense fight. I'm looking forward to it," Pan Lin said.

While the commentators were discussing, the players had already exchanged greetings, entered the player booths, and the timer was ticking down to the start of the team competition.

"Let's see what map Tiny Herb has picked for the team battle," Pan Lin remarked.

"Sky Arena!" Li Yibo was momentarily stunned when he saw the map that the players eventually loaded into.

"Selecting this map during the team battle... is really very rare!" Pan Lin was also shocked.

Sky Arena was a map that could be considered extremely simple for use in the team battle. The only change in terrain in the whole map were the stairs. At the outermost regions of the map were terraces that looked down on the stage from above, in the middle was the stage itself, which in turn was surrounded by steps.

"This map... there shouldn't be too many complex ways to use the map features strategically," Li Yibo said.

"Would Tiny Herb have put any special effort into researching how to use the height difference from the steps?" Pan Lin said.

"This..." Li Yibo searched his mind for the details of Tiny Herb's past matches, but for a while couldn't give a definite answer.

"It seems that Tiny Herb has been very thorough in their aggressive stance!" Ruan Cheng said.

"Let's take a look and see how they're going to play aggressively," Li Yibo said, obviously favouring Ruan Cheng's opinion in this case.

Very quickly, the characters from both sides finished loading in, each standing at opposite ends of the arena. Because of the high stage in the center of the map, the two teams couldn't see each other, but in reality, they were more or less at an equal distance from the stage, a special feature of the team battle.

"Sky Arena, hm, why don't we just go on the stage and determine the winner?" Ye Xiu asked in the global channel, but none of Happy's characters made any immediate moves.

"Or how about you just come up, Old Wang, and the two of us can fight it out, whoever loses will just have their whole team GG?" Seeing that there was no response from the other side, Ye Xiu provoked them once again.

Team Tiny Herb still had no reaction, but the entire stadium was already in uproar because of Ye Xiu's unbridled arrogance.

"I think I'm beginning to understand the hate that Tyranny has for him," Tang Rou said to the others with her. Losing three times in a row to Ye Xiu and Excellent Era was still bearable, but the crux of the issue was that they still lost after all the provocation and ridicule, making it truly unbearable. This kind of unbridled arrogance was something that was usually displayed by the villain, and afterwards, the hero would go and defeat him, slapping his face. But now, the hero couldn't win, instead losing to this kind of villain, how disgusted would the viewers be? And on top of that, this had happened for three years straight, Team Tyranny's hatred was indeed very scientific.

It looked as if the Team Tiny Herb fans in the crowd were already going insane, but the players in the field looked pretty calm, with no one bothering to respond in the global channel. Instead, the characters from Team Tiny Herb all followed their established paths and advanced tactically.

"It can't be that you want me to let you have the first move?" Ye Xiu was still talking.

"That's enough, what's the point of talking so much rubbish?" Wang Jiexi replied at long last, disapproving of Ye Xiu's trash talk.

At this time, Ye Xiu sent a "sigh of relief" emoticon and said, "And here I thought that all of you weren't here!"

"We're here!" Wang Jiexi once again replied and informed him. At this time, Tiny Herb's five players had already appeared at the edge of the stage, looking down from above and meeting Team Happy's five players face-to-face.

"No one move, let them come down here!" Ye Xiu simply issued his orders in the global channel.

Tiny Herb didn't hesitate and immediately charging down the flight of stairs from the stage.

"Damn, they really came, let's retreat!" Ye Xiu once again shouted in the global channel.

As such, Happy's characters started to turn around and ascend the stairs to the viewing terraces behind them, and the team that occupied the high ground abruptly changed again.

"Let's open fire!" As Ye Xiu issued his command, Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain launched the first attack of the match.

The artillery shells spat tongues of flame as they flew, but Tiny Herb's five members all scattered, with none of them being hit by the attack. But by their team composition, Team Tiny Herb didn't have any long-ranged attackers, with no one being able to directly engage in a firefight with a Launcher. Team Happy, who were now occupying the high ground, seemed to be in a superior position at the moment.

"Possessing the high ground means having a definite advantage. If we were to use control of the high ground as the deciding factor in victory, then this map could be considered very complex. Each set of stairs has many layers, and the map is filled with them, so to make use of the high ground requires awareness of the details of the entire map, unlike many other maps where controlling one focal point means establishing an absolute advantage," Li Yibo began discussing the current circumstances in the match.

'That's true, for now, Happy has the height advantage, but looking at the map, Tiny Herb could just change their position and climb to the same height as Happy," Pan Lin replied.

"So in this map, the battles that occur won't be the vertical battles centered around the stairs, but instead horizontal battles," Li Yibo said.

"You're right, Tiny Herb has already made such arrangements. It seems that they aren't too worried about Happy's temporary control of the high ground."

"The lowground is the inner circle of the map, with a smaller circumference, so it's not possible for Happy to occupy a high position and continually suppress Tiny Herb," Li Yibo said.

"That's right, Tiny Herb has moved around the inner circle, and gained horizontal distance from Happy."

"Yes, with this position, they can more or less start their advance."

"Alright! Tiny Herb is advancing! When the two teams face off horizontally on the stairs, the difference in height created by each step will affect many minor details. Tiny Herb must have done some special practice in this area, which is probably why they picked this map. Tiny Herb has charged up! Fuck!" Li Yibo was excitedly explaining, but at the end, he let his mouth run for a moment, uttering a vulgarity during the broadcast and leaving the broadcasting team completely flustered. It was only one word, and it was too late now that it had been said, so Li Yibo had already covered his mouth.

Tiny Herb charged up the stairs, but Happy's members once again descended the stairs…...

And from the directions given out in Happy's team chat, everyone could see what Happy's intention was.

The stage in the center!

"The stage in the center... If we're talking about controlling the high ground, this would be the most appropriate spot. The difference with the viewing terraces on the edge of the map is that here, the inner circle is the high ground, while the outer circle is the low ground, so if they have the high ground here, Tiny Herb can't just pull away horizontally and create a breakthrough point that way," Pan Lin exclaimed.

"Ah! Tiny Herb has also reacted very quickly, they've immediately turned around and come down."

"The two sides have the same intentions! They're both rushing towards the stage now."

"Is this really going to be where the match is decided? The steps here aren't as numerous as at the viewing platforms, but it's still enough for ten people to battle it out."

"Oh! Without reaching the stage, the two sides have already started attacking!"

"This isn't just a race, the two sides are using their attacks to control and restrict their opponent's movements!"

The two teams finally began to fight in earnest.

Chapter 1329: Happy’s Primary Target

Boom! Boom!

As always, Dancing Rain struck first with her longest attack range. However, the cannonfire did nothing to stop Tiny Herb's advance.

Xu Bin, Angelica, the Alliance's Number One Knight, with the so-called strongest shield Wall of Sigh, blocked Dancing Rain's line-of-sight cannonfire.

Team Tiny Herb advanced as a whole and soon enough, two star cards rose from behind the Wall of Sigh, one high, one low. Tiny Herb had two Witches in their midst.

Star Ray!

The two star cards cracked, releasing two rays of light right at Happy's formation.

However...

Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shield!

Lord Grim came to the head of the formation and opened up is Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, blocking the attacks like Xu Bin's Angelica.

The two sides were now at mid-range of one another.

Stringer, Sky Piercing Strike!

Happy's Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea launched attacks simultaneously. This was clearly an AoE attack that Xu Bin's Angelica alone didn't have the ability to block. As for Tiny Herb? The two Witches once again struck as one.

Lava Flask, Acid Rain Flask!

The two flasks had only just been tossed when, with two bangs, Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations had already switched to gun form, smoke rising from the muzzle. The two flasks had barely gone anywhere before they were smashed, lava and acid rain spraying across Tiny Herb's formation. Naturally, it wouldn't harm them, but this skill was clearly useless against Happy too. Instead, Happy's Stinger had arrived above their heads.

Scatter!

Team Tiny Herb's characters scattered in all directions. Just as they dodged the Stinger, Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree was already charging up the stairs towards the arena. Their offensive might've been stopped, but utilizing their need to dodge Happy's offensive, they could gain the higher ground first.

Plus, on these steps, Happy didn't have anyone who could move as swiftly as a Witch, thus they had to attack to prevent this.

Laser Cannon!

A beam of light came roaring out from Dancing Rain's cannon, but it wasn't headed for Kind Tree.

Vaccaria!

Dancing Rain's target was, shockingly, Vaccaria. As they scattered to avoid the Stinger, Tiny Herb's members lost Xu Bin's Angelica's protection. Dancing Rain's attack was surprisingly sent towards Vaccaria.

What sort of decision was this?

Wasn't the crux of the current battle fighting for the high ground? Happy wasn't going to try and stop Kind Tree? Did they have other plans?

The three in the broadcasting room were puzzled. However, the pace of the battle didn't give them time to consider this problem carefully.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Soft Mist charged out from Happy's formation, yet her target was also Vaccaria.

Boundless Sea, Lord Grim, all of Happy's characters had begun to attack, but their targets were all clear as day.

Wang Jiexi, Vaccaria.

Tiny Herb's best player, Tiny Herb's most powerful character. Happy actually decided to charge straight at this wall from the beginning of the match. They ignored Kind Tree who had charged towards the arena to gain the higher ground. Happy didn't seem to have any intentions to fight over this with Tiny Herb.

"No way! Happy's main target is Wang Jiexi?" Pan Lin yelled.

"Heh, what a joke," Ruan Cheng sneered.

"This…" Li Yibo fell silent, not sure what to think of this. He felt that Happy's strategy was irrational, so there must be something else to happy's plans. He'd wait before judging.

So this is your plan?

Wang Jiexi gazed at the attacks headed for him. Vaccaria side stepped the Laser Cannon, jumping on his broom and circling in the air, causing Soft Mist's Dragon Breaks the Ranks to miss and leaving her five body units behind. Wang Jiexi ignored these obvious attacks, attention fixed on the other two who were charging over. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim and Fang Rui's Boundless Sea. What were these two planning to do?

Wang Jiexi had seen through Happy's intentions, but he didn't try to avoid them, instead heading straight at them.

Qi Blade!

Boundless Sea struck first, sending out a knife-hand that escaped almost everyone's notice. However, it didn't escape Wang Jiexi's gaze. Vaccaria once again spun himself as he flew, dodging the wave of qi from the Qi Blade with alarming precision. Lord Grim and Boundless Sea were now right in front of him and he quickly gave them a Disperse Powder. However, there was no chance that these two would be struck so easily. One left and one right, they jumped to the side to avoid it.

Shadow Cloak!

Lord Grim flung a hand forwards, sending a grasping shadow at Vaccaria. Vaccaria swerved at an incredibly strange angle in midair, managing to dart out of the shadow.

Shadow Cloak!

Vaccaria used the exact same skill in response. Lord Grim jumped back, but the Shadow Cloak continued to advance, unwilling to let him go. However, just as it was about to catch him, the shadows seemed to split and a figure darted through.

Dragon Tooth!

Lord Grim had went right through Vaccaria's Shadow Cloak with a Dragon Tooth. What bold judgement and mechanics!

Would countering be possible if they waited for their opponent to make the first move? Too many people were unable to make such a judgement, buty Wang Jiexi could. He could detect these miniscule timings, so he couldn't let Ye Xiu do as he wished. Vaccaria immediately retreated, dodging the attack, but tightly following this, a flash of cold light appeared in his view. Lord Grim had darted to his side with a Shining Cut.

Swerve!

Vaccaria once again swerved through the air, dodging Lord Grim's attack. His swift flight speed allowed him to pull away from Lord Grim by a full two body units. The other members of Tiny Herb didn't just stand and watch their captain get ganged up on. At a time like this, with Wang Jiexi luring in the opponent's offensive, the others did what any core player of a powerhouse team would do and took the chance to find opportunities to attack.

Charge!

As Vaccaria swerved elegantly through the air, Xu Bin's Angelica was already charging over.

Triple Slash!

Liu Xiaobie's Flying Swords had also rapidly approached Fang Rui's Boundless Sea, interrupting the attack he was about to launch at Vaccaria.

It was just that Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree seemed to be a little out of sync with the rest of the team. With Happy's strategic intentions exposed, his position made him seem like he had been lured away. However, was Happy really trying to take out Vaccaria? Were they really going to kick this wall of Tiny Herb's from the get go? Gao Yingjie was suspicious. Should he really give up such a good position?

Shattering the Lands!

Gao Yingjie had yet to make a decision when Soft Mist, after her unsuccessful Dragon Breaks the Ranks, had already charged back. This level 75 skill had been thrown rampantly towards the three Tiny Herb members over there.

Boom!

The magical energy seeped through the cracks into the ground. Liu Xiaobie dodged nimbly. On the other hand, Xu Bin used Angelica's impressive defense to tank the hit and quickly headed towards Soft Mist, who was stuck in her ending lag. Vaccaria was even more elegant. The moment Shattering the Lands struck, he had sped out of range, and the moment the magical energy began to disperse, he was already back, launching an offensive on Soft Mist with Xu Bin's Angelica.

Satellite Beam!

That was when the Launcher's high-level skill descended from the skies, covering Soft Mist. The smaller beams whirled out from the center, aiming to strike at the two. However, Angelica raised his shield, catching the beam that crashed down on him and breaking through with brute force. Vaccaria, on the other hand, gave a display of impressive agility, darting through the gaps between the beams without a scratch.

The broom swung up, but, noticing an attack coming from the side, Wang Jiexi had to have Vaccaria dodge once more. Lord Grim had already arrived in front of him.

"Yingjie, keep an eye on Boundless Sea. Xiaobie go after the healer."

In the Tiny Herb team chat, Wang Jiexi calmly made strategic arrangements. Against Happy's strategy, Tiny Herb was finally making arrangements to counter.

Boundless Sea? After hesitating for a moment, Gao Yingjie, having already decided to give up this vantage point, began to search for the Qi Master's form with orders from his captain.

Because the player was Fang Rui, the Master of Dirty Play, his presence and intentions could become a major threat to Tiny Herb at any time. Tiny Herb did not dare underestimate him, even having someone go to keep an eye on him.

Whoosh!

Kind Tree flew down from the arena, advancing straight towards Boundless Sea. Fang Rui had already noticed, but wasn't willing to give up on the attack he was prepping.

Seismic Throw!

Boundless Sea slammed his palms onto the ground and qi rushed at Angelica and Vaccaria, who were advancing on Soft Mist.

Soft Mist had managed to get out of her ending lag by then and used the opening Boundless Sea's Seismic Throw created, Tyrant's Destruction!

Retreat!

Angelica and Vaccaria had to back away to dodge the sweep attack, and Soft Mist then sent forth a Sky Strike, the angle of it pulling them both in range. But Angelica threw his shield forth and turned, knocking the blow to one side. Vaccaria then advanced, Sweeping Soft Mist into the air.

However, this knockup skill of Witches was the worst of all 24 classes. The knockup height was very limited. Usually, Witches would fly up and use their broom and their other special methods of attack to send the target higher and higher. However, Vaccaria wasn't given that opportunity. Lord Grim's attacks once again came down on him.

Clang!

Vaccaria's Stardust Extermination parried Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and a figure flashed by behind Vaccaria.

Kind Tree!

Though Wang Jiexi had told him to keep an eye on Boundless Sea, the situation on the battlefield was ever changing. Orders shouldn't be ignored, but often times, players had to judge the situation and make decisions on their own. Seeing that Vaccaria needed a helping hand with continuing his offensive and that Kind Tree was close enough, Gao Yingjie immediately flew over to continue the attack that had been blocked by Lord Grim.

Chapter 1330: Joint Attack

Could Kind Tree hit Soft Mist?

Everyone was nervously watching for this, but then heard, with a shlink, a blade of sword energy unsheath and arc through the air.

"Sword Draw? This close?!" Li Yibo exclaimed in shock.

Yes, Lord Grim and Vaccaria stood so close, and at such a distance, Sword Draw shouldn't have had a chance to be used. Before the sword even came out of the sheathed, it would've probably already been suppressed.

　

However, right now, Lord Grim's Sword Draw successfully arced through the air in a circle. Not only did Wang Jiexi not block the attack, but he was jumping back to dodge as well, and Kind Tree, behind him, was instantly exposed to the sword energy of this Sword Draw. Gao Yingjie wasn't slow, but it was too late now. Blood splashed into the air, and his advance had been pushed back by Lord Grim's Sword Draw.

　

How did this Sword Draw find its way out?

Everything had happened too quickly, and no one had been paying attention to that moment. Playback? During such an intense moment, how could they have time to watch a playback? It was unfortunate, but probably only Wang Jiexi was the only other person who understood why Sword Draw was successful. It was because… Lord Grim's weapon was the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella!

The ribs of the umbrella at the top flipped up into spear form had stopped Stardust Extermination's attack. At the same time, the bottom of the shaft was unsheathed into sword form in a Sword Draw, allowing Lord Grim to successfully use this skill at such a distance. For any normal Blade Master, it would be impossible to parry another's attacks and use Sword Draw at the same time. In other words, this was a pace that was unique to unspecialized Lord Grim, the unspecialized blitz that no one had been able to counter yet.

If you didn't experience it personally, then it really was hard to notice!

Wang Jiexi thought to himself, already back on the offensive after dodging Sword Draw's sword energy.

"Xiaobie, behind you!" At the same time, he sent this message.

Shlink!

Sword Draw appeared once more on the field. Liu Xiaobie didn't even look. His Flying Swords turned half way and sent out a wave of sword energy. Behind him, Boundless Sea was charging over. Fang Rui naturally couldn't see Wang Jiexi's warning and this attack came abruptly to him. It was just unfortunate that this wasn't the best distance for such an attack. Wang Jiexi was in an intense battle himself, after all. A warning was already good enough; there was no way he could help Liu Xiaobie calculate the timing, too.

　　

His relatively far distance gave Fang Rui enough time to react. Boundless Sea jumped backwards, avoiding the strike, but Liu Xiaobie couldn't just ignore Boundless Sea and continue attacking Little Cold Hands. He immediately made a decision to advance on Boundless Sea.

That was when Little Cold Hands raised his cross and began to cast, a holy white light shining like a flame on the cross.

"Xiaobie, behind you!" On the field, Tiny Herb's five members had different views of the field, and it was natural for them to warn others of these sneak attacks when they saw it. Right then, it was Tiny Herb's healer, Yuan Baiqing, that saw Little Cold Hands casting. He realized, with a single glance, that Little Cold Hands wasn't aiming to heal, but to attack. This was a Sacred Fire.

Seeing another warning, Liu Xiaobie knew who was behind him. Striking wouldn't be able to interrupt the other this time. He could only dodge!

　

Move, turn! Flying Swords rapidly dodged to one side. Now, he didn't dare let either Boundless Sea nor Little Cold Hands out of his sight. He was trying to find a good vantage point now. As for Little Cold Hand's attack, he must've dodged it, right?

Indeed, he had dodged it and the Sacred Fire didn't even touch Flying Swords. Just as the holy white flame jumped, Little Cold Hands turned and Yuan Baiqing realized that something was wrong.

"Captain!" He never would've thought that Little Cold Hands' Sacred Fire wasn't directed at Liu Xiaobie's Flying Swords, but at Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria.

His incorrect warning not only interrupted the offensive Flying Swords who was charging at Boundless Sea, but also made Wang Jiexi let his guard down.

Damn it!

Yuan Baiqing was frustrated with himself. However, even if he could go back and redo things, what should he do? Little Cold Hands had such precise control over the timing of skills, able to finishing adjusting his aim at the very last moment of his casting. Even if he had realized that Vaccaria was being targeted and gave such a warning, Little Cold Hands would probably adjust Sacred Fire so that it was aimed at Flying Swords instead.

　

The other acted in accordance to Tiny Herb's actions. He couldn't not warn, but doing so didn't do them any good. The only way would have been to interrupt the skill. Unfortunately, it was too late now. The holy white Sacred Fire flared, and Wang Jiexi, facing off against the unspecialized blitz, was oblivious to the danger. An Wenyi's judgement was precise, and the Sacred Fire vanished practically the moment it flared, but everyone could see how this holy white flame latched itself onto Vaccaria's form.

Not bad at all!

Vaccaria's view clearly turned towards Little Cold Hands for a moment, seeming to have glanced towards the young player over there.

However, how much use would it be?

Wang Jiexi didn't panic at all and didn't make any extra actions apart from the glance he gave Little Cold Hands. He didn't stop either. Vaccaria was still doing whatever he had been doing before. Sacred Fire's three seconds of silence could be fatal, but for a Witch, they used all sorts of magic tools to strengthen their brooms in close combat. They had little to no skills which were directly used to attack. Using tools to strengthen their broom, in the end, the effects were only displayed through normal attacks.

　

In the next three seconds, Vaccaria had merely lost the enhancements from his magic tools, weakening his attacks. To a Witch, this wasn't a fatal blow. In fact, he didn't even need to stop his offensive. Normal attacks, Vaccaria had already been using normal attacks originally!

Stardust Extermination continued to sweep forth and Lord Grim swung his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, parry!

However, in the moment he parried Stardust Extermination, Lord Grim's figure suddenly swayed.

A seemingly useless action, but like that, a bloom of light appeared in front of Wang Jiexi's eyes.

Heat-Seeking Missiles!

Sweep it away? Stardust Extermination had just been knocked to the side by the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. It was too late.

Dodge it? Heat Seeking Missile's AoE wasn't small, and he was also under the silencing effect of Sacred Fire and was thus unable to fly on his broom.

The other member of his team wouldn't be able to get there in time to help, so Wang Jiexi could only watch as the missile plummeted towards him, boosted by the flames it spat and splitting the air with a piercing howl.

Boom!

The immense mushroom cloud enveloped Vaccaria's form at once and the other members of Tiny Herb could only watch, unable to help. They even had to be careful that they themselves weren't caught up in the shockwave.

The three seconds of Sacred Fire's silence also ended then, but all of Happy's members launched attacks at that swaying, but still present figure in the smoke.

Flash Burst!

　

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

　　

X-1 Extruder!

Three characters, three directions, in addition to Lord Grim who stuck to Vaccaria's side. Their attacks disregarded all else. Tiny Herb didn't just have Wang Jiexi, after all, they still had Xu Bin, still had Gao Yingjie, still had Liu Xiaobie, but Happy completely ignored these three attackers, even if attacks came towards them.

They might not be able to stop these attacks, but they could disrupt them. So long as there was an opening in the opponent's formation, Wang Jiexi would be able to get Vaccaria out. All of Tiny Herb's members were infinitely confident in that, so they each chose their quickest attacks.

Star Refraction! Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree cast out a star card.

Roar! Xu Bin's Angelica bellowed, releasing the Knight's AoE taunt skill.

Shadow Steps! Liu Xiaobie's Flying Swords immediately split into eight, all swarming forwards to disrupt Happy's offensive.

Even Yuan Baiqing's Aweto, seeing that he was being ignored, silently began to cast a Hypnosis.

Whose skill would be faster?

After Star Refraction's star card cracked open, Star Ray shot out, striking each of Happy's members. However, Dancing Rain's X-1 Extruder had already been released, and attacking the character wouldn't knock the X-1 Extruder off course.

Knocked by the refraction, Soft Mist swayed to the side, but Dancing Fire Flowing Flame in her hand remained on course under her mechanics.

Fang Rui once again displayed his cunning as a Master of Dirty Play. Before the Star Refraction hit, he purposefully turned Boundless Sea slightly, and thus, the attack knocked Boundless Sea back to his original position.

Lord Grim, well, his actions were even more simple. Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up and he just ignored everything behind him.

As for Angelica's Roar?

The Knight's aggro-pulling skill was the ultimate counter to this sort of focused attack, but Xu Bin wasn't so optimistic. He had a Knight's Roar, but his opponents weren't bereft of a method to stop it.

Calm and Composed!

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea immediately stopped his Flash Burst when Angelica used Roar, releasing a Calm and Composed instead. All characters in range would be cleared of fear, taunts, and other such statuses.

Knowing that the opponent had a Qi Master, Xu Bin had already expected this, However, this at least interrupted Boundless Sea's Flash Burst, and that would at least give Vaccaria an opening, right?

In the yet to disperse smoke, Vaccaria's form charged in Boundless Sea's direction as expected, but in the next moment, Lord Grim had darted in front of him.

Swerve!

Vaccaria, flicked the handle of his broom, changing direction in midair and flying low with the body bowed.

Shining Cut!

　　

With a flash of cold light, Lord Grim once again flashed in front of Vaccaria.

Swerve again!

Vaccaria turned a full right angle.

Charge, Lord Grim skidding in front of him.

Swerve again!

　

This time, Vaccaria shot upwards towards the sky.

　　

There was a humming sound, and Wang Jiexi recognized it as the sound of Rotor Wings. Lord Grim had flown up as well.

Too slow! Watching Lord Grim use that skill in an attempt to fly up and block him, Wang Jiexi felt rather incredulous.

"Captain, behind you!" However, he soon saw such a warning in the team chat, four such warnings, one from each player.

Too late.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart pierced through his chest.

Chapter 1331: Forceful

Blood sprayed into the air. Everyone could clearly see the way Soft Mist's dDancing Fire Flowing Flame impaled Vaccaria.

How could it be?

　　

The crowd stared, dumbstruck with gasps of shock.

First consumed by a Heat-Seeking Missile, then pierced through the chest by Soft Mist's spear. This was theirat most reliable captain, Wang Jiexi, and their most powerful character of their team, Vaccaria! Yet now he was hanging from the spear of that disgrace who had promised to 1v3, like helpless prey. What a joke… How could this happen?

This couldn't be real!

The audience in the stadium couldn't accept what was happening before their eyes, but the match wouldn't wait for them. Soft mMist retracted her spear and Vaccaria's Stardust Extermination seemed like it was about to fly up again, but before he could do so, Lord Grim arrived from above and crashed down.

Eagle Stamp!

Vaccaria was sent to the ground.

Qi Blast!

Boundless Sea had readied a high-level skill, and the turmoulous qi energy was blasted into Vaccaria's body. His magic robes swelled up and blood seemed to spray once more from where Soft Mist had impaled him.

The qi energy silently broke Vaccaria down from the inside out, and Dancing Rain's X-1 Extruder arrived. Vaccaria was pulled in, unable to resist.

Liu Xiaobie's Shadow Step clones flashed in and out, but from beginning to end, no one evenr really paid the clones any mind. Happy seemed to only see Vaccaria. The only attacks they went to deal with were the ones that would disrupt their offensive on Vaccaria. For example, Lord Grim landed once more and turned, suddenly shooting a bullet behind him. The bullet flew, heading directly for their Cleric, Aweto. He had been so close to finishing that long cast for Hypnosis, but in the final moments, Lord Grim had struck him...

Boom!

The X-1 Extruder finally exploded, and Vaccaria was once more consumed by light and fire. The audience couldn't keep watching, and nor could the members of Tiny Herb, on or off stage.

　

This was their captain, the one that had always led them forth. How could he be toyed with by Happy like that?

Formless Phantom Blade!

Liu Xiaobie's Flying Swords threw forth a wave of sword-light wildly and crazily, cutting through the fire and light. Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree also darted into the sky with a Broom Tornado and then dropped down swiftly. Knight's Spirit! Xu Bin activated Angelica's Awakening skill and Angelica, under Knight's Spirit, used a Fair Heroic Leap, leaping to the other end with an earth-shaking landing.

Tiny Herb's three members stood steady around their captain, protecting him. But...

Charged Artillery!

Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

That was when Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea simultaneously launched attacks, both using charged AoEs in a pincer attack. Even Angelica's Sighing Wall wouldn't be able to block these two attacks completely.

These were the awakening skills of Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea, their specialty being that they could both be charged. After charging, their power was immense. No matter if it was the explosion that Charged Artillery created or the eruption of qi from Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, neither of these were something that a shield could block completely.

　

Dodging was a priority, but what about their captain? Would he have the time to dodge this wave of attacks?

　　

"Dodge!"

In the Team Tiny Herb chat, an order appeared from their captain, clear as crystal.

Everyone was mentally jolted back to clarity, and the Tiny Herb fans in the stadium began to cheer once more, and this was just an order. Tiny Herb hadn't even done anything yet!

However, if that's what the captain wanted, then they had to dodge!

Xu Bin, Gao Yingjie and Liu Xiaobie all scattered in their own direction and prepared to counterattack in accordance with their own observations and judgements. Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria had also raised his Stardust Extermination.

"Happy really is bold…" In the broadcasting room, Pan Lin's comment was thus after he had finished admiring Happy's performance, wide eyed in surprise.

Directly choosing Wang Jiexi as their main target was a bold enough strategy from Happy, but what was shocking was that they were carrying it out pretty well.

"It's rare to see someone who can place Wang Jiexi at such a disadvantage," Pan Lin noted.

"Perhaps, he's the only one…" Li Yibo replied.

Pan Lin naturally knew who the "he" Li Yibo was talking was was. Ye Xiu, there was only Ye Xiu, the Ye Xiu that had been at the peak of Glory when Wang Jiexi had only just joined the alliance. Compared to the legend of three consecutive championships, Wang Jiexi was a mere Best Rookie in season three. It was impressive that he didn't hit Rookie's Block, but faced with the one who erected a dynasty of three consecutive championships, it was nothing.

　　

One, an ultimate god that had dominated the heavens like the sun, and the other, simply the most talented of a bunch of newbies. Against Wang Jiexi, what did Ye Xiu have to fear or worry about?

Nothing. Nothing at all.

Happy could execute such a bold plan of attack, because this member of Team Happy wasn't someone who feared and respected Wang Jiexi like most players.

Attack, only relentless attack.

When Xu Bin and the other two scattered, Wang Jiexi noticed that Happy's characters didn't react. They continued to fixate on the center of the pincer attack, on Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria.

Wasn't this a little too stubborn of them?

Wang Jiexi was surprised. Happy seemed to have set killing him as their ultimate goal . Were they not going to consider the result of this team competition any longer? Otherwise, why would they play in such an unbalanced waystyle? Why would they be so relentlessly stubborn in focusing their offense on him, even at such risks?

Their attacks might be successful, but they'd pay a higher price to do so. Had they not thought of that? Or, perhaps, had they thought of it, but were ignoring it?

Wang Jiexi's Vaccaria had already hopped onto Stardust Extermination, prepared to escape the terrifying attack Happy had was launchinged. However, that was when Ye Xiu Lord Grim and Tang Rou's Soft Mist charged over.

They had done nothing when Xu Bin and co had escaped, but when Vaccaria moved, they immediately acted.

This wasn't a good situation at all! If they came back to save him, then they would be hit by the two awakening skills. If they didn't, then there'd be little chance he could throw the both of them off, and those two skills were about to arrive. Was having the three of them dodge a bad judgementcall? Should they have gathered their strength to break through one side?

In that moment, many thoughts flashed through Wang Jiexi's mind. This match, the simple map, had come to a situation that was rather complicated. The practice they had put into using this map's terrain to their own advantage had been for naught. The battle had erupted here. If they purposefully went to use the strategy they had originally planned with the steps, it might just have the opposite effect.

But at least, they had to figure out their opponent's strategic intentions!

Boom!

The explosive power of the Charged Artillery was immense, and the thunderous boom blanketed everything. Meanwhile, Boundless Sea's Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow seemed to have been charged until it became tangible, finally blasting Vaccaria as well. This time, he failed to escape. Happy's members were more or less completely ignoring the other three members of Tiny Herb, fixated on Wang Jiexi. This definitely wasn't normal for any match. But this time, Happy had finally paid the price for such an unbalanced arrangement. Xu Bin and co, realizing that they had been ignored, turned back to counterattack and more or less repaid them for the damage Happy had dealt to Vaccaria in full.

"Isn't Happy being a little too bull-headed?" Pan Lin called out, unable to comprehend their thought process.

At first, their encirclement of Wang jJiexi really was very spectacular and successful, but this time, this was clearly an unequal trade. However, Happy still stubbornly tried to take out Vaccaria first, and what they traded for that, was the advantage they had worked so hard to build up.

"Happy is truly too naive if they think it'll be so easy to defeat Tiny Herb's ace!" Ruan Cheng laughed, as if having completely forgotten how his soul had practically left his body when Wang Jiexi had been beaten down.

"Happy is really being very forceful today," Li Yibo noted.

"Heh. So this style is called being forceful? Maybe we could use a different adjective, like reckless?" Ruan Cheng's brain, particularly clever when it came to hating on Happy, once again got to work.

"Have you two noticed Fang Rui's performance today?" Li Yibo said.

"Fang Rui? Boundless Sea?" The two were both deep in thought.

"Don't you two think that today's Fang Rui is particularly not Fang Rui? He hasn't done any dirty sneaking around, ambushes or strange tricks… Today, he hasn't used the style he's used to. Today, he's fighting openly and directly like a normal Qi Master!" Li Yibo explained.

"Is he perhaps planning on changing styles again?" Ruan Cheng considered.

"I don't think so. I think it's just because their offensive strategy today requires him to play such a role," Li Yibo analyzed.

"Offensive strategy? What offensive strategy?" Ruan Cheng laughed.

"Risk everything to wipe Wang Jiexi out," Li Yibo replied.

　

"Heh," Ruan Cheng laughed again. "Too bad that this is a team competition. Defeating one person doesn't mean defeating a the whole team, no? No matter how central to the team. With this recklessness, I'm really curious how many of them will be left when they finish executing this 'offensive strategy' of theirs."

How many will be left?

It almost seemed like Happy really didn't care about this.

Attack, relentlessly, furiously attack. Anything that didn't affect their offensive against Vaccaria, they ignored it, even if it would harm their characters or send them into a danger zone.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

　

Flash Burst!

The last time. This was the last time.

Boundless Sea sent his qi energy into Vaccaria's body, and then the dragon condensed from the magical energy of Rising Dragon Soars the Sky roared as it crushed Vaccaria between its jaws.

A net of sword energy instantly unleashed itself onto Boundless Sea. Fang Rui didn't seem to care about his own life, simply turning around for the last time. He saw Xu Bin's sword slam down against Soft Mist's head. The magical energy swirling around her instantly dispersed. He saw the ground approach rapidly, but he could no longer Quick Recover. He saw Vaccaria, far off, encircled by the magical energy of Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, which exploded along with the qi energy that had injected through Flash Burst.

Chapter 1332: A New Future

These guys actually did it!

Under the eruption of Rising Dragon Soars the Sky and Flash Burst, Vaccaria's health was finally wiped out. Their healer couldn't make it in time to provide support and Vaccaria fell without resistance.

However, Happy had also paid a high price for this.

Soft Mist and Boundless Sea, as they dealt this last blow together, had been killed by Tiny Herb's furious offensive.

Three characters wiped out at the same time?

This was truly a rare and devastating trade. The entire stadium was sent into shock. The three in the broadcasting room were speechless.

Bang bang!

Two gunshots.

In that moment, even the players on the field were stunned, their rhythms slowing. Only one person was still doing as they should. In the face of such a devastating situation, he hadn't been affected in the slightest. He didn't even spare a glance for the three fallen characters before his character switched targets and charged.

Lord Grim's two gunshots had been aimed at Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree.

Naturally, they wouldn't have been able to successfully execute this sort of kill without CCing the opponent's healer.

Tiny Herb's Aweto was being blasted by Dancing Rain to the point where he was completely incapable of acting. Happy's Little Cold Hands, on the other hand, was being knocked witless by Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree.

The kill had only just happened, yet Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had already turned his fire towards his next target. With bullets on the way, Lord Grim used movement skills to flash to Kind Tree's side. Gao Yingjie was a little out of it because of what had just happened and was easily blasted into the air by Lord Grim.

Everyone snapped back to reality, seemingly only just realizing what had happened on the field.

Wang Jiexi, Vaccaria, Tiny Herb's core, the strongest part of their team, had been destroyed by Happy.

The stadium went silent.

No one had any grasp of the weight of the one for two trade. The audience only noticed one thing: Vaccaria had fallen, Wang Jiexi was out of the match.

What now?

Such a thought took over the hearts of countless fans. With Wang Jiexi gone, they were lost. They were used to seeing Wang Jiexi lead Tiny Herb to victory, vying for the championship cup year after year, season after season, match after match. From the third season, when he took the role of captain onwards, the regular season, the playoffs, sponsorship matches, sparring matches, exhibition matches, Tiny Herb's 398 matches, their captain Wang Jiexi was always present.

　

No matter when, he would be on the field to lead his team.

　

No matter when, so long as he was there on the field, everyone would feel secure.

But now, Wang Jiexi was the first to be sent out of the match.

In all these years, it wasn't that no team had ever tried, it was that no one that they could remember had ever succeeded.

But now, in front of their very eyes, the one thing that had never happened in all these years had, and in their home game, too, executed by a team that was new to the Alliance.

"The match isn't over!"

　

On the screen, in Tiny Herb's team chat, a message suddenly popped up.

After Kind Tree had been sent flying by Lord Grim, Gao Yingjie was the first one to clearly understand: their captain had been killed, but the match wasn't over.

In the current situation, Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi, his Vaccaria had been wiped out, but they still had Xu Bin, Gao Yingjie, Liu Xiaobie, and Yuan Baiqing on the field. Their sixth player Liang Fang had also switched in automatically.

For Happy, two of their characters had been killed and their sixth player Qiao Yifan had been switched in. Currently, only Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng and An Wenyi were there with Gao Yingjie and his teammates.

Their captain was no longer there, but Tiny Herb still held a clear advantage in numbers. They couldn't just stop and stare. Happy, over there, was at a disadvantage, yet their performance was still as stable as ever. Ye Xiu had immediately saved Little Cold Hands, and Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain was still blasting their healer, Aweto, as she ran to regroup.

It's a four versus three right now, and we hold the advantage!

Gao Yingjie told himself again and again.

But, what should they do?

After telling himself that, he then questioned himself.

Should he be making arrangements for what they were to do next?

Gao Yingjie knew of the expectations his team had of him, and the future his captain hoped he could shoulder. He always worked hard for this, yet when this moment was placed in front of him like this, ever so abrupt, he floundered. After he sent that message, "the match isn't over", he didn't know what to do next.

This shouldn't be!

Even if he were just a normal team member, he shouldn't feel so lost, so adrift. He had to do something.

You're going to be the one to shoulder Tiny Herb's future!

His captain's voice echoed in his ears ever so clearly, yet the current him was unable to shoulder such responsibilities. He couldn't even do what he had to do on the field like a normal player.

"With Vaccaria dead, Tiny Herb's morale has been severely impacted." Even the commentator, Pan Lin, could see what state Tiny Herb's players were in. After Vaccaria had been sent from the match, they had lost their way, flailing in the match without direction.

They had the advantage in numbers, their opponents were right there in front of them, but it was Happy's three that had managed to adjust first and it was Happy's three who took the initiative to attack.

"Tiny Herb won't just lose like that, will they?" The difference in the states of mind of the players had Pan Lin doubting Tiny Herb despite their advantage.

"Not everyone," Li Yibo said, abrupt.

"What?" Pan Lin didn't get what this was referring to.

"Xu Bin!" Ruan Cheng yelled.

Wang Jiexi really had been sent from the match by Happy. This was shocking, but fortunately, it hadn't been without dire consequences for Happy. One for two. Happy had killed off their opponent's core player, but dong so had sent themselves into a disadvantage in numbers. Their actions didn't seem worth it.

However, Ruan Cheng soon realized he was wrong.

From the reaction of the audience and the players of Tiny Herb, he finally truly understood what Wang Jiexi was to Tiny Herb. He was no normal core player.

He was their heart, their foundation, their hope, their confidence… Anything that they needed to continue fighting, Tiny Herb only had because of Wang Jiexi.

And now, he had fallen.

What he left to the players on the field was shock, the unknown, the sense of being lost, anxiety.

However, there was one exception.

Xu Bin.

　

A player who debuted in the sixth season and transferred to Tiny Herb from 301 Degrees, he had been a part of Tiny Herb for one and a half years, seeing great improvement and even becoming an All-Star, becoming Glory's Number One Knight.

He adapted to Tiny Herb well, but, in the end, he transferred over. He had only been a part of the team for a year and a half. Compared to the players of Tiny Herb who were born and raised there, his dependence on Wang Jiexi wasn't that strong.

When Vaccaria had fallen, he felt the same shock, but he didn't lose his cool, nor did he stop.

He had dealt with Soft Mist and had prepared to continue this offensive, but he hadn't expected that all his teammates would suddenly stagnate.

Xu Bin had intended to team up with Gao Yingjie and gang up on Little Cold Hands. So long as they got rid of Happy's healer, then their victory was pretty much assured. Who would've thought that Happy would adjust themselves even faster. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim swiftly came back to support and Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain also hurried over to regroup. However, what was more shocking to Xu Bin was that Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree had been easily blasted away by Lord Grim.

Angelica, having prepared to charge over and help him, could only stop. Then, seeing Gao Yingjie's message, he thought that there would be some sort of arrangement forthcoming. Though he had only come to Tiny Herb a year and a half ago, he had been named vice-captain. However, Xu Bin knew with clarity that Tiny Herb's future captain was Gao Yingjie. He was certain to be the one who would take up Vaccaria and continue Tiny Herb's fight after Wang Jiexi abdicated from his position. As for Xu Bin, he would always be a supporting character.

Xu Bin wasn't that ambitious and didn't have any complaints about this arrangement. After Vaccaria was defeated, the match would go to Gao Yingjie's control, so he was still that vice captain, the Knight that would stand by his king.

Yet after Xu Bin saw Gao Yingjie, the one who should take over, type that message into the chat, the other had fallen silent. In contrast, Happy's three players adjusted themselves decisively, swiftly removing themselves from the devastating trade and beginning to counterattack.

Boom boom!

Dancing Rain's missiles soared over.

No matter how lost Gao Yingjie was, his instincts as a pro player were solid. The opponent had attacked, and if he didn't know to dodge, then he deserved to die. Following Happy's attacks, Liu Xiaobie and Yuan Baiqing started waking up, facing the current situation with a more focused mind.

They still had the advantage.

That was obvious to them.

But, what should they do next?

Everyone looked to Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree

Tiny Herb had always revolved around their Witches. Their strategy and playstyle revolved around the Witch; they needed a hero to guide them.

The Tiny Herb of the past only had a Vaccaria. He was so dependable, always there to guide them on the battlefield. But now, they also had a Kind Tree. The dual Witch arrangement made them feel like they had two safety nets. However, everyone knew that this was merely a transitional period, slowly shifting the core of their team. Wang Jiexi, debuting in the third season, was coming to the end of his pro career. Of the talented players debuting in the same season, Zhao Yang had already retired and Yang Cong had abdicated from his position as ace, changing playstyles.

Only Wang Jiexi remained the way he was on the very first day, shouldering the entire team, allowing them to lean on him.

But now, it was time to switch players. From today onwards, another would hold up this team.

"Yingjie!" Liu Xiaobie called out in the team chat. They were doing their all to avoid Happy's attacks. Though it was four against three, they needed some sort of team tactic. They needed someone to led them into battle, and that person should be Gao Yingjie.

But.. what should I do? Gao Yingjie gazed at their opponent, their numbers depleted yet still closing in. Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, even against Tiny Herb, who had won two championships, they were still the Best Partners on the field.

Could he do it? Gao Yingjie gazed into the distance as if his and Team Tiny Herb's new future was over there.

Chapter 1333: Overlapping Ghost Boundaries

"Go, Yingjie! We'll follow your pace!"

In Tiny Herb's team chat, Liu Xiaobie sent this message. As a longtime teammate of Gao Yingjie's, he could sense the other player's confusion and panic.

If he's still not confident enough, then let's help him establish confidence! Aren't we used to supporting a Witch? No matter who it is, we'll go along with him.

"Go!" Xu Bin understood Liu Xiaobie's intentions and also encouraged Gao Yingjie. At the same time, their healer player Yuan Baiqing was controlling Aweto, preparing to give aid to the whole team.

With the encouragement of his teammates, Gao Yingjie's emotions gradually steadied. He was carrying everyone's hopes, how could he let them down? He had to carry Tiny Herb's future!

"Go!" Gao Yingjie also sent a message in the chat, displaying his state of mind to his teammates, and after that, the Witch Kind Tree once again took flight.

Target: Little Cold Hands!

Gao Yingjie decided to resume the objective that he hadn't been able to complete earlier. At the moment, they had the advantage of numbers, so there should be many openings through which they could attack Little Cold Hands. If they managed to kill the opponent's healer, the game was set.

But he had barely taken a few steps when he saw that Little Cold Hands was already retreating. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim smoothly intercepted Kind Tree's path of attack.

"Charge past!" Gao Yingjie sent in the team channel. There were three of them, so even if he got tangled with Lord Grim, there were still two others who could force their way toward Little Cold Hands.

Charge!

Triple Slash!

Xu Bin's Angelica and Liu Xiaobie's Flying Sword, assisting this new generation Tiny Herb Witch from the left and right, rushed forward together.

Boom boom boom!

From a long range, Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain had found an angle from which she could fire. With a Tri-Shot Anti-Tank Missile, three shots fired toward the three of them. They each dodged with their own techniques: Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree twisted in the air; Liu Xiaobie's Flying Sword changed direction on the second slash of his Triple Slash; Xu Bin's Angelica simply used a Heroic Leap, aiming to land in Lord Grim's direction.

But then…

Boom boom boom!

Another Tri-Shot Anti-Tank Missile came, this time from Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella at a much closer distance. In the end, they burst into three explosions.

All three Tiny Herb players were hit. The methods they used to dodge Su Mucheng's initial attack had all been predicted by Ye Xiu.

Kind Tree and Flying Sword were directly sent tumbling by the shockwaves of the explosion, but Angelica's Heroic Leap had priority. Plus, he had the stronger armor of a Knight, so even though he too was hit, his body was only slightly buffeted, and his offensive wasn't diminished at all. But just when he was about to land, brilliant white flames suddenly surrounded his body, and the priority of Heroic Leap vanished. A Sacred Fire from Little Cold Hands had Silenced him.

"Unbelievable! After sealing Vaccaria, he now seals Angelica. And these predictive attacks were both made under conditions of high-speed movement! We didn't even see the Sacred Fire burning on the ground before it took effect. An Wenyi has truly taken the precision of this skill to the limit…" Li Yibo exclaimed in shock. He too was surprised that he would save such unrestrained praise to give to An Wenyi, of all players.

After all, at the beginning, this was the guy whose mere ability to exist in the professional scene had been questioned!

"Happy ignored the doubts of the outside world and insisted on keeping An Wenyi as their main healer. Are they finally reaping the rewards?" Li Yibo continued to exclaim.

To the side, Ruan Cheng's expression darkened. As long as there was something negative said about Happy, he would always take part, and he was extreme with his criticism. With An Wenyi, for example, not only did he criticize An Wenyi for having such a low skill level, he used this as a lens through which to criticize the judgment and management of Team Happy as a whole. But now, Happy's support of An Wenyi brought them this kind of reward. Of course, this was the strongest retaliation toward his type of criticisms.

Ruan Cheng had opened his mouth, prepared to say something, but because Li Yibo had dragged the topic here, he had no way of adding anything. He could only shut his mouth, depressed.

Sky Strike.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had already become a spear in Lord Grim's hands, thrusting directly toward the falling Angelica. At the same time, another round of fire exploded upon his body. Clearly, Dancing Rain was still helping Ye Xiu output damage from afar.

But the combo didn't last too long, because Gao Yingjie and Liu Xiaobie were already back.

Boom!

Lord Grim used one last Falling Flower Palm to shove Angelica toward Kind Tree. Gao Yingjie immediately wanted to dodge, but a Laser Rifle slammed into Angelica's body again. Instantly, Angelica's body accelerated from the force of the impact and was in front of Kind Tree in the blink of an eye. Gao Yingjie hadn't anticipated this and couldn't react fast enough. Angelica slammed into him, and the two became tangled together. Even though the damage from this wouldn't be too high, this interrupted Tiny Herb's offensive and put them in an unbearably weak position.

Did Tiny Herb's offensive trio have no way of dealing with these two from Happy?

At this time, the sixth players of both sides finally arrived.

Tiny Herb, Liang Fang, Berserker Black Bamboo.

Happy, Qiao Yifan, Ghostblade One Inch Ash.

We can't let them set up Ghost Boundaries.

This was Gao Yingjie's judgment at this moment, but on Happy's side, Lord Grim was already covering One Inch Ash as the Ghostblade prepared to cast the first Ghost Boundary. Dancing Rain opened fire with Gatling Gun, sending a storm of bullets flying their way. The four from Tiny Herb scattered, and Angelica used the cover of his weapon Sighing Wall to take the direct path.

But they were still too slow. By the time the close-range fighters arrived, the light gathering on One Inch Ash's blade was released.

Ice Boundary!

The boundary landed right beneath the feet of Lord Grim and One Inch Ash. The close-range fighters who had planned to stop him immediately had to retreat.

Ye Xiu's Lord Grim used this opening to complete a cast - another Ghost Boundary, a Sword Boundary that used blade aura as a buff.

Dancing Rain and Little Cold Hands entered the range of the Sword and Ice Boundaries. Under the protection of these Ghost Boundaries, Happy's four players steadily began to advance their position.

Ghost Boundaries appeared on the map one after another. In Tiny Herb's roster, Xu Bin, Liu Xiaobie, and Liang Fang were all close-range classes, and after the Ghost Boundaries forced them out of range, their choices of attack were extremely limited. Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree could still attack the target from outside the range of the Ghost Boundaries, but his attacks alone were far from enough to stop Happy's step-by-step advancement.

"Retreat for now!" Gao Yingjie made this decision.

The biggest limitation of Ghost Boundaries was that they couldn't move. Happy had established a strong formation, so even though Tiny Herb had an extra person, they couldn't brute-force their way through. They'd wanted to try this, relying on their healer, but they had nothing to show for their efforts.

Boom boom!

Su Mucheng sent the Tiny Herb players on their way with a few cannon shots. Tiny Herb's players dodged, feeling depressed, when all of a sudden, Happy's Little Cold Hands suddenly raised his weapon Holy Contract. There was a flash of brilliant light, so bright that it would attract everyone's attention. It was a Hypnosis attack.

Aweto!

Tiny Herb's Cleric instantly stopped in his tracks. His body swayed, clearly already asleep. And at this moment, Lord Grim's two hands opened outward, and a gust of qi flowed outward…

Cloud Grasping Fist!

When they saw this skill, the faces of the Tiny Herb players turned ashen.

Happy's formation needed the support of the Ghost Boundaries, so they couldn't move quickly. Yuan Baiqing's Aweto, had been far back in a secure location the whole time. Because of this, Tiny Herb hadn't worried too much about protecting him, because in their view, there was no way Happy could charge out of the Ghost Boundaries, and the long-range firepower of Dancing Rain or Lord Grim alone didn't pose a great threat.

But now, Happy actually pulled Aweto into their formation. Tiny Herb had neglected the protection of Aweto, and it was now too late to interrupt the Cloud Grasping Fist. There was no way they could retreat now and come back later. Disregarding everything else, all of the Tiny Herb players turned around and rushed back to rescue Aweto.

But Happy was prepared for this. One Inch Ash continued to lay down Ghost Boundaries without rest, connecting into a chain of obstacles that hampered their movements. Just like that, Aweto was pulled by Lord Grim into Happy's formation, and the various Ghost Boundaries he passed through caused him to suffer all sorts of damage and status effects. As soon as he landed, Lord Grim didn't hold back in attacking him. Dancing Rain used her firepower to continue to take care of everyone else, and Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash maintained the completeness of the Overlapping Ghost Boundaries.

How did things end up like this?

Gao Yingjie was in a daze. It was five against four, they clearly had the advantage of numbers, so why had they been countered at every step? How had they ended up in this situation, where their healer was stolen away and they had no way of rescuing him?

If only Captain were still here, this battle never would've become such a mess!

In the end, it's because I'm useless, isn't it?

Too useless.

Tiny Herb's future? Everyone's hope? How in the world could I ever carry that?

Ah!!!

Gao Yingjie gave a shout of anger in his heart. Kind Tree, a character who could still attack from the edge of the Ghost Boundaries, now arrived there.

Dark Boundary? Ice Boundary?

Gao Yingjie studied the Ghost Boundaries on the ground. The status effects from these were too strong; no matter what, he couldn't enter those regions.

Plague Boundary?

That would only decrease his defense. He could take that.

But… that was a trap. Gao Yingjie carefully observed the positions of Happy's players. If he charged through the Plague Boundary, then all of the opponents' attacks could easily focus upon him. Under the defense-reducing effect of the Plague Boundary, the damage and effects from the attacks would all be magnified. If he tried a charge like that, he would definitely be forced back, and just the smallest mistake could result in his own death.

Gao Yingjie felt a rare clarity of mind. All of these thoughts flashed through his mind, and he made his judgments. He couldn't enter any of these areas sealed by the Ghost Boundaries. Then, all that was left was…

Silence Boundary, a region that would lock all skills. Anyone else would skip this option without a second thought.

But, I'm a Witch! Even with ordinary attacks, I can go in and cause some chaos. If I can interrupt one of Yifan's Ghost Boundaries, then my teammates can seize the opportunity to counterattack.

It'll be a bit hard, but I have to try!

Kind Tree, under everyone's shocked gazes, stepped into the Silence Boundary. His skills were instantly sealed, but his footsteps didn't halt.

Was there an open area where he could stand? Was there an opening caused by switching skills that he could seize?

Gao Yingjie concentrated everything he had on his surroundings. His Kind Tree charged toward One Inch Ash. HE was going to interrupt the opponent's array of Ghost Boundaries.

"Behind you!"

But at this moment, he received a warning from his teammate. He immediately tried to roll and dodge, but blood was already flying from Kind Tree's neck. Then, someone was already lifting him, and carelessly tossing him to the side.

Lord Grim's silhouette had already used another movement skill to return and resume his offense against Aweto. Just like that, Kind Tree was tossed into the middle of the Dark Boundary.

The entire world went black.

Chapter 1334: Decisive

Is this the end?

Gao Yingjie felt the dejection swelling in his heart as his camera view turned into a screen of darkness.

No!

But another sound rose in his heart, because he felt that he heard that sentence once again.

Shoulder the future of Tiny Herb!

This isn't over yet.

The Dark Boundary didn't cause any damage, only the loss of vision. The position he'd been in when he hit the ground, the direction he was facing…

Kind Tree clambered to his feet, turned his body slightly to face the direct center of the Ghost Boundary, and charged through!

What?

Everyone was shocked and had to double-check that that Dark Boundary hadn't already faded.

No, the Dark Boundary was still there, and there was no way the Blind effect would fade so quickly. In other words, Gao Yingjie's vision was still nothing but darkness, but he could still make such accurate controls? He had done all of this based on his memory? What incredible instinct and intuition!

Kind Tree flew into the air, riding atop his broom, Morning Dew.

At this moment, there was no way for him to make many precise controls. He could only use a few sweeping skills to try and disrupt the opponent.

Broom Tornado!

Morning Dew swung through the air, Kind Tree spun and a tornado whipped up… To win this match, he was using everything he had, even if his skills had been sealed by the Silence Boundary, even if the Dark Boundary stole away his vision, he still refused to give up.

But the audience couldn't bear to watch any longer.

They couldn't bear to see Gao Yingjie work so hard only to fail to accomplish anything in the end.

Dancing Rain had already lifted her cannon. She aimed right at Kind Tree, and shot a Laser Rifle right at him.

Boom…

The midair Kind Tree was instantly sent flying by this Laser Rifle.

In the end, it still wasn't enough?

Gao Yingjie let out a sigh… This was far from an opponent he could defeat with his eyes closed!

The moment that Kind Tree flew out of the area affected by the Dark Boundary, he recovered his sight. Gao Yingjie immediately adjusted his position. Then, he saw Aweto trapped by countless overlapping Ghost Boundaries, with all sorts of status effects and damage stacking on top of him. Light and shadow intertwined; the occasional flashes were all black in color.

One Inch Ash's tachi was raised in the air. Those Ghost Boundaries lying upon the ground seemed to hear some sort of call, and the power of the Phantom Ghost became shifting and restless.

Ghost Feast!

In this instant, all of the phantom power exploded! The power flew in chaotic patterns through the air, searching for targets within the range of the Ghost Boundaries. Which Tiny Herb player would dare advance at this moment? But in the very center of the boundaries, where they all overlapped, Tiny Herb's Cleric was being devoured by all of the phantom power.

Boom!

Another Satellite Beam fell from the sky. Along with the waving claws and dancing fangs of the Phantom God's power, it swallowed Aweto whole, leaving not a scrap of clothing…

Tiny Herb's Cleric fell.

In that moment, for countless people, this match was decided. Tiny Herb's stadium was silent. Only the loyal Happy fans sitting in the away team audience area were jumping and singing, welcoming the crazy victory that was just about to arrive.

"This is really… unbelievable." This adjective appeared again and again in the commentary of today's match. And this time, seeing Happy kill Tiny Herb's healer, Pan Lin once again used this adjective to describe the situation.

Even though Tiny Herb had become somewhat disorganized and depressed when Happy had killed Wang Jiexi earlier, they still had the absolute numbers advantage, and so most people still favored Tiny Herb. Ruan Cheng gritted his teeth as he waited for Tiny Herb to kill Happy, so that he could pick apart Happy's faults one by one.

But now, it looked like there was no need.

Tiny Herb's Cleric was killed. This one move was simply too decisive. Now, there probably wouldn't be any more earth-shaking miracles, would there?

There wouldn't be.

Enough shocking events had already happened today.

After this, Tiny Herb's four attackers attempted to kill Little Cold Hands, but One Inch Ash's Ghost Boundaries quickly gave Little Cold Hands the best protection. When An Wenyi was able to stand at a secure position and focus on healing, then Lord Grim, fighting on the frontlines, could be that much more reckless in his attacks.

No reversals, no comebacks. The battle ended here. Happy won their away game against Tiny Herb, with a final score of 8-2.

There was too much that needed to be digested, and so the stadium was a bit subdued. The players from both teams walked out of the competitor booths and met in the middle, just like they had before the team competition. But now that victory had been determined, one side could laugh heartily, while the other side could only taste bitterness.

Wang Jiexi, the first one killed in this team competition, calmly looked at the players of this team standing before him.

Ye Xiu… Counting from when Wang Jiexi had first entered the Alliance, the two of them had already competed with each other for a full seven seasons. If only speaking of their results during that time, then Ye Xiu, who had never appeared in a season finals after Season 4, seemed a bit inferior to Wang Jiexi, who had played in the finals three times and won two of them.

Over the regular seasons, they had met 14 times, each with his share of wins and losses.

In the playoffs of Season 7, the two teams met in the first round, and Tiny Herb sent home the Excellent Era that Ye Xiu led. It was after that battle that everyone started screaming, believing that Ye Qiu's era was over for good. But for some reason, Wang Jiexi felt that he hadn't truly defeated this opponent. This wasn't only because of the achievements and trophies that both sides had accumulated, this was a feeling closer to the battlefield. The battle strength that Excellent Era had displayed during that playoffs match was so fragmented that even Wang Jiexi, as their opponent, almost couldn't bear to watch.

That battle became the last time the two of them fought. During the regular season of Season 8, before Tiny Herb and Excellent Era could meet, Ye Xiu announced his retirement.

When he first heard the news, Wang Jiexi couldn't understand it at all.

The outside world believed this and that. But as his opponent, Wang Jiexi only knew one thing - Ye Qiu's competitive condition was far from the point where he would need to retire. Some internal conflict must have occurred within Team Excellent Era…

But all of this became unimportant with Ye Qiu's retirement. Wang Jiexi's job was to lead Tiny Herb on a road of endless victory.

And now, he had returned. Wang Jiexi didn't know what was up with Ye Qiu becoming Ye Xiu, but either way it wasn't important. This player had used that one and half years of time to pull together this team standing here now, and then once again defeated Wang Jiexi in battle.

When was the last time I lost to this guy?

Wang Jiexi couldn't remember anymore. What he could remember in clear detail was Season 3, when he'd won Best Rookie. He was the so-called king of rookies, but that was nothing in front of God Ye Qiu! The world had likened his Magician style to the sight of heavenly horses crossing the sky, but in front of Ye Qiu there were none of the stunning effects of magic. One Autumn Leaf waved that famed Silver weapon Evil Annihilation, using that Battle Mage style that was everywhere in the player guides, and beat his Witch bloody. The Excellent Era that he had raised was truly invincible in that era.

This time, do you plan to carry such a team once again?

"Congratulations," Wang Jiexi said, extending his right hand toward Ye Xiu.

"Thank you." Ye Xiu also extended his hand, and they shook.

"Next time, we will win," said Wang Jiexi.

"Oh? You guys?" Ye Xiu laughed, and looked at the line of Tiny Herb players arranged before him. Having lost the match, they were of course in low spirits. Gao Yingjie especially seemed painfully upset. His head hung low, and the teardrops were clear to see as they fell from his eyes.

"Maybe if they treated you as a role model, and not a crutch."

When Ye Xiu said this sentence, he had already moved past, and was shaking hands with the person standing next to Wang Jiexi.

Role model?

Crutch?

Wang Jiexi was dazed. Even when Fang Rui walked in front of him and extended his hand, he didn't react until Xu Bin reminded him. He hurriedly recovered and shook hands.

Is he saying that I've been working too hard all this time? But when you were in Excellent Era, weren't you also giving your all to carry the team on your shoulders? Wang Jiexi watched Ye Xiu's retreating silhouette, which now arrived in front of Gao Yingjie at the end of the line.

Gao Yingjie's head was bowed. He saw that someone had walked in front of him, but he didn't lift his head, and only extended his right hand.

"You did well." Ye Xiu took the initiative to speak with him. "But awareness and determination are far from enough. Who doesn't have those things?"

As soon as he finished speaking, he was already gone. But Gao Yingjie, surprised, finally lifted his head to look at him. Behind Ye Xiu, the rest of the Happy players walked by, one by one, shaking his hand, until the very last Happy member. Qiao Yifan.

In over a year's time, young players like them could grow a lot, whether in appearance or character.

Both of them had grown taller, and the childishness had faded from their faces. Gao Yingjie's face was still streaked with tears, but now that he was facing his old friend, he finally reacted and hurriedly wiped his face.

Qiao Yifan didn't laugh at him. He pulled some tissues out of his pocket and offered them to Gao Yingjie.

Gao Yingjie took them, but he didn't use them to wipe his tears.

"Yifan, you're really amazing now," Gao Yingjie said.

"So are you, still as genius as ever, being able to play even in the Dark Boundary," Qiao Yifan said.

"But what use is that? We still lost." Gao Yingjie's sadness was still clear when he said this.

"Keep working hard!" Qiao Yifan said.

"Yes. Next time I'll win for sure," Gao Yingjie said.

"Alright," Qiao Yifan smiled, not fussing over how the statement "I'll win for sure" had the implication "you'll lose for sure."

With that, the match came to a close. In the post-match press conference, both sides expressed extremely high praise toward their opponent's performance. In Tiny Herb's press conference, Captain Wang Jiexi frequently revealed a pensive expression while answering questions, and their genius player Gao Yingjie, after this failure, expressed a strength and determination that he had never shown before.

Ruan Cheng had been so prepared to sarcastically mock Happy after they'd lost this battle, but in the end, he didn't even show up to Happy's press conference. But soon, the television broadcasting station received countless calls from viewers, all expressing that they'd rather hear the commentary of someone whose skill wasn't high enough than the commentary of someone as biased as Ruan Cheng.

At the conclusion of Round 27, Happy's away game victory against Tiny Herb was one of the more unexpected results. But aside from this, there was another surprise: Team Wind Howl, after stumbling in so many battles, finally found their footing in this match, and won 8-2 against Team Blue Rain.

Chapter 1335: Don’t Worry About the Details

Not even Wind Howl's fans felt any hope for them, and in a match against a powerhouse like Blue Rain, not even 70 percent of the tickets had been sold. Many fans gathered outside of the stadium, refusing to go inside and watch and thus expressing their displeasure for Wind Howl's recent performance.

Yet it was on this night that Wind Howl won an individual competition, won the group arena, and then won the team competition. They beat the current number two, Blue Rain, 8 to 2.

"There are many factors that can influence a match. Doing the right thing at the right time is the most efficient way to win a match. Wind Howl's offense was strong tonight, and our defense wasn't up to par," Blue Rain's captain, Yu Wenzhou, commented at the post-match press conference.

The reporters in the audience had a very clear understanding of this match. Team Wind Howl had fallen, their fans cooled, but there was one aspect that was indisputably admirable about them. No matter how terrible their performance was, their desire for victory burned as brightly as ever.

Yu Wenzhou's comment was a good summary.

If you say that victory required doing the right thing at the right time, then the previous Wind Howl could never find that right time to do that right thing.

And this time? In this team competition, Wind Howl had used an extremely crude playstyle. After their starting lineup had loaded into the map, they immediately switched their healer out for their sixth player, creating an all-DPS formation. Then, they had attacked Blue Rain, forcing their members to fight 1v1.

This sort of strategy was extremely rare in the high-end pro circle. Once the 1v1 arrangement was completed by Wind Howl, Blue Rain's team was ripped asunder. Apart from their healer, Yu Wenzhou wasn't good at 1v1s either, making things far more difficult for Blue Rain. In the end, they were unable to regroup and support each other efficiently, losing the team competition.

　

The right thing at the right time...

The reporters digested this comment from Yu Wenzhou. It seemed like words of courtesy spoken post-match, but the meaning behind the words were clear. There was no need to comment any further.

As for the stars of the day, Team Wind Howl… This long-awaited victory against such a powerhouse finally let them raise their heads, standing tall and confident at the press conference.

"The competition is just beginning," they intoned solemnly.

　

Sure...

The reporters looked to the rankings after 27 rounds. Wind Howl was still just outside of the playoffs, though they were only 8 points away from the eighth ranked team. The problem was that none of the top eight seemed to be falling behind.

The one who was one place above Wind Howl was 301 Degrees, who had been rising up ever since the winter transfer window. This round, they had defeated Heavenly Swords 8 to 2 in their away game, scoring their tenth consecutive win. The Life Risking Strike assassination didn't appear in this match, but that meant that 301 Degrees didn't just have that one method of winning. They would judge the situation for the method necessary to obtain victory. Their captain Yang Cong wasn't so stiff as to stubbornly stick to his new Life-Risking style no matter what. He could still use the warrior-like playstyle that he favored before, charging at the head of his team if the team so required.

301 Degrees wasn't planning on relying on this singular strategy; everyone had realized that by now.

Team 301 Degrees had risen through the ranks, and the one they had knocked out of the top eight was Wind Howl. Now Wind Howl had become the pursuers and the reporters checked the schedule. A good show was soon to come. Round 28 was a faceoff between these two teams: Wind Howl's home game would be against 301 Degrees.

This seemed quite like a fight to the death.

There were still eleven rounds in the regular season. Eight points of difference wasn't a small gap, but it wasn't a very big gap either. If you wanted to turn the tables in one round, then this face off was a chance. If they won with a 9 to 1, then they'd be even. Ten to zero and they'd overtake them.

However, Wind Howl, having already disappointed everyone so much, couldn't win back everyone's faith and admiration with just a single victory against Blue Rain, especially compared to 301 Degrees with their 10 consecutive wins.

However, Team Wind Howl's members had an indomitable will to fight against the tides. The more the outside world didn't believe, the more focused they were on the match.

On March 28th, the day before Round 28 of the Pro League, the teams generally would choose such a time to announce the lineup they were to use in the match the following day.

"What? You're putting me in?"

For Tema Happy, when their lineup was announced, the loudest voice came from the computer on their meeting table.

The last time Luo Ji had played in an official match since coming to Happy was all the way back during the Challengers League. His contributions to Team Happy were more like that of a R&D member, rather than a player.

However, Luo Ji was doubtlessly a registered player of Happy's. Though he usually couldn't stay with the team because of his studies, when matchday came, no matter home or away game, Luo Ji would rush over to the stadium and meet with everyone.

Though he had never been on the stage, he had the chance to watch up close and personal. Luo Ji was no longer the noob he once was. His judgement, knowledge, were far from average. As for skill, he naturally knew his own level. In the current Happy, not even Wei Chen had much of a chance to be fielded. For himself, he was satisfied with just sitting at the sidelines. Maybe, after honing himself for another year and half, he might get some chance to play.

That was what Luo Ji thought. He never would've expected that Ye Xiu planned to field him in this crucial time as the season approached its end.

"Do you want to play an individual match or group arena?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I, I, I…" Luo Ji stuttered, speechless. It was shocking enough that he was getting a chance to play, never mind being able to choose the match for himself. This… was probably the encouragement and reward he was getting for this season.

There are still eleven rounds. It's time you gained some real battle experience," Ye Xiu decided.

Luo Ji was one of the elite students of an institution for higher education. His IQ was high, that was undebatable, and he soon figured out the logic in Ye Xiu's words.

From his view, with only eleven rounds left, if Happy had a massive lead like Samsara, then it was fine to let some newbie take the stage and gain experience in some relatively unimportant matches as the regular season came to a close. However, Happy was currently sixth with a total of 178 points, 4 points ahead of number seven Hundred Blossoms and 12 ahead of number eight 301 Degrees. Compared to number nine's Wind Howl, they did have quite a lead with 20 points ahead.

However, even if Happy didn't drop out of the top eight, falling to eighth place wasn't good either. If the current situation was any clue, Samsara's lead was certain to continue. In accordance with the playoffs rules, the eighth ranked team would be up against the number one team, Samsara, in the first round… Everyone was naturally trying to avoid such a strong opponent. If it became unavoidable, like in the finals, then they'll just go all out and hope for the best.

Happy wasn't at the point where they could relax and train their newbies. However, if Ye Xiu fielded him now, that seemed to mean that Ye Xiu was placing importance on his use later and not throwing him some unimportant matches to gain experience!

Yet Ye Xiu had said that he had to gain real battle experience in these eleven rounds. Could it be that Ye Xiu was planning on having him play in the playoffs?

Though he was sitting down, Luo Ji felt his legs go weak.

After gaining some experience in eleven rounds, he'd have to contribute to that vicious competition where a single mistake could mean a year's worth of work wasted called the playoffs?

"Is that… really alright?" Luo Ji didn't voice any of what he had thought, merely asking the question that was going through his mind.

"You've been working hard for a long time. It's time to experience what being on the stage is like," Ye Xiu replied.

"But my skill…" Luo Ji hesitated.

"Your skill is already at the point where you need real battle experience to improve. It'll tell you what to give up and what to strengthen, how to make decisions. You have to develop such an awareness yourself; if I just tell you, there's little use," Ye Xiu explained.

"You can tell me first, I'll focus on it," Luo ji said.

"Don't worry about the details," Ye Xiu intoned.

"Just say it, I'll definitely be able to look at things clearer if you do," Luo Ji reassured.

"I already said it!"

"Ah? Just don't worry about the details?" Luo Ji was dumbfounded for a moment. He had thought Ye Xiu had been telling him to not worry about the detail of "listen to it first and then focus on it".

"Yes, see? There's not much use, no?" Ye Xiu said.

This harsh reality had Luo Ji struck speechless. These words really weren't much use to him.

"Or, rather, pay more attention to the details you need to," Ye Xiu added.

"Pay attention to what details are important?" Luo Ji's IQ was impressive, able to easily find the implications.

"Yup," Ye Xiu confirmed.

"I'll pay close attention to it." Luo Ji nodded and didn't say much more. This was because he realized this really was something you could only develop through going through the battles yourself. Then he considered his current situation. Paying attention to details was his habit and style, and it was because of this that he could create those incredibly detailed guides. However, when 1v1ing, the more you paid attention to, the more you had to worry about. In addition, Summoners already had very complex mechanics so he often floundered and flailed when it came to it.

　

Ye Xiu's advice of paying attention to what details could be ignored and what should be considered wasn't telling him to stop paying attention to detail, but to find the details that would benefit him the most when it came to defeating his opponent and then utilize them effectively. If he could do this, then he probably wouldn't be all over the place when it came to controlling his character. Luo Ji knew that he was no hand speed expert. He couldn't control a bunch of summons under complex battle situations.

Choosing between these details really was something he needed to master to improve from his current level. Ye Xiu had probably noticed that he had reached such a level and arranged for him to improve through actual matches.

　

However… there were only eleven rounds left.

Even if he played one match per round and even gained some experience from the team competitions, was it enough to improve and allow him to perform well in the playoffs?

　

This question lingered in Luo Ji's heart, and Chen Guo had doubts about it, too.

"Will Luo Ji be alright?" Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu after the meeting was over.

"Don't forget, he has a high IQ!" Ye Xiu replied.

Chapter 1336: The Freedom to Choose

Luo Ji was more prudent, choosing to appear in an individual competition in the 28th round. At the end of the day, he was still worried that his skill level would end up dragging down his team in the group arena, which would cost 2 points, whereas a loss in the individual competition would only cost 1 point. As for the team competition, having no available slots for him to take instead gave him a sense of relief.

Luo Ji's attitude made the members of Team Happy sigh with sorrow, especially those veterans who had more experience as a professional player.

When it came to players nowadays, who wouldn't want to have as many opportunities as possible to shine? How many people would actually have misgivings about their own ability being insufficient and dragging down their team?

"He's a really honest kid..." Chen Guo sighed sorrowfully. She may not have had much experience, but she had seen enough to know that characters as sincere as Luo Ji were hard to come by, especially amongst rookies.

Round 28 soon arrived.

It was unanimously decided that the match between Wind Howl and 301 Degrees would be the one to be broadcasted. As it was coming towards the end of the regular season, many teams would be out of hope, with the exception of those fighting over the 8th place, where the most intense competition would be taking place. And in a match like this, where the two teams were directly competing for a spot in the top 8, both teams would definitely exert their fullest effort, making the match that much more exciting and intense.

In Wind Howl's home game, during the first round of the individual competition, Wind Howl's captain, Tang Hao, took the stage.

In the Round 18 of the regular season, Tang Hao also appeared first, with the goal of sniping Ye Xiu's streak of consecutive victories in order to boost the morale of the team. Unfortunately, he was unable to win, and Team Wind Howl ended up losing to Team Happy in a 10-0 blowout victory.

After ten rounds had passed, when faced with what could be Team Wind Howl's most important match of the regular season, Tang Hao once again took up the same role.

Perhaps, under his command, Wind Howl may not have achieved the results that everyone expected from them, but still, Tang Hao was filled with valor and confidence, leading Wind Howl in their charge towards victory. His appearance in the first round showed their intentions clearly; he could not afford to lose. If he postured like this and still lost, the morale of the team would definitely suffer a severe blow. On top of that, given that he had tried this before and failed, if he attempted it again without success, the damage to the team's morale would be even greater, and he would definitely be the subject of even more ridicule.

But even so, he was devoid of fear. In such an important match, he shouldered all of this pressure and stood as the first player on stage. Team 301's vanguard was also their team captain, but if one were to call him the nucleus of the team, that would be outdated information.

After testing and tempering their new strategy in the last few rounds of the competition, it became clear that Bai Shu was the core of Team 301. Whether in attack or defense, it was still Bai Shu who was leading 301. As for Yang Cong, he now had more freedom in the role he played. The team placed great faith in him, allowing him to use his own intuition and experience to decide what to do in the battlefield. Of course, Yang Cong took up this responsibility, and in the second half of the season, his performance was very eye-catching. If they only had the foreign monk Bai Shu and not him, Team 301 wouldn't have been able to perform as well as they had.

The Brawler, Demon Subduer, and the Assassin, Scene Killer. Both characters quickly loaded into the match, and Yang Cong could immediately see Demon Subduer at the other end of the map.

Maybe it was due to Ye Xiu's map choices, but during this season, choosing this kind of plain and simple map had become increasingly popular. Tang Hao also ended up picking such a map that left out almost any room for tactical maneuvering, instead forcing his opponent to clash with him head on!

Assassins had no fear of this kind of head-on combat, and Yang Cong had originally been a player who had such a direct playstyle anyways. Seeing that the map was like this, he wasted no time in hesitating and just decided to adopt his old playstyle and attack!

Ding!

The curtains to the competition lifted with that tiny sound. Demon Subduer lifted his hand and threw out a Paralysis Needle, but the Silver weapon Dancing Shadows was lifted into the air by Yang Cong, sending the Paralysis Needle flying harmlessly to the side.

Powerful Knee Strike!

Tang Hao directly and unambiguously started his assault.

How fierce!

Yang Cong was filled with regret in his heart. Truth be told, the Brawler class wasn't particularly strong at these kinds of direct attacks, instead, it was there numerous dirty tracts that allowed the class to have stronger control abilities, making Brawlers more suited as a control-oriented class. If it was just about pure attack power, there were many classes that were stronger than the Brawler in that regard.

But it was exactly this class that became extremely aggressive in Tang Hao's hands, completely different from when Lin Jingyan was playing it in the past.

It was precisely because of these players with different dispositions piloting all the different classes that made Glory such a rich and colorful game. Wasn't it Yang Cong himself who had turned his Assassin into a forceful fighter on the front lines?

Seeing Tang Hao's violent and forceful Brawler, Yang Cong could only lament, "it must be nice being young". If it were a few years ago, he would also have the heart to compete against his opponent in such a forceful and direct manner. Comparing whose reactions were quicker, whose hand speed was greater, whose mechanics were more perfect.

But now, he had to adjust a little bit.

Yang Cong controlled Scene Killer to Dodge towards the side, avoiding Demon Subduer's incoming attack before quickly striking out with the Dual Swords, sending a Heart-Piercing Stab directly at Demon Subduer's back.

Tang Hao wasn't bad enough to get hit this easily. When Powerful Knee Strike didn't connect, Demon Subduer had already twisted his body in mid-air, sending out a Sand Toss instead. Yang Cong hurriedly turned his field of view away, relying on his memories and experience to try to hit his Heart-Piercing Stab. In the end, Scene Killer's movements suddenly became stiff after the attack.

Not good!

Yang Cong's experience allowed him to determine what had happened. Once Sand Toss was over, he turned his camera back to the original angle, and saw that Dancing Shadows had been gripped firmly by Demon Subduer's claw, Blood Vanishing Soul.

If it was just an attack being parried, he wouldn't feel as if he couldn't control his character properly. Instead, that kind of sensation was as if he had been controlled by a grab skill.

Empty-Handed Blade Block!

Surprisingly, the skill that Demon Subduer used was from the Striker class and had obviously been added to his weapon beforehand.

A low-levelled Empty-Handed Blade Block didn't have much attack power, but its effectiveness in dismantling attacks was the same. Professional players were only able to add a level 1 skill to their weapon, so they wouldn't pursue damage output, but instead pursue a unique effect that only that particular skill possessed.

Blocking and dismantling at the same time!

After this hit, blows immediately rained down upon Scene Killer's body, and the combo began…...

He really was aggressive enough!

As Scene Killer took hit after hit, Yang Cong concentrated on Demon Subduer's frantic offensive. To unleash such an offensive, it meant that the player behind the character was frantically inputting controls as well.

Do you really think this kind of attack can defeat me?

What do you think I relied on to stand firmly in the Alliance for so long?

Yang Cong's chest boiled with hot-bloodedness under the continuous attacks from Demon Subduer. Originally, he wanted to play more calmly and achieve victory, but now, he very much wanted to be like Demon Subduer and unleash his own flurry of attacks.

Yang Cong stared at his opponent's attacks, and finally saw an opening.

Assassin Movement Technique: With the Wind!

Scene Killer's body flickered strangely, and Demon Subduer's head-on attack actually missed him by a little bit. Attack again! Demon Subduer sent another strike out.

Assassin Movement Technique: Against the Lightning!

Demon Subduer's clenched fist suddenly lagged behind Scene Killer's body.

With the Wind, Against the Lightning, Turning Flame, Standing Ice.

The four movement techniques that the Assassin possessed were actually to retreat, to advance, move left and right or not move, things that could be achieved through normal controls. However, using the skills would naturally have a far stronger result.

Yang Cong saw an opening, used the two movement techniques and shook free of Demon Subduer's offensive in a flash.

Now... it should be my turn, right?

The Assassin's Dual Swords, Dancing Shadows, flew through the air towards Demon Subduer…...

Another kind of alternative Assassin style in the Alliance.

Scene Killer!

Two classes that were perhaps more suited to a different playstyle completed a furious bout of direct attacks. Yang Cong let go of the misgivings in his heart and used the the playstyle that he had used for so many years.

Every competition needs an end, and victory or defeat had to be decided.

This time, it was Yang Cong who lost.

"Ah, what a shame..." Yang Cong sighed.

He had lost, but that kind of free-spirited play was something that he very much enjoyed. He could try out the most eye-catching kind of Assassin playstyle, with Life-Risking Strike, or he could make use of the direct playstyle he was most familiar with after so many years.

Just like in this match, where he had started off hot-blooded, directly fighting against Tang Hao, but in the midst of it, he had also tried to find an opportunity to land a Life-Risking Strike.

He was pursuing the end-goal of victory, but he was also enjoying the thrill of competition.

Losing was a bit of a shame, but who could say that using a certain method would definitely result in a win?

For the past eight years, during every competition, he had to carefully consider what methods and tactics to use, but now, he had abandoned all of that, allowing him the freedom to do as he pleased, and the end result wasn't too disastrous. This time, he had lost, but who knew what would happen the next time?

Yang Cong left the stage having lost, but he still felt a sense of fulfillment.

"Captain, what a pity..." Team 301's players all surrounded him, breaking down the countless moments in the match that had made them excited or left them with regret. Losing, but not being discouraged because of it; Yang Cong's match had conveyed this sort of message.

"Continue to try your best!" Thus, he was able to magnanimously encourage his teammates.

"Understood!" Everyone responded, and the next contestant took the field.

At the same time, in another stadium, Luo Ji shakily stood up from his seat.

He was finally going to welcome the first match of his professional career, and he felt a hundred times more nervous than the time in the Challenger's League.

"Don't be nervous," Ye Xiu told him, after having continued his winning streak in the individual competition.

"Mm," Luo Ji said, thrice, as he rigidly nodded his head.

"Your opponent is the same as you, a new player in a new season!" Ye Xiu comforted him.

"But it isn't his first time appearing on stage!" Luo Ji felt that Ye Xiu's reassurance was completely useless.

"Don't sweat the small details!" Ye Xiu said.

"..." Did that have some kind of double meaning? Luo Ji, with his high IQ, began to ponder.

In this round, Team Happy was up against Team Miracle.

In the first half of the season, they had won in a 10-0 victory against Miracle in their away-game, beginning their frantic journey of snatching points. Team Miracle, on the other hand, had stumbled and staggered before gradually producing more stable results. Being the number thirteen team, with 110 points, this could be considered an extremely impressive result for a new team. In their team, they had many rookies who had never played competitively before, and now, they were against a player who had never played until the Round 28 of the regular season.

Team Happy's Luo Ji, and his Summoner, Concealed Light.

Chapter 1337: Who’s Being Bullied?

Since he had never appeared in a competition before, Luo Ji's Summoner, Concealed Light, obviously wasn't the focus of Happy's tailor-made Silver equipment. At the moment, there weren't more than 3 pieces of Silver equipment on Concealed Light's body, and they were all put together from the leftover scraps after Guan Rongfei had finished making equipment for the other characters. After half a season, Concealed Light had only collected 3 pieces of Silver equipment.

This set of equipment was below average in the Glory Alliance, but where equipment was concerned, Luo Ji's opponent for this match wasn't better off than he was.

After Team Miracle took in the three players who had previously been in Excellent Era, their expenditure was significant, and they weren't able to make any big moves in terms of their equipment or materials. In their team, the development of equipment similarly had an order of priority to it. He Ming, Shen Jian and Wang Ze, these three former Excellent Era players were obviously the core generals of Team Miracle, so their equipment priority was naturally the highest. After them was their rookie, Guo Shao. After these four players, Miracle's equipment was more or less accounted for. In terms of equipment, they really weren't even a match for Team Happy. Whether it was their stockpile of materials or their R&D talent, they still lost to Happy by quite a bit.

This time, Luo Ji's opponent was a very pitiful player who had no standing in Team Miracle: Jia Xing, and his character, Battle Mage Prideful Mage.

The classes that Team Miracle prepared for their players was an exact duplicate of Excellent Era's original class line-up. But in practice, their structure was actually the exact opposite.

He Ming's Elementalist was originally the sixth player in Excellent Era. Shen Jian's Striker and Wang Ze's Sharpshooter were both second-string players, but now all three of them formed the backbone of Team Miracle. On the contrary, it was the Battle Mage, Launcher and Spellblade, the classes that originally belonged to the core players of Excellent Era that had become secondary characters in Team Miracle.

Jia Xing was one of these players. His Battle Mage, Prideful Mage had an arrogant-sounding name, but he actually didn't have anything to be arrogant about. Team Miracle hadn't received much attention. If they had achieved the same kind of results as Happy, there were many in the team who were likely to face the question of "whether or not they were at a professional caliber", just like An Wenyi.

Jia Xing could be considered part of the main force of Team Miracle, and his standard wasn't too bad. In the competitions, he was always careful and prudent. A stifling and oppressive performance like that of the Battle God was something that he had begun to dare to dream of.

As a rookie who had just entered the professional scene, Jia Xing was perpetually walking on thin ice. But being part of a team as new as Miracle did have a benefit: while he was still a rookie, he had far more chances to compete than rookies in other teams.

After half a season, he had grown considerably, and Team Miracle's performance was receiving favourable evaluations. Jia Xing didn't receive much attention, but still, there was a seed of restlessness in his heart. Who would be willing to continually play the role of an obscure and unknown player? A performance as grand as the Battle God's was no longer something limited just to Jia Xing's wildest fantasies, but something that he had begun to have a the tiniest bit of hope for.

So today, when he had been selected to represent Miracle in the second round of the individual competition, he had looked at his opponent's name on the television screen, and his heart skipped a beat.

Luo Ji? Who was that?

Happy had always received a lot of attention, and Miracle, a new team, just like them, could only be jealous of them. But Luo Ji was a player who had never once appeared in a competition. No matter how much attention the team was receiving, it would still be very difficult to have news about him. Luo Ji was just like Qiao Yifan in the old days. Despite being in a champion team, he had no chances to appear in the battlefield, leaving the outside world to have no way of gauging his strength. At most, when one looked at the player seats, they would realize that the team actually still had such a person.

Never appearing in a competition simply meant that their caliber wasn't high enough. Concealing a hidden weapon? The Glory Alliance was a serious place, with no room for such a whimsical playstyle!

A rookie, and a player who had never appeared in a competition before; Jia Xing's excitement was as if he had just discovered the New World for the first time. As someone who had been around the block, he couldn't be clearer on how nervous one would be when they first appeared on stage. He had used quite a few rounds before managing to slowly get rid of that kind of discomfort. As for how much that discomfort would affect one's technical skill, he was also clear on that matter.

So, in his eyes, Luo Ji was a sub-par rookie who would be in complete shambles because of his nerves.

Finally, I've encountered an opponent that I can bully!

Jia Xing was fairly happy about this.

In the past 27 rounds of competition, there was no need to talk about the strong teams. Even when facing Bright Green and Seaside, two teams that looked doomed to be relegated in this season, someone as new as Jia Xing couldn't afford to look down upon their players, and had to use all his effort when facing them. But now, he finally had a chance to show-off to his heart's content, and display all of the fighting strength that he had.

Luo Ji?

Hahaha, this was a convenience delivered to his doorstep!

Jia Xing impatiently entered the player booth, impatiently waited for the competition to begin, and impatiently waited for the timer to countdown before the two of them loaded into the map. Then, he impatiently controlled Prideful Mage to charge out.

At the same time, Luo Ji was still taking deep breaths and still trying to rid himself of the nervousness and dread that he felt. He felt as if his whole body was on fire, and as stiff as hemp…...

Huu, huu, huu!

After taking three deep breaths, Luo Ji controlled Concealed Light and left the spawn point.

This was Happy's home game, and the map was selected by them. For his very first competition, how could Luo Ji dare to be careless? He had selected the map he had felt most comfortable and familiar on during his practice sessions for the individual round.

As he walked out of the spawn point and saw the familiar landscape around him, Luo Ji felt his mood lightening greatly.

"This should probably be the home team's advantage? It's really useful!" Luo Ji thought, controlling Concealed Light as he began to execute his mental plan for this battle.

After finding out that he was to appear in this round, Luo Ji had visualized countless scenarios in the match. Last night, he had slept very late, but woke up very early. Still, the lack of sleep didn't show on his face at all. He was too nervous, to the point where he couldn't even tell if he was tired anymore.

"Adopt your normal frame of mind."

"Just do it like you did in your practices, and you'll be fine."

These were some lines that his teammates told him to ease his anxiety, and the effectiveness was basically zero. Everyone dropped a few vague lines, with no one really hoping to be able to dissipate his nervousness with just a few words. At the end of the day, it was still left to Ye Xiu to be honest, telling him, "Go and carefully experience the feeling of competing!"

This kind of feeling, did it include nervousness?

As Luo Ji controlled Concealed Light, he thought about this and that, before suddenly realizing that his concentration was far too scattered. He frantically purged all of these useless thoughts from his mind, completely focusing on the road in front of him.

Jia Xing's Prideful Mage very quickly reached the center of the map, took a glance, and realized that no one was there.

He still wants to play tactics! Jia Xing laughed. A rookie who hadn't even competed before, what tactics could he possibly come up with?

Jia Xing had no fear. He originally wanted to just wait for Luo Ji to arrive, but after thinking about it, he decided to be a little more proactive, to appear more domineering. As a result, his character moved everywhere, searching for Concealed Light's whereabouts.

Fuck!

Luo Ji's heart leapt violently. He was just controlling Concealed Light to move very carefully when Prideful Mage's silhouette suddenly flitted across his camera. Just a flicker in his field of view had caused Luo Ji to be unbearably nervous. He frantically controlled Concealed Light to take cover in a corner, before inwardly guessing whether or not the other player had seen him.

If he had seen me…...

As Luo Ji thought about it, he promptly began casting a spell, and a Devil World Flower was immediately summoned near his leg. Immediately after that, he summoned a Frost Wolf.

The Frost Wolf's attacks were physical in nature, but they had the chance of applying a magical freezing effect. Under Luo Ji's inputs, it curled up next to the Devil World Flower, giving Luo Ji a fair bit of peace of mind.

However, his opponent hadn't appeared from start to finish.

He didn't see me?

When he had first seen his opponent, Luo Ji was hoping that his opponent hadn't noticed! But after completing his summons, when his opponent didn't appear, he actually felt a little disappointed.

Had he really not noticed?

All of the spectators in Happy's stadium had their hearts in their throats!

Jia Xing had seen Concealed Light and had clearly seen where he had gone to hide. But this fellow wasn't stupid. Even though he took Luo Ji as a gift sent to him to bully, when he saw how Concealed Light had hidden himself, he knew that his opponent had noticed him. If he just charged over, who knew if his opponent had an army of summons waiting to pounce on him? That would be difficult to deal with!

So, Jia Xing chose to take a roundabout path. At the same time as Luo Ji was anxiously making his conjectures, Prideful Mage had already used another path to loop around, spying on Luo Ji's arrangements from a corner.

Of course there's an ambush.

Jia Xing laughed coldly.

There weren't a lot of summons, but the Devil World Flower was capable of attacking in all different directions, and the Frost Wolf's attacks could cause a freezing effect that would slow enemies, making them particularly annoying to deal with. If he had rashly charged over just now, things wouldn't have ended well. Even though it was his opponent's first time on stage, Jia Xing still didn't look down on him too much. He couldn't just assume that his opponent was some normal player that he could deal with easily.

Waiting a bit more would be good enough.

The Devil World Flower could attack in all 360 degrees, so mounting a sneak attack from behind wouldn't make much sense. JIa Xing decided to let the Devil World Flower time out. He didn't believe that Luo Ji would repeatedly summon a Devil World Flower at the same spot to protect him. The Summoner's summons had a high mana consumption, they couldn't simply be summoned for no reason.

Jia Xing adjusted Prideful Mage's position slightly, waiting for the Devil World Flower to time out before launching a sneak attack.

It was at this moment that a cat's cry could be heard from his character's side. It wasn't a languid purr, no, it was the wrath-filled cry of a cat chasing after a mouse.

What?

Jia Xing was greatly alarmed and frantically turned his camera, only to see a black Spirit Cat already flying towards him. At this moment, Prideful Mage was already crouching down and couldn't crouch any lower, so Jia Xing could only control him to roll towards the side. Surprisingly, the Spirit Cat was extremely nimble, twisting its body in mid-air as its claws stretched out, leaving three bloody lines on Prideful Mage's face.

The audience let out a sigh of relief.

Were they worried about Concealed Light being sneak attacked? Of course not! With the 360 degree protection from the Devil World Flower, a sneak attack was impossible. They were worried because they had seen Concealed Light summon a Spirit Cat before simply letting it free.

Would such an attack be able to hit Prideful Mage? This was what the crowd was nervous about, because Luo Ji's commands to the Spirit Cat weren't very definite, as if wasn't confident that Prideful Mage was there. But now, the Spirit Cat's attack had completely uncovered Prideful Mage's location. Luo Ji immediately turned around and started casting.

Chapter 1338: I Can Too

Did Spirit Cat have an auto-targeting system?

Of course not. The summons of a Summoner, when set to free attack mode, would automatically attack any non-teammate target that wandered into its aggro range. Spirit Cat and a comparatively larger aggro range, more or less meaning that it's senses were sharper.

This map was carefully chosen by Luo Ji. There was no other one on one map that he was more familiar with. Jia Xing had thought that he would be able to sneak up on Luo Ji just by taking a more roundabout route, viewing Luo Ji as a complete newbie and underestimating his meticulous mind and familiarity with the map.

A sneak attack from behind was something Luo Ji he had accounted for! Spirit Cat had been arranged in a position where it would be able to sense if any enemies were in that area. Poor Jia Xing had no idea, happily waiting for a chance to strike. In the end, what he got was a Spirit Cat, and then another Devil World Flower.

Concealed Light had summoned another Devil World Flower, making sure Prideful Mage was placed within its attack range. Then, Frost Wolf rapidly approached as well.

Concealed Light, on the other hand, was continuing to cast, another summoning array appearing on the ground, followed by the cry of an eagle. Thunder Eagle burst out of the array and, after circling for a bit in the sky, darted towards where Prideful Mage was like a streak of lightning.

It flew through the air like lightning, spitting thunderbolts; this Thunder Eagle was one of Concealed Light's main summons.

Four Beasts Style!

Seeing Spirit Cat, Frost Wolf and Thunder Eagle appearing one after the other on the battlefield, the players more familiar with the game had an idea of what style Happy's debuting Summoner was using.

Young Wyvern, Frost Wolf, Thunder Eagle, Spirit Cat.

They were called the Four Summon Beasts, each being one of the four elements in Glory, Fire, Ice, Light and Dark respectively. Any summons combos that revolved around these four beasts were known as Four Beasts Style. With the level 75 update, an ultimate skill that could be activated when all Four Summon Beasts were summoned: Beast King Elemental Formation, once again increasing the strength of the Four Beats Style.

Now, Spirit Cat, Frost Wolf, Thunder Eagle had all appeared, so Young Wyvern probably wouldn't be long.

Luo Ji didn't disappoint. Young Wyvern was the lowest leveled of all four beats with a quick summon time. With a swift cast, Young Wyvern also flew out of the summoning array with a breath of flame, flying towards Prideful Mage after Thunder Eagle.

Seeing the beasts heading his way, Jia Xing's mood plummeted.

Spirit Cat was very, very hard to throw off and now that he was in Devil World Flower's attack range with the other three beasts rapidly approaching, aiming to surround him. If the Elemental Beast King Formation was then activated, then that would take a chunk out of Prideful Mage for sure.

This guy wasn't bad!

Jia Xing was careful to not underestimate him anymore, already realizing that Luo Ji wasn't an opponent he could easily wipe the floor with. Currently, with the summoned creatures coming one after the other, there were layers to this offensive, a system. It was almost too much.

Flee?

　

With Spirit Cat already on him and Thunder Eagle's speed, fleeing wasn't a good idea. Currently, it seemed like the only solution was to brute force his way out of these summons.

This guy was no easy opponent, managing to force him into a dire situation like this.

The situation was a pain, but there was no other choice. The earlier he acted the better.

Swinging his spear, he knocked Spirit Cat aside as it leaped at him once again. With a Dragon Tooth, he forced Frost Wolf to back off a little.

Boom!

Sparks danced across Prideful Mage's body. After two actions, he was then hit by the thunderbolt that Thunder Eagle spat out.

　

How troublesome.

Jia Xing no longer felt like showing off anymore. He could tell that Concealed Light's four summons weren't put on automatic, but being controlled manually instead. That was why it was so systematic, so well-paced, and so hard.

Wasn't he going to come forward a little?

Jia Xing kept an eye on Concealed Light's movements. Summoners had the skill Lash, which lashed the summons and increased their combative power. With him already in an encirclement, most Summoners would come over to lash their summons to strengthen them.

However, Concealed Light didn't. He merely stood far off, constantly using Mark to adjust the actions of his summons.

Looks like he'd have to wait for the summons to switch out...

Jia Xing felt helpless. He was rather helpless against these meticulously executed attacks. He couldn't flee and could only wait until one of the summons disappeared and his opponent summoned another. There might be an opening to be found there.

Thus, Jia Xing didn't bother trying to break through and started fighting the summons. One against four with a Devil World Flower disrupting him… if it weren't for summons having rather simple and bland ways of attacking, Jia Xing definitely wouldn't be able to last. Right now, though, he could just about hold on...

Summons depended on two things to live, one was time and the other was health.

Waiting for their time to run out was too passive, so Jia Xing had to attack and try and get rid of one. However, these four summons weren't so easy to kill. Spirit Cat was quick and nimble, hard to hit; Thunder Eagle and Young Wyvern were both fliers, even harder to hit; in the end, the easiest one to deal with of the four was Frost Wolf, but Frost Wolf just so happened to also be the tankiest one of the four, with a huge chunk of health.

How did it end up like this? Jia Xing felt like crying. He had originally thought he could easily bully this newbie, but now who'd have thought he'd be struggling to survive. In these 27 rounds, he, as a rookie on a rookie team, had been through so many hardships. Why was he falling into the same position against a rookie from a new team, in their debuting match, too?

Could it be that he had become overcautious by habit?

Did he turn to defense whenever he met any sort of trouble?

After facing off against so many experienced seniors, could it be that he had been so oppressed that he had lost his aggression?

These questions surfaced in Jia Xing's mind one after the other.

　

He wasn't willing to continue like this!

However, if even this opponent could suppress him like this, then when would he ever be able to gain the initiative in battle?

Initiative!

He had to take the initiative!

He shouldn't get used to this passivity. If he accepted it, then wouldn't he just continue to live in this mediocrity?

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

As if suddenly waking up, Jia Xing saw an opening in front if him and acted without even thinking. The subconscious nature of his actions had his fingers darting across the keyboard much swifter and more dexterous than before. Prideful Mage charged out!

Bang!

Spirit Cat had lunged a moment too late. It's priority was nothing compared to Dragon Breaks the Ranks, and it was flung to one side. Thunder Eagle's thunderbolt and Young Wyvern's fireball all struck the spot behind Prideful Mage, missing him entirely.

　

He broke through!

Delight washed over Jia Xing, though even he was a little confused as to how he had succeeded. That opportunity just now… If he hadn't been reckless, if it hadn't been subconscious, then he'd probably have given it up, thinking he couldn't do it, no?

So he really could do it!

With his delight, Dragon Breaks the Ranks broke out of the formation made by the Four Beast Summons. Devil World Flower's vines quietly creeped out of the earth, but Jia Xing was ready for it.

Shattering the Lands!

Prideful Mage leaped skywards, surging magical energy pulsing from the tip of his spear. This only made Jia Xing feel a delighted warmth spread through his heart and mind.

This wild battle style was something he had only seen in the matches of gods! Yet now, he had managed to execute the same style in a match! He could do it! He really could!

Prideful Mage landed, and the magical energy roared, bursting out. Even the flying Young Wyvern and Thunder Eagle couldn't approach.

Luo Ji's Concealed Light backed away quickly, escaping from the range of this attack. However, by then, he had already been separated from his summons by this powerful, surging skill. How would a Summoner face the powerful Battle Mage without any summons?

How did everything fall apart?

　

Luo Ji was puzzled. His control over the situation wasn't bad.

Under Ye Xiu suggestion, he ended up choosing the Four Beasts Style as his Summoner style because he was decent at controlling four summons at once to make offensive arrangements. Though the Spirit Style and its sea of summons was powerful, especially with the new level 75 skill Spirit Sacrifice which was the ultimate damage skill for a Summoner, he wouldn't be able to maintain control. Even with that skill, he wouldn't be able to utilize it properly.

However, his opponent had still managed to break through the four beasts Luo Ji was confident in being able to control. Did he miss some important detail?

As Luo Ji thought to himself, he was already making new arrangements.

If a summon died, it could be re-summoned, so they could stay and tank damage, usually. However, Shatter the Lands came with a huge shockwave. Even if you let your summons tank out the damage, they'd still be knocked away by the magic energy. The four beasts had their way blocked and couldn't immediately come to help, so Luo Ji hurriedly had Concealed Light resummon a creature while Prideful Mage was still in his ending lag.

He could make it!

As for his ability to calculate, that was something Luo Ji had even more confidence in. As expected, Concealed Light managed to summon a new Frost Wolf to protect him before Prideful Mage arrived, but...

Circle Swing.

Just like that, Frost Wolf was tossed behind Prideful Mage and then a Dragon Tooth struck him.

A Summoner that had been closed in on was helpless. The good thing was that even if he didn't make any moves, so long as his summons were still on the field, they would attack automatically.

However, Prideful Mage darted back and forth as he struck again and again before suddenly disappearing.

Teleportation!

This Battle Mage had shockingly chosen to add the Elementalist's Teleportation into his weapon.

A Falling Flower Palm hit from behind, and he was shoved forward. That's when he saw his Four Summon Beasts standing obediently in a straight line.

Summons without manual control really weren't any good! Luo Ji hurriedly had them scatter, but, it was too late.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Prideful Mage's spear shot forwards, magic energy forming a massive dragon which devoured Concealed Light and all of his Four Summon Beasts.

Boom!

The magical energy erupted, darting and flashing through its multiple victims, absolutely spectacular.

I really can do it!

Jia Xing was very satisfied with his performance today.

Ai… It had been going so well in the beginning, so how did things end up like this? Luo Ji, on the other hand, was lamenting.

Chapter 1339: Writing a Guide For Yourself

Luo Ji had lost.

This result wasn't too unexpected, but at the beginning, he felt that he had been doing quite well. His confidence was being slowly built up, but who would have predicted that his opponent would knock it down again so quickly.

His opponent wasn't anyone impressive either. He was like Luo Ji, a rookie on a new team. The only thing he held over Luo Ji was 27 rounds of experience.

Luo Ji took a deep breath and exited the player booth, not at all expecting the entire stadium to explode into applause.

What was this?

Luo Ji was puzzled. At first he thought that this was their home game fans respecting Miracle's spectacular performance and applauding them. However, after he left the stage, walking away, he noticed the calls of "Luo Ji, you did great" and the gazes that were on him. He knew then that this applause was his, an encouragement for him.

Though he had never played a match before, Happy's fans all knew of his existence in Happy. This wasn't just from observing the player bench during matches, but because Happy's boss Chen Guo never forgot to mention Luo Ji when she brought up Happy's players. In fact, to make sure Luo Li was noticed, she'd often be willing to talk more about Luo ji. Though Luo Ji had never fought a match, Chen Guo wouldn't hesitate to tell everyone of the contributions he had made to the team.

This was a testament of Chen Guo's attentiveness. She hated the thought of this benched player feeling uncomfortable or left out, so she did her best to show that he was equally as much a part of the team as anyone else.

　.

Chen Guo's actions finally bore fruit at a time like now. Not only did Happy's fans know Luo Ji, they all liked this member of Happy who, despite not having much of a chance to play for the team, had still carefully and sincerely contributed to the team. They were even hoping for the day Luo Ji would have a chance to play.

Thus, when Luo Ji really did get the chance to play a match, what he received wasn't pressure, but encouragement.

Applause and well-wishes escorted Luo Ji step by step back to the player bench.

Miracle's Jia Xing was stunned.

When he first came out of the player booth, he had truly thought that the applause was for him because he had thought he fought spectacularly in this match, just like an expert.

I've even managed to sway the hearts of my opponent's fans, Jia xing thought to himself in delight. That wasn't an easy thing to accomplish at all. He waved, continuing to show off his demeanor, and acknowledging these cute Happy fans that were clapping for him.

　

It was only until he had come off the stage and approached the stands that he heard what the fans were yelling. He stiffened. He suddenly wanted nothing more than to cut of that damned waving hand.

This Luo Ji was so well liked amongst Happy's fans? Even if he lost he could still gain everyone's love like that? Jia Xing stared at Luo Ji, who had returned to the player bench, with a heart full of envy.

Luo Ji sat in the empty seat next to Ye Xiu without needing any prompting.

Even if Ye Xiu didn't come to to find him, he would go and ask Ye Xiu for pointers regarding this match. Depressed from losing? When it had just ended, a little, yeah! But Luo Ji had been prepared to lose so he soon shook off those feelings. Then, hearing the cheers and encouragements from the fans after exiting the booth, Luo Ji was determined to work even harder in order to thank his team and the fans for their support.

Luo Ji had noticed Chen Guo's efforts in trying to make sure he didn't feel left out.

"You started off well." Ye Xiu didn't bother with courtesies, getting straight to the point.

"Yes." Luo Ji nodded.

"Your control was meticulous; that's your strength," Ye Xiu continued.

"Yes." Luo Ji nodded again. His calculations were accurate, thus his actions were meticulous. Luo Ji understood himself well.

"Yet that's exactly how you lost," Ye Xiu then said.

Luo Ji fell into contemplation.

"Your opponent is a person, not a machine. A person's mechanics, a person's performance, will never be as precise as theory. Sometimes they might be in a poor condition, other times they might go beyond their usual limits. Your playstyle has to account for these changes in your opponent's pace," Ye Xiu explained.

"Do you remember the Dummy's Guides you used to make often?" Ye Xiu asked.　　

"I do." Luo Ji nodded.

"Your current control has the same flaws as your guides for dummies: They don't tolerate mistakes and deviations," Ye Xiu said.

"Oh…" Luo Ji immediately understood what Ye Xiu was getting at.

He thought of when his opponent had used Dragon Breaks the Ranks to break through his summons. In his calculations, that opening wasn't something this opponent had the ability to grasp.

But his opponent had broken past his own limits, achieving a hand speed and mechanics he wouldn't have been able to usually. Thus, what Luo Ji had thought wouldn't happen, happened, and his playstyle didn't have any way to make up for this.

It seemed like his calculations regarding his opponent's ability wasn't comprehensive enough! However, just as Ye Xiu had said, a person's condition would fluctuate and change. Even they themselves would be incapable of controlling this. It was impossible for another to completely account for this in their calculations.

"Then what do I do?" Luo Ji asked.

"The best way is, of course, to refine your playstyle further," Ye Xiu replied.

Luo Ji felt a headache coming on. He naturally understood this reasoning. More refined attacks, harder to counter attacks, that would naturally allow him to suppress and defeat his opponents. The problem was that his ability was limited. He could only refine his playstyle within the boundaries of his talent. This best way was something he couldn't choose, or else he'd have tried ages ago.

"If you can't refine everything, then what about smaller parts?" Ye Xiu then said.

"Partly refine?"

"Consider Mo Fan," Ye Xiu suggested.

Luo Ji was stunned for a moment. What did Mo Fan have to do with this?

Currently, Mo Fan was already on the stage for the third individual match. The projection and the big screen were both playing the scenes of his and his opponent killing each other.

　

Whoosh!

　

A rapid five part combo had Deception's opponent floundering.

I'll probably never be able to accomplish that, Luo Ji thought to himself. However, Deception, after a few impressive combos, quickly fled the area.

Luo Ji naturally knew why Mo Fan's playstyle was like so, and thus instantly realized why Ye Xiu wanted him to consider Mo Fan.

Ye Xiu meant that for certain controls, Luo Ji might not be able to refine completely, but some simpler actions were things that he could definitely master with his current ability.

Rebuilding his offensive system through fully utilizing these actions he could master?

　　

Luo Ji felt like he was beginning to understand.

　

All this time, he had been referencing guides, learning all sorts of Summoner knowledge. He already knew what he should learn, what he should master. Therefore what he needed to do now was find the things that were most suited to him, the things he could do the best in. Just like deciding on the Four Beasts Style, he had to choose what suited him the most.

It was time he wrote a Dummy's Guide for himself.

"I understand!" Luo Ji nodded.

　

Ye Xiu smiled. Speaking with smart people was always the easiest! Just look and Luo Ji and then consider Mo Fan, who was currently onstage. Ok, he'll admit, speaking to Mo Fan wasn't all a waste, but getting Steamed Bun with his unique brain structure and planes of thinking to understand was truly harder than hard!

　

After the individual matches, the group arena soon ended.

　

Mo Fan had claimed victory for the third individual match and the group arena saw the powerful formation of Tang Rou, Su Mucheng and Fang Rui successfully defeating Miracle giving them a 4 to 1 lead as they entered the team competition.

In the team competition, Happy had everyone shocked, fielding Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, Tang Rou, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi and Steamed Bun. They had let Ye Xiu rest for a round!

　

"Holy crap!"

Before anyone else reacted, Miracle, who was fielding all their core members, expressed their discontent first.

Miracle had three previous Excellent Era members! They believed that they had a comprehensive understanding of Ye Xiu, of Su Mucheng and of their teamwork. Last time, Happy had swept them 0 to 10. Thus, this time, they had made even more preparations. They had carefully honed their tactics to deal with Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, determined to win back their points on Happy's home turf. Yet then… Ye Xiu wasn't even participating in the team competition this round.

Was this Ye Xiu looking down on them?

Miracle's little group felt somewhat offended, but then, thinking back on the time they were with Ye Xiu in Excellent Era, when had the other ever looked down on anyone? No matter how weak, he'd never do that. He would only mock them! No matter how strong the opponent, he'd always manage to find something to mock them for.

So was this a way of mocking them?!

The three considered it again.

However, not playing a match didn't seem like Ye Xiu's method of mockery.

The three were distressed.

They should've been laughing in delight at their opponent's strongest player not being fielded, but Miracle treated this as some sort of hateful, despicable thing. Nothing was more painful than dedicating yourself to rehearsing and practicing, but then finding out right before going on stage that it was no longer necessary; the show had been changed.

Absolutely shameless!

Miracle's three brothers felt anger burning inside them.

"Even so, we can't lose!" He Ming said to the players about to go on stage. Then he saw Guo Shao's confused blinking.

He Ming immediately realized his words seemed off.

Even so? Even so what? With his tone and wording, it was like without Ye Xiu, their opponent's just got stronger!

That wasn't right at all. Ye Xiu was Happy's core. Without him on the field, Happy's overall strength would only decrease, not increase.

"Ahem…" He Ming cleared his throat, trying to figure out what to say.

"If Senior Ye Xiu isn't being fielded, then does that mean our tactic is useless?" Guo Shao's words struck them straight in the gut.

"Yes. However, without Ye Xiu, their strength will definitely be affected. This is our chance," He Ming used this to turn them back on track.

"What should we do then?" Guo Shao asked.

He Ming short circuited.

This was because the current situation was truly the worst. Their pre-match practice was all about dealing with Ye Xiu, completely ignoring this possibility. Who would've thought that after 27 rounds, on the 28th with them, Ye Xiu would decide to do this? Miracle's pre-match preparations were all for nothing and they couldn't really come up with any detailed plan on what to do.

"Focus on… on…" He Ming looked through Happy's lineup.

　

"Qiao Yifan!" This name suddenly popped out. "Yes, Qiao Yifan!" He Ming nodded, saying with confidence.

Chapter 1340: Wind Howl’s New Playstyle

He Ming was the sixth player when he was at Excellent Era. Players of this position were generally suddenly switched in while the two sides were deep in conflict, so they had to have the ability to read the situation and immediately understand what was happening, thus allowing them to join in and come to their teammates' aid as soon as possible.

He Ming usually played this position in Excellent Era, so his abilities in regards to this were considerable. Judging the situation, observing the tactics, he was rather good at all that. So who should they focus on first out of Happy's current lineup?

Cleric Little Cold Hands? Often considered Happy's weakness, Happy's Cleric was usually the main focus of other teams in the team competition. However, precisely because of this, Happy would often have a very meticulous plan to protect their Cleric. The teams who tried to attack Happy from this direction would often get led around by the nose instead.

Using the opponent's strategy against them! That was something Ye Xiu simply loved to do. Of the Four Master Tacticians, Ye Xiu was definitely the one with the most sophisticated plans and schemes, no matter if it came to his sheer experience or simply his style. As the Glory Textbook, he could put himself into another's shoes and predict a lot of possible strategies his opponents would use and counter them. Thus, any team of which he was a part of, if you didn't have absolute confidence in being able to take advantage of an obvious weakness, it was best to leave it be.

Miracle was currently a new team, not any sort of powerhouse and He Ming naturally didn't have enough confidence to challenge the traps Ye Xiu had laid. Thus, the choice Little Cold Hands was thrown out.

Apart from that?

Su Mucheng? They were familiar with Su Mucheng from a teammates perspective, but Su Mucheng was a Launcher. For ranged fighters, if they wanted to use Screen Cannon, they could often stay out of the main battlefield. If they targeted her, the entire team might get kited around and thus fall to a heavy disadvantage. This wasn't a good breakthrough point.

Then, Fang Rui, Master of Dirty Play. This… nope, never mind! He Ming thought to himself. A tricky and cunning opponent like that wasn't one a young, new team like them could deal with.

Then, there was Tang Rou, the fearsome Battle Mage. Even if her reputation had taken a hit, no one dared to underestimate her actual skill. Just now, in the group arena, Tang Rou had gone first and had almost managed to wipe out two of Miracle's players. Though she had yet to defeat a God, her persistence, her aggression meant that she definitely had the ability pin an opponent like a god level player. If they targeted Tang Rou, they might end up pinned by her, unable to escape.

Thus, looking over Happy's starting lineup, it seemed that Qiao Yifan was the only choice for a breakthrough. Plus, his Ghost Chaining was very dangerous. Dealing with him first would mean to alter the battle situation entirely.

"Let's go!" With limited time, He Ming quickly adjusted their tactics a little before leading the team onstage.

At the same time, at another much anticipated match, Wind Howl versus 301 Degrees had already entered the team competition stage.

In the 1v1s, the two teams had ended up with a 4 to 1, Wind Howl taking the lead on their home turf and only losing one point.

As for the team competition afterwards...

Man to man!

Wind Howl seemed to have tasted the sweetness of this strategy after their victory against Blue Rain. For them, who didn't have any sort of high-end strategy at the moment, dividing the opponent and conquering them through isolating the match into five 1v1s which depended on individual strength seemed like a good choice.

Of course, Wind Howl wasn't naive enough to think that 301 Degrees wouldn't be watching out for this strategy after that last match. When the match begun, Wind Howl, very uncharacteristically, didn't charge right for the center of the map. This was something extremely rare after Tang Hao had become the captain.

Wind Howl used their map advantage for their home game and split up, preparing to observe 301 Degrees from the flanks. After approaching, they saw that, as expected, 301 Degrees was on guard against their man to man offense they had used against Blue Rain. The characters of 301 Degrees were all standing closer together than usual. Every character could assure that they'll have at least two other characters' support. If they charged right in, they probably wouldn't be able to tear their team apart.

　　

However, since Wind Howl had been expecting their opponents to be on guard against this, they naturally had their own way to deal with it. This week, Team Wind Howl had focused on practicing how to dismantle an opponent in a formation primed for teamwork and support, tearing them apart into one on ones.

After observing 301 Degrees' current formation, they quickly communicated their plans in their team channel and then Wind Howl's characters charged out from the sides.

Brawler Demon Subduer, Elementalist Beautiful Light, Spell Blade Total Darkness, Qi Master Qi Breaker, Thief Doubtful Demon.

Five classes, no healer. Wind Howl had once again executed this daring strategy.

　

Demond Subduer, Tyrannical Chain Punch!

Tang Hao's Demon Subduer was the first to lunge. For this skill, shoving the opponent onto the ground was equal to a grab, a very powerful control.

Qi Breaker, Cloud Grasping Fist!

Guo Yang had truly met an opportunity at Wind Howl this season, though his current Qi Master character, Qi Breaker, was rather weak. Although this was that powerful Qi Master of Excellent Era's glorious past, when the Challenger League happened, Excellent Era didn't have a Qi Master character and so this character wasn't upgraded with the big update. It wasn't until Wind Howl bought the character for a low price a Excellent Era's clearance sale that its equipment began to be upgraded, so it was natural that it was a little behind. However, for Guo Yang, this was the character he was most familiar with, one he had used for years, and it was much smoother than the character Wind Howl had given him last year. Although Wind Howl hadn't had the best journey this season, he only got better with time and stabilized his position as the last member of Wind Howl's team competition lineup. In the current Wind Howl, apart from Ruan Yonglin, all the players had changed from before.

Right now, he cooperated with Tang Hao, of the two Fighters, one closed in and grabbed a target and the other snatched a target from afar.

Afterwards, Beautiful Light began the cast for the AoE Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire while Liu Hao's Total Darkness sent Wave Sword after Wave Sword into 301 Degree's formation. Lin Feng's Doubtful Demon, a battle Thief that didn't care for dirty play, went into pursuit, using this opportunity to start isolating his own target.

"Wind Howl's teamwork isn't bad!" Commentator Li Yibo called out. Team 301 Degrees was clearly having some trouble reacting to Wind Howl's offensive.

Demon Subduer's attack should be dodged.

Qi Breaker and Beautiful Light's attacks should be interrupted, but the two were far off.

Total Darkness' Wave Sword attacks were sweeping into their team, cutting up their formation.

Everything had occurred simultaneously, and there wasn't enough time for giving orders. In these situations, they could only rely on their teamwork and synchronization, on the reactions of the individual team members.

However, 301 Degrees' weakness was unfortunately exposed. Their team had their new core member join during the winter transfer window and their strategy had gone through a metamorphosis. Though they were doing well, it didn't change the fact that they were still in a transitional period, still trying to get familiar with one another.

Thus, in a situation that necessitated a high level of synchronization between team members, where they had to be able to divide up their workloads, they erred.

Qi Breaker's Cloud Grasping Fist wasn't interrupted, and Knight Tide was pulled out of the formation.

Tide was originally using his shield to shield his teammates from Total Darkness' Wave Swords, preventing their formation from being ruined. But with him dragged off, Total Darkness' Wave Swords reached their formation, and 301 Degrees' formation scattered as the team members dodged. Lin Feng's Doubtful Demon took the opportunity to dart in, using a Staggering Blow to dizzy Gao Jie's Stellar Sword. Though Demon Subduer's Tyrannical Chain Punch had been dodged, Demon Subduer managed to grab 301 Degrees' Paladin, Sun Mingjin's Double O Seven, and throw him out of the formation in the confusion.

Currently, 301 Degree's formation had been completely destroyed. They hurriedly tried to adjust, but the weakness in their lacking synchronization once again surfaced. In the blink of an eye, they were thrown to a dire disadvantage.

In the end, Wind Howl won, which surprised many. No one would have thought that the 301 Degrees that everyone was nervous about facing, having been reborn after the winter transfer window with a new set of tactics, would lose to a team like Wind Howl, who was seen as weak.

"After Blue Rain, 301 Degrees, too… If succeeding the first time was just because they had it easy by catching their opponents off guard… But this time 301 Degrees had clearly been on guard against this playstyle of Wind Howl's, yet in the end, they still didn't manage to defend against it. Team Wind Howl acted swiftly, precisely, utilizing this man to man offensive to its fullest. I believe that we can reignite our hopes for this team. They seemed to have found the style that suits them," Li Yibo commented post-match.

"But wouldn't just one playstyle be too simple?" Pan Lin wondered aloud.

"One playstyle can be used in many different ways. I believe that Team Wind Howl won't just just stop here. They'll definitely continue to practice and perfect this playstyle. Of course, this doesn't mean that we can say for certain that they don't have any other strategies. In any case, this playstyle is a good new addition to Team Wind Howl's strategies. In the future, whenever a team faces Wind Howl, they'd have to be on guard for this and will have to practice countering this. This, in and of itself, is already one way to hinder their opponents," Li Yibo explained.

"You're too right! And this is where Wind Howl and 301 Degrees' match ends. This match really was fast. Currently, all other matches are still fighting their team competitions!" This live broadcast was surprisingly quick to end and the broadcasting channel was probably adjusting the plans for the time they had left over. The match had ended, but the broadcast was continuing. Pan Lin and Li Yibo then turned the match broadcast into a talk show.

"Hey, we can take a look at the other matches!" Li Yibo suggested.

"Wait!" Pan Lin merely took a glance before he cried out, "Ye Xiu didn't appear in the team competition between Happy and Miracle!"

"Oh? How come? We didn't get any news of this. Is he hurt or…? Did he fight in the individual competitions?" Li Yibo asked, rapidfire.

"He did fight in the individual competition, continuing his streak." Pan Lin looked over the information. "Huh? Luo Ji's appeared to play in this round."

Li Yibo was stunned for a moment. "Sending up rookies for experience, their team's core player Ye Xiu not playing… Does Happy think that their position in the playoffs are secured and they can treat the remaining matches as training for their troops?"

Chapter 1341: An Uneventful Round

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were surprised at the arrangements Happy had made this round, and at this point, Happy and Miracle were deep into their match.

Target Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash?

He Ming's analysis and plan was good in theory, but reality told them that Qiao Yifan wasn't someone they could wipe out so easily. When the two sides met, they didn't see a hint of One Inch Ash. The other had gone on some strategic approach.

Matches weren't so inflexible. Since their target wasn't there, they weren't going to cling to this plan, ignore what was in front of them and run off to find their target. Thus, Miracle, seeing that they had the advantage in numbers, decided to just go for it!

They did, in fact, have the advantage in numbers, and a huge advantage, too.

When the two sides met face to face, Miracle was a full team of five while Happy was only Tang Rou and Su Mucheng's characters.

5v2, what was there to be afraid of?

　

Miracle swarmed over, but they knew that Happy wouldn't just send to people for them to kill, so they were on guard for if Happy would suddenly attack from some other direction.

5v2, with this exchange, there had yet to be a result, but He Ming, Wang Ze and Shen Jian felt rather anxious.

What were they up against? The combo of a Battle Mage and a Launcher! The combo they were most familiar with, the one that the team they had spent years in revolved around. Plus, in the past this combo had done it all: 2v1, 2v2, 2v3, 2v4, 2v5. Subconsciously, He Ming and co had erased their advantage in number from their mind. Advantage? What advantage? They were the ones pinned!

Soon enough, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea appeared and Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash also arrived from their right and left flanks, executing a pincer attack on Miracle.

One Inch Ash had appeared, but the goal of focusing on getting rid of One Inch Ash wasn't going to be easy to accomplish at all. He Ming and co shockingly realized that they had been trapped. Also, this scene was too familiar! In the past, it was their opponents who would be trapped by the Battle Mage and Launcher duo, while they caused trouble from the sides.

So in the end, it was the strategy we were most familiar with?

He Ming and the other two's spirits fell. Lord Grim and Dancing Rain had used their familiarity with these two opponents to craft a strategy to counteract them. Lord Grim straight up didn't show up though, yet it was like Miracle had lost their core. In the end, however, Soft Mist and Dancing Rain had executed a playstyle that was far more familiar to them than Lord Grim and Dancing Rain, giving them a sense of deja vu.

　　

Sigh, if they had known earlier...

He Ming and co all held such thoughts. In the end, the team competition ended in Happy's victory, and Happy had won a spectacular score of 9 to 1 this round.

In the post-match press conference, no one had much interest in Miracle, and their press conference ended quickly. When Happy arrived, the reports naturally expressed great interest in Luo Ji's appearance in the match and Ye Xiu's lack thereof in the team competition.

The answer they received was that they were preparing for the playoffs.

Happy already getting into the pace for the playoffs!

Soon enough, such headlines appeared on the news. However, this wasn't really anything to be too shocked about. The season was approaching its last stages, and teams that had stable scores were already preparing themselves for the playoffs. No matter now or before, the playoffs had always been different from the regular season. The matches were frequent, and you'd have to travel back and forth for the home and away games. This truly did necessitate some adjustments and planning.

However, it was only Round 28! Wasn't Happy getting into the pace of the playoffs a little too soon? If they started preparing their troops and training them, then weren't they afraid of accidentally slipping out of the playoffs list?

However, this round of training their troops still ended up with a landslide victory of 9 to 1, so what could anyone really say? Those Happy haters could only swallow their words in the face of reality.

Round 28 was a round of landslide victories from the powerhouses. Apart from Wind Howl's 9 to 1 victory against 301 Degrees, nothing unexpected happened in any of the other matches.

Team Happy, gaining another 9 points to their score, had 187 points in total, continuing to place sixth. Next was Team Hundred Blossoms with 183. After Wind Howl had beaten 301 Degrees, they had managed to overtake the other team with their 9 to 1 victory. Though they had the same number of points at 167, Wind Howl had beaten 301 Degrees 9 to 1 this round and lost to 301 Degrees 3 to 7 in the ninth round. The total score of their matches was 12 to 8, Wind Howl in the lead, so Wind Howl was ranked above 301 Degrees despite their equal point value.

　

Wind Howl and 301 Degrees' ranking switch was the only movement for this round. The other teams all retained their original rankings. For all the teams ranked lower than number 12's Royal Style, it was more or less over for them this season. Now all that was left was to see if they would make a final charge towards gaining a few more points on the rankings. However, this motivation was primarily present in the club, and not the players.

The media was diving into the small area surrounding 8th place. They didn't even bother reporting on the top ranked powerhouses Samsara, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, etc.. The fight for the top place in the regular season had long since lost its suspense. The powerhouses' score were stable and there was no way they would fall out of the top eight. What was there to write about? The teams heading for the top four did have some juice to them. After all, being in the top four did have the advantage of an extra home game. However, compared to the fight for the eighth place, the charge for the top four could be pushed to the backburner.

April 3rd, Round 29 of the Pro League, 301 Degrees welcoming Misty Rain to their home game became one of the more interesting face offs.

　

Misty Rain currently had 149 points, ranked tenth, was 18 points away from the ninth and eighth ranked 301 Degrees and Wind Howl. They still had hope for getting into the playoffs. However, considering Misty rain's performance this season, most people didn't really expect anything.

Team Misty Rain's new playstyle had been constantly criticised, but after the winter transfer window, they still didn't make any adjustments. In the latter half of the season, their performance hadn't improved any. Now in these last ten rounds, no one knew if they even had the courage to make the charge for the playoffs. Though the club PR always sprouted messages about trust, diligence, fighting for a chance to turn the tables, these were things everyone knew to say. Bright Green and Seaside had also said that they wouldn't give up, but anyone could see that they had already disarmed themselves.

Round 29 was rather calm. Happy had an away game against Royal Style this round. Once a top team, they had already fallen to the point where they didn't even have a chance for the playoffs. However, Royal Style's home turf was still as lively as ever. This was an old team with ten years of history, after all. How many other teams in the alliance had ten years of history?

There were many older fans in their home stadium, middle aged fans were no rare sight. This was probably a scene exclusive to older teams. These people probably hadn't dedicated themselves to Glory much later than even Ye Xiu. Though they were only normal players, lacking the accomplishments that Ye Xiu had achieved, they definitely didn't love Glory any less, able to persist for a full ten years. Glory had already become an integral part of their lives.

Royal Style had completely fallen, but these people didn't leave. Like how Glory was an integral part of their lives, Royal Style was an integral part of their Glory. They had gotten used to supporting this team. If they did well, then good. If they didn't, it didn't matter either. They were no longer fans at an age where they would run over to young players and new promising teams, howling with excitement.

In the first individual competition, Happy continued to field Ye Xiu, and the audience even applauded when Ye Xiu entered the stage.

They had watched ten years of Glory, so they held respect for this veteran of ten years. Thought this guy had crushed Royal Style in the finals of the very first season of the Glory Pro League, Royal Style didn't have as big of a grudge as Tyranny. After all, they only held a grudge for this one year, not like how Excellent Era and Tyranny had gone back and forth for a full four years, always clashing in the finals; that would naturally result in such a huge grudge.

The applause was rather surprising for Ye Xiu, and he acknowledged the audience with a wave. Thinking of Royal Style's past, and then their present, Ye Xiu grew deeply nostalgic.

Then, on the stage, seeing the opposing player and character, Ye Xiu's breath hitched with emotion.

　

Tian Sen, Peaceful Hermit.

Royal Style had sent out their core and captain in the first match against Ye Xiu.

Unlike Wind Howl sending Tang Hao up first, Royal Style had probably arranged this with a very different attitude. In this season, they wouldn't be able to do much more or aim for anything further. Thus, they relaxed, and even their core came over to fight an individual match. They probably wanted to try breaking Ye Xiu's record, giving their team a little boost and their fans some action! After all, if they just ended it like this, it would be way too calm.

Peaceful Hermit!

Ye Xiu gazed at the character projected by the central projector of the stadium.

This was the character that fought with Ye Xiu over the championship of the very first season of the Glory Pro Alliance. Back then, One Autumn Leaf, Desert Dust and this Peaceful Hermit were the three most elite, most famous characters of the alliance. And now? Peaceful Hermit… Now how many young people still remembered the strength of this character? In the All-Stars this season, Peaceful Hermit didn't even get in.

Tian Sen. Ye Xiu looked to Peaceful Hermit's current player, getting into the player booth on the other side. This player, tall and built more like an athlete than an esports player, always seemed to struggle to get into the booth more than others; it was somewhat comical.

The Golden Generation, the batch of rookies that had shone the brightest, had all become core members of their teams. Tian Sen was probably the most tragic of them. His pro career had consisted of watching as Royal Style declined from a top powerhouse to a team that didn't even had hope to enter the playoffs. Yet he still persisted, silently. In the winter transfer window, 301 Degrees had invited him to join their team. Before Team Royal Style could express anything, he had stepped forth to speak his own mind.

No matter how well they did, just by this heart, he was a player deserving of respect.

As Ye Xiu entered the player booth, he thought of the player who had Peaceful Hermit before Tian Sen. That player had been known as one of the Three Gods of that era along with Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing: Guo Mingyu.

"God, my ass," Ye Xiu cursed as he inserted his account card into the card reader, "He owes me money, and he just disappeared like that. What an ass!"

Chapter 1342: They Call It Counter?

Happy versus Royal Style, individual competition match 1. Both characters had already loaded onto the map.

On one side was a ten-year player who had changed character; on the other side was a ten-year character who had changed player. These two sides rich with history stood on the stage now, and quickly met at the center of the map.

This was Royal Style's home game, but Royal Style had actually chosen to use a simple map like the ones that Ye Xiu normally chose. For a team that already had no more goals for this season, these matches had no pressure. Tian Sen probably wanted to use this kind of battlefield to directly break Ye Xiu.

"How daring." Ye Xiu couldn't help but praise the opponent.

"Bring it!" Tian Sen answered.

He had joined Royal Style just in time to witness the team's decline from prosperity. Everyone said that his story was a tragedy, but in reality, Tian Sen felt that he was still rather fortunate. At least Team Royal Style was still here, and he could still be its member. But what about the person in front of him now? Where was the team he once represented, Excellent Era? Once upon a time it was at the pinnacle of Glory, a dynasty-establishing team, but it had since collapsed until it was nothing more than smoke and ashes. And the final blow had been delivered by this person himself. This person standing here now, he was the most tragic person in Glory, was he not?

There had been numerous discussions about what had happened between Ye Xiu and Excellent Era. Tian Sen wasn't someone who liked to gossip, but he believed Ye Xiu. He believed that as long as he was allowed, he would absolutely fight for Excellent Era until the end. No matter how well or poorly the team fared, he wouldn't leave or quit. This wasn't mere loyalty. This was a sort of unbreakable tie that existed between the first generation of players, their teams, and their characters. Tian Sen understood this well, because he had inherited all of this. Even though he was part of the Golden Generation, he adhered to spirit and ideas of the Founding Generation.

Parting from one's team, parting from one's character, it was undoubtedly painful.

So Tian Sen refused to leave Team Royal Style, no matter how many promising invitations he received.

As for this person before him now? He parted from his team, parted from his character, and even had to fight a death match against his One Autumn Leaf. When he thought about these things, Tian Sen always felt deeply wronged on Ye Xiu's behalf.

But even so, Ye Xiu hadn't fallen. He continued to advance forward, all for the sake of Glory!

Yes, for Glory!

This was the spirit of the first generation of players, the Founding Generation. No matter what situations they faced, they would never give up.

Why had Ye Xiu chosen the extraordinarily difficult road of building his own team? Tian Sen felt that he understood. Because, aside from Excellent Era, he wouldn't choose anywhere else. He could only start over from zero, and create a team himself.

Perhaps everyone could see the hardships he went through, perhaps they could see the miracle that was his return to the Alliance. But no one would ever truly know the tragic journey his heart had taken.

But even so, Tian Sen would still use everything he had to defeat him. This was the greatest respect he could offer to this type of player.

Bring it!

After saying this, Tian Sen was already attacking.

Back in the day, Peaceful Hermit hadn't beaten One Autumn Leaf. Then what about today's Lord Grim?

It was said that the Exorcist was the counter to the unspecialized Lord Grim. But as the number one Exorcist in Glory, Tian Sen had only two words to say to this: how naive!

If an equipment-sealing talisman was enough to make an Exorcist the counter to Lord Grim, then what about those who had methods to dizzy, to put to sleep, or any other control techniques? Would those become all sorts of counters?

Every skill had its value. But for one skill to raise a class to the status of being a perfect counter, that was too shallow a way of thinking.

The skill was there. But how to use it?

Team Void's Ge Caijie was an excellent Exorcist rookie, but hadn't he fallen to Ye Xiu all the same? Counter, what counter?

There was no such thing as a perfect counter in Glory. Those who thought they were counters, they were just waiting to be countered by the opponent! Because the opponent would always successfully use what you were trying to block. Especially this person here, the Glory Textbook Ye Xiu, the master of calculation… No one who had heard the words and deeds of the older generation would ever forget this.

Team Void? Still too young! That was why Ge Caijie, when placed on the field, would be sent running in circles.

Tian Sen wouldn't be that naive. He didn't treat himself as the counter. He faced this confrontation as he would any match.

Two players, two characters, two classes. On one side, the unspecialized, on the other, the Exorcist.

Peaceful Hermit's left hand snatched a talisman from the air, while his right hand was already waving the scythe Death Savvy as he charged forward. Without fear, he began close-ranged combat with Lord Grim.

But Ye Xiu was unalarmed. Lord Grim swung the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, switching to gun form, and fired a rapid burst of shots toward Peaceful Hermit: Gatling Gun.

Tatatatata...

The gunshots were nonstop. Under Ye Xiu's control, the bullets flew everywhere, attacking not one point but an area.

Peaceful Hermit shook his left hand and the talisman flashed with light. Characters had already formed on the paper, and it was quickly slapped onto his own shoulder.

Hardening Talisman!

Peaceful Hermit didn't dodge, he simply continued to charge straight forward. The bullets exploded on his body in sparks, and he took some damage, but his forward momentum wasn't hampered by these bullets. This was the effect of Hardening Talisman, a stronger version of the Striker's skill Reinforced Iron Bones.

Using the increased defense granted by this talisman, Peaceful Hermit swiftly approached Lord Grim. Lord Grim threw a grenade at Peaceful Hermit's feet, but Tian Sen completely ignored it as well. When Peaceful Hermit stepped there, that grenade exploded, but even though it left a hole in the ground, it didn't shake Peaceful Hermit at all.

Shadow Cloak!

Lord Grim swept his sleeve and sent another skill flying. This type of grab skill was the counter to Super Armor skills like Hardening Talisman. But Tian Sen was fast with his controls. Peaceful Hermit swung Death Savvy down, and the scythe carved through the air with a burst of light. At first glance, it really seemed quite similar to the darkness swung out by Shadow Cloak.

Two skills. Which was faster?

The viewers waited for the result, but the two players had already made their judgments in an instant.

Death Savvy's swing would come faster! The attack speed of a scythe was naturally 10, and the top Exorcist Peaceful Hermit, having chosen such a fast weapon, would definitely have the best equipment to enhance his attack speed even further.

Jump back!

Ye Xiu immediately canceled his Shadow Cloak and controlled Lord Grim to jump backward and dodge. But to his surprise, Death Savvy flew out of Peaceful Hermit's hand toward him. Tian Sen had actually used Spirit Guidance!

Throwing his weapon of course increased his attack range drastically, still carrying the trajectory it'd had when Peaceful Hermit was swinging it. Lord Grim, jumping backward, couldn't escape this range, and it was too late to parry. Death Savvy hit Lord Grim right in the shoulder.

Peaceful Hermit lifted his hand, already prepared to retrieve the weapon. But the scythe was hooked around Lord Grim's shoulder, so when the Spirit Guidance pulled the weapon back, it carried Lord Grim along with it. Peaceful Hermit's left hand had already snatched another talisman, a character already written on it: Immobile.

Immobilizing Talisman!

His right hand pulled back his weapon, dragging Lord Grim along, while his left hand slapped out a talisman. They met, time slowed down, and this talisman was stuck right on Lord Grim's forehead.

Instantly, Lord Grim was unable to move. But the audience burst into shouts.

It wasn't because Peaceful Hermit had played excellently. It was because, as soon as that talisman landed on Lord Grim, another Lord Grim had already flashed behind Peaceful Hermit.

Too bad I saw it. Tornado!

Death Savvy suddenly flipped under Peaceful Hermit's elbow. Tian Sen hadn't turned his camera view, but he already sent this attack to Lord Grim's real body.

This attack came so suddenly, and Peaceful Hermit's attack speed was so high. Lord Grim, who had wanted to sneak up and use a Cut-Throat, was actually slashed by this backward, upside-down attack first. A sheet of red sprayed into the air.

"Ah!" Chen Guo couldn't help but shout.

She had already watched who knew how many matches of Ye Xiu's, but this was the first time she'd seen him caught by his opponent like this. She'd been so sure that Peaceful Hermit's neck would soon be spraying blood, but this time, the one bleeding was actually Lord Grim.

And the scythe once again demonstrated its unique uses. After slashing, it once again hooked Lord Grim, preventing him from retreating to Peaceful Hermit's side. Peaceful Hermit had already turned around, his left hand already gripping yet another talisman. The character written on the paper flashed in the light, as though it were about to fly out.

The Level 75 skill, targeting the opponent's equipment, the Seal Talisman!

Tian Sen didn't agree with the "counter" mindset, but that didn't mean he disagreed with the value of this skill. When there was a suitable opportunity and he could use it, he of course wouldn't let it go.

Seal Talisman. With a twist of this body, Peaceful Hermit sent this talisman toward the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in Lord Grim's hand.

Kaka!

But with two sounds, the umbrella suddenly broke apart into two. Peaceful Hermit couldn't retract his slap, and the talisman landed upon Lord Grim's chest…

Clothes were equipment. The Seal Talisman immediately took effect, and whatever stats granted by this upper-body clothing were temporarily nullified. But this absolutely was not what Tian Sen wanted, and he didn't think "better than nothing." A skill could only be considered successful if it achieved the effect it was meant to achieve. He failed this attack, and what was waiting for him afterward was of course a counterattack. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella split in two, that was its tonfa form. The Fighter class skills relied on this weapon form.

Pow pow!

Kicks and punches landed nonstop upon Peaceful Hermit's body. There were regular attacks, there were skills, and in the end there was a Fling which sent Peaceful Hermit flying. Taking advantage of this grab skill's priority, which locked the target's movements, Lord Grim chased after with a Shining Cut, and at the right angle, he was able to use a Sand Toss at point-blank range right onto Peaceful Hermit's face. When Peaceful Hermit hit the ground, his vision was completely dark. All he could see was a message from Ye Xiu in the chat box to the side.

"You've studied my playstyle pretty thoroughly!"

Tian Sen had indeed studied Ye Xiu extremely well, and discovered that Ye Xiu loved using Shadow Clone Technique to circle around behind the opponent. So, he carefully watched Lord Grim's hands at all times. No matter what, Shadow Clone Technique required hand seals to form. Unfortunately, even though he correctly anticipated the attack, he still fell short.

Chapter 1343: The True Gunner God

Ye Xiu versus Tian Sen. Ye Xiu still won in the end, but Tian Sen's loss wasn't ugly at all. He unleashed the style of Glory's number one Exorcist Peaceful Hermit to the fullest. After the final attack, Ye Xiu put away his battle mindset to genuinely express his feelings.

Even though he didn't know where the familiar person had gone, the familiar character was still here, and a player who had inherited the spirit was still here. This sort of feeling was enough of a comfort.

"You played well," Ye Xiu said in the chat. Whether opponent or teammate, he wouldn't be stingy with his praise. "You played well" - the words were simple, but they were sincere to the fullest.

The two left their competitor booths at about the same time, and the stadium was already filled with thunderous applause. It was for Tian Sen, and for Ye Xiu as well. Perhaps it was because Royal Style already didn't need anything else from this season, and so the fans were more accepting, sending applause to the opponent both before and after the match. This opponent was worthy of respect, and the 28-consecutive individual win record was worthy of this applause.

Happy earned a point first. Next up was Luo Ji, Luo Ji again.

Royal Style didn't have any feelings toward this player, so of course they didn't have much of a reaction. After experiencing last round's battle, Luo Ji was finally less nervous. During this week, he had watched the recording of the previous match over and over again. That was his first battle of his professional career, not diluted in the slightest, a true you-die-I-live death match on the professional stage.

Luo Ji analyzed many conclusions from that match. His online documents and the paper notebook at his side were dense with notes. It was just a 1v1 that had lasted only a few minutes. How many little details had he noticed, in order to write so many things?

But this was just Luo Ji's method, so no one disturbed him. He drew what he needed from this, and when he came across something he didn't understand, he would ask his seniors for help without hesitation.

How much could he improve in one week? Luo Ji didn't know either. But he was standing on this stage, so he would simply do his best.

As it turned out, Luo Ji's opponent this match happened to be the Summoner player in Royal Style's roster, named He Weitang.

In the end, Luo Ji still lost, but he wasn't discouraged.

One week of effort still wasn't enough. He just told himself this. Now, he had one more recording which he could study.

And then, in the third individual round, Happy's Su Mucheng earned a point.

Next, Happy sent Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Fang Rui in the group arena, but, unexpectedly, they lost. Royal Style's players were very relaxed as they played, with no pressure at all. Perhaps it was this attitude that allowed their performance to peak, and they ultimately won the two points of the group arena.

In the team competition, Happy sent out Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Steamed Bun, An Wenyi, and Mo Fan.

The lineup had a bit of rotation, but Happy played the team round very carefully. Royal Style could relax, but they couldn't. Ultimately, Happy won this team round, defeating Royal Style 7 to 3.

"Please work even harder in the playoffs." As they exchanged greetings after the match, Tian Sen didn't hold back with his words, sending Happy into the playoffs nine rounds early.

"Alright. Want to come with us?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"No need. Sooner or later, we'll return to that stage as well," Tian Sen said. Even though their scores had been poor for several years running now, he didn't lose the pride of being a member of Royal Style. As long as they were still here, anything was possible. Tian Sen believed this deeply.

"Keep it up!" Ye Xiu shook his hand firmly. Thus, the curtain fell on Happy's away game against Royal Style. In another stadium, the live televised match between 301 and Misty Rain also ended at this time. Ultimately, the recently-strong 301 turned out to be fiercer. Their loss to Wind Howl hadn't stopped their good condition, and in this home game, they defeated Misty Rain 8-2. However, their main competitors right now, Wind Howl, had done better this round. They had their away game against a team that was already viewed as relegated, Seaside, and didn't hold back in winning a 10-0.

With this, Wind Howl now surpassed 301 by two points, slightly expanding the lead they had just won last round.

301 was in ninth place, followed by Void. Void defeated Heavenly Swords 8-2 in their away game, continuing to maintain their chance at the top 8. They just had to wait for someone to mess up. However, with their current 11 point difference from eighth place, one mistake wasn't enough. The other team would have to make consecutive mistakes, and they would need to seize consecutive opportunities, if they were to have their shot.

Because of this, their chance was very uncertain, and Void's supporters were all extremely nervous. As for Misty Rain, after once again losing to their direct competitor, they now had a 26 point difference from the top 8. At this point, continuing to bite down on the theoretical possibility was no more than self-delusion. Misty Rain could be considered yet another team that had to say farewell to this season. This was the first time in recent years that this team had dropped out of the playoffs.

In reality, Misty Rain's greatest point of criticism was still how they tended to crumble at crucial points. But there really wasn't any fault to be found on their technical or tactical aspects, and their scores had always been fairly stable. In order to try and improve, Misty Rain had made adjustments, but it now looked like their adjustments had only given them a rather failed season. People were already beginning to discuss what move Misty Rain would make next.

After Happy finished this round, they prepared to rest overnight in City B. Heavenly Swords was also in City B, and had just played a home game. After the match, they contacted Happy to get together. Heavenly Swords right now was like Royal Style, right in the middle, with no more goals for this season. Losing a match would still be saddening, but the sadness would disperse relatively quickly. At least, when Happy's members met the Heavenly Swords team, they couldn't tell from their faces that they had just lost 2-8 in a home game.

Once Heavenly Swords' players arrived, they pulled Happy for a late-night snack. Every week, this day right after playing a match was indeed the most relaxed day of the week for pro players. As long as they were in the mood, hanging out during this weekend was fairly common. However, by the time they finished the match and the interviews, it wasn't very early, and both teams' players had the self-restraint not to stay out too late. When they were about to disperse, Lou Guanning wanted to extend the friendship of a host, and invited Happy to stay an extra day the next day. But Ye Xiu made a polite but clear refusal for himself, and Su Mucheng followed suit.

"Tomorrow is A Qingming Festival 1 ," someone from Heavenly Swords quietly reminded Lou Guanning, giving him pause. He didn't know if this was Ye Xiu's reason, but of course he couldn't ask. If someone was observing Qingming Festival, there was nothing cheerful about that.

"Then I won't hold you guys up. We can get together next time, we have plenty of opportunities." Lou Guanning let the whole team of Happy go.

"Next time," Ye Xiu smiled. The two teams said their farewells. The next day, Luo Ji returned by himself to City T, while the rest boarded a plane back to City H.

Qingming Festival…

Chen Guo of course didn't forget this holiday. Yesterday, even if Ye Xiu hadn't backed out, she herself would have. Now, it looked like Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng had the same intent as her?"

"Want to head over together in a bit?" Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu while they were on the plane.

"Alright!" Ye Xiu nodded.

After the plane landed in City H, Happy's members split into two groups. Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Chen Guo went one way, and the others gathered together.

"Where are they going?" The three of them hadn't really said anything, so after they left, everyone else began discussing out of curiosity.

"Probably to sweep the tombs!" Tang Rou had been at Happy the longest and had known Chen Guo's background for a while. Even though she hadn't heard Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng's story directly from them, she knew a little from what Chen Guo had said.

The players also knew that Chen Guo's father had passed, but they didn't really know about Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng's situation, and so they asked.

"It's Su Mucheng's older brother," Tang Rou told everyone and then looked at Wei Chen. She knew that the young man who had passed was also a Glory expert in the past, and Wei Chen was an old player from those days, so maybe he knew this person.

After hearing Tang Rou's introduction, Wei Chen did reveal a somewhat stunned expression. "So that's what it was."

"Old Wei, you know him?" Fang Rui asked.

"Of course you brats wouldn't know," Wei Chen said, beginning to reflect on his memories. "At that time, there was no Heavenly Domain, and Glory only had one server at the start, only later opening the second server. At the time, all of us spent our time in the first server. We were probably the first batch of Glory players! And at the time in our first server, the Battle Mage One Autumn Leaf was already extremely famous. But there was another guy often with him, very famous, and no less skilled than One Autumn Leaf."

No less skilled than Ye Xiu!

This could be considered the highest praise in the Glory circle. With Wei Chen's shamelessness, for him to give this sort of praise to anyone other than himself was extremely rare to see.

"What was his name?" Fang Rui quickly asked.

"Autumn Tree," said Wei Chen.

Fang Rui shook his head to show that he'd never heard of that name before. That era was too far in the past, and this was just a character in the game. Very few such stories could be passed on for that long.

"Of course, how would you little brats have heard of him?" Wei Chen said disdainfully. In his eyes, Fang Rui was just another little brat.

"So this person was Su Mucheng's older brother!" Wei Chen continued under his breath.

"Autumn Tree, 'Qiu Mu Su'… Su Muqiu?" Fang Rui realized, after slowly voicing the characters aloud.

"Yes." Tang Rou had heard this name from Chen Guo, and nodded her head.

"Oh, so it was his real name in reverse," Wei Chen realized. "But at that time there was no Su Mucheng. No one would make that connection. By the time Su Mucheng entered the Alliance and became famous, this name had probably long been forgotten!"

"Yeah…" Even though Fang Rui hadn't experienced that era, who would pass on the legend of a mere in-game expert? By the time Su Mucheng entered the Alliance, it was already Season 4. Three years was long enough to forget a name.

"This Autumn Tree, what class was he?" Fang Rui asked.

"He was a gunner god," Wei Chen said. "A true gunner god."

Chapter 1344: There Are No Ifs

"Gunner god? A Sharpshooter 1 …" Happy's members began to imagine a Sharpshooter called Autumn Tree running through the game, but unexpectedly, Wei Chen shook his head.

"No, not Sharpshooter. All of the Gunner subclasses."

"All of the Gunner subclasses?"

"Sharpshooter, Spitfire, Mechanic, Launcher," said Wei Chen.

"Another expert like that!" Fang Rui exclaimed. Everyone understood this "another." Wasn't their Ye Xiu an even more ridiculous all-class expert, a king's avatar 2 ?

"Actually, at that time, there were many people like that. Who didn't have main and side accounts? But very few could play every class to the limit like they did," said Wei Chen.

"Then what happened later?" Fang Rui asked.

"Later, wasn't it like Little Tang said, he died…" Wei Chen said.

"Car accident, I'm not too sure about the details," Tang Rou said.

And then everyone looked at Wei Chen.

"I don't know too much either, but after the Alliance was established and everyone was making teams to participate, he never appeared again. Probably someone asked Ye Xiu out of curiosity, and then the news spread that he had passed away. But the fact that he was Su Mucheng's older brother, no one knew that…" Wei Chen, the shameless old man, actually let out a sigh when he reached the end, with a face full of regret and pity.

"How skilled was this person?" Fang Rui asked.

"I'll say this. Whenever I fought against him, I didn't even have the chance to cast any curses," said Wei Chen, a profound respect in his voice.

The members of Happy exchanged looks, but after a few moments, Wei Chen didn't see the expressions of shock that he was hoping for.

"That's… not that impressive, is it?" Fang Rui finally said.

"You bastard!" Wei Chen instantly knew what Fang Rui was implying. "This was over ten years ago! Back in those days, I was still a godlike youth!"

"Damn!" Fang Rui looked like he couldn't listen to any more.

"In any case, he was incredibly skilled!" Wei Chen said.

"Compared to Ye Xiu, who was better?" Tang Rou always tended to care about the question of who was stronger.

"This… They always fought side-by-side. We were all curious as to who was stronger between the two of them, but sadly there was never an answer. Not back then, and definitely not now. There never will be…" Wei Chen's expression was once again filled with melancholy.

Everyone fell silent. For Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, and the others, this was the first time they'd heard of this person, and so they couldn't truly empathize so quickly. But seeing the extremely shameless Wei Chen suddenly show such emotion, they could feel how tragic this was, the story of a young genius meeting a premature end.

"If he had joined Excellent Era with Ye Xiu…" Even just thinking about this scenario, Wei Chen couldn't help but shiver.

"If he were still here, what would things be like?" Tang Rou was also thinking about this.

If only…

Who wouldn't think about these sort of "ifs"? But such was the nature of "if," to refer to the impossible.

"What kind of flowers are these now?" In front of Su Muqiu's grave, Ye Xiu watched as Su Mucheng placed down a bouquet.

" Hyacinths 3 ."

"Is there anyone else like you, changing the type of flower every year?" Ye Xiu asked.

"There needs to be innovation," said Su Mucheng.

"Innovation?" Ye Xiu laughed. "So you use every type of flower to express this meaning in the flower language?"

"He would like this kind of method," Su Mucheng said.

"Yes." Ye Xiu nodded. The person who had imagined the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and brought it into reality, was there anyone in Glory more innovative than him?

And the things left behind from his innovation were still sparkling on the Glory battlefield.

28 consecutive victories.

Ye Xiu's hand reached into his pocket, where Lord Grim's account card was quietly lying. This record would be firmly bound to this character. And it hadn't finished yet, it was still being updated.

I'll let this record last forever. But from the very start, I left out one match, to leave you a chance to surpass me.

Ye Xiu stretched out his hands to touch the gravestone. These were the hands currently controlling Lord Grim to write miracles in Glory.

"If it wasn't me here right now, and it was my brother, what would things be like now?" Su Mucheng suddenly asked this question.

"Oh?" Ye Xiu gave it serious thought, but he couldn't think of an answer.

"Would it just always be, championship championship championship championship championship like that?" Su Mucheng asked.

"Maybe so!" Ye Xiu said.

"And Dancing Rain would definitely be more famous than now."

"Not necessarily," said Ye Xiu. "Some guy with a female account is much much worse than a beautiful female player."

"Haha," Su Mucheng laughed, and touched the gravestone with her hands as well.

"Well, those things aren't really important," Su Mucheng said. "If only he could be here, that would be best."

Ye Xiu didn't say anything, because… there were no ifs.

This time, Chen Guo spent a longer time in front of her father's gravestone, because there were just too many things that had happened in this past year. She said many, many things, but she still couldn't finish it all.

Their team winning the Challenger League.

The difficulties they'd faced at the start of the season.

Their team's crazy win streak.

So many 10-0s.

Every team member's improvements.

The expanding guild.

The developing account characters.

And now, advancing toward the playoffs, the rhythm of sprinting toward the championship.

There was really too much…

Chen Guo actually grew tired from all the talking, and all that was just an overview. There were still many details, many other things she wanted to add!

Chen Guo was in a bit of a daze, not really knowing whether she should continue. Because of the fullness of this year, her tomb-sweeping method now became a bit unsuitable. There were too many things, she couldn't finish them all!

"Boss, want to drink some water?" Right then, Chen Guo heard someone speak. When she turned her head, she saw Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng smiling as they stood by her side.

Tomb-sweeping was a rather sad event. But Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng both knew that this year, to Chen Guo, was very happy, and for this year's tomb-sweeping, she wanted to bring this happiness here.

"Oh oh, thank you." Chen Guo took the bottle of water and gulped down some mouthfuls.

"You two are done?" she asked.

"Yeah." The two of them nodded.

"Alright, then let's go!"

"You're done talking? It didn't seem like it?" Ye Xiu said. It looked like they'd been listening to the side for a while.

"That's enough for today, I can come back and continue later. No one said that I can only come here on Qingming!" Chen Guo waved her hand, and took the lead in heading down the mountain.

When they returned to Happy Internet Cafe, everyone was gathered in the training room. They'd all been huddled together and whispering to each other, but when the three entered, they all instantly returned to their seats, they all sat upright and attentive.

"Went to sweep tombs?" Wei Chen asked with a cough.

"Yeah."

"Autumn Tree?" Wei Chen asked.

"Right," Ye Xiu nodded. It was no surprise that the experienced Wei Chen knew this name.

"It's a real pity," Wei Chen said.

"No one said it wasn't!" Ye Xiu smiled, and took his seat as well.

The room was quiet; no one dared to say anything else. For this sort of topic, it didn't feel right to ask the person in question to find out more. Everyone only knew that there was once a monstrously skilled Glory expert, but he left before he had the chance to strive for any glory. Compared to that, everyone here, whether strong or weak, whether new rookies or old veterans, they were still working hard to strive for everything. There was no greater fortune than that.

Click click click click…

The room was filled with nothing but the sounds of the computer mice and keyboards. Everyone was working hard for their own goals, but at the same time, everyone thought of the other burdens that they were carrying upon themselves.

Wei Chen thought of his teammates from back when he was on Blue Rain. They had already left the Glory Alliance, left this battlefield. Some people he might still be able to meet in life, but others had already disappeared without a trace to unknown places. The championship was what they had pursued back then, but in the end they had all departed with regret. And now, Wei Chen again returned to this stage, with his old skills completely insufficient in coping with the intensity of today's matches. But even though this was the case, he could still carry his burdens, couldn't he? If he really could win the championship, then when his old brothers heard and saw it, wouldn't they feel that he had fulfilled for them their strings of conviction?

This kind of feeling wasn't bad at all!

"Hey!" After thinking to here, Wei Chen suddenly gave a rough shout.

"Hey who?" Ye Xiu asked.

"You!"

"What's up?"

"Next match, I want to play," Wei Chen said.

"Oh? Ready to blaze a fire?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"Did you really think that I only came to watch?" Wei Chen said.

"Not many rounds left, is it enough?" Ye Xiu asked.

"It's enough," Wei Chen grinned arrogantly. "I understand matches much better than these noobs here."

"Hmph…" The training room was instantly filled with boos.

"I say, in terms of real Pro League experience, aren't you worse than me?" Fang Rui spoke up. He was a Season 5 player, and had now played for over five and a half years. And Wei Chen? His professional career had been only two seasons, two years. Plus, there had been fewer pro teams at the time and skill levels were all over the place. The competition format was entirely different from what it was today.

"Pro League?" Wei Chen sneered. "Why do I call you noobs? This battlefield is called Glory. The Pro League is no more than a part of it."

"So you're saying you're about to go to Heavenly Domain and get some materials for us?" Fang Rui said.

"You look like you need to be taught a lesson! 1v1, let's go!" Wei Chen shouted.

"Who's scared of you! Make the room," Fang Rui yelled.

And thus the two went to compete in shamelessness and dirty playing. To the side, everyone else was listening and laughing, but they were all sprinting forward with more active, more positive, more hardworking attitudes.

The past could only be turned into ifs and remembered in the heart. Only the present could truly be grasped, and only by grasping the present could they take control of the future.

Nine rounds remaining.

Everyone looked at the leaderboard in the training room. There were still nine full rounds remaining. Play these nine rounds well, then they would enter the playoffs, and step upon an even more brutal journey. Everything had to be grasped tightly, starting from now.

Chapter 1345: That Was Only the Past

In Round 30 of the League matches, Happy played a home game, welcoming the currently last-place Team Seaside. Seaside was in low spirits, as they were essentially already relegated. The players were all worried about their future prospects, and very few fans had come along with the team.

As usual, Ye Xiu was the first in the individual round, earning a clean victory. And then Luo Ji came up, finally winning the first victory of his professional career. The audience was a sea of cheers, congratulating Luo Ji.

And then, Wei Chen.

The stadium burst into excitement again. This especially down-to-earth old player had been absent for while. No one even remembered the last time he had come onstage, but now he was pulled onto the stage once again.

Wei Chen boldly and grandly waved toward the audience, and the audience gave him an enthusiastic answer, but the end result wasn’t what people expected.

Wei Chen, Happy’s representative in the third individual battle, lost.

Seaside already had no prospects, but some of the individual players were still considering their own futures and putting their full effort into performance to try and attract more attention. Wei Chen met one such player, resulting in a long battle that ended with a slight mistake he made causing his loss.

Real battle was still a whole different matter from daily practice. Regularly training and sparring with teammates couldn’t replace the rhythm of one professional match a week.

“Old Wei, can you even keep up anymore!” When Wei Chen came offstage, Xiaoshan Stadium came alive with many hollers from the audience.

It wasn’t mockery, it was just the lighthearted joking from the fans that knew him well. Even though these words hit a sore spot, the shameless Wei Chen could always stand up to these kind of jokes.

“The hell do you guys know, this is tactics,” Wei Chen yelled. But his voice had no way of competing with the noise of so many audience members talking at once, and it couldn’t carry. Wei Chen could only hear everyone continuing to mock him as he helplessly walked back to the player area.

“Can’t keep up, huh, Old Wei!” Fang Rui was following along with the audience.

“The hell do you know? This is called tactics.” Finally, Wei Chen could make his retort heard.

“What tactics? Please, do enlighten us,” Fang Rui said.

“Stop messing around,” Ye Xiu interjected. “Old Wei is very upset after losing that match. Don’t provoke him, or else he might cry.”

“Pah!” Wei Chen spat in contempt.

“How are you?” Ye Xiu sat next to him, his tone becoming more serious.

“Even you’re still doing fine, would I be any worse?” Wei Chen gave him a sideways glance.

“I have 29 consecutive victories,” Ye Xiu said.

“Soon I’ll be kicking ass, just you watch,” Wei Chen said.

“Of course, we found you just for that purpose,” said Ye Xiu.

“Well, I have to say, you found the right person.”

“Good luck.”

“I’ll get into condition quickly.”

The joking tone had finally vanished with those last two sentences.

“Now it’s our turn!” Ever since becoming the the anchor of the group arena, he often had this grand air of a general. The group arena roster of him, Tang Rou, and Su Mucheng wasn’t something that Seaside could defend against. Just two of the Happy players were enough to defeat and destroy Seaside. Seaside didn’t even have the chance to see in individual battle that character which had once been their core, Boundless Sea.

In the intermission, Happy actively prepared for the team competition. Seaside’s players, however, just sat scattered around the player area, each lost in their own thoughts. There was no communication at all.

This was a team that had already completely splintered apart. Just last season, they hadn’t been doing so poorly, but this season had been a nonstop plummet. After Zhao Yang retired, the team said they sold Boundless Sea so they could set down a burden and travel light. But now, there was a big discrepancy between expectation and reality.

What they set down wasn’t just the burden of economic investment and resources. At the same time, they had set down what had always been this team’s soul and conviction.

To Team Seaside, Boundless Sea was more than just a contribution to their strength. He was the support on which the team’s spirit rested. Zhao Yang’s retirement was already a huge blow to the team. By selling the character Boundless Sea immediately after, this two-hit combo completely destroyed this team’s courage and belief to continue fighting.

Tear down and rebuild. But Seaside had torn down too much, until there was nothing left of their team. This team, perhaps, had collapsed the moment that Boundless Sea was sold off.

And at the same time, the most attention-grabbing match of this round, the match chosen for television broadcast, had also entered the most exciting part of the group arena.

Blue Rain vs Hundred Blossoms.

Huang Shaotian vs Yu Feng.

Former teammates, now the core players of their respective teams.

And now, it was finally time for them to stand opposite each other with their swords drawn, fighting to the death in this battle to decide the group arena.

Troubling Rain still had 96% health remaining, while Blossoming Chaos was at 100%. With such a slight difference, the two characters were essentially beginning this match at the same starting line.

“Let the match begin!” When commentator Pan Lin made this announcement, the two characters had already finished loading onto the map. But, shockingly, the chat wasn’t instantly flooded with a huge amount of text.

The instant the battle began, the television broadcast had already switched the close-up display to the chat. But there wasn’t a flood of messages?

“What’s going on?” Pan Lin exclaimed. “This is a match with Huang Shaotian! And it’s only the opening, they’re not fighting each other yet, how come there are no messages in the chat? Ah! It’s already been seven seconds and there isn’t a single message! What is this? Did something happen? Is there a problem in the player booth? Did Huang Shaotian faint? Can someone go and check?”

“I think…” To the side, Li Yibo finally opened his mouth. “Even though Huang Shaotian hasn’t sent a message yet, you sounded a lot like him just now.”

“…”

Fortunately, Pan Lin didn’t need to worry, as just at that moment, Huang Shaotian’s message finally appeared on screen.

“We meet onstage again. But after so long, we’re probably used to this feeling by now! Come on, let’s have a fierce battle. Let’s see if your greatsword is fiercer or my lightsaber is faster.”

At the same time the messages appeared, Troubling Rain was already Swift Running out, his weapon Ice Rain at his side glowing with faint blue light, leaving blurred afterimages like the marks left by raindrops freezing as they dripped down.

Just one message. For Huang Shaotian, this was truly unprecedented. Such an atypical performance seemed to indicate that he still wasn’t quite used to treating this former teammate as an opponent? Even if Yu Feng had already left Blue Rain over a year and a half ago.

“I’m sorry that I can’t continue to walk alongside everyone…”

Every time he met Yu Feng again, Huang Shaotian flashed back to what this guy had said just before he left Team Blue Rain, when he was bidding farewell to them all.

“I want to see what I can accomplish with this greatsword in my own hands,” Yu Feng said.

What he could accomplish?

These two seasons, everyone had seen his accomplishments. Under Yu Feng’s lead, Team Hundred Blossoms rebuilt its former trademark duo, the Berserker and the Spitfire. The number one Berserker, after leaving Blue Rain and joining Hundred Blossoms, was still the number one Berserker. But his simplest, most sentimental season would always belong to Blue Rain.

That was Blue Rain’s most beautiful summer.

In Season 6, Blue Rain defeated Tiny Herb in the finals, winning that year’s championship.

At that time, Yu Feng was a mere rookie in the team. He wasn’t like Lu Hanwen, who had taken up the responsibility of main attacker in his very first year. In that year, Yu Feng’s position still wavered between main roster and substitute as a rotating player.

But he played a role in Blue Rain’s championship victory. Everyone saw his talent and anticipated his growth.

As expected, he quickly became a solid, indispensable member of Blue Rain, always the one who stood at the very front of the team to meet the enemies that came at them.

But unfortunately, this situation only lasted for two seasons. In Season 9, Yu Feng voluntarily transferred, wishing to leave Blue Rain. And his reason was exactly as described above: he wished to forge an era that was his own.

“But if that’s the case, then what was Blue Rain to you?”

Only Huang Shaotian would ask such a sharp question without hesitation.

“Thank you everyone, for your care all this time…” But this was Yu Feng’s only reply, and he left just like that. And Huang Shaotian, who had wanted to go up and demand answers, was ultimately pulled to a stop by Yu Wenzhou.

A position truly as the core. A team that truly belonged to him.

Perhaps some people wouldn’t care about these sort of things, but others would care about them greatly. And Blue Rain could not give these things to Yu Feng. Even if they had once had that perfect summer, even if Yu Feng had always led Blue Rain forward like the front of a train, these were not what he most wanted.

He wanted to use the greatsword in his hand to forge an era that belonged to him!

Even when Huang Shaotian hurled that “what was Blue Rain to you” question at him, he felt no guilt or remorse. What was Blue Rain to him? Every time he faced Team Blue Rain in battle, every time he met Blue Rain’s players, he would always think of this question.

At the time, he hadn’t known, and so he hadn’t given a reply. But now, he had found his answer.

The past.

To him, Blue Rain was the past.

That place had brought him laughter and tears and sweat and emotion. But all of that was in the past. Now, his body bore the emblem of Hundred Blossoms. He was this team’s captain. He had already waved farewell to the past. Now, he was using his sword to strive for what he wanted to obtain.

And no one could block him, not even Huang Shaotian, this person who talked so much and yet could never be hated.

Even if the one blocking his way was the Sword Saint, he would knock him down for good.

Blossoming Chaos, charge forward!

Without pause, without retreat, the two characters flew toward each other at the center of the map, and without hesitation, the swordlight clashed.

AAAAAH!

Blossoming Chaos seemed to roar. In terms of power, the Berserker of course had the advantage over the Blade Master, especially since he had activated the Berserk status from the start. Blossoming Chaos’ two eyes had gone red, and blood energy roiled around him. The Silver weapon he held, Blossoms Burial, with all the strength to bury everything in its path, swung toward Troubling Rain.

Chapter 1346: The Instant Spotlight Steal

“Right now Yu Feng has the advantage!!” Commentator Pan Lin described the current situation in shock.

When the two characters met, Troubling Rain was actually instantly suppressed by Blossoming Chaos. Under the ferocious attack of the Berserker, Troubling Rain was clearly in a bad position.

The broadcasters couldn’t help but cut to a close-up of the chat every so often. This was a habit born from broadcasting many of Huang Shaotian’s matches. But now, there was nothing… The chat was clean and empty.

“Huang Shaotian has said unusually little during this match!” Li Yibo observed.

“Looks like Yu Feng is giving him a lot of pressure. Maybe he doesn’t have any time left to type words?” said Pan Lin. The pace of the players’ attacks and defenses was so fast that Pan Lin had no time to discuss any details of the battle. He could only insert some side comments like this.

“After spending over a year in Hundred Blossoms, Yu Feng has indeed improved significantly,” said Li Yibo.

“Maybe it’s the responsibility of captaincy that gave him more courage, gave him more of a role to play!” Pan Lin said, before glancing at the two sides’ health bars once again. “The battle is extremely fast-paced. Troubling Rain’s health has already dropped to 71%, while Blossoming Chaos still has 79%. Just looking at the health, we see that even though Huang Shaotian doesn’t have the initiative, he’s still managed to take away a large portion of his opponent’s health. Plus, at the start of this match, Troubling Rain was already at 96%, meaning that up to now, he’s lost 25%, while Blossoming Chaos has lost 21%. That’s only a 4% difference!”

“On that point, we have to remember that Blossoming Chaos is a Berserker. During these exchanges, Yu Feng will likely be bolder,” Li Yibo said.

“Whoa, just in the time it took us to say that, their health has dropped again, Troubling Rain 67%, Blossoming Chaos 70%! Blossoming Chaos ate a big attack here! If we consider the two characters’ starting health, doesn’t this mean that Troubling Rain is now in the lead?” Pan Lin was surprised, because looking at the current offensive, Yu Feng clearly had the upper hand.

“Huang Shaotian’s defensive ability has always been exceptional, and his ability to attack while defending is also strong. This has to do with the role he often plays within the team,” Li Yibo said.

“That’s true,” Pan Lin agreed. The two didn’t describe this point further, because all sorts of reporters, critics, and commentators had already talked about this many times. Huang Shaotian’s defensive ability was high because Team Blue Rain had several characters that needed to be defended. Aside from the healer, Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar also needed his support frequently.

But the protection of Swoksaar was different from the typical protection of a healer. After all, Yu Wenzhou wasn’t someone who could be casually killed off. Even though his hands were slow, he relied on experience and rhythm to fight in his own way. So, Huang Shaotian’s protection of Yu Wenzhou more often contained a counterattack. This strategy of Blue Rain’s was very mature by this point: from Swoksaar, launch a defensive counterattack.

So Blue Rain’s players were all skilled in this area, with Huang Shaotian as the leader. Right now he was being suppressed by Yu Feng, but while defending, he managed to gain the upper hand in health. It had to be said that Huang Shaotian’s defensive counterattacking was extraordinarily effective.

Having been teammates for three years, Yu Feng wouldn’t overlook this special trait of Huang Shaotian’s. But at this moment, it seemed like he didn’t care, as he tenaciously continued to attack.

“Is Yu Feng playing too carelessly?” Pan Lin said at this moment. “Even though he has the initiative, if this keeps up, the initiative won’t help him win!”

Just as he said these words, Yu Feng finally fell behind in terms of raw health. Troubling Rain was now at 61%, while his Blossoming Chaos had been brought down to 58%.

“He still won’t stop to consider strategy?” said Pan Lin. Indeed, it looked like Yu Feng had no plan of stopping. The battle rhythm was just as fast as before, and in the midst of flying blood droplets, the health bars continued to drop.

60%, 57%;

58%, 54%;

54%, 51%;

50%, 40%…

After a flurry of blows, Blossoming Chaos’s health suddenly plummeted drastically, from 51% all the way down to 40%.

“Ah, this…” Pan Lin was already losing his voice as he cried out. Blue Rain’s home stadium erupted in cheers to welcome victory.

“No! Now, Yu Feng’s offensive truly begins!” Li Yibo shouted. After seeing this sharp drop, he realized something.

Blood Awakening. Activating once a Berserker’s health was below 50%, this granted a massive increase in strength. The lower the health, the greater the increase. And Yu Feng’s health had dropped all the way to 40% in one step. The strength increase granted by this 10% would boost Blossoming Chaos’ attack power and priority. And this sudden boost in attack priority would instantly put greater pressure on Huang Shaotian’s defense. If he couldn’t keep up with this increased rhythm, it was very possible that he would be crushed.

It looked like Yu Feng wanted to use this moment to attack explosively, directly defeating Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain in one go. Now that his own health was at 40%, Blossoming Chaos used his Awakening skill: Bloodthirsty Craze.

Boost!

Aside from the boost to strength, Bloodthirsty Craze also boosted Blossoming Chaos’ movement and attack speeds. It relied on the same logic: sacrifice one’s own health to drastically increase attack power.

In just this short instant, Blossoming Chaos completed a massive explosion of stats. This explosion wasn’t a coincidence, of course. Yu Feng had planned for this long ago. He had a very clear plan here: relying on this explosiveness, he would deal the final blow to Huang Shaotian.

It’s here!

The Silver weapon Blossoms Burial once again whipped up a hurricane of blood. All of these boosts had come so suddenly, even Huang Shaotian probably didn’t expect Blossoming Chaos to swiftly enter a 40% health Blood Awakening and activate Bloodthirsty Craze. This was all completed in an instant. Blossoming Chaos’ attacks now were on a whole different level from before.

Could Huang Shaotian withstand this sudden increase of power?

No, clearly not.

When Troubling Rain lifted his weapon Ice Rain to defend, it was instantly forced back by the greatsword Blossoms Burial. Blossoming Chaos’ attack priority right now wasn’t something that Troubling Rain could casually block with his blade.

Hit!

It looked like even Ice Rain was thrust into Troubling Rain’s flesh. The blood sprayed up like a screen to cover the two people. Only their health bars could be seen, reflecting the current situation as they jumped downward.

Troubling Rain: 45%; Blossoming Chaos: 39%.

43%; 38%;

40%; 37%;

35%; 36%…

In an instant, in just this instant, Blossoming Chaos completed his counterattack. His health was now higher than Troubling Rain’s. There wasn’t even an exchange, there was only Yu Feng’s crazy offensive. Blossoming Chaos’ health depletion was only an automatic side-effect of Bloodthirsty Craze.

I can win! I will win!

Yu Feng saw the opportunity, the opportunity that he’d constructed from the very beginning, finally in his hand. He loved this feeling, truly loved this feeling, the feeling of having everything firmly in his grasp. It felt so enriching, and so very real…

32%; 35%;

29%; 34%;

25%; 33%;

20%; 32%…

Controlled well, his attacks were controlled excellently, the gap between their health was only widening. Even more importantly, as Blossoming Chaos’ health depleted his strength was still increasing, and his offensive grew more and more violent.

The Bloodthirsty Craze status was about to wear off, and a large portion of his battle ability was about to vanish. Afterward, he would need to rely on Berserk to make up for it. But Huang Shaotian had probably already grown accustomed to this current rhythm; the replacement boost from Berserk probably wouldn’t be enough to suppress him.

Still, he didn’t need to worry too much. It wasn’t a big deal if he sacrificed some health. Consider it a one-time interest payment on Bloodthirsty Craze! The final offensive was about to begin here.

Berserk!

Yu Feng didn’t wait for Bloodthirsty Craze to wear off before using a new skill. Just before Bloodthirsty Craze was about to end, he activated Berserk.

His offensive continued, but as Yu Feng expected, the 25% decrease that Berserk represented couldn’t help Yu Feng suppress Huang Shaotian completely.

He needed an exchange. He just needed to complete one exchange.

His 12% health lead allowed Yu Feng to feel calm. This battle would end after this final wave of attacks.

Whirlwind Strike!

Blossoming Chaos’ attacks continued. He used a Whirlwind Strike to send his sword spinning toward Troubling Rain.

But…

Falling Blossom Form!

Troubling Rain suddenly darted out with his sword. So fast, so accurate. The attack was clearly initiated just slower than Whirlwind Strike, but it landed upon Blossoming Chaos first.

Blossoming Chaos was sent falling down out of his control, and Yu Feng was stunned. What happened? How was his offensive broken here? Troubling Rain’s attack came so quickly that he truly had no way of responding. This one attack came as though it had been waiting for a long time, as though it had been ready for a long time. One touch completely shattered Blossoming Chaos’ offensive.

“Dropping health like that in front of me, you really are too bold. Have you already forgotten what my style is?” Huang Shaotian finally graced the chat with some of his words. He mentioned his style. This style… He probably wasn’t referring to how he was finally talking now, he was evidently referring to something else… Huang Shaotian’s style, aside from his talkative nature.

Opportunist. The greatest opportunist in Glory. One opening was enough to create a reversal. One opening was enough to kill.

It wasn’t that Yu Feng didn’t know this, nor would he forget this. He simply believed that he wouldn’t give Huang Shaotian any openings, any opportunities. But now…

Swordlight. Ice Rain’s swordlight, like strings of frozen raindrops, landed over and over upon Blossoming Chaos’ body.

20%, 28%;

20%, 25%;

20%, 22%;

20%, 15%;

20%, 11%;

20%, 0…

Just like that, Blossoming Chaos’ 32% was wiped away in one go. Troubling Rain took no damage.

As expected of this guy! Yu Feng watched, helpless, as Blossoming Chaos fell. This guy always had a sudden explosion at a critical point, instantly stealing your spotlight. On the battlefield, no matter how hard he worked, no matter how well he played, it could never compete with the elegance of that guy’s instantaneous strike.

He thought he had grasped victory in his hands, but it still slipped through his fingers in the end. That feeling of fullness turned empty in the blink of an eye.

This is why I had to leave Blue Rain!

At Blue Rain, your sudden appearances always crushed the presence I worked so hard to build up. It was truly too cruel…

Chapter 1347: Sprint

In the group arena, Troubling Rain defeated Blossoming Chaos, giving the victory to Blue Rain. In addition to the two points they had earned in the individual competition, Blue Rain entered the team competition with a 4 to 1 lead.

In the end, Blue Rain used their home advantage to crush their opponents in the team competition, winning an impressive victory of 9 to 1 against Hundred Blossoms. 　 In the same round, Happy also managed a 9 to 1 victory against Seaside. Conquering Clouds was crushed by 301 Degrees in their away home, not getting a single point and losing 0 to 10. As for Wind Howl, 301 Degree’s most direct competitor, they had managed to win against Misty Rain 8 to 2 on their home turf, but their 2 point lead was eliminated by 301 Degrees. They only managed to remain eighth thanks to their victorious battle against 301 Degrees.

There were two matches that roused public interest this round, Tiny Herb’s home game against Void and Tyranny’s home game against Thunderclap.

In the end, the two home teams ended the match 8 to 2. Thunderclap’s team once again lost; this time to Tyranny’s team. Something that was rather unexpected, however, was that Han Wenqing, Zhang Jiale, Lin Jingyan and Zhang Xinjie, after a long time of not fighting together, all appeared in the starting lineup this time.

Was it a coincidence of their rotation?

No one would think that way. Team Tyranny had implemented this rotation for Han Wenqing, Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan to switch off. With all three of them present, Tyranny seemed to perform perfectly well, so what was the point of the rotation?

“Tyranny’s begun the sprint for the playoffs.” With Team Happy, Ye Xiu merely glanced at the lineup before making a conclusive judgement.

In the past, Chen Guo would probably ask why, but she didn’t need Ye Xiu to explain something like this anymore, because she could read between the lines. In reality, Happy also had such plans for Wei Chen, and Wei Chen’s situation was far worse than Tyranny’s veterans.

Veterans like them didn’t have enough energy for the entire season, especially not with the fact that there was an even more anticipated, even more intensive, even more frequent playoffs after the regular season.

Last season, Tyranny was ever so impressive, but lost at the finals.

Perhaps they had felt their efforts taking a toll on them ages ago, holding on only through their faith. Another match, just another match… Perhaps, that was what they were chanting in their heads. Getting to the finals, fighting three rounds against Samsara, they were holding on stubbornly through sheer willpower. However, no matter how strong they were, their energy would eventually be depleted. Under this exhaustion, they had met their strongest rivals in the Alliance and Tyranny had fallen, and many people could only think of what a shame that was.

Thus, in the new season, they had discarded their headstrong ways, not opening the season very well. Everyone felt that it was such a shame; they sighed: the spirit of these veterans were admirable, but what was the use in this stubborn persistence?

The voices cheering for Tyranny for the championship slowly died out, but Tyranny didn’t care, continuing forth like that. Their scores soon stabilized. Though they weren’t as impressive as last season, there was no pressure for them to get into the playoffs. Nonetheless, some people still felt it was a shame. They longed for the time where the four kings lead Tyranny to victory together, sweeping through the alliance with high-spirits.

Yes, high-spirited, but they ended up losing the finals.

But this time, Tyranny wouldn’t act according these personal feelings anymore. They fought steadily, stably. The veterans, including Han Wenqing who hadn’t backed down in ten years, all began playing in rotation. He was the team captain, after all – the soul of Tyranny. Currently, there wasn’t a single team that had such a figure in such a consistent rotation. It was rare that these people would even sit out for a single match. Yet now, this was something that had happened to Han Wenqing. The Han Wenqing that always pressed forth and never backed down.

Everything was for the championship.

Team Tyranny’s members, after their loss last season, had clearly realized that they could no longer fight freely and without restraint like the younger generation. They had to preserve their strength. They needed enough energy to face the playoffs, to face the finals. Thus, they stayed in rotation this season, marching forth and keeping a low profile. The three veterans had each played two thirds of what they had played last season. They maintained their condition throughout the intense pro level matches and didn’t deplete so much of their energy.

And now, it was Round 30 of the regular season. After this round, there would be eight more rounds in the regular season before the even more intense playoffs begun.

Team Tyranny’s low profile would end here. In the match against Thunderclap, they revealed their fangs and claws. The three veterans and Zhang Xinjie appeared in the starting line up together, wiping out Thunderclap, who were using their team competitions to make miracles this season. They were announcing their return, announcing that they were prepared for the playoffs. They were going to use the following eight matches to once again get completely used to their team, to find the state they needed, because this was their true pillar. This was weapon they wielded in this fight for the championship. That was something they never doubted since they had formed this team last season, this team had people had thought senile.

“It’s time to start.”

That was the simple and straightforward reply Han Wenqing gave in response to the reporter’s questions on their lineup.

It was starting.

All the teams were preparing.

Those who hadn’t secured their position would begin their final slaughter to the top. Those who had already reached the door to the playoffs were all adjusting their teams to get into the rhythm of the playoffs.

Tyranny had the three veterans fight together, and Happy also had Luo Ji and Wei Chen find their optimal state through the following matches. As for the teams that didn’t have much hope, they were beginning to change their tactics, too, willing to try out new things. Each team, depending on their own situations, would be adjusting to a different pace in these last eight rounds.

Often times, strange and unexpected situations would result from the clashes of these differing rhythms. Some would be at a disadvantage, others would be able to take advantage.

Happy was, unfortunately, one of those disadvantaged. In Round 31, they played their away game against Misty Rain, and Happy somehow lost with a shocking 1 to 9. Apart from the victory Ye Xiu gained in the first individual round, they lost spectacularly until the end.

If it was last season’s Misty Rain, this score wouldn’t be too shocking, no matter what team they had managed it against. However, Misty Rain’s condition clearly wasn’t very good this season, and their strategic structure had completely collapsed. But in this round, Misty Rain had fought unrestrained and won a landslide victory against Happy.

“Don’t underestimate us!” Chu Yunxiu grinned, saying to Ye Xiu as they shook hands after the match. 　 “We didn’t underestimate you, we just really weren’t expecting it,” Ye Xiu said helplessly.

The individual rounds were acceptable. Happy had been prepared to lose points when they sent up Luo Ji and Wei Chen. The thing was that in their team competition this time, Misty Rain completely ignored the criticism from both outside and inside the circle. This time, they were even crazier. Chu Yunxiu took Shu Kexing and Shu Keyi, and the three ranged fighters fought elegantly and without a care for a world. Li Hua’s Ninja didn’t bother acting as a close ranged guerrilla tank anymore, instead running around and launching sneak attacks. 　 Misty Rain had gone completely off the rails, leaving Happy floundering to react, and swept a victory for themselves.

“How was it? Our strategy?” Chu Yunxiu was enthusiastically asking for Ye Xiu’s opinion.

“Be happy about catching us off guard elsewhere. Stop shoving it in my face, would you?” Ye Xiu said.

“Heheh,” Chu Yunxiu didn’t mind this at all. It was clear she understood that their performance had simply caught Happy off guard. If Happy had prepared and dealt with this more carefully, Misty Rain’s strategy wouldn’t be all that reliable. 　 “Good luck!”

After Ye Xiu walked past Chu Yunxiu, Su Mucheng came over and grasped Chu Yunxiu’s hand, giving her words of encouragement, as if they had been the one to win and not Misty Rain.

Chu Yunxiu naturally understood what Su Mucheng was talking about. Her encouragement wasn’t about this match, but Misty Rain’s overall situation.

Faced with her good friend, Chu Yunxiu didn’t bother with the triumphant demeanor she had worn in front of Ye Xiu, shaking her head and giving a strained smile.

“Let’s hang out after this!” Chu Yunxiu suggested.

“Alright!” Su Mucheng didn’t reject the offer. The two didn’t dawdle any longer. After the players of each team finished giving each other their post-match regards, they each returned to their prep rooms to prepare for the post-match press conference.

Misty Rain were the victors, so their press conference was after Happy’s. The sudden victory was exciting for the reports, and they enthusiastically tossed questions about the playstyle Misty Rain had used this round as well as what they thought about the playoffs.

Chu Yunxiu answered the questions one by one. Their strategy was something the team had been figuring out and researching. With the victory today, it seemed pretty good, so the team would continue to look into it and hone themselves. As for the playoffs? No one would know until the last moment, and Misty Rain wasn’t planning on giving up.

Watching the satisfied reporters, Chu Yunxiu could only sigh to herself. Was there really any hope for Misty Rain this season?

After the press conference, Misty Rain’s players bid each other goodbye. Chu Yunxiu was the last to leave the prep room and she flipped open her phone to a text from Su Mucheng: “Waiting at Exit E.”

“Coming.”

Chu Yunxiu replied before heading for Exit E.

The moment she stepped out from Exit E, Chu Yunxiu saw the somewhat blurred but elegant figure of her friend in the night lightning. Next to her was another, a fitful spot of red light fading and burning.

The elegant figure waved at her and Chu Yunxiu quickly walked over.

“How come you’re here, too?” Chu Yunxiu didn’t greet Su Mucheng, instead choosing to side eye the smoking Ye Xiu.

“I felt like the Great God Chu seemed after uncertain and was wondering if she needed some advice from a helpful senior,” Ye Xiu replied.

“Give me a cig!” Chu Yunxiu demanded.

Ye Xiu didn’t hesitate to take out a cigarette and hand it over and even offered a flame. Chu Yunxiu accepted the cigarette and lit it smoothly.

“Let’s go to the coffee shop over there!” Chu Yunxiu suggested after taking a puff from the cigarette.

Chapter 1348 - Misty Rain, Helpless

The coffeeshop was fairly remote. It hadn’t been too long since the match ended, and the more eye-catching places along the road were popular hangouts for gamers who had just finished watching the match. If the three of them had gone to one of these places, there would definitely be onlookers. Fortunately, this was Misty Rain’s home stadium, and Chu Yunxiu was extremely familiar with the area. She led the two to this very quiet location.

They took their seats, each ordering a cup of coffee. The cigarettes were already finished during their walk over here. Ye Xiu stared blankly at the prominent no-smoking signs hanging in the coffeeshop.

Finally, Chu Yunxiu opened her mouth. “Happy really is doing well.”

“What about Misty Rain?” Ye Xiu didn’t dance around, going straight to the topic. He could tell that Chu Yunxiu was really feeling quite depressed. There must be some problems with the team, for her to ask to meet them after the match.

“What do you think?” Chu Yunxiu asked Ye Xiu.

Misty Rain’s problem right now was one of strategy, everyone knew this. In general, things like strategy should be kept secret from competitors. But unlike the stats of Silver equipment, strategies were publicly demonstrated in battle. So, strategies themselves weren’t considered some secret weapons. The key was their execution. 301 adapted to their new strategy of the Knight covering the Assassin like a fish to water, but if you tried to get a different team to emulate it, it probably wouldn’t be as effective. Different players and characters required different strategies. There needed to be adaptability.

So, there wasn’t anything taboo about talking strategy. Anything you can do, everyone else can too. It just came down to whether or not it’d be useful or effective. Still, mutually asking for tips and advice was rarely seen. Who had time to help the competitor improve?

But now that Chu Yunxiu said this, Ye Xiu didn’t seem like he cared about all that, and he directly said what he had to say. “It’s clear that the current strategy isn’t suitable. Let’s make an analogy! In basketball, there’s a strategy of having one tall player with four perimeter players, but there’s no strategy with a short player running around with four perimeter players. Misty Rain right now is the latter. You could play with this strategy occasionally to trip people up, but it’s not suitable as a main strategy.”

“Who said that wasn’t the case?” Chu Yunxiu said.

“If you know the problem, then why don’t you adjust?” asked Ye Xiu.

“How do you think we should adjust?” said Chu Yunxiu.

“Sun Liang should play in the starting lineup for the team competition,” said Ye Xiu. Sun Liang was a member of Misty Rain, a Striker. He used to be a main player for the team, but after Misty Rain changed its strategy this season, he became a rotating player.

“Oh, then who should be switched out?” Chu Yunxiu asked.

Ye Xiu hesitated.

For such a simple question, Chu Yunxiu didn’t need to ask him step by step. Who should be switched out? When Chu Yunxiu said this, the frustration and bitterness on her face was plain to see. Clearly, there was more to this question. After Ye Xiu thought for a moment, he realized where the problem must lie.

“When it comes down to it, that pair of sisters will just have to be separated,” said Ye Xiu.

“That’s the problem. They can’t be separated,” Chu Yunxiu said.

“Oh…” Ye Xiu understood and fell silent. He had already guessed the general situation.

The Shu siblings couldn’t be separated? How could something like that be so absolute? Their partnership wasn’t guaranteeing the team’s success. On the contrary, it was because the two of them were on the field at the same time that the team couldn’t adjust their class composition. They couldn’t be separated, not for strategic reasons, but for other reasons. And the only thing that could supersede strategic demands were the decisions of the club itself. This wasn’t a problem of strategy. This was a problem of the operations of Club Misty Rain. The club required that both of the Shu siblings be on the battlefield.

Just from how Misty Rain had specially requested the Alliance to change the genders of these sisters’ characters, the hope and importance placed on these two was clear. And for pro players, value was ultimately demonstrated on the battlefield. So it wasn’t strange that the club directly required that these two had to appear together on the field.

And this was something that players could hate, but could do nothing about.

Business operations overrode strategy. The outside directed the inside.

Chu Yunxiu hadn’t asked to meet Su Mucheng to try and find some solution. She was simply feeling depressed and wanted to chat and share with a good friend. Now that the situation had been made clear, the three sank into silence. For a problem like this, if Chu Yunxiu was powerless to fix it, then how could outsiders like Ye Xiu or Su Mucheng help?

Chu Yunxiu, Li Hua…

This was the true strategic core duo of Misty Rain. The value of this pair was higher than that of the Shu siblings. If it came down to it and this pair needed to sacrifice in order to achieve a more suitable class composition, then it wouldn’t just be an individual sacrifice. The team as a whole would be sacrificing its fighting strength. If Misty Rain resorted to such a method to get a reasonable class composition, how much strength would they ultimately have remaining, anyway?

Furthermore… between these two players, if they had to choose one to remove from the roster, then Chu Yunxiu was a better choice than Li Hua. After all, the Shu siblings were both long-range Sharpshooters and had some overlap with the use of an Elementalist. Keeping Li Hua’s Ninja on the field would allow greater flexibility of tactics. But with that, the problem became even more unsolvable. Chu Yunxiu was this team’s captain; Windy Rain was this team’s core character. If she didn’t play on the main roster, was Misty Rain planning to start over from zero?

Ye Xiu combed through Misty Rain’s situation in his mind, and he discovered that this really was a frightening problem with no clear solution. No wonder Chu Yunxiu was so helpless.

“Then what do you plan to do?” Su Mucheng suddenly asked. She hadn’t said anything since entering the coffeeshop, but she’d thought of everything that needed to be thought of.

“I don’t know…” Chu Yunxiu’s gaze was somewhat empty. This season, she had truly felt rather lost and confused. The heads of the club had ordered that the Shu sisters be placed in the main roster, but Misty Rain’s core wasn’t suited for the sudden addition of two Sharpshooters.

But no one talked reason with her. The club simply wanted all of these players on the field at once. Windy Rain, Dark Forest, Lower Your Head, None Dare Attack, all four characters had to be there.

Ye Xiu had proposed the hypothetical of either Chu Yunxiu or Li Hua sacrificing themselves, but in reality, even that wasn’t possible! Misty Rain was greedy; they wanted not only the beautiful sisters, but their core partnership as well. They demanded that this irrational roster win results. Misty Rain had already drifted unsteadily through half a season, but the upper management still refused to change. In their view, Misty Rain just needed to push a little more to get results. The players needed to work just a little harder, the strategies needed to mature just a little more, and then they would begin winning matches beautifully.

While they treated this as an obvious fact, they overlooked the reality.

While Misty Rain’s players were working hard, the players of all the other teams were working just as hard.

While Misty Rain’s strategies were maturing, the operations of the other teams were only growing smoother and smoother.

And Misty Rain’s class composition gave them a natural handicap that they could never overcome.

A Misty Rain like this could not win.

Chu Yunxiu had racked her brains for half a season, but in the end, this was all that Misty Rain could accomplish. What else could she feel, beside frustration and bitterness?

“If you can’t make adjustments, then you can only try even bolder things!” Ye Xiu suddenly said.

“Say it.” Chu Yunxiu looked at him.

But Ye Xiu only said two words: “Wind Howl.”

“So that’s how it is?” Chu Yunxiu looked not at Ye Xiu, but at the ceiling.

“You’ve already noticed it, haven’t you? Misty Rain could possibly emulate Wind Howl’s playstyle,” said Ye Xiu.

“It’s a desperate playstyle,” said Chu Yunxiu.

“Do you all have any other choice? If you don’t want to give up right here.”

Chu Yunxiu was silent.

Anyone could use a strategy. The question was whether or not it was suitable. Misty Rain was traditionally viewed as soft, so much so that it was basically considered part of their style. To have such a soft team try and emulate Wind Howl’s ferocious and desperate style, it clearly wasn’t a very suitable choice. This was a choice made when there were no other options, a choice to beg for victory in the midst of defeat. Even Wind Howl themselves wouldn’t have gone to such extremes if their performance hadn’t been so unstable. A fight without a healer was just too risky.

The three fell into silence once again. Chu Yunxiu rested one arm on the table. Her other hand held a small spoon to stir the coffee in front of her. She stirred it for a very long time, but in the end, didn’t take a sip.

“Let’s go, let’s head back.” She suddenly stood up.

“You’re leaving like that?” Both Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were surprised at her suddenness.

“I still have two episodes of my TV drama to watch,” Chu Yunxiu said.

“This late?” Ye Xiu looked at the time.

“You think I’m watching it on TV?” Chu Yunxiu scoffed.

“Alright, then!” Ye Xiu said helplessly, as he and Su Mucheng also stood up to leave.

Night had already fallen. There were no streetlamps around this out-of-the-way coffee shop to which Chu Yunxiu had brought the two of them. Under the starlight, her blurred silhouette walked at the very front. Misty Rain’s troubles were both internal and external, but as the team’s captain, Chu Yunxiu could only quietly carry this burden. On this point, she needed to be even tougher and more resilient than too many of her fellow male pro players. Misty Rain was in a disastrous situation, the outside world all criticized their strategies, the club was unwilling to change. But even in this situation, she had never said anything. She only continued to try and think of solutions, think about how she could use this unreasonable roster to earn results with which people could be satisfied.

“Alright, I’m going this way. What about your hotel, where is it?” At the intersection, Chu Yunxiu stopped and asked them.

“That way.” Su Mucheng pointed.

“Okay! When you get back, let’s chat online.” Chu Yunxiu walked back and hugged Su Mucheng.

“Keep your chin up,” Su Mucheng said. In reality, they hadn’t really talked about much this night. Everything that Ye Xiu said, Chu Yunxiu had understood long ago. Perhaps she only wanted to lay bare her emotions to her girlfriend; perhaps she wished to draw from this the courage and faith she needed to continue.

In any case…

“I will,” Chu Yunxiu said softly. She turned, waved her hand, and disappeared into the distance.

Soon, Round 32 was upon them. That night, Misty Rain presented a shocking roster to everyone who believed they were already done for the season.

Six attackers. No healer.

Chapter 1349 - Team

The current round was Misty Rain’s home game against Team Void. In the 1v1 matches, Misty Rain won one individual round and the group arena afterwards, gaining a lead of 3 to 2. Then, when their formation for the team competition appeared onscreen afterwards, the entire stadium erupted.

Team Wind Howl had created an all DPS formation, but they were smart about it, arranging for their healer to appear in the starting lineup like any normal team. As for if they’d switch their healer out for an all DPS formation, that was something their opponents had to contemplate. They might do a man-to-man offense, but they might do a normal one healer four DPS formation.

However, Misty Rain’s formation didn’t even have a healer in it. This was something that hadn’t happened in the Alliance for who knows how many years, but now it had appeared with Misty Rain, a team which was often considered rather soft.

Were they cutting off all chance of backing down?

Everyone could feel their determination with this lineup.

“How fierce…” Team Void’s captain, Li Xuan, looked over at Misty Rain, where Chu Yunxiu was telling the players of Misty Rain something. This captain, the only female captain in all twenty teams in the Alliance, might truly not have as much hot-blooded passion that was typical of male players, but her dedication to her team didn’t lose to anyone. 　 “But is Misty Rain’s formation really suited to this playstyle?” Wu Yuce looked up at the player lineup on the big screen.

Chu Yunxiu and the Shu sisters, one Elementalist and two Sharpshooters, these three ranged fighters had no problem with DPS, but they lacked CC. Melee classes, even if they didn’t have any control skills, usually had an easier time restricting an opponent’s actions. Could Misty Rain use three ranged fighters to completely pin their opponents?

“Don’t let your guard down,” Li Xuan said. Misty Rain wouldn’t neglect to consider such simple problems. If they still dared to use such a formation, then there must be a reason. After all, didn’t Happy get crushed by Misty Rain’s sudden switch in tactics, despite having a home game advantage? Perhaps Misty Rain was now preparing to use a different strategy every round and hoping to win through catching their opponent’s off-guard.

“It’s time.” After the referee approached to call them over, the players of the two teams entered the stage.

For Void, their starting lineup was comprised of Li Xuan and Wu Yuce’s Ghost Duo, Li Xun’s Assassin, Ge Caijie’s exorcist, Tang Lisheng’s Paladin and their sixth player was Ge Zhaolan’s Spitfire.

How would Void’s typical team arrangement face off against Misty Rain’s extreme?

Currently, Misty Rain’s fans were extremely anxious. Thought they were 32 points away from the current eighth team, but what if they really did achieve a miracle?

Last round, Misty Rain had crushed Happy with their sudden and drastic change in playstyle and rhythm. This round, they had made significant adjustments too, so maybe they would claim victory again? If and only if they continued like that, would their opponents’ mistakes be of use. Perhaps the conditions of the top eight teams would suddenly slide, allowing Misty Rain into the playoffs?

You have to win… 　 All of the audience members in the stadium were all thinking of the same thing, even those players who had given up on their team this season felt the embers of passion flicker to life.

Just maybe, there was still hope?

They hadn’t seen a victory, but they saw Misty Rain’s attitude. This attitude reignited their hope.

The team competition between a Misty Rain with a six DPS formation and Void begun! Unfortunately, this wasn’t the match that had been chosen to be live broadcasted on television, so there was no way of drawing everyone’s immediate attention. The match broadcasted this round was also much anticipated. 　 At Tiny Herb’s home game against Thunderclap, the two sides had reached the team competition.

In the 1v1 matches, Tiny Herb had claimed 4 points and Thunderclap only 1. It was a good lead and should’ve given them a huge morale boost, but when the opponent was Thunderclap, then a lead in the 1v1 matches didn’t mean much for a morale advantage. Thunderclap had always relied on their performance in team competitions to achieve such heights, after all.

In the current round, they were playing their away game against Tiny Herb. How would their team competition end?

Oh… 　 After several rounds of exchanges, Team Tiny Herb’s Wang Jiexi understood what was happening.

So everyone has started to focus on me? It was probably because the match against Happy had given everyone too clear of a message.

If you defeated Wang Jiexi, then you’ve defeated Tiny Herb. That’s probably what everyone believed! So, was that Thunderclap’s current plan as well?

Divide, encircle, reserve Box-1.

Wang Jiexi had noticed Thunderclap’s strategic intentions, but what should he do? Wang Jiexi gazed at the team members at his side. Under his leadership, it was true that Tiny Herb had obtained two championships, but he couldn’t be their pillar forever. Ultimately, he would retire, and the team would have to depend on themselves. 　　 Be a role model instead of a crutch, huh?

Wang Jiexi recalled Ye Xiu’s words. In the past, he really hadn’t considered that much, simply carrying Tiny Herb on his shoulders unthinkingly. Perhaps, it was precisely because of their previous successes that the team had developed such a strong dependence on him.

However, he would eventually be incapable of bearing such a weight, so they had to find a way to break away from this dependence. Gao Yingjie, Gao Yingjie had grown up under his careful attention and protection. The other had gained confidence, but it seemed that he had yet to gather the courage necessary to truly bear the weight of Tiny Herb.

They had to grow under a trying situation! Those who overcome adversity would gain more courage, and their confidence would be fortified. He couldn’t continue to shoulder all their difficulties; he had to leave some for them to overcome on their own.

Yes, just let them deal with it themselves!

Wang Jiexi made this decision, and Vaccaria fell into Thunderclap’s attempt at divide and encircle.

Perhaps he had the ability, the chance to throw off this attempt at dividing them, but this time, he decided to try and brute force his way out of the encirclement and destroy it. Of these two choices, there wasn’t one that was particularly better or worse. Wang Jiexi’s choice had always been to deal with it himself if he could, though. Butnow, he had chosen the latter, depending on the power of the entire team to destroy Thunderclap’s strategic arrangements.

Would it work?

Wang Jiexi didn’t know, but this was a trial, a trial for all the players of Tiny Herb.

Happy had added more chess pieces to hone for the playoffs, Tyranny’s veterans were adjusting their pacing and condition in preparation, and as for Tiny Herb? Tiny Herb had to prepare for the playoffs, and even the future beyond them. They had to change their ways, completely. 　 “Ah… Tiny Herb’s been divided by Thunderclap!” the broadcast commentator Pan Lin cried out in surprise.

“Yeah…” Li Yibo gave a very simple reply. He had a feeling that the reason Thunderclap’s strategy was executed so successfully was because of Wang Jiexi’s choices. If it were the Wang Jiexi of the past, it definitely wouldn’t have been so easy. Perhaps, he would’ve once even managed to crush Thunderclap’s attempt at dividing them with a peak in performance. Yet this time, it felt like he was going with their plan and letting it succeed. What for? To push Tiny Herb as a team? Was it because he didn’t want what happened with Happy to repeat?

No one knew about the words Ye Xiu and Wang Jiexi exchanged post-match, so Li Yibo felt like there was a barrier, preventing him from truly understanding. He had long since developed caution and didn’t dare make a hasty judgement. He needed to continue observing. He thought to the last round where Tiny Herb faced off against Hundred Blossoms and lost their away game 4 to 6. Since that match wasn’t broadcasted on tv, Li Yibo simply checked the post-match report, not bothering to rewatch the match.

Did any specifics happen with Tiny Herb in that match?

Li Yibo didn’t know. After Tiny Herb had lost to Happy, they had fought another four matches. Did they make any adjustments? Li Yibo didn’t know. Since they hadn’t broadcasted any of the four matches, the attention he paid to Tiny Herb had fallen to such lows.

He wasn’t like this before…

Even if he didn’t watch all of the matches, he would at least follow the matches of the powerhouses. Not watching four rounds of matches of a powerhouse like Tiny Herb is something he wouldn’t have even been able to imagine.

Why did it end up like this? Was it because now that Glory was growing in popularity, the number of reports by the media and commentaries also grew in number, making it easier to obtain large amounts of information, so he got lazy?

If he continued like this, then what was the point of his presence?

Never able to see deeper into the match, getting his face slapped all the time, was it fun?

No, not at all! 　 The stockpile of Glory knowledge he had was running out. He had to keep learning, keep up with the pace at which Glory was developing!

The match was still continuing and Li Yibo once again admonished himself for not daring to express his own opinion.

“Ah, Vaccaria’s been surrounded; Thunderclap has focused fire. They’re trying to one wave rush him! They’re keeping Tiny Herb’s healer under careful control. That’s right, their goal is to get rid of Tiny Herb’s captain, Wang Jiexi first,” Pan Lin explained excitedly.

“Tiny Herb’s other members have reacted quickly, coming to Vaccaria’s aid! Can they break through? Thunderclap will probably continue trying to take down Wang Jiexi first! In the match between Happy and Tiny Herb, Team Happy had sacrificed two characters to kill Vaccaria.”

“Huh?! They’ve doubled back, switched targets… Thunderclap has adjusted their offensive, this… They’ve gone back and surrounded the rest of Tiny Herb’s players. Vaccaria has been thrown to one side…”

“This… is isolation! Thunderclap has isolated Wang Jiexi! How to say this… This is probably a reverse of Happy’s strategy. Thunderclap may have realized that they didn’t have the power to finish off Vaccaria quickly, or they thought they might not be able to assure their final victory after the sacrifices needed to get rid of Vaccaria. Thus, in the end, their strategy was isolation! Vaccaria is still on the field, but he’s been cut off from the rest of Tiny Herb. Thunderclap has gone to fight a Tiny Herb without Wang Jiexi, while Wang Jiexi is actually still on the field, right? Coach Li?” Pan Lin gave commentary after commentary and suddenly realized, didn’t it seem a little too quiet over here?

Chapter 1350 - The Battle Never Ends

Li Yibo didn’t speak because he felt like he had been enlightened. From not daring to be certain of Wang Jiexi’s intentions, to Thunderclap’s changing strategy. If dividing Tiny Herb up and ganging up on Vaccaria was something within his expectations, the double back and isolation afterwards was completely unexpected for him.

Brilliance, brilliance that he couldn’t predict at all. His own skill really had fallen behind. He had once been a member of a championship team, and now he had fallen this low? His minds drifted to Team Tyranny; his once teammates, his once captain, who were still fighting on the frontlines. Every time people thought “that’s enough, it’s time he retires”, he would reply resolutely: next year.

Next year next year next year.

It had been six years since Li Yibo’s retirement. Li Yibo was a little older than him, but back then, had he really reached the point where he had no choice but to retire? No… it wasn’t like that. It was only because that year, they had won the championships, so Li Yibo, who wasn’t all that young anymore, decided that it would be the optimal time to retire.

This was called knowing when enough was enough. Li Yibo had always thought his decision wise, yet now, he was beginning to question himself. Was his decision made because he lacked a certain quality? Why had Han Wenqing, who had also gained one championship, still fighting for another with all his might? Why was Wang Jiexi, who had gained two championships, still suppressing his preferred playstyle for the good of Tiny Herb? 　 He had fallen.

Tiny Herb’s healer had shockingly become the first casualty in this battle. After all that, Thunderclap’s actual primary goal was the most typical ‘kill the healer first’. In this, how many strategic maneuvers and details had helped them secure their success? Li Yibo felt his head spin. He really was… absolute trash.

Losing the healer was a problem for any team. Perhaps it was because Thunderclap had let their guard down for a moment, relieved at being able to get rid of the healer, but Tiny Herb had managed a powerful wave of counterattacks then. It was good that Thunderclap had managed to steady their footing. They didn’t rush to end this, instead slowly pulling the battle into one of positional warfare and utilizing their healer advantage to its fullest. In the end, Thunderclap won, overturning Tiny Herb 6 to 4, managing to defeat Tiny Herb both in their home and away games this season with 6 to 4. They generally fell behind on the one on one matches, proving that the strength of their individual players weren’t the best, but when they acted as a team, they were a force that didn’t lose to any other team in the alliance.

This was no longer just about their tactics. Thunderclap’s players were the pinnacle of the alliance in terms of their tactical execution and their teamwork and cooperation.

“Thunderclap wins, in their away game too. Spectacular, especially in the team competition!” Commentator Pan Lin cheered.

“Yes. However, while Thunderclap might have spectacular results in the team competitions, they’ve never entered the top four in the rankings. Their performance in the 1v1 rounds are rather worrying. With the current playoffs format, falling too behind in the 1v1 rounds will place huge pressure on their team competition!” Li Yibo considered aloud. According to the playoffs format, the five person group arena and the team competition would be calculated by headcount. If Thunderclap lost too many points in the group arena, then they’d be playing under much more pressure and more restrictions in the team competition. This would certainly impact the flexibility of their tactics.

“You’re right, but this problem isn’t so easy to solve,” Pan Lin said, finding it unfortunate.

“Thunderclap might really need one or two players with strong individual strength to help them!” Li Yibo lamented.

“Indeed.” Pan Lin nodded in agreement. “Now, this match between Tiny Herb and Thunderclap has come to an end. A few other matches have also finished. We still have some time left, so let’s take a look at the results of the other matches.”

“Ah!” Just as Pan Lin finished speaking, he cried out in surprise after receiving the results from the other matches.

“In the match between Misty Rain and Void, Misty Rain didn’t have a healer!” Pan Lin exclaimed.

“Oh? They’re copying Wind Howl’s playstyle,” Li Yibo said.

“No, they… none of the six players in their team for their competition were healers,” Pan Lin said.

“And the results?” Li Yibo questioned.

“Void won…” Pan Lin’s tone held a hint of disappointment. It wasn’t that he was taking sides, but seeing Misty Rain dedicate themselves like this, it was natural for people to be anticipatory for what they could achieve. Unfortunately, Wind Howl had been successful, but Misty Rain still lost.

“To be honest, Misty Rain’s lineup isn’t very suited to this sort of playstyle…” Li Yibo also lamented, seeing Misty Rain’s roster. This problem was something that many people had noticed, but how many were there who knew of how helpless Misty Rain truly was right now?

“Seven to three, Void won against Misty Rain. It seems like this is it for Misty Rain this season…” In the live broadcast, Pan Lin finally dared to say this. Void was the team who stood in front of Misty Rain in the rankings, and now that they had defeated Misty Rain in a direct confrontation, it was naturally a huge blow to Misty Rain. With only six rounds left to the regular season, this really was it for Misty Rain. 　　 “Amongst the other matches that have ended, 301 Degrees has swept a 10 to 0 against Bright Green, Samsara defeated Parade 9 to 1, Tyranny crushed Radiant 9 to 1 and Happy won against Conquering Clouds 8 to 2,” Pan Lin rapidly announced the results of the finished matches.

“Oh? How did Happy lose those two points?” Li Yibo asked. 　 “It… was the individual competition…” Pan Lin scanned the report on the match, “Luo Ji and Wei Chen each lost a round.”

“Happy’s two players…” Li Yibo really did want to comment on them, but he once again lost his confidence. They were Happy’s players after all… No matter who it was, if they were Happy’s, then he felt like he had no grasp over them.

This really wasn’t a good feeling at all… Li Yibo began to worry again. He imagined his current self, standing on the battlefield. What would that be like? He wouldn’t be able to figure out his opponent’s intentions, he’d hesitate in indecision, his heart would constantly be in his throat. On the battlefield, he’d lose like that, and right now as a commentator, his current self kept getting slapped in the face to the point where he was hesitant to speak.

“Ah! Another match’s results have come out!” Pan Lin really was his savior this time, not giving Li Yibo the chance to continue his commentary on those two players and instead running off to announce the news.

“Wind Howl… swept Hundred Blossoms 10 to 0 in their home game!” Pan Lin’s announcement was full of surprise, after all, it was no easy task to get a 10 to 0 against Hundred Blossoms. Last round, Hundred Blossoms had even defeated Tiny Herb. Yet this powerful team had been obliterated by Wind Howl. Wind Howl had powerful individual strength, and now they seemed to have found something that works for the team competitions, too, like they had suddenly all achieved enlightenment.

“301 Degrees and Wind Howl are neck and neck!” Pan Lin exclaimed with a smile, “After this round, their scores are still the same!”

“But the other teams’ scores have changed!” Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin paused for a moment and then checked the rankings. After each getting a perfect victory of 10 to 0, especially since Wind Howl’s opponent had been Hundred Blossoms, 301 Degrees and Wind Howl were now both in the top eight. Instead, Team Hundred Blossoms had fallen to nineth with 199 points, 5 points away from the top eight.

“If I recall correctly, Hundred Blossom’s following match schedule won’t be easy on them,” Li Yibo noted.

“That’s right.” Pan Lin had already brought out the match schedule. “Team Hundred Blossom’s next six opponents are Misty Rain, Void, Royal Style, Thunderclap, Tyranny and Samsara…”

“It seems like… Team Hundred Blossoms is really in need of some luck!” Li Yibo said.

“I didn’t expect for such a change at a time like now. Looks like you really can’t relax until the very last moment,” Pan Lin said.

“Indeed!”

“Alright, our broadcast ends here. We’ll see you all again next time,” Pan Lin announced the ending of the broadcast. Round 32’s matches all soon came to an end. The uneventful rankings had experienced a whirlwind of change after this round, especially in the top ten. Blue Rain had risen to third, Tiny Herb fell to fourth, Happy rose to fifth, Thunderclap fell to sixth, Wind Howl and 301 Degrees had risen to seventh and eighth respectively, while Hundred Blossoms had fell by a full two places and out of the playoffs cut-off.

As for numbers ten to twelve after them, the three teams hadn’t budged. However, after Royal Style, Misty Rain had also more or less given up on the playoffs.

“In the end, we still lost…”

The current round was still Misty Rain’s home game. Chu Yunxiu, after the match, sat on the player bench, gazing at the score on the big screen. Seeing the audience leaving, she heard a lot of sighs and cursing from them. She saw her teammates sit next to her, silent.

“You guys head out first, I’m going to sit for a while,” Chu Yunxiu said.

“It’s almost time for the press conference,” Li Hua came over to remind her.

“How about you take charge for it? I want to rest a bit,” Chu Yunxiu replied.

After a match that crushed their last hopes for the season, the captain wasn’t going to attend the press conference. This clearly wasn’t very appropriate. However, after a moment of hesitation, Li Hua still nodded. “Alright.” 　 Her teammates left one after the other and some of them looked back at Chu Yunxiu, worried. Chu yunxiu ignored it, continuing to stare at the score on the big screen. The audience behind her were exiting the stadium in an orderly fashion, sighs and reproachful comments towards Misty Rain audible amidst the clamor.

How exhausting…

Chu Yunxiu really wanted to just lie down on this player bench.

Everyone said that she was too soft, and in turn caused the team to become soft. Perhaps that was true. She wasn’t strong enough, and it was easy for her to feel fatigued. Wouldn’t it be great if she wasn’t captain? Chu Yunxiu thought to herself, absentminded.

With Round 32, yet another team bid the season an early goodbye. What was to be of Misty Rain’s future? Perhaps people would wonder, but this wasn’t the focus right now. After Round 32, the top eight had gone through a whirlwind of change and Hundred Blossoms had been squeezed out of the playoffs by 301 Degrees and Wind Howl. It seemed like the fight this season was far from over. From number 5 to 9, there was only a 13 point difference. It wasn’t just 301 Degrees, Wind Howl and Hundred Blossoms fighting. If Happy and Thunderclap slipped up, they might get left behind, too.

Chapter 1351 - A Brutal Six Rounds

With six rounds left in Season 10, the battle between the top eight suddenly became harsher. Originally, everyone had thought that 301’s strength had allowed them to replace Wind Howl for good, and the top eight would be set like that. But out of nowhere, Wind Howl had suddenly resorted to the harsh method of fighting person-to-person, and they sang boldly and loudly as they marched through their team battles.

After defeating Blue Rain in Round 26, Wind Howl consecutively defeated 301, Misty Rain, Void, and Hundred Blossoms.

Weaklings?

It looked like that designation was no longer accurate. But this new strategy of Wind Howl’s had only appeared in the past few rounds. As to whether they could actually maintain this, everyone still held doubt.

At the end of Round 32, the commentator and honored guest expressed sympathy toward the match schedule that Hundred Blossoms was about to face. But when everyone thought about it, they realized that Wind Howl’s upcoming match schedule wasn’t easy either.

Wind Howl’s opponents in the final six rounds were Thunderclap, Royal Style, Heavenly Swords, Parade, Happy, and Tiny Herb.

Among the six teams, three were in the top eight. Those wouldn’t be easy fights.

But the most demonic match schedule still had to be 301’s. Their final six opponents were Miracle, Samsara, Tiny Herb, Blue Rain, Seaside, and Happy.

This match schedule was enough to make one suffocate. Wind Howl only had to fight three of the top eight, but 301? They were basically fighting the top four.

And between these two match schedules, there were two teams in common: Tiny Herb, and Happy.

Tiny Herb was currently in fourth place with 224 points, a twenty point difference from Wind Howl and 301. Their lead was relatively stable. But the situation wasn’t as relaxed for Happy. They currently had 212 points, only eight points ahead of those two teams. If they slipped up during their confrontations with these two, then they could be dragged right down. Behind that, Hundred Blossoms was still eying the top spots, and if they performed well, one good counterattack could directly kick Happy out of the top eight.

Happy’s opponents in the last six rounds, aside from their direct competitors Wind Howl and 301, included Void, Lightly, Bright Green, and Thunderclap.

These opponents weren’t weak either, especially Thunderclap, another team currently trapped in the mudhole. Currently, Thunderclap had slightly fewer points than Happy, only 211, and in the final six rounds they would be facing Wind Howl, Misty Rain, Happy, Hundred Blossoms, Samsara, Miracle…

Another brutal match schedule.

After analyzing the match schedules of the last six rounds, everyone was dumbfounded. Of the five teams currently embroiled in a battle for a spot in the playoffs – Happy, Thunderclap, Wind Howl, 301, and Hundred Blossoms – not a single one had an easy schedule, and there were multiple matches where they would be going head-to-head. Among the five teams, no one dared to predict right now which team would be kicked out of the top eight.

After Round 32, Happy’s Boss Chen found herself so anxious that she couldn’t fall asleep.

Originally, she’d thought that Happy already had a safe spot in the playoffs, but now at the end things had become so difficult and intense. Happy had actually played quite well in the past few rounds. After they’d begun to send up Luo Ji and Wei Chen, they might lose one or two points here and there, but wins of 8 and 9 points were still very pretty! Their one loss was their away game against Misty Rain, who’d beaten them 9-1. In an instant, the teams behind them had closed the distance. Perhaps it was true, that the other teams’ recent performances had simply been too excellent, too strong.

In Round 33, Happy played their away game against Void.

Void was currently 28 points behind the top eight. Normally, they probably would’ve given up on the playoffs just like Misty Rain. But as of now, the current struggle for the top eight was a mudhole. Maybe there’d be a few teams that completely collapsed?

Void didn’t want to give up. But their upcoming match schedule was also worthy of tears. For the final six rounds of the season, they still had to play Happy, Hundred Blossoms, Radiant, Royal Style, Blue Rain, and Tyranny…

But Void’s dedicated fans had drafted an especially beautiful blueprint. According to the fans’ plan, Void would use their home-field advantage to take care of their direct competitors Happy and Hundred Blossoms. Then, they would get the points they could off of Radiant and Royal Style. By then, four rounds would be over and the leaderboard situation would be clearer. Even though Void would have to face Blue Rain and Tyranny, these two teams had stable spots in the playoffs, and they might even be resting up in preparation for the playoffs. Void might have an easier time getting points off of these two teams.

This so-called “Void’s Plan of Counterattack” post instantly became very popular. Some mocked it, but others voiced their support. After all, the analysis in the post wasn’t without basis. Void’s match schedule looked demonic, but the latter four matches might not be too bad to play. The same was true in general: if a team met one of the top four teams at the end of the season, it might not be a brutal match. It wasn’t that the top four teams were going easy necessarily, it was simply logical to let their main players get a chance to rest after a full season of difficult matches and then use their full potential in the playoffs.

So, Rounds 33 and 34 became crucial. Void’s dedicated fans had already pointed out the path for them, they couldn’t fall here, could they? The team players were also chanting their slogans. These next two home games, they had to win, in order to see the dawn of entering the playoffs.

The discussion, commentary, and analysis from all sides worried Chen Guo, especially after she saw that Happy’s training plans didn’t undergo any special adjustment. She almost wanted to say, at such a crucial time, shouldn’t they let Wei Chen and Luo Ji take a break? After all, entering the playoffs in the first place should be the priority!

But judging from the rhythm of recent practices, Ye Xiu wasn’t planning on changing the original arrangement.

Should she say something to him?

Chen Guo hesitated, because to express this at this point of time would be expressing her lack of faith toward those two. It was the reality that this old player and this new player were weaker in strength, but to prepare them for this crucial moment and then not use them, wouldn’t that upset them? Did Ye Xiu anticipate this, and that was why he couldn’t say anything?

If those two could take the initiative to bring this up, that would be ideal. Chen Guo had no hope for someone as shameless as Wei Chen, but Luo Ji wasn’t Wei Chen. Luo Ji understood his own level very clearly, as well as the current situation. In the meeting before Round 33, when Ye Xiu scheduled him to go onstage as normal, Luo Ji actually brought up this point, wondering if it would be more suitable to make an adjustment.

What understanding! Chen Guo was moved. For the sake of the team, he didn’t care about his individual gains or losses. What a good kid. Compared to him, Wei Chen was really an infuriating guy.

But to Chen Guo’s surprise, Ye Xiu rejected Luo Ji’s suggestion altogether.

“The current situation is critical, but the playoffs will only be even more so. If you hide from this now, then what will you do in the playoffs?” said Ye Xiu.

“Um…” Chen Guo wanted to say “we should at least ensure that we make playoffs first,” but after opening her mouth, she restrained herself in the end. All this time, she had only listened from the side during these strategy meetings. Sometimes she would ask a question if something was unclear, but she never voiced an idea or suggestion. She knew exactly what level she was at, and she didn’t want to become an idiotic backseat driver. This time, Chen Guo felt that this had nothing to do with strategy, it was just an attitude, and she had the right to say something. But just when the words were on her lips – she didn’t know why, perhaps from habit or something else – she automatically swallowed them back.

But it seemed like Ye Xiu knew what she wanted to say. He turned his head to glance at her, and said, “Our goal is to win the championships! We need the courage to face any situation. You too, Luo Ji, this kind of match is training for you. After this round, be ready to play in the team battle.”

“This is just a small stage. Relax, relax!” Wei Chen said, with the confident air of a veteran.

Chen Guo was speechless. But at least now she knew that Wei Chen wasn’t truly shameless at this crucial time. He understood what choices Happy should make at this point. His and Luo Ji’s going onstage now wasn’t the typical training that teams would arrange for their rookies. This was all so that they could be useful in the playoffs. That was why Happy hadn’t sent them up from the very start for matches that would only waste their time. Happy sent them up now so they could have value on the field. Because they were about to face the playoffs, they needed the courage and belief to take responsibility.

“I understand.” Luo Ji was as anxious as ever, but he understood the rationale. Anxiety? Nervousness? Pressure? It was alright that he felt all this, because sending him onstage now was so that he could get used to this sort of anxiety, nervousness, and pressure. There were still six rounds left. He should value these chances. How could he retreat?

“Send me onstage!” Luo Ji mustered his determination, but his voice still trembled. He was truly terrified, terrified that he would lose one or two or even more points, and ultimately prevent Happy from entering the top eight. But he already demonstrated the determination to face difficulties head on. He would overcome all of this.

“Good,” Ye Xiu nodded. “Then the plan is as it was before. Work hard, strive for this victory. Let’s end Void’s plan of counterattack right here.”

“Ha…” Laughter in the meeting room. Evidently, they all had seen that recently trending post. The team that theoretically had the least chance of entering the top eight actually became the most attention-grabbing. It had to be said that people were miracle chasers. They wanted to see the seemingly-impossible become reality, that is, miracles.

After the meeting ended, everyone split up to gather their belongings. In the afternoon, they would be flying to City X. Ye Xiu watched everyone leave one by one, but he himself headed toward Happy’s R&D department.

Guan Rongfei, along with the other R&D workers Happy had found, were all working frantically.

Pseudo-Silver equipment!

This was what Ye Xiu and the others ultimately decided to call their planned Level 80 Orange equipment. After all, any equipment that came out of the equipment editor would have its name in Silver. But because its stats were purposely weaker and closer to those of Orange equipment of the same level, everyone decided to call them “Pseudo-Silver.”

Happy didn’t have enough resources to create more Level 75 Silver equipment. Now, they were prepared to bolster their strength with Pseudo-Silver equipment. But Pseudo-Silver couldn’t just be created on a whim either. The direct jump from Level 70 to Level 80 was possible in Guan Rongfei’s research through accumulating materials. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella itself required a large amount of materials, but other equipment didn’t. So, right now, they had to figure out how to change the blueprints so they could add more materials without ruining the stats of the equipment and ultimately push them to Level 80. This was one of the hardest parts in investigating Pseudo-Silver equipment. It was proven that this was possible, so Happy was currently working on creating as many Pseudo-Silver equipment as they could.

Chapter 1352 - A Map Suited to Phantom Demons

The Pseudo Silver equipment might have cost huge expenses in materials, but since they weren’t trying to achieve the best possible stats, the requirements for the materials weren’t quite as high. For Orange equipment stats, even rare materials were rarely needed. This solved a huge problem. After all, no matter high level or not, rare materials were limited in number and held great value. Yet now, with low requirements for rare materials, most of the other materials were easily obtainable from their guilds. Anything else they lacked weren’t something they couldn’t buy with a little money.

Sixteen pieces.

That was the answer Ye Xiu obtained when he came asking about it. They had already produced sixteen pieces of Pseudo Silver equipment. From nothing to this was impressive, terrifying even, progress. Thus, Happy decided to forgo switching their new equipment in for now.

May 1st, Round 33 of the Pro League began. Though Void had drawn attention with their “Plan of Counterattack”, however, this analysis made by attentive and hopeful fans, was more anticipation than anything. In the Round 33, it was clear that the match between Thunderclap and Wind Howl was the hottest topic, and it naturally became the match to be live broadcasted.

However, none of the fans that came to the stadium cared about that. Banners, signs, they practically flooded Void’s home stadium. For Void, this was like an early finals. If they lost, this season would end here for them. If they won, then they might still have a chance.

Amidst the cheering, the players entered the stage, their accounts projected one after the other in the center of the stage. To Happy, Void’s fans weren’t all that friendly. For one, the match was crucial, and second, Happy had beaten Void 10 to 0 last time.

Though a 10 to 0 and a 9 to 1 only had one point of difference, but they held two completely different meanings. A 10 to 0 was a flawless victory, a true sweep. It was equal to getting a perfect in a PK. The victorious side would be showered in glory and the losing side would be humiliated. No team’s fans would be as naive as to not hate someone after such a humiliation.

Team Happy’s members settled in their seats amidst the ear-piercing jeers of the fans. However, they had already experienced over thirty matches, with over ten of them away games. Happy’s players wouldn’t be scared by this. No matter how scary it was, it couldn’t compare to Tyranny. They had already experienced Tyranny’s home stadium.

The pre-match preparations came to an end and soon the time for the match arrived. For Team Happy, Ye Xiu was sent out, as expected. As for Team Void? All the fans were curious as to who their team would send out to beat Ye Xiu and his 31 consecutive victories. But… 　 Li Xuan!

When the name appeared on the big screen, the entire stadium went into uproar. What was going on? Was it becoming fashionable for captains to challenge Ye Xiu recently?

Wind Howl’s Tang Hao, Royal Style’s Tian Sen, they had both done it, and now, their captain, the Number One Phantom Demon, Li Xuan, had stepped up to the challenge, too.

“Good luck, captain!” The stadium had erupted into cheering.

Fielding their captain was a display of Void’s courage and confidence. However, if he lost, then that was sure to be a huge blow to their morale. Li Xuan’s Crying Devil was a Phantom Demon, too, a class that was more on the supporting side. Yet, he had stepped up in this moment.

The two entered their booths and their characters were loaded into the map. The match soon began.

A Phantom Demon’s map choice naturally wouldn’t tilt the scales in Ye Xiu’s favour. This map was a town with many alleyways, perfect for a Phantom Demon’s Ghost Boundary’s AoE effects and damage.

Seeing the map, Ye Xiu naturally understood Li Xuan’s intentions. Lord Grim very uncharacteristically didn’t head straight for the center of the map, instead choosing to move strategically.

The two characters, one took the left path, the other took the right. Once they were at the center, they looked out and neither of them saw the other.

“Huh? How come you’ve switched playstyles today?” Li Xuan asked in the public chat. In one on one matches, Ye Xiu had maintained a simple and brutal style, charging right into the center, hunting down his target and beating them into a pulp.

“Your map choice is too much! If you left even a slight opening, you think I’d have to resort to this?” Ye Xiu replied.

Li Xuan paused for a moment and then realized that Ye Xiu wasn’t just trash talking. For this map of choice, even the area at the center of the map was just the right size for Crying Devil to cover as a Phantom Demon. He really didn’t leave any room for his opponent. Under these circumstances, his opponent definitely wouldn’t be able fight in such a straightforward manner any more. Playing dirty was pretty much his only choice.

“Hahaha, next time, next time.” Even as Li Xuan wasted his breath with Ye Xiu, he began to pay more attention to what was behind him. He had chosen this map and was naturally very familiar with it. It took but a moment for him to analyze the routes his opponent could take to get behind him. It was a one on one map, after all, so it wouldn’t be very large; it’s complexity was therefore also limited.

Where would his opponent be? Just as Li Xuan was considering this, he heard the sound of cannonfire. Looking up, he saw a character fly into the air. Apart from Lord Grim, who else could it be? The other wouldn’t just stay in the alleyways and wait for death, so he jumped right onto the roof.

This playstyle wasn’t unexpected to Li Xuan. The alleyways were narrow. In comparison, the rooftops were much more wide and open.

Lord Grim turned this view on the rooftop. Li Xuan didn’t make his presence known. In a direct confrontation, there was little chance his Phantom Demon would be able to take on the powerful Unspecialized! Thus, this match would rely on tactics. He had to find a chance and CC Lord Grim for good. He couldn’t let him escape; he had to take him down in one go.

Thus, the first strike was critical. This strike may very well decide the entire battle. Li Xuan wouldn’t act without 100 percent certainty. However, if he kept waiting like this, it wasn’t like opportunity would just come to him. Li Xuan considered his options for a moment before letting Crying Devil stick his head up into Lord Grim’s field of vision for a moment.

“I see you!” The message jumped out and light flashed. Lord Grim was already launching attacks over at him. Anti-Tank Missiles, the three artillery shells shot over.

It wasn’t anything that could threaten him. Li Xuan easily had Crying Devil charge and dodge the attack, heading towards Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu, naturally, wasn’t afraid of close combat. Seeing his opponent approach him, it was exactly what he wanted. Lord Grim didn’t enter the alleyways, remaining on the rooftops as he approached.

Bang, bang bang…

Currently, Lord Grim was the only one who could attack. He shot normal attacks at Crying Devil as he leaped across the rooftops. These attacks were nothing significant, and it didn’t matter even if Crying Devil didn’t dodge. The two characters, after sneaking to the center, suddenly decided to show themselves one after the other and charge right at one another. Considering this, their earlier actions seemed completely wasteful.

Finally, the two characters were mid range from each other, and Lord Grim gained more usable attack methods. As for Crying Devil, his Ghost Boundaries were finally in range. However, face to face, there was no point in trying to unleash Ghost Boundaries. Ghost Boundaries required casting. If they didn’t control their distance and used them in a head on confrontation, then it’d definitely be interrupted. Currently, Crying Devil and Lord Grim were a little closer, and it didn’t seem like the former had any chance to summon a Ghost Boundary. But that was when Crying Devil suddenly swerved and entered Lord Grim’s blind spot.

However, Ye Xiu was very experienced. Even just from this view, he could guess what the terrain was like in his blind spot. Standing above, his mind rapidly constructed the possible route Crying Devil had used the blind spot to take. However, he couldn’t grasp the other’s movement speed.

Not being able to grasp the other’s movement speed meant that he couldn’t estimate his opponent’s position. Even if he could calculate the routes his opponent might take, Ye Xiu couldn’t make a precise judgement. He really wasn’t that familiar with this map, otherwise he’d be able to figure out where the other might attack from through sheer experience. Right now, Ye Xiu could only use what was in front of him to make a vague judgement.

There?

Ye Xiu glanced at a spot and immediately had Lord Grim charge over. He still didn’t come down, remaining on the rooftops. He would jump over what gaps he could and those he couldn’t, he’d jump down then right back up…

As he advanced, he continued to turn his view, looking out for any hints of Crying Devil.

A figure suddenly flashed in his periphery. Ye Xiu immediately had Lord Grim come to a stop. That position, that direction, it was off from Ye Xiu’s prediction. Where was his opponent trying to go?

He had yet to come to a conclusion when another figure suddenly flickered into view.

How come he’s come to this side now?

Ye Xiu turned around, observing the two places Crying Devil appeared, unable to figure out his opponent’s intentions.

Was he just taking a longer route to hide his actual goal? Ye Xiu didn’t think it was so simple. This seemed more like a trap, baiting him into investigating further. Thus, after Ye Xiu had Lord Grim carefully take a good look at the surrounding terrain, he stopped moving.

Li Xuan had Crying Devil run and run, popping out here and there. All this trouble, only to find that his opponent had stopped moving.

Crying Devil once again walked out of Lord Grim’s blind spot, giving the other a clear view. However, he only saw the other turn to look, not move.

“That’s enough of that. You can stop. I’m not going over,” Ye Xiu said in the chat.

“If you don’t come over, how are we going to fight?” Li Xuan saw that his opponent was far too experienced and cunning. He was running around, but the other just watched him like some sort of circus monkey, not bothering to move. Thus, Li Xuan also gave up.

“You come over,” Ye Xiu suggested.

“No way, I can’t fight you while you’re over there like that,” Li Xuan replied.

“Then give me a place you can fight in. We’ll go over,” Ye Xiu replied.

“I like where I am now.”

“Then perish the thought.”

“What about we roll die? We’ll take the numbers we roll as coordinates and go over,” Li Xuan suggested.

“Sure, you go first!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ok,” Li Xuan agreed and then really did roll in the chat.

34!

Li Xuan’s number had been rolled.

“Your turn,” he messaged.

And so this time it was Lord Grim rolling dice in the chat.

41! 　 “34, 41. There,” li Xuan said.

“I was already moving when 34 was rolled. Haven’t you realized I’ve disappeared?” Ye Xiu replied.

“I’ve realized for a while now,” Li Xuan said.

“Because I already knew you’d roll a 34,” Ye Xiu said.

“I knew that you would know,” Li Xuan said.

“Really? Then guess where I am now,” Ye Xiu said.

Li Xuan didn’t reply, because he had to keep his attention on his surroundings and not the chat. He knew that Lord Grim had already approached Crying Devil.

Chapter 1353 - A Battle of Awareness

Cast!

Without a trace of hesitation, Crying Devil’s blade flickered.

One shouldn’t be fooled by the idle chatting and banter in the public channel. In reality, the two of them were carefully controlling their characters while relying on their wealth of experiences to determine the other’s actions.

In the instant that Li Xuan had stopped chatting, he already knew that Lord Grim was nearby, and without the slightest hesitation, Crying Devil called forth a Ghost Boundary. But halfway through the cast, Lord Grim’s figure suddenly flashed in front of him.

So fast!

Li Xuan was startled. This speed was a fair bit faster than what he’d predicted. With the cast halfway done, could he complete it?

Bang!

Lord Grim opened fire, sending bullets precisely towards him.

He couldn’t complete it!

Li Xuan made an accurate judgement in a split second, cancelling his previous Ghost Boundary cast. Crying Devil jumped to the side to avoid the gunfire as the Silver Weapon, Four Heavenly Wheels spun one round next to him, casting a Shadow Image.

Shadow Image was a Ghostblade’s protective skill. Within 1 minute, the player could activate it any number of times to offset the damage that they took. In a head-on fight, especially against a veteran like Ye Xiu, Li Xuan didn’t make Crying Devil summon a Ghost Boundary, instead casting Shadow Image before immediately retreating.

Lord Grim had appeared at a speed which exceeded his expectations, but if one were to say that moment had decided the difference between victory and defeat, it really wasn’t so simple. Crying Devil retreated, and in just a few steps, he had already turned another corner. Without hesitation, he began to cast his Ghost Boundary once again.

Crying Devil’s cast speed was very fast. Li Xuan was confident that Lord Grim had no way of once again appearing before him so quickly that he couldn’t finish his cast. But this time, an explosion rang out. The wall in front of Crying Devil had been blown up by Lord Grim’s cannonfire, immediately sending fragments flying inches away from Crying Devil, who was now worried that he wouldn’t be able to get out unscathed.

Interrupt!

Before even being able to see Crying Devil’s situation, Lord Grim used such a method to indirectly interrupt his Ghost Boundary cast.

The two of them were carefully analyzing each other. The back-and-forth combat so far had been completely reliant on their snap decisions and conjectures made from their awareness. Apart from the time when Lord Grim had interrupted the cast with his gun, the two people hadn’t seen each other’s movements directly at all. This was purely a battle of awareness and experience.

Retreat!

Li Xuan, who once again had his cast interrupted, had no choice but to retreat. Crying Devil continued to retreat frantically. On this map that Li Xuan chose, he didn’t even need to look to know what the next street would look like. But before he could even retreat two steps, Li Xuan heard heard another gunshot before hearing the sound of Rotor Wing being used.

Chasing from above!

Li Xuan quickly raised his camera angle and adjusted Crying Devil’s movement accordingly.

In the end, what the audience saw instead was Lord Grim using Aerial Fire, with the Rotor Wings only being used for hovering at a low elevation. Ye Xiu was too crafty!

The crowd was awed. Ye Xiu had made use of the sound effect of the two skills, managing to cloud Li Xuan’s judgement. In reality, he controlled Lord Grim chase on level ground at first before suddenly popping out from a corner and charging straight towards his opponent.

As he had to defend from aerial attacks, Li Xuan had chosen to turn a different street corner. But at this time, he was suddenly face-to-face with Lord Grim, who had charged straight over, creating an extremely awkward situation.

Run!

Upon seeing the distance between the two of them, Li Xuan knew that he had no time to cast his skills, and could only run away again to find a better position.

But this time, it wasn’t so easy for him to escape. Lord Grim’s various movement skills were put on full display, and in that instant, his explosive speed wasn’t something that a Ghostblade could compare to at all.

His once faraway opponent had very quickly begun to latch on to him.

Li Xuan immediately realized that Lord Grim’s earlier burst of speed that had exceeded his expectations could really end up being the factor that decided victory and defeat! Because of that one moment, he had been passive at every step, and Ye Xiu had never given him the chance to summon his Ghost Boundaries again. And now, Ye Xiu had already succeeded in latching on to him. In this battle, as the number one Phantom Demon, Crying Devil had surprisingly not laid down even a single Ghost Boundary.

Wasn’t this just too laughable?

Earthquake Sword!

Crying Devil suddenly turned his body, sending an Earthquake Sword towards Lord Grim, who was chasing him from behind.

Lord Grim jumped lightly, dodging the attack.

Moonlight Slash, Full Moonlight Slash!

The two skills slashed out in succession.

“Stop struggling!” While controlling Lord Grim to dodge, Ye Xiu still had time to send this message in the global channel. Evidently, this attack really didn’t pose much of a threat towards him.

But at this time, Crying Devil unexpectedly started casting. Surprisingly, he was trying to forcefully summon a Ghost Boundary.

In the end, Ye Xiu completely ignored it, and Lord Grim charged forth!

The Ghost Boundary was summoned.

Crying Devil had unexpectedly managed to summon a Ghost Boundary, but……

Sword Boundary… It raised the Strength and Intelligence of characters, but it didn’t have any direct effect that restrained an opponent. At the same time as the Sword Boundary was completed, Lord Grim’s sword had already reached Crying Devil’s head.

“You’re too obsessive!” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Yeah, if I couldn’t even lay down one Ghost Boundary, that would just be too outrageous…” Li Xuan replied.

The Sword Boundary that he laid down was the only Ghost Boundary he’d managed to cast the entire match, but it didn’t have any real influence on the battle. Afterwards, Lord Grim latched onto Crying Devil like glue, not giving him another opportunity until he finally fell.

It looked as if Ye Xiu had taken the first victory effortlessly, and it seemed as if the so-called “First Phantom Demon” didn’t pose any real threat to him. Yet, real experts wouldn’t have that kind of opinion.

In this round, it had really been one move that decided victory or defeat. Now, because Lord Grim had managed to latch onto Crying Devil, it looked as if he had effortlessly obtained victory. But if at the very first step, Crying Devil had managed to use Ghost Boundaries to restrain Lord Grim, it could very well be that everyone would be watching Crying Devil effortlessly dispatch Lord Grim.

And the real factor that decided that one moment were the countless actions that the two sides had taken before that. The essence of the match was the decisions that the two had made without seeing their opponent at all, instead relying purely on their awareness and experience to make all kinds of judgements. But to most of the audience, a match like this, with no real head-to-head combat wasn’t worth watching at all.

Void’s supporters in the stadium were evidently somewhat dissatisfied with Li Xuan’s performance. But this was their captain, their core player, so everyone still gave him a bit more face. When Li Xuan stepped down from the stage, sparse clapping could still be heard from the crowd. But Void’s so-called “Plan of Counterattack” really wasn’t off to a good start, the very first point had already been lost. In a matter of minutes, Void’s home stadium, which had originally been a flurry of excitement and energy now had a slightly depressed mood to it.

At this stage, every single point was extremely valuable.

Quite a few spectators were listening to the outcomes of other matches while watching the competition unfold in front of them. For Void to enter the playoffs, it was no longer purely dependent on their own effort. They also needed to rely on the misfortune of other teams in order to snatch a place for themselves.

As their first individual round finished, there was some news about the other matches going on at the same time.

Team Wind Howl was already up 1-0 against Thunderclap, Hundred Blossoms was up 1-0 against Misty Rain, and 301 was up 1-0 against Miracle. Everyone else was winning, only Void had lost this one point.

Was there no hope left?

Everyone silently watched the players go onstage for the second round of the individual competition, and rigid applause filled the air. To the fans of Team Void, losing this one point was as bitter and painful as losing ten points. Even if they saw that they had a better chance of winning in the second individual round, they still weren’t able to drum up much enthusiasm.

In the second round of the individual competition, Happy’s Luo Ji was against Void’s Ge Caijie.

Their ages weren’t too far apart, and they could both be considered young in the Glory circle. But where Luo Ji had only just begun to temper himself in real competitions, Ge Caijie had already displayed the air of a general in the last season, cementing himself as an important member of Team Void.

Ge Caijie very calmly entered the player booths, but what about Luo Ji? His facade of calmness was only to cover up the nervousness he felt in his heart.

It really could be said that he had to summon all his courage to take up the responsibility of competing in this round. He had already begun feeling some anxiety in his heart from yesterday, and until now, it hadn’t subsided at all. He didn’t know when he would be able to get rid of these feelings of nervousness. All he knew was that upon understanding that Happy’s situation was somewhat dire, his heart began jumping even more fiercely.

It was a pity that the referee didn’t care for such things. Upon seeing the two players enter the player booths and the characters loading in, the second round of the individual competition quickly began.

The moment his character loaded in, Luo Ji promptly examined the map.

Hamlet was a map with nice scenery, with red clouds floating in the horizon. In the middle of the map, there was a main street, and at the end of the street, he could see Ge Caijie’s Blue Exorcist already walking over steadily, at a pace that was neither fast nor slow.

Luo Ji immediately controlled Concealed Light to take a roundabout route, hiding behind a straw house. He still didn’t have any confidence when it came to taking on a professional player in a head-on fight, so he persisted with using tactics in every round. If he was playing a home game, with the ability to choose his map, things were a lot smoother, but in an away game, where he was faced with a map that he wasn’t familiar with, it only made him more flustered.

Unfortunately, this map happened to be one that Luo Ji wasn’t familiar with. After temporarily having Concealed Light hide, Luo Ji momentarily had no clue as to what to do next.

He controlled Concealed Light to sneakily stick out his head, taking a look at the main road, only to realize that Blue Exorcist had already disappeared. At this moment, Luo Ji had even less of a clue as to what to do next.

Go out?

Stay at his position and wait?

Opponents that could fight directly and tactically created a lot of difficulties for Luo Ji.

His calculation skills were not bad to begin with, but when his opponent had adopted a pace that was neither fast nor slow from the start, he had no way of determining how quickly his opponent would arrive. Now that his opponent had clearly opted to take a tactical approach, Luo Ji also had no way of figuring out which corner of the hamlet his opponent had hidden in.

It seemed as if he could only rely on careful observation and thorough preparations now.

Luo Ji started to line up his Summons. He definitely wasn’t a player that didn’t use his brain. Seeing as he wasn’t familiar with the entire map, then he would have to understand it one part at a time, and then use those parts to establish his battlefield, making full use of the map’s features.

Luo Ji controlled Concealed light, quickly and carefully observing this corner of the map.

His Spirit Cat was the first to be sent out, moving and hiding in an underbrush in front of him.

Afterwards, the Devil World Flowers were planted behind a tree. From the direction that Blue Exorcist was coming from, it probably wouldn’t be within his field of view.

Afterwards, his Young Wyvern and Thunder Eagle split up and flew to the roofs of the straw houses to his left and right.

Afterwards, Concealed Light himself holed up in the straw house on the left. The house didn’t have a window, and Luo Ji’s actions were as if he wanted to dig a hole for Concealed Light to hide in.

The entire audience was stunned.

Wasn’t this supposed to be a fighting game? Why was it being played this way?

Chapter 1354 - Decided by Details

Seeing Luo Ji’s careful arrangement, the Void fans were on the verge of collapse.

What kind of people were these Happy players? What the hell was all this? This was an official match, you know? What were you taking it as, Carrot Fantasy or Plants versus Zombies or something? Seeing the summon creatures scattered across the map, it didn’t seem like Glory anymore, but some sort of tower defense game.

However, Luo Ji didn’t seem to notice at all. Concealed Light poked a hole in the wall of the straw hut and looked out through the hole.

The Void fans in the stadium were restless. They had an omniscient view, so they were even more clear on Blue Exorcist’s movements than Luo ji. Blue Exorcist really was approaching in this direction. Seeing his progress, it wouldn’t be long before he entered the formation Luo Ji had set. Though everyone looked upon this tower defense-like setup with contempt, but it also seemed very powerful.

Ge Caijie… wouldn’t lose to this rookie would he?

The Void fans began to worry. After Li Xuan had lost the first match they were disappointed like they had just lost ten points, their focus had subconsciously shifted as the match began, and they began to worry that Ge Caijie might walk into a trap. 　 He’s close! 　 On the big screen, it was showing Concealed Light’s view from where he was looking through the hole. Ge Caijie’s Blue Exorcist strolled right into view, looking completely unsuspecting.

The audience felt their heart in knots, many of them yelling, but none of it could be heard by the players in the booths.

However, Ge Caijie seemed to realize that it wasn’t logical that he still hadn’t seen hide nor hair of Concealed Light from this position. Blue Exorcist slowed his movement speed slightly.

Step by step, carefully now. 　 However, Luo Ji was very patient. Although his heart was already jumping into his throat, he held himself still. He believed that this was his only chance for victory; he had to grasp it. His fingers were a little stiff from nerves, but his mechanics couldn’t go wrong.

From Luo Ji’s view, everyone had realized what he was doing.

Under the default settings, summon creatures would attack anyone who came within their aggro range. However, a summoner could command their summons to defend. That way, they would only attack those that came within attack range or those that attacked them first. They wouldn’t initiate combat or pursue targets. However, that wasn’t all that Luo Ji was doing with his summons. He was suppressing even the attacks that would be released when a target came within attack range. There was no setting for this, so if one wished to accomplish it, they could only continuously order their summons to defend.

This was, of course, to make sure that his target was as deeply positioned within the formation as possible before attacking. However, if you wanted to suppress these attacks, you had to repeat actions at a certain rhythm. This sort of thing, for pro players, wasn’t anything hard, but Luo Ji was nervous! His fingers were stiff, and he wasn’t all that practiced at this sort of repetitive mechanics. It didn’t feel like his fingers were actually his. By this time, Blue Exorcist had already gotten rather deep into range and the audience was cursing up a storm, but Luo Ji didn’t think it was enough; his opponent hadn’t gotten to prime position yet! However, he really couldn’t continue with this repetitive actions that pro players shouldn’t find very hard. His stiff fingers broke rhythm.

Swoosh!

The ones to attack first was the Devil World Flower, hiding behind a tree. A vine creeped out of the ground and curled towards Blue Exorcist’s leg. Luo Ji, seeing this, knew that he was at his limit and couldn’t help but be overwhelmed by disappointment. But, at a time like this, he might as well hurry and attack.

With Devil World Flower launching the assault, Young Wyvern and Thunder Eagle on the rooftops to the left and right also flew into the sky automatically, one spat a fireball down and the other spat a thunderbolt. Spirit Cat was a melee summon creature, so after telling it to defend, it wouldn’t move. Luo Ji immediately cancelled his defend order and then had Concealed Light begin casting to summon Frost Wolf.

Ice Wolf was relatively large in size and didn’t have an appropriate hiding place in this area, so Luo Ji had Concealed Light summon directly.

Outside of the straw hut, Devil World Flowers’ attack had come far too suddenly and by the time Ge Caijie noticed, hurriedly having his Aqua jump to dodge, it was too late. The vine whipped up, grabbing the limb it had caught and sending Blue Exorcist crashing back to the ground. 　 He couldn’t move!

That was the side effect that the vine attack came with. Devil World Flower was extremely annoying because it had such an effect.

Boom boom!

A fireball from one side and a thunderbolt from the other crashed down.

Blue Exorcist, unable to move, could only twist his body to dodge. However, he couldn’t dodge them completely like this and immediately, flames and electricity scorched his body. 　 Whirlwind!

Ge Caijie was very decisive as well, knowing that it wasn’t the time to save up his skills. Blue Exorcist brandished his battle scythe, whirling it around and around. The vines of Devil World Flowers were like individual characters, having their own HP gauge. Once you used attacks to deplete its health, it would immediately break. Blue Exorcist ate another fireball and thunderbolt, but regained his movement, immediately lunging into a charge.

He had already figured out the position of Devil World Flower. This summons had the strongest CC. Ge Caijie could tell that Blue Exorcist was too deep in his opponent’s formation. Trying to escape Devil World Flowers wasn’t the best choice at a time like this; killing it first would be the best option.

Swoosh! 　 Another spike stabbed up from the ground. Devil World Flower’s attacks were considered very troublesome precisely because of how concealed they were. However, Ge Caijie’s Blue Exorcist was already leaping up to dodge it. He was extremely calm, and even when surrounded like this, he could still make clear judgements on when Devil World Flower would attack.

The airborne Blue Exorcist already had a third of the Devil World Flower in view, his scythe raised and about to strike when suddenly, with a howl and a breath of cold, Frost Wolf lunged from the side and tackling him to the ground. 　 Concealed Light had also followed Frost Wolf out of the straw hut. Even though it was safer to hide inside the straw hut, his vision was limited and therefore would be limited in his control over his summon creatures. For example, if Concealed Light had been in the straw hut for Frost Wolf’s lunge, then he could only depend on the system-automated attacks and it probably wouldn’t have been timed so well. Summons on auto were rather dumb, knowing only to attack and attack and attack. They wouldn’t synchronize their actions and work with allies, and definitely wouldn’t time their attacks. Thus, Concealed Light showed himself, and Luo Ji would use this field of vision to carefully control his summons and make sure Blue Exorcist didn’t get another chance to escape. 　 Blue Exorcist, tackled to the ground and torn at by Frost Wolf, had been slowed. With two explosions, the airborne Young Wyvern and Thunder Eagle once again spat out their fireball and thunderbolt. Spirit Cat and already arrived as well. It was only by Luo Ji’s orders that it had yet to attack, leaving the tackle to Frost Wolf. Now, with the situation under control, Spirit Cat was free to come up and make its DPS contributions.

Blue Exorcist rolled on the ground, dodging the attacks from the four Beasts, occasionally jumping up to avoid Devil World Flower’s sneak attacks from below. However, under the control of its summoner, Devil World Flower wouldn’t necessarily attack according its set rhythm any longer. Considering Luo Ji’s IQ, there was no way he’d let Ge Caijie use the set rhythm to his advantage and Devil World Flower began choosing the worst moments to attack. Blue Exorcist jumped to dodge five times and failed four times, beaten.

“Good job!” Chen Guo was so excited! If Luo Ji could win, then that was already very impressive, let alone being able to control the situation so fully. With Blue Exorcist surrounded by summons like this, there probably wouldn’t be any chances to turn the tables, right?

Luo Ji’s confidence was steadily growing as well. His tactics were very successful, managing to trap even Ge Caijie, a young and composed player. This was definitely a boost to his morale. Luo Ji had his summons attack relentlessly, relaxing more and more. He slowly regained feeling in his stiff fingers and Luo Ji suddenly thought, this actually wasn’t so hard.

Who would’ve thought that at that exact moment, Blue Exorcist managed to grasp an opening, his scythe twirling around and blue light shining on the ground…

Not good! Rising Emblem!

Luo Ji was startled. Blue Exorcist’s successful attack was naturally because an opening had appeared amongst the four beasts around him. Luo Ji hurriedly had Devil World Flower attack, but as he did so, he was stunned by a sudden realization. 　 Blue Exorcist was no longer within Devil World Flower’s range.

Though it seemed like Blue Exorcist was been crushed by the encirclement of the four beasts and Devil World Flower, he had been carefully moving out of Devil World Flower’s range. It was just that Ge Caijie had been carefully concealing this movement amongst the four beasts’ attacks and Luo Ji, in the end, didn’t have enough experience, allowing this movement to go unnoticed until Blue Exorcist had moved out of range and grasped an opportunity to counterattack.

Whoosh! 　 Blue light rose from the ground, shooting towards the sky. Luo Ji desperately had his Four Summon Beasts dodge out of range, but he was too late for all of them. No matter if it was Spirit Cat and Frost Wolf on the ground, or Young Wyvern and Thunder Eagle in the sky, they were all within range of Rising Emblem. In that moment, they were all thrown upwards.

Blue Exorcist ignored them, lunging for Concealed Light, yet the scythe in his hand was thrown out with Spiritual Guidance, heading for Devil World Flower.

Boom! 　 The scythe also had an Explosive Talisman stuck to it, and Devil World Flower was instantly enveloped in a ball of flame. Fire element attacks dealt a huge amount of bonus damage to Devil World Flower, too. Just this one attack had Devil World Flower charred and blackened, unable to continue.

Blue Exorcist continued to approach Concealed Light, empty-handed. He brandished his right hand through the air and formed another talisman while his left hand stretched out, catching the scythe returning from Spiritual Guidance.

It’s over…

Seeing Ge Caijie’s smooth attack combo, Luo Ji sighed in acceptance. Concealed Light’s summon creatures had all been left behind. Right now, what else could he do? He wouldn’t have the chance to cast and summon again. As for the four beasts, their time was coming to an end and they would soon disappear.

His opponent had considered all the details and currently, Luo Ji, really had no way of turning this around.

Pay attention to the details!

When Concealed Light finally fell, Luo Ji was feeling rather depressed. This had originally been his forte, but this time, it was where he had lost.

Chapter 1355 - Battle of Nightwalkers

1355 Battle of Nightwalkers

Ge Caijie’s counterattack succeeded, and he won the battle. Void’s fans in the audience were jumping and cheering in joy.

Walking offstage in this sort of atmosphere only made Luo Ji feel even more upset.

The huge digital display kept replaying the moment where Blue Exorcist leapt out of range of the Devil World Flowers, and then used a Rising Emblem to counterattack, successfully killing Concealed Light. It was Void’s home stadium, after all! Of course they would replay their own player’s soul-stirring moments for everyone to enjoy. Another wave of applause rose within the stadium.

I was so close…

Watching these images, Luo Ji’s heart felt a wholly different emotion.

He actually hadn’t noticed at all, when Blue Rain jumped out of Devil World Flowers’ range. Pay attention to the details, pay attention to all of the details, this was supposed to be his specialty, his greatest strength, but just then he had overlooked such a key point, something so important that it couldn’t even be called a detail.

Luo Ji truly couldn’t forgive himself, especially for such an important match. He had held the advantage, but because of such a big mistake, he ruined his victory.

When Luo Ji arrived back at the player area, he couldn’t even bear to lift his head.

“It’s nothing,” said Ye Xiu. “It’s just a mistake, everyone makes them. When Old Wei was your age, his mistakes were much worse than yours.”

“Oh, fuck off. When I was his age, Glory probably didn’t even exist yet, did it?” Wei Chen said to Ye Xiu angrily.

“Oh? Really? Want to calculate it?” said Ye Xiu.

“I don’t want to look into this question,” Wei Chen said with a wave of his hand.

Standing to the side, Luo Ji knew that these two seniors’ light-hearted bickering was all to comfort him. He felt moved, but he couldn’t just brush this off like it didn’t matter.

“It won’t happen again.” Luo Ji solemnly expressed his determination.

“No…” But Ye Xiu shook his head. “I’m serious, don’t let this weigh you down. No matter how much you pay attention, mistakes can never be avoided completely. In fact, you can easily become too tense and do even worse. Relax. As long as you focus, pursue victory, work your hardest to do the best you can, maintain this kind of conviction, that’s enough. Don’t worry too much about the little details like mistakes.”

Again, he was supposed to stop worrying about the little details? Still, Luo Ji understood what Ye Xiu was trying to say.

Focus?

Maybe this was where his problem lay in this match!

In the instant when Blue Exorcist had fallen into the encirclement and been knocked over by Frost Wolf, Luo Ji had also fallen into an encirclement, one of happiness. In that situation, it seemed like all of his focus had gone to feeling happy, hence how he had overlooked something so important.

I really haven’t seen enough of the world!

Luo Ji mocked himself, knowing that this was because his match experience was still lacking. What kind of player would get so happy after just one successful attack?

Luo Ji continued to think quietly as he returned to his seat. But as soon as he sat down, a hand came down hard upon his shoulder.

“You played pretty well!” Steamed Bun praised him loudly, wearing a proud expression, as though it were the result of his own work.

Luo Ji had no idea what to say in response to Steamed Bun’s words.

“That defending radishes playstyle of yours seems really strong,” Steamed Bun continued.

Defend… defending radishes. What did that even mean?

Luo Ji was so agitated that he actually stood back up again, but seeing Steamed Bun’s serious face, he quickly felt discouraged. When did Steamed Bun ever make sense? Whatever he said, just accept it!

But. Defending radishes. Luo Ji still felt rather baffled.

It was now the third match of the individual competition. Happy sent up Wei Chen, while Void sent their Assassin player, Li Xun.

Li Xun was originally the most famed user of Life-Risking Strike, but ever since Yang Cong changed his strategy, he gradually became more overlooked. Yang Cong used Life-Risking Strike more frequently, and his success rate left Li Xun in the dust, especially when he used it in the team competition.

Even though Yang Cong was gradually stepping down from his position, he remained a main attacker for 301. Even if 301 wanted to use Life-Risking Strike, their strategy would still revolve around him. But Li Xun in Void didn’t have such privilege. Void’s core was the Ghost Duo, and all strategies revolved around those two players. Li Xun’s Life-Risking Strike was his own decision in individual battle, but in the team battles, unlike Yang Cong, he didn’t have a whole team serving his needs.

I never knew that Life-Risking Strike could be used to this level!

Li Xun, who especially loved this skill, felt all sorts of longing in his heart when he saw 301’s playstyle. But he knew that Void wouldn’t give him that kind of environment very often.

Only in the individual competition could he run freely. But Li Xun already didn’t pass up any opportunity to use it there. What he really wanted was to use it in the team competition. That feeling of taking out the opponent’s core or important character with one attack, trading his tragic death for the team’s victory, Li Xun felt a thrill just thinking about it.

It’s just… too bad!

Li Xun sighed. He could probably only continue to seize his chances in individual battle.

The third match of the individual competition began. Since Li Xun was this kind of Assassin, of course he chose a more complicated map.

This was another street map. Void was generally good at such maps, which wasn’t unrelated to the fact that their core was a Phantom Demon. This kind of map was good for Phantom Demons, so Void often chose such maps during team competition. After a long time, they would begin to like such maps for individual battles as well.

The characters loaded in and the match began. A Warlock on one side and an Assassin on the other, both Nightwalkers. They both started moving strategically from the very start, ducking into alleys and slowly moving forward.

Wei Chen, Windward Formation…

Before the match, Li Xun hadn’t expected that he would meet this player from Happy, so he hadn’t really prepared for this. For such a critical match, Happy was still brave enough to use a player that hadn’t really gone onstage much this season. This was a rather unexpected move.

Wei Chen had basically been overlooked in Void’s preparations for this match. But even if they had paid attention to him, they didn’t have much to work off of. There was only so much information to be found about a player who had appeared so infrequently. It wasn’t like they could dig up old Blue Rain matches from Seasons 1 and 2 a decade ago, could they? The Glory competitive scene was tied to the game itself. Skills and tactics were constantly updating, becoming stronger and more extravagant. Ten years ago, levels were capped at 50, 55, there were fewer skills, and current playstyles had evolved so much since then. And with the Level 75 update, with the addition of Level 75 equipment and skills, even data from just a few years ago had to be scrutinized with care. Some playstyles had grown extinct because of new equipment or skills.

About Wei Chen and Windward Formation, there were only two phrases in Li Xun’s mind.

Dirty playing. Cast range.

Yes, dirty playing!

This Warlock was truly very dirty. This sort of match attitude couldn’t be erased by new strategies or skills. It was like how Fang Rui was still dirty even after changing classes to Qi Master.

It was really hard to imagine. The old Swoksaar was actually a dirty-playing Warlock? Li Xun tried to compare Wei Chen and the current user of Swoksaar, Yu Wenzhou, and instantly shuddered.

The difference was too great!

Li Xun thought.

In general, when teams searched for someone to inherit such an important character, they would try and choose someone with a similar style. That way, the team’s overall style wouldn’t have to change much, and the transition would be smoother. But Blue Rain, this… Li Xun honestly had no idea how they’d transitioned. Wasn’t there another person between Wei Chen and Yu Wenzhou at the time?

Was that person both dirty-playing and hand-crippled?

To Li Xun, Season 3 was a long time ago, and he wasn’t a Blue Rain fan, so he didn’t really know much about this extra Swoksaar user hidden in Blue Rain’s history. Even Wei Chen – if he hadn’t jumped back into the spotlight by joining Happy, how many young players would know about this old senior from Blue Rain?

Against dirty-playing guy, he couldn’t become overconfident. Especially since this guy had that massive cast range. Li Xun couldn’t let himself die without even managing to touch him.

Li Xun’s Assassin Ghost Lantern walked along the streets, quickly arriving at his planned destination. And then Ghost Lantern jumped up, displaying the Assassin’s special passive skill Air Jump. Jumping with his left and then right foot, he easily hopped atop this small two-story building.

The roof was spacious. Although it wasn’t very high up, the angle and field of view from this position were really quite good. From here, many regions on this map could be examined. As soon as Ghost Lantern jumped on here, Li Xun found where Windward Formation was.

He’s taking the middle road!

Li Xun silently watched for a while, judging what Wei Chen’s plans were.

Windward Formation was using the most standard method of strategic movement, heading toward the map’s center in a roundabout way, finding the target so a sneak attack could be launched from the side or back.

But too bad, I’m over here!

Li Xun’s Ghost Lantern crouched on the rooftop, and he continued to silently study Windward Formation as the character appeared and disappeared. Finally, Li Xun made his judgment and Ghost Lantern gently jumped from the roof, directly landing upon another two-story rooftop across the street, and then directly headed toward where Windward Formation was.

“Hm? How come I don’t see anyone, the little guy’s hiding?” At this time, a message from Wei Chen arrived in the chat.

Dirty playing, as expected!

Dirty-playing guys always liked saying a few words in the chat to rile up the opponent. Speaking of this style, Blue Rain had really succeeded in carrying it on. But Huang Shaotian’s method was entirely different from the dirty-playing style of riling up. His method was just straight-up bombing the opponent to exhaustion!

What in the world had happened in Blue Rain? How had the senior’s talents been passed on like this? No more dirty plays, but the trash talking became so frenzied.

As Li Xun controlled Ghost Lantern forward, he actually grew quite curious about Blue Rain’s past. He even made the decision, next time he met Blue Rain, he had to ask about their story. As for whatever Wei Chen said after that, apologies, but he didn’t look! It was just trash talk, who wanted to see it?

Li Xun chose to ignore it, and his gaze didn’t even wander toward the chat window.

Ghost Lantern continued to move, and finally, Windward Formation’s sneaky-looking posture clearly appeared in front of him. Ghost Lantern rolled onto the ground. From now on, his movements needed to be even more careful.

How should he go about this? If he directly went up and used a Life-Risking Strike, could that take care of him?

As soon as he thought of this possibility, Li Xun instantly became fired up.

Chapter 1356 - A Casual Poke

1356 A Casual Poke

Updated by NovelFull.Com

Closing in, step by step. Right now, the entire stadium’s feeling’s were bound to Ghost Lantern’s movement. On screen, everyone saw from Li Xun’s point of view. Windward Formation’s outline became larger and clearer.

Closer and closer.

Life-Risking Strike!

Almost everyone had this thought, since they were familiar with Li Xun’s style. This was a player who would always pursue a kill with Life-Risking Strike.

But could he do it this time?

This really needed to be considered. Just judging from their life totals, Ghost Lantern was capable of assassinating Windward Formation with a Life-Risking Strike. However, would Windward Formation’s equipment affect the outcome?

Armor values weren’t useful. Life-Risking Strike traded hitpoint for hitpoint; it removed health directly and ignored armor. However, what if Windward Formation’s armor had damage absorption effects? Damage absorption would be able to reduce incoming health removal from Life-Risking Strike. If the absorption percentage was high enough, then this skill wouldn’t be able to directly kill Windward Formation.

Unfortunately, Void had no such information on the Silver equipment on Windward Formation, since their team lacked information and research on both Wei Chen and Windward Formation. Li Xun could only rely on his own judgement.

When directly comparing health values, Ghost Lantern was 12% higher than Windward Formation. The Assassin’s HP stat growth was below average. Ghost Lantern’s equipment had some additional HP boosts; it was necessary for someone who loved Life-Risking Strike, where the damage output scaled with HP. The difference was that the HP was not stacked as high as possible like normal players would do, with disregard to anything else; Void did not want him to just focus on Life-Risking Strike and needed him to contribute in other ways too.

Right now, his health points were 12% higher than Windward Formation’s. This meant that if Windward Formation’s equipment carried more than 12% damage absorption, he could survive Ghost Lantern’s Life-Risking Strike; if not, then Life-Risking Strike would be a one-hit kill.

Maybe attack a few times and do a calculation first?

It’s possible an opportunity like this would not arise again. The opponent had a dirty playstyle, and all pro players knew how hard it was to successfully ambush a dirty player. Li Xun really just didn’t want to give up this huge opportunity that presented itself before him.

Take a shot at it?

Li Xun pondered. 12% damage absorption was not high. However, Warlocks wore Cloth armor and had subpar defensive attributes. This meant not just basic defence values, but also other defensive attributes, such as armor values and damage absorption values. Cloth armors were the worst in this aspect, amongst all other armor types.

A lowly 12%. However, for it to appear on Cloth armor, quite a chunk of other useful attributes might have been traded off for it. Would a Warlock sacrifice these useful attributes for some extra survivability?

This was really hard to say; after all, survivability was useful for any class and couldn’t be considered a waste. So did Windward Formation have it?

Ghost Lantern’s movement grinded to a halt. Li Xun could not reach a conclusion and did not advance any further. If he kept going, he would have to act.

Equipment chosen by someone who loved playing dirty. Would he prioritize attributes like damage absorption?

Li Xun was trying to answer the question from perspective of the opponent’s playstyle. However, before he could reach any conclusion, Li Xun suddenly remembered something else.

Cast range!

Windward Formation’s biggest distinctive feature was his absurdly long cast range.

A long cast range meant a big attack area, which also meant a larger protective zone. A Warlock that had an advantage in that aspect, would he need more protective measures? Would he?

He shouldn’t need it!

Li Xun’s mind was made. It wasn’t from the opponent’s playstyle, but rather from his character’s specialty. Then, let’s go!

Ghost Lantern once again began his advance. He leapt down from a rooftop and landed in a half-crouch soundlessly, then patiently stalked forward.

Patient bastard, I’m behind you!

Li Xun couldn’t resist complaining to himself after seeing that Wei Chen seemed to be patiently and cluelessly waiting for his target to appear. Ghost Lantern approached, step by step.

Finally, he ran out of cover and could only approach directly from behind. There were only a few steps left, but the closer he got, the more nervous Li Xun got. If the opponent suddenly turned around now, then it would all have been for naught.

Approach with a Shining Cut or continue slowly moving?

The two options crossed Li Xun’s mind, and he made his decision in a split second.

At this time, Li Xun decided it was better to be fast about it. He didn’t want to risk all his work being wasted after coming this far.

Shining Cut!

Immediately, a cold light flashed out, along with the fluttering of cloth in the wind. Ghost Lantern had already abruptly flashed behind Windward Formation.

Life-Risking Strike!

Life-Risking Strike as expected. Li Xun boldly used this skill to directly decide the match.

Windward Formation hastily turned around after hearing the sound behind him, but Ghost Lantern’s dagger had already arrived. Fueled by his own life, a one-hit-kill assassination skill from Ghost Lantern. Fierce, powerful. Windward Formation’s reaction was meaningless. Turning around only presented his chest to be stabbed by Ghost Lantern’s dagger.

Shluck!

A hair-raising sound was produced as the dagger buried itself deep into Windward Formation’s chest. However, an ominous feeling arose in Li Xun’s mind.

Something’s off, something’s really off! Something had to be off!

The attack hit, and Windward Formation’s health-bar slid down quickly. However, Li Xun felt something went terribly wrong. His intuition told him that he shouldn’t stay here and pose; he needed to turn tail and run.

But… Windward Formation’s arm was already raised. Death’s Hand casually poked at a random spot on Ghost Lantern’s body.

He fell…

Ghost Lantern fell.

Life-Risking Strike left the user with 1 hit-point. That meant that even a normal melee attack from a Warlock’s staff was enough to kill him. For Windward Formation to be able to carry out that attack, however, it only meant one thing: Life-Risking Strike did not one-shot him.

Miscalculation.

Li Xun only had regret in his mind, but it was all too late. Ghost Lantern’s 1 hit-point was not enough to handle anything, and a poke from his opponent’s staff dispatched him.

How ludicrous.

No skills were used, and a regular poke ended the match? He really handed himself to his opponent…

Yes, he did. Handed himself on a silver platter.

Everything suddenly became clear to Li Xun. The opponent planned his whole strategy around his playstyle and gave him an opportunity to use Life-Risking Strike. Li Xun knew something was wrong, but now he knew exactly what. It was his opponent’s reaction.

This was the Pro League. They were all pro players with unmatched experience. Even for someone who had not played for a long time, being part of the Pro League meant his Glory experience was richer than a regular player.

Just then when Ghost Lantern charged forth with Shining Cut, what was the opponent’s reaction when he heard it? He turned around.

He actually turned around!

This was way too much of a rookie’s reaction. Any Glory player who had some PK experience would know to dodge instead of turn around if they felt something was off behind themselves.

Roll, jump, strafe, rush forward, or use a skill. Anything was fine, but there was no reason to turn around. What would that do? If they saw your poor face, would they suddenly feel a rush of sympathy and stop their attack?

As it turned out, Windward Formation’s reaction was to turn around.

Even though he barely made an appearance this season, wasn’t it laughable for this antique of a player with more than ten years’ experience in Glory to turn around in this situation?

Not realising immediately was absolutely moronic.

Turning around at that time meant Wei Chen was prepared way ahead of time. Wei Chen already had a plan in mind, so when the attack came, he did not dodge or retreat but turned around. When Life-Risking Strike hit, he just casually poked away.

I got fucking poked to death! Li Xun clutched his head and wished he could stuff his whole head into his monitor.

I got played, completely played!

If he realised a split second earlier, there was still time to cancel the attack.But he didn’t; he completely missed it. At the time, he was already immersed in the elation of winning the match with one strike.

Turns out, the match really did end, not with his one strike, but the opponent’s one poke.

A Warlock. Raised his staff. And poked. Thinking of this, Li Xun once again felt the urge to stuff his head into his monitor.

Thus, the third match of the individual competition was concluded.

It hadn’t sunk in for the whole stadium yet. It hadn’t even sunk in for the referee. Wei Chen appeared from his player booth, grinning ear to ear, and waved at everyone watching.

This isn’t Happy’s home stadium!

The audience didn’t even have time to feel bad about him winning; who the hell would appreciate him showing off?

Wei Chen was purely trying to stir shit up. He waved his hands the stadium filled with boos. He then left the stage happily amongst the booing.

Boo away to your heart’s content!

Wei Chen looked at this stadium full of people. So what if there were boos? Summoning boos was a special ability for playing an away game. I came, I won. Booing was the proof of that.

Wei Chen returned to Happy’s bench. He glanced at Li Xun on Void’s side, who looked distracted and lost after leaving the stage, and laughed scornfully. He raised his right pinky finger and said, “I can take care of this kind of small fry with my pinky. I hope you can give me more of a challenge next time.”

Everyone laughed, and this time, even Ye Xiu didn’t go burst his bubble.

Taken care of with a pinky? This really was a joke.

Wei Chen put a lot of effort into preparing for the match against Void. Li Xun was someone who would definitely play in the individual competition, since his playstyle was not suitable for the group arena. So for Wei Chen, there was a solid one in three chance that Li Xun was his opponent, and thus researched him a lot.

Fortunately, he did run into Li Xun in the individual competition, and everything indeed went according to his plan. This was the reason why he could topple Li Xun with just his pinky.

Small tricks. This was a specially targeted trick, and most likely wouldn’t work again. The problem was, an old player like Wei Chen had more than ten years of experience and who knew how many more tricks he had up his sleeve! You would be underestimating him if you expected him to repeat the same trick twice.

Chapter 1356 - Void’s Send-off

The Void fans in the audience booed Wei Chen for a very long time. But when they looked at the screen displaying the current score, they felt another wave of despondence.

1 to 2, they’d already lost 2 points. Void was already far away from the top 8, and after losing these two points, their future was becoming increasingly bleak.

Next was the group arena. Happy sent Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Fang Rui, while Void sent Ge Zhaolan, Yang Haoxuan, and Wu Yuce.

There were still fans who refused to give up now, and they persevered in cheering Void on. But Tang Rou’s performance when she came on was extraordinarily strong, nearly a 1v2. After Steamed Bun came one, he used 17% of his health to take care of Void’s second player, Yang Haoxuan, who’d already been beaten bloody by Tang Rou.

Wu Yuce came out, facing a near 1v2 situation. The crowd was quiet; they couldn’t bear to cheer. It looked like Void’s season was ending here just like this. There was no need to increase the pressure on any one person at this time. A season’s failure wasn’t any one person’s fault.

Even the audience members were pessimistic, but Wu Yuce hadn’t given up. He was a pro player, someone who understood the difficulty of matches better than ordinary people did. But at this time, even more so than the audience, he anticipated a miracle. He believed he could create a miracle.

Wu Yuce came onstage, and Carved Ghost cleanly took care of Steamed Bun Invasion.

Fang Rui came onstage, facing a Carved Ghost at half health.

The map was another street map that Void was used to. For the dirty-playing Fang Rui, he could also take to this map like a fish to water.

“This time, I won’t lose to you again,” Fang Rui said after entering the match. During the previous Happy vs Void, Fang Rui had indeed lost to Wu Yuce, but back then he had already fought one person earlier. For the group arena, the fact that he had still managed to knock away half of Carved Ghost’s health was already considered a success.

And this time, his Boundless Sea had the health lead, and his Qi Master style had undergone a season’s worth of testing and was now solidified.

“Give it a try.” Wu Yuce generally wasn’t inclined to chat, but he actually said this tough sentence in the chat. He knew Fang Rui’s strength, especially since they were from the same season. Compared to everyone else, he had gotten to know Fang Rui’s dirty Qi Master style earlier than everyone else. Last time after fighting Happy, Fang Rui had called him to spar for many matches. In the end, it was unclear who had gotten more wins, but Wu Yuce knew for sure: Fang Rui’s new unique playstyle was definitely viable.

The reality confirmed this point. Fang Rui indeed walked a new path with his Qi Master, even though traditional Qi Master players all looked down upon his style. But with Zhao Yang’s retirement, there was no longer one leading Qi Master. This season’s All-Stars, there had been no Qi Master, but what about next year? Next year, given Happy’s strong results and Fang Rui’s performance, this guy could actually enter the All-Stars with the identity of a Qi Master. That would really show everyone who looked down upon this dirty Qi Master style!

You look down upon my playstyle, but I am the number one Qi Master.

When he thought about this, Wu Yuce felt that it was really quite interesting, and he very much wanted to see this happen. However, even so, he did not want to become Fang Rui’s stepping stone. For the sake of Void’s victory, he would not hesitate to block Fang Rui’s way.

I will not lose!

Void’s season is not yet over!

With a roar, with the Phantom God’s power flashing around him, Wu Yuce fought even more fiercely than he had last round.

He… won?

In the instant that the results came out, even the live audience couldn’t believe their eyes.

Wu Yuce’s Carved Ghost remained standing at the very end, with four percent health remaining.

“You…” Fang Rui left this final message in the chat. Dirty players like him could really be helpless against an opponent like this. This kind of guy, bold and decisive, wouldn’t play those psychological games with you dirty players. He would simply use his swordlight to slash through everything.

Void won the group arena. Those Void fans who had already given up suddenly all awakened once more. The crowd exploded like a volcano that had slept dormant for many years, releasing all of their enthusiasm in one instant, powerful enough to burn through everything. When Happy’s three players returned to their player area, they could only shout to communicate with each other. The noise of the stadium was simply too loud.

3-2, now Void was in the lead. If they won the team round, a final result of 8-2, maybe there was still hope?

Wu Yuce’s strong performance didn’t just win two points, it ignited everyone’s hopes for Void.

But, it ends here…

Wu Yuce sighed as he rotated his camera view, seeing his fallen comrades around him.

Blue Exorcist, Soul Defender, Ghost Lantern, Translucent.

“It’s just the two of us left!” Wu Yuce was never one for melancholy, but this time, their season, Void’s season, was ending here.

“Yeah,” said Li Xuan. Standing behind Carved Ghost, back-to-back, was his Crying Devil.

Void’s Ghost Duo. On Void’s side, only these two remained. Even though they were an experienced partnership, expecting them to pull off a 2v5 was simply too much.

Happy had already surrounded them completely, but they weren’t rushing to attack. Crying Devil didn’t have much mana left, so he couldn’t maintain the defense of Ghost Boundaries. They just had to wait until the Ghost Boundaries ran out, and then they could calmly attack them.

“Last one,” Li Xuan said. Crying Devil’s blade surged with the power of the Phantom God as he casted a final Ghost Boundary.

Boom!

But at this moment, Dancing Rain opened fire. Li Xuan was forced to interrupt the cast as he moved to dodge.

“Tsk, our last one’s gone too,” Li Xuan said. Crying Devil’s mana was used up for good.

“So it ends like this!”

“Yeah, it’s over…”

The Ghost Boundaries faded, leaving openings, and Happy’s characters charged forward. Long-range, short-range, they all began their attacks, and Void’s Ghost Duo finally fell upon the ground they had so tightly defended with their Ghost Boundaries for so long.

In the end, Happy won their Round 33 match with a score of 7-3. Void, having only achieved 3 points, could consider themselves finished for the season. Even if their competitors had abysmal performances in the upcoming rounds, with only five rounds left to close such a large point gap, there was no point in imagining what was theoretically possible. Only those who were especially stubborn in refusing to give up would still hope for that extremely unlikely possibility, hope that those competitors wouldn’t earn a single point in the next rounds and that Void would surpass them.

But, would that happen?

The moment that the Void vs Happy match ended, there were already people frantically checking for news from the other matches this round.

Hundred Blossoms, 9-1, a huge home victory against Misty Rain. The gap between them and Void was pulled from 23 to 29 points.

301, a 10-0 perfect victory against Miracle, which pulled their gap with Void from 28 to 35 points.

There was still one match in progress!

It was the match that had received the most attention this round, Thunderclap against Wind Howl.

After Thunderclap lagged behind in the individual matches, 1-4, the two teams were now engaged in a fierce team battle.

Wind Howl’s recent team performance was quite fierce. Their strategy of tearing apart and playing one-on-one had shaken a number of strong teams. Maybe they would win again in this match? If they won 9-1, Thunderclap would have only won one point, and maybe they would just continue to lose and lose, and Void would win and win, and eventually surpass them?

The stubborn Void fans who refused to despair carried these sort of dreams as they studied the details of this match. But in the end, even they had to let go of their last strands of hope.

Thunderclap had taken teamwork to the peak. Individually, their players weren’t all that strong. But they were all team players. They understood strategy well and their cooperative awareness was strong. Once they were together, their strength didn’t lose to that of any team. And Wind Howl? Their new playstyle was the antithesis of Thunderclap’s. Their “cooperation” was to not cooperate. Their method was to turn the team battle into individual battles.

By this point, they had already chopped apart many strong teams, but they finally met their match in Thunderclap. The most cooperative, cohesive team in the entire Alliance wouldn’t be broken apart so easily. Wind Howl messed up, and with their playstyle, one mess-up meant defeat. They had played their best to last this long, but unfortunately for them, Thunderclap still won in the end.

6 to 4.

With the conclusion of this battle, the results of all the teams who were currently fighting for a spot in the playoffs were known.

Void was out for good, but Hundred Blossoms had caught up once again. They were tied with Wind Howl in terms of points, 208, but because they lost to Wind Howl in terms of their head-to-head point scores, they were in ninth place for now.

All of the current rankings were only temporary. The points differences between the teams was worth more attention. Smaller differences could be flipped in the course of one round. After the end of this round, the fifth place team Happy had 219 points, while the eighth and ninth place Wind Howl and Hundred Blossoms had 208 points. This was a difference of only 11 points from fifth to ninth. Happy was directly going against three of these direct competitors in upcoming battles, so this current 11 point lead really wasn’t much.

This round was only one hurdle they’d had to make it through. Void had dropped out, but no team had made it to safety.

The upcoming Round 34 was, for a Happy, a good chance to grab points. Their opponent was Lightly, a weaker team that had no more prospects for this season. Chen Guo wanted to directly add these ten points to Happy’s total.

But Happy’s roster for this round once again gave Chen Guo something to worry about.

“You’re not going in the team competition?” Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu in shock. In the team round’s roster, Ye Xiu and Lord Grim’s names were absent.

“Yes. For these upcoming rounds, I will try to rest as much as possible,” said Ye Xiu.

Chen Guo hesitated. She had worried time and time again about Ye Xiu’s professional life expectancy; she had worried about whether he was working himself too hard. From in-game to the Pro League, from management to strategy, from training to equipment, Ye Xiu was involved in it all. Was he really not tired?

Chen Guo had had these doubts before.

And now, Ye Xiu, using this method, was telling her clearly: he, too, was tired. He, too, needed to rest.

Chapter 1357 - Mistake

Ye Xiu could tire too.

Perhaps sometimes, perseverance would be enough to overcome fatigue, but Chen Guo knew that Ye Xiu did not lack perseverance. He needed to rest for the same reason that he insisted Wei Chen and Luo Ji play matches: he needed to prepare for the playoffs as well. He needed a hundred percent of his energy to face the playoffs.

And now, even though they were stuck in the struggle for top eight, Happy did have the most points out of all their direct competitors.

Chen Guo tried to think optimistically, and when they trained for the team round this week, they practiced without Ye Xiu and Lord Grim.

Soon, May 8th arrived, and Round 34 began.

Happy and the other teams vying for the playoffs underwent their desperate struggle, while the powerhouses at the top were already preparing for the playoffs.

Team Blue Rain was rotating their team battle roster nonstop.

Team Tiny Herb was working hard at strategies that didn’t rely too much on Wang Jiexi.

Team Tyranny’s three old generals ended rotation after that one round where they all appeared. Now, they all played both the individual and team battles.

And this round, Tyranny played a home game against Heavenly Swords.

There weren’t many interactions between these two teams. Tyranny’s fans cheered for their own team, just like normal. But when the names for the first individual battle were announced, the entire stadium froze.

Tyranny, Zhang Jiale.

Heavenly Swords, Sun Zheping.

Team Hundred Blossoms, Blood and Blossoms, one of the most quintessential partnerships of the Alliance. These former partners suddenly met in this match.

Reunited at last, but in a confrontation that had never occurred before.

Neither Tyranny nor Heavenly Swords would care about this one point very much, but the significance these two carried…

Tyranny’s home fans and Heavenly Swords’ visiting fans wouldn’t have the same deep ties to these two that Hundred Blossoms fans would have. But who hadn’t heard of the madness that these two brought, back in the day?

Blood and Blossoms had made its lasting mark in Glory’s history. Even though they ultimately hadn’t managed to win the championship, but in competition, heroes weren’t determined solely by success or failure.

That former prosperity had ended on that summer five long years ago. Since then, the two had never reunited on the battlefield, and there was no more Blood and Blossoms, only victory and defeat.

But the outcome of this one battle truly didn’t matter too much, and when the audience saw this pair of opponents, they didn’t care too much who won or lost. They were more curious about what this duo, who had left behind countless regrets, would say to each other, when they had this sort of meeting on the battlefield.

And so, no one watched the match. Everyone was staring at the chat displayed on the large screen.

Nothing. Nothing at all.

The two had no conversation, no exchange. The characters simply charged forward and met at the center of the map.

Flowers blossomed, concealing Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. But the Berserker’s slashes were no longer creating a scene of blood, and even if they were, it would be the blood of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Charge!

Sun Zheping’s Berserker Another Summer of Sleep once again charged forward. Would anyone understand Zhang Jiale’s playstyle than he? This playstyle relied on the light and shadows created by skills, and those on the same team weren’t immune to these effects. It could impede teammates just as easily as opponents. Sun Zheping, as the partner who had once stood the closest to him amidst this light and shadow, of course understood how to maintain his bearings and search for targets to attack.

But this time, he was searching for the owner of this expanse of light and shadow.

Wild Blood Strike!

The blood-red silhouette of the greatsword instantly carved through the dazzle, and Another Summer of Sleep advanced forward as though there were nothing in his way.

“Oh…” The whole stadium made noises of understanding. From Sun Zheping’s camera view, they could see how the light and shadow didn’t give him any confusion at all. His field of vision was just as clear as always.

As expected! Everyone thought. As expected of former partners. They understood each other too well.

But just in this moment, when Another Summer of Sleep continued to advance, taking one step closer to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, the light and shadow suddenly closed in, enveloping Another Summer of Sleep in their midst.

Is that so?

Sun Zheping rotated his camera view, looking around him in a circle. This time, he couldn’t very much see through it.

So the Hundred Blossoms playstyle had also changed a lot! These years, he’d purposely not paid much attention to it, and now, he was truly beginning to feel that he couldn’t keep up…

But, this shouldn’t be enough to cause him any difficulty, right? He would never forget the logic of this playstyle! It wasn’t too late to learn now!

Another Summer of Sleep looked left and right, as though searching for directions.

The audience watched silently, and Zhang Jiale, controlling the blossoming display, gradually revealed a shocked expression.

This was no longer the Hundred Blossoms style he had used during his time with Sun Zheping. After all, after so many years, the levels, equipment, and skills had all changed so much. But, just over the course of this battle, Sun Zheping’s Another Summer of Sleep caught up. Slowly, step by step, he had already entered the rhythm of the new Hundred Blossoms style.

Sun Zheping, knowing the Hundred Blossoms style so thoroughly, only needed the span of one match.

As expected of old partners. Just like this, Zhang Jiale watched as Another Summer of Sleep finally charged in front of his Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. The greatsword came down without a moment of hesitation – Dazzling Hundred Blossoms leapt aside and counterattacked.

Another Summer of Sleep fell. Charging through the cover of the Hundred Blossoms style was already his limit…

“Good luck.” When he fell, Sun Zheping simply said this.

“Yeah,” Zhang Jiale answered.

The only words exchange in the whole battle…

At the same time, Ye Xiu helped Happy win a first point in the individual competition. Although he was not playing in the team competition this time, he was still first in the individual competition as always.

And then Luo Ji and Wei Chen were up. This time, Luo Ji won, but Wei Chen made a mistake and lost the point. Winning and losing matches was an ordinary thing, but Luo Ji and Wei Chen were in a very delicate position. If they lost points, there would always be people jumping forward to question Happy’s plan, as though if it weren’t for the two of them, if other people fought instead, Happy would be guaranteed to win points.

But nothing was ever guaranteed on a battlefield.

And so even though Wei Chen lost a point, they were open and forgiving.

Then, in the group arena, Happy won a clean victory, entering the team round with a score of 4-1.

When the team competition lineup came out, without Ye Xiu’s name, the crowd burst into whispers.

Beginning to let the main force rest? The team was really confident! Everyone thought this way, but no one was too worried, as Lightly wasn’t a very strong team and didn’t have much fighting spirit.

But in the end, in their home game, Happy lost the team competition.

4-6. The digital scoreboard recorded this all. In this crucial time before the playoffs, Happy lost a team competition.

The reason? Ye Xiu hadn’t played.

No matter what, this point could not be avoided. Core players were simply like this. Even if they weren’t onstage, they had to carry the responsibility of their team’s mistakes. You weren’t onstage! This was your biggest mistake…

Happy paid the price for their arrogance!

This was how multiple media reported it, especially those who liked to hate on Happy. They liked this angle.

After the match, all was quiet in the prep room.

Everyone could see Ye Xiu’s hard work. No matter what, none of Happy’s members would object to Ye Xiu’s choice to rest, even during this crucial time where every point mattered. They were all upset, all blaming themselves, that as soon as Ye Xiu was gone, they lost points.

No one said anything. In the prep room, everyone silently watched the television, which was currently broadcasting the match between Samsara and 301.

To face Samsara during this crucial point-earning period, 301 seemed fairly unlucky. But a number of people felt that perhaps 301 was lucky.

Because no team’s position was more stable than Samsara’s right now. After 33 rounds, they had 282 points, over 42 points above the current second place.

Samsara didn’t need any more points in the regular season. They could casually let their main players rest, train rookies, practice strategies. They faced no pressure.

Perhaps these conditions would give their opponents a precious opportunity. Perhaps a match against Samsara would actually be easier to fight.

301 won two battles in the individual competition. Samsara had sent up their rookies, and everyone believed their hypothesis was correct.

Then, in the group arena, Samsara sent up their strongest lineup as always, and won.

For the team round, they also used their strongest lineup this season. At that moment, although the match had yet to end, 301’s loss was set.

Even with two championships under their belt, Samsara was still hungry for more. They didn’t relax, they didn’t let their team enter a trash or a performative period. They still faced battles with all they had. They continued to strive for victory above all else; they didn’t want to slack off while still sprinting forward.

Let the main players rest? They might not even need it. Samsara’s players were all in their prime. For them, one match a week was no great burden.

Just like that, Samsara still won in the end, 8-2. Samsara did not give 301 a so-called break.

After 34 rounds, Samsara had 290 points, and by now, Blue Rain’s match against Parade had ended, with Blue Rain winning 9-1. But even so, this only shrunk their difference with Samsara from 42 to 41 points.

With four rounds remaining, Samsara led second place by 41 points.

The moment that Samsara won the match, their home stadium burst into cheers and applause louder than any other during this season.

Samsara had earned first place in the regular season, four rounds early. Even though there was no trophy associated with this, this was a still a result to be proud of.

It seemed that Samsara’s home stadium had anticipated this possibility, and so they’d prepared a small celebration ceremony beforehand. Of course, it was just a small ceremony. After all, the season still hadn’t ended, and having a large celebration now would be inconsiderate to the other teams.

Samsara, four rounds early, celebrated a beautiful end to their regular season. Happy, meanwhile, because of their failure this round, continued to struggle in the mud.

This round, their fellow competitors’ results: Wind Howl defeated Royal Style 8-2, Thunderclap defeated Misty Rain 9-1, Hundred Blossoms defeated Void 9-1.

And so Thunderclap, with 226 points, surpassed Happy by 3 points, charging into fifth place and pushing Happy down to sixth. Hundred Blossoms beat Wind Howl by one point, rising to seventh. Wind Howl and 301 were once again tied with points, and based on their head-to-head score, Wind Howl was eighth, and 301 was pushed to ninth.

The situation became more of a deadlock. Happy was only 7 points away from ninth place. And in Round 35, Happy was playing their away game against a strong opponent, the team that had just surpassed them by three points, Thunderclap.

Chapter 1358 - Tide and Xu Bin

Translator: Nomyummi

Editor: Nomyummi

In Round 35, Thunderclap would be playing Happy in their home game. These two teams would be fighting for the number five spot between themselves, so being direct competitors was not key. What was more important were the teams hot on their tails. The loser of this round might fall several spots and be a step closer to the danger zone.

For this round, of the three teams in pursuit, Wind Howl would play Heavenly Swords in an away match; Hundred Blossoms would play Royal Style in an away match, and 301 again faced a powerhouse as they did last round: they would be playing against Tiny Herb.

301 was perched precariously on the edge of the playoffs zone. They were currently out of the standings for the playoffs, and the schedule gave them an even larger obstacle. After this round, they had to face Blue Rain and finally Happy…

The television broadcast for Round 35 faced yet another dilemma: should they show Thunderclap versus Happy, or 301 versus Tiny Herb?

Finally, the broadcasting team decided on 301 versus Tiny Herb. Even though Thunderclap versus Happy was a key match, the two teams had already met and was broadcast once in Round 16. Also, Happy still had plenty of key matches coming: both their Round 37 clash against Wind Howl and Round 38 against 301 were candidates for broadcast.

The broadcasters could only choose one match, but the media focused equally on both. 301 became the primary team to stir things up following the winter transfer window and into the second half of the season. If it weren’t for their sudden surge up the leaderboard, the top 8 would have been pretty much set in stone, after seeing the performances of teams just out of reach such as Void or Misty Rain.

Since 301 could stir things up, they became well received by the many enthusiastic Glory fans. Because of this, they managed to attract many otherwise-neutral fans. Their current style that used Life-Risking Strike liberally was very interesting to watch!

The Glory Alliance’s Round 35 commenced on May 15th. 301 welcomed Tiny Herb to their home stadium.

“301’s stadium is jam-packed today!” Pan Lin exclaimed in the broadcast.

“Well of course. For 301 to have reached this stage, their fans should also come out and do their best to support their team, ” Li Yibo said.

“No one would have expected 301 to create such a hectic scene before us at the start of this season. Actually no, even after the half-way mark of the season, no one expected it,” Pan Lin said.

“Who would have guessed that 301 would go to Europe and come back with an expert suitable for their Knight character?” Li Yibo replied with a smile.

“If 301 manages to slaughter their way into the playoffs, I reckon their winter transfer will go down as one of the most brilliant moves in Glory history,” Pan Lin said.

“I think the other teams would also broaden their horizons for next year’s summer transfer window. Glory’s player exchange market might gradually globalize from here on out,” Li Yibo said.

“But the rules and formats being different around the world is a show-stopper!” Pan Lin exclaimed.

“The formats are indeed different, but not vastly so. In the end, the different game versions are the biggest barriers to establishing a conversation. But, the Glory game company has taken strong steps towards unifying game versions over the past two years. The large-scale level 75 patch last season has finally mostly synchronized the game on a global scale,” Li Yibo said.

“The rumor going around right now is that the game company is planning far ahead. Their sole intention of leaving the level 70 patch for so long was to synchronize the game globally. The game company had long been scheming for players from across the world to be able to play together,” Pan Lin said.

“I don’t think this is a complete rumor,” Li Yibo nodded. “The game company’s actions must indeed be taking this into account. Looks like Glory’s competitive scene will have an even richer future!”

“Haha, having said all that, let’s first focus on how our own Glory League’s current season will play out! The first round of the individual competition is starting soon. The big screen hasn’t shown the players yet, but we can already see the players on both sides rising from their respective benches. It looks like they are getting ready to get on stage. On 301’s side, we’ve got a game changer for 301’s season, the former English Glory league pro, Bai Shu! How about Tiny Herb’s side? This is… ah! It’s Xu Bin! It seems the first player to go up for Tiny Herb is Xu Bin. Oh my, what a coincidence,” Pan Lin became more animated.

Xu Bin happened to be a former player of 301. He had been the previous owner of the Knight character, Tide. When Bai Shu arrived, he was given the Knight Tide, whom 301 was previously unable to find a replacement for when Xu Bin left. Two players who controlled Tide, old and new, who would come out on top? This really was an engaging match to watch. The audience didn’t seem to have noticed the little movements at the player benches. However, the clamoring immediately grew in the stadium when the big screen confirmed that it would be Bai Shu playing against Xu Bin.

Xu Bin was traded for Tiny Herb’s All-Star Grappler Li Yihui. However, after Li Yihui’s arrival at 301, the title of All-Star Grappler was very quickly snatched away by Samsara’s Lu Boyuan. Li Yihui didn’t seem to have as much value to 301 as Xu Bin used to. When 301 failed to reach the playoffs last season, the exchange was viewed as a loss in the eyes of the fans. The character Tide was benched because no player was found for him; it really was incomprehensible for them.

But now, 301 has acquired Bai Shu. Even though they were perched on the edge of the play-off zone, Bai Shu only became a member of 301 in the second half of their journey this season. Compared to the first half, Bai Shu had really improved their performance by leaps and bounds.

The fans couldn’t not support Bai Shu. Additionally, this successor has accelerated the weakening of their reminiscent feelings towards Xu Bin. In the minds of 301’s fans, the so-called Grind King Xu Bin would always be tangled up with an opponent, trying to wear them down slowly. Bai Shu was not like this; his individual fights were straightforward and he would balance attacking and defending in team fights. He was good at both providing protection and sudden aggression. This Knight player from the European Alliance had a different playstyle to those who were brought up in the Chinese pro circle. He almost seemed to be more in touch with the Knight character. The so-called Knight’s Spirit was not just a class awakening skill for him. His awareness, his playstyle, his habits; they all seemed to carry the true spirit of a knight. Under his control, the class seemed to symbolize some kind of glory.

This was a difference in playstyle influenced by a difference in culture.

There have already been articles focused on Bai Shu that tried to explain how his Knight style is different from those who grew up in the Chinese Glory circle from a cultural perspective.

Then, was this visitor from afar the real deal, or was the Knight of this land the better warrior? No one would have guessed that the Bai Shu’s first match with Tiny Herb as a member of 301 would lead to the confrontation between these two top Knight players.

Enter the stage. Load the characters.

Bai Shu’s chosen map, Training Field, was reasonably simple. It was an unbiased, symmetric, and small map. The two opponents could see each other as soon as the match begun. Bai Shu did not hesitate to have Tide move forward. Xu Bin seemed to hesitate for a moment before he controlled Angelica to go forth and meet his opponent.

The two knights faced each other and walked faster and faster, eventually breaking into a sprint. Both characters raised their swords and shields into place, and locked their gaze on their opponent’s every move, but neither launched an attack.

Ten units away.

Eight units.

Six units.

Four units!

When there was just one step left before they could wipe each other’s faces with their shields… Charge!

Xu Bin’s Angelica acted first and unexpectedly unleashed the knight’s Charge skill at four units’ distance. Angelica’s left hand gripped his shield, and the sword in his right was thrust forth. The four units gap vanished in an instant!

Dong!

A resounding gong instantly rang out.

Bai Shu actually managed to accurately block Angelica’s sudden Charge. Angelica’s Charge ended up colliding with Tide’s shield.

Silver of Life!

This is the Silver shield held by Tide. Xu Bin has used it for three entire years and knew its attributes like the back of his hand. Even though it was raised to level 75 by 301 since and he didn’t know if there were any adjustments, Xu Bin was confident that the health regeneration attribute on Silver of Life would not be abandoned by 301.

Not counting Silver of Life, if Tide’s other equipment hasn’t changed too much, they all held health regeneration attribute . Fighting Tide in a long match would be very unfavorable!

This was Xu Bin’s judgement. But he was called the Grind King; famous for slowing the pace down. And Tide’s equipment was painstakingly created to suit this playstyle.

A character specialized in drawn-out battles and a Grind King who slowed the pace of battle down. There wasn’t a better combination of player and character. But now, Tide is Xu Bin’s enemy. He found himself having to overcome his previously most valued attribute. In addition, he had to change his playstyle…

If the Grind King could not grind, then what would he do?

After Angelica’s Charge was blocked, he immediately began to attack. A ferociously fast and violent attack.

The whole stadium was stunned. They were familiar with Xu Bin! That guy up on stage initiating attacks with an unmatched pace and ferocity, was that really Xu Bin? Did he change that much after going to Tiny Herb? No one has seen otherwise so far!

In the live broadcast, Pan Lin also froze. He stared for a full three seconds before saying: “Xu Bin is proactively attacking,”. As soon as he spoke, he felt he said something super awkward. Xu Bin proactively attacking? This is a sentence with a syntax or semantic error, right? The individual words didn’t string together properly to form a sentence, right?

“Haha, looks like Xu Bin is pretty clear on Tide’s attributes. He knows that grinding away at Tide would only be walking away from victory. So he had to force himself to change his style!” Li Yibo said.

“This change, isn’t it a bit too much?!” Pan Lin exclaimed.

“It doesn’t suit him. His play looks uncomfortable. Bai Shu is defending well, Xu Bin’s attack doesn’t pose much of a threat!” Li Yibo said.

“Then this match…”

Li Yibo stayed silent. As it was, he wouldn’t be as bold as to predict the outcome!

But once again he regretted not doing so. The match played out exactly as he had analyzed. Xu Bin really wasn’t suited for this playstyle, and the playstyle he was comfortable with could not deal with Tide. Finally, he was miserably dealt with by Bai Shu.

Updated by NovelFull.Com

“How do I say this… Bai Shu really did slow down his pace for this match. He was also well aware of the implication of Tide’s attributes and took advantage of it. This game, it feels like 301’s Xu Bin defeated Tiny Herb’s Xu Bin…” Li Yibo said.

Nomyummi The chapter numbers have been finally fixed. Hooray!!!

Chapter 1359 - Happy, Unmoved

“301’s Xu Bin would beat Tiny Herb’s Xu Bin?” Pan Lin repeated Li Yibo’s words.

“Of course, I’m not saying that the past Xu Bin is better than the present one. I’m just saying that what’s inhibiting his playstyle the most is his familiarity with the Knight character Tide,” Li Yibo explained.

“Understood!” Pan Lin nodded his head.

301 started strong and took the initial lead. The stadium had erupted with cheers, but soon afterwards, in the second and third rounds of the individual competition as well as the following group arena, Tiny Herb took a string of victories. By the end of the individual rounds, Team 301 had lagged behind 1 to 4. How could the audience still be smiling? With their rise and fall, all that was left were sighs.

At this moment, news arrived for a different match. Wind Howl versus Heavenly Swords ended the individual rounds 3 to 2. On the other hand, Hundred Blossoms entered the team competition against Royal Style 4 to 1. The other closely watched match was Happy’s away game against Thunderclap, ending with an incisive 5-0! Happy didn’t let Thunderclap win a single point in the individual rounds.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were using the mid-match break to analyze the current situation. Team 301 had been behind in the rankings in the first place. Their current predicament was naturally grim. Even though Thunderclap was farther behind in terms of this current round than 301, they were farther ahead in the rankings, so their situation was just slightly better than 301’s.

The team competition between 301 and Tiny Herb had yet to start, but the other matches had already started, so Pan Lin and Li Yibo naturally took the opportunity to discuss those. Happy and Thunderclap was undoubtedly the biggest spotlight. After the two saw the lineups for the team competition, the two were greatly surprised.

“Ye Xiu isn’t coming up again!” Pan Lin gasped in astonishment.

“No way?” Li Yibo replied subconsciously and immediately checked the info in front of him. Ye Xiu hadn’t appeared last round in the team competition. People could still understand that. After all, their opponents, Team Lightly, weren’t that formidable. Letting a core player like Ye Xiu take a break was necessary. Team Tyranny’s old generals had rotated the entire season, but their age was practically the same as Ye Xiu’s.

After seeing Team Tyranny’s intentional rotations, everyone began realizing that the reason why Ye Xiu didn’t play in the group arena might just be to lessen the burden on him. After all, in the group arena, he might not only have to play against a single opponent. In addition, after finishing the group arena, he would have to start in the team competition. The break he got couldn’t compare to if he started resting from the first individual competition.

Since playoffs were coming up, Ye Xiu resting was something everyone could understand. Unfortunately, without Ye Xiu, Happy had lost in their team competition against Lightly.

Those five points were truly a bit of a pity. As a result, their Round 35 against Thunderclap became even more crucial. Everyone thought Ye Xiu would be going up this time, but Ye Xiu ended up choosing not to. After the individual competition, he just sat there firmly at Happy’s bench and never got up after that. Happy’s lineup for the team competition was Fang Rui, Tang Rou, Su Mucheng, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, and Wei Chen.

“Leave it to us!”

Everyone in Happy said these words to Ye Xiu while preparing for this round.

Ye Xiu indeed had been planning on coming out for the team competition, but the rest of Happy had unanimously agreed to stop him.

“Oh? You don’t need me?” Ye Xiu smiled.

“You’re not that important,” Wei Chen replied.

“Alright then!” Ye Xiu nodded his head, and the matter was done just like that.

Happy’s arrangements had been completed easily, but the amount shock brought by it was not small at all. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were shouting on the broadcast. Thunderclap’s home crowd were also hollering after learning that Ye Xiu would not be going up. Thunderclap’s fans were feeling a bit complicated. Ye Xiu not appearing should be good news, but Ye Xiu not appearing for such an important match felt like disdain towards their Thunderclap. To think there was still a team that dared to underestimate their Thunderclap?

Thunderclap’s Xiao Shiqin saw Happy’s lineup and was also stunned. When they greeted each other before the match, he even spoke to Ye Xiu about having another good match, to which Ye Xiu laughed it off nonchalantly. He had thought that Ye Xiu had been acting nonchalant as a psychological attack, but Ye Xiu had truly been indifferent at the time. He wouldn’t even be playing, so why wouldn’t he be?

“Show them some color!” Thunderclap’s Dai Yanqi was clearly a part of the group that felt like Happy was looking down on them. She was currently going beyond her position and urging the players who would be going on stage.

“Calm down,” Xiao Shiqin regained his composure and hastily went over to advise against everyone going into the match with this mentality. Their individual strengths weren’t that outstanding. What they had was team cooperation. Every individual was an important part of the system. If any one of them broke away from the team’s rhythm due to a peculiar mindset, the negative effects on Thunderclap would be multiplicative.

“Captain, they’re looking down on us!” Dai Yanqi seemed to be complaining to Xiao Shiqin.

“Don’t treat this so simply,” Xiao Shiqin said seriously. His gaze shifted towards Happy’s bench. Happy’s players were gathered together for a pre-match huddle, and although Ye Xiu wouldn’t be going onto the stage, he was also standing among them, talking to the team seriously.

Ye Xiu not coming out for the team competition definitely had a reason behind it.

Xiao Shiqin thought about it.

Is he pretending to look down on us to shake up our mentality? This sort of psychological attack was certainly one reason, but apart from that… Xiao Shiqin looked at Happy’s lineup. Ye Xiu wasn’t there, and Tang Rou took his place. Wei Chen was their sixth player. The only player who rarely appeared this season was Wei Chen.

They probably have a counter strategy planned! Xiao Shiqin thought. Ye Xiu not going up was a surprising arrangement that had thoroughly messed up Thunderclap’s pre-match plans. They could not be careless facing this Happy lineup. He needed to quickly come up with a new strategy.

Xiao Shiqin was constantly thinking, but Thunderclap’s players were waiting for what was coming after “Don’t treat this so simply”, but all they got was silence and a few glances towards Happy.

The captain was thinking.

Thunderclap’s player knew. Ye Xiu not appearing in the team competition required them to make adjustments to their plans. Xiao Shiqin was most likely thinking about this issue.

At this time, Happy’s six player had started walking towards the stage. Xiao Shiqin snapped back to the present and called out to his teammates: “Let’s go.”

Seeing how Xiao Shiqin’s expression was extremely serious, the other Thunderclap players didn’t dare be negligent. They readjusted themselves to the correct mentality and followed Xiao Shiqin to the stage.

The match began.

Team Happy rushed forward eagerly. As for Thunderclap, as soon as they loaded into the map, Xiao Shiqin’s orders immediately started appearing in the chat. A screen of words quickly scrolled down. Quite a few of them were team-agreed-upon words. If one did not do specialized research on Thunderclap, it would be difficult to understand.

Thunderclap’s players had collected their thoughts of taking revenge on Happy for looking down on them. They were following Xiao Shiqin’s arrangements precisely. Xiao Shiqin’s brain was constantly turning. The initial strategy was formulated, but what followed afterwards, the opponent’s reactions and what changes needed to be made to their strategy were all things he needed to think about. He wouldn’t neglect any of Happy’s possible class compositions.

Thunderclap’s team capabilities were truly exceptional. Immediate corrections and commands were accurately implemented. Their ability to carry out orders wasn’t mechanical either. Everyone in Thunderclap understood Xiao Shiqin’s tactical intentions. They weren’t Xiao Shiqin’s wooden puppets. All of their thoughts combined together to form a whole. The less Xiao Shiqin talked in chat, the stronger the team.

Soon, the two sides met. Their confrontation wasn’t direct. Both sides had players sent out to move strategically.

From the direct confrontations to the wandering players, the two sides’ setups began to slowly reveal themselves. It was too much for the eyes. Without Ye Xiu, they thought Happy would instantly collapse, but that didn’t happen. A Happy without Ye Xiu still had the strength to compete with Thunderclap. Thunderclap could not be careless.

Xiao Shiqin felt glad as well. He was glad that he was able to control his teammates’ emotions at the start of the match. If their mentality had truly been disturbed as a result, they would have certainly paid the price.

The battle spread throughout the map. Every player was brilliantly displaying their abilities, but in the end, the scales gradually tilted towards Thunderclap. They had the home game advantage, after all. For a very tactics-oriented team, being able to choose the map was an incredible advantage.

Thunderclap won.

But it hadn’t been an easy one. They were on the edge until the very end. When Happy’s final player fell, Thunderclap only had two players remaining as well. Up until the last moment, they couldn’t be careless. 2v1? With everyone at such low health, if they made a slight mistake, the opponent could turn things around. The healers on both sides had died early on.

5-5.

The final score on the big screen made Thunderclap’s players and the audience members let out a sigh of relief. In the end, they were able to win. Happy hadn’t shaven them bald.

Even though they had been leading eighth and ninth place by 10 points, if they didn’t win a single point here, their days ahead wouldn’t be great. Their next opponents were Hundred Blossoms and Samsara.

Hundred Blossoms was their direct competitor. Samsara had already established themselves firmly as the number one, and Samsara was still maintaining their thirst for victory.

Happy and Thunderclap’s intense match ended rather quickly. The results quickly spread to the other stadiums. From many people’s perspectives, Ye Xiu not appearing for the team competition meant a certain loss for Happy. 5-5 seemed to be a pre-determined result. No one was surprised in the slightest.

As for the highlight broadcasted match, it had also finally ended. 301 had won a bitter battle against Tiny Herb, earning those five precious points.

Chapter 1360 - Excellent Era's Return

Round 35 had ended, but strangely, the rankings hadn’t changed in the slightest. Hundred Blossoms, Wind Howl, and 301 had all won, while the leaders Happy and Thunderclap had tied 5-5.

There were only 3 rounds remaining, but none of these teams held a firm spot for playoffs. The leader among these five teams was Team Thunderclap in fifth place, but the difference between Team Thunderclap and the ninth place Team 301 was only 9 points. If Team Thunderclap performed too poorly in the following three rounds, they might not make it into playoffs.

The fight for top eight had reached such an extent. Everyone wanted to analyze this battle between the five teams. Those who published print issues all felt like there wasn’t enough space to write what they wanted. And even at such an urgent moment, they had no choice but to give a few pages to cover another competition.

The Challenger League.

The Season 10 Challenger League.

This time’s Challenger League finals had a certain level of hype to it.

Team Excellent Era was back!

Even though they were no longer powerhouses and they no longer had the Battle God One Autumn Leaf, the name Excellent Era could not be buried. The team had charged their way through to the final step in the Challenger League. Just one more step, and this name would once again return to the Glory Alliance.

What was Excellent Era like now?

Now that Excellent Era had reached the final stage, the Esports Weekly was finally willing to give a few pages to give an introduction.

This new Excellent Era was still centered around a Battle Mage.

Qiu Fei and his Combat Form.

Those who watched last season’s Challenger League matches should still have an impression of this youth. When Excellent Era crumbled and their players went separate ways, he had been regarded by numerous teams as a talented youth and had received numerous invites. In the end, this youth chose to stay; he chose to stay in a team that had fallen and looked to be at death’s door.

Excellent Era still had a number of fans, but the media had practically abandoned it up until this moment. Now that they looked to have hopes of returning to the Alliance, a few introductions and reports started coming in. As it turned out, the surviving Excellent Era wasn’t as bad as people had initially imagined.

Qiu Fei’s talent had already been recognized. This year, he seemed to have improved remarkably. Combat Form had been a part of Excellent Era’s main roster in last season’s Challenger League. As a team with vast amounts of experience with a Battle Mage, they had been able to create impressive equipment for him, and this year, his equipment had been upgraded to Level 75. The other main roster players were found to be members of Excellent Era’s training camp that year. New Excellent Era no longer had the capacity to continue operating the training camp. Instead, the exceptional trainees from there were directly kept as official members.

During the disbandment, while Excellent Era’s players, characters, and precious materials were being sold wantonly to other Clubs, Excellent Era’s successor Xia Zhongtian made his move at the last moment and secured two items.

First was Qiu Fei as New Excellent Era’s core and soul.

Second was Guild Excellent Dynasty. Xia Zhongtian had accurately grasped the fact that competitive Glory relied on the game. Having a firm control over the in-game guild was an important foundation for a club and a team.

New Excellent Era had set foot onto another season of the Challenger League and had once again reached the finals. Friday would decided their final fate.

Excellent Era’s opponent was Mysterious Fantasy, the other team that had been relegated alongside Excellent Era in Season 8. But in Season 9, the one to have the last laugh was Happy. Both teams had been eliminated by them. After another bitter struggle, the two sides stood against each other in the finals.

The Excellent Era now was not the Excellent Era then, but the Mysterious Fantasy now was still the same Mysterious Fantasy. Their coach Zhang Yiwei had stayed last season, and Mysterious Fantasy’s players had stayed as well. On their way through to the finals, Mysterious Fantasy had eliminated the two Season 9 relegated teams, which had boosted their confidence greatly.

As for their opponents in the finals, the new Excellent Era did not scare them. Mysterious Fantasy were extremely confident from top to bottom in wait for the finals to come.

Friday was the day before the Pro League matches. Teams usually wouldn’t arrange for any practice on this day. As a result, Ye Xiu was walking in circles out of boredom in Happy’s Forest Park residence.

“Are you going to watch?” Chen Guo asked.

“Watch?” Ye Xiu asked back. He didn’t ask what she was referring to. Everyone knew.

The TV was turned on and switched to the esports channel. Six Pine Stadium, the place Happy had battled at one year ago.

Both sides had entered the venue and were just waiting for the match to officially begin. Pan Lin and Li Yibo, the golden duo, once again commentated for the Challenger League, though they didn’t seem to spirited at the moment. The story for this year’s Challenger League finals didn’t even come close to last year’s: a mere river was nothing after having crossed the vast sea.

“Okay, the first players for the individual competition are about to go up,” Pan Lin remarked dully.

“Ahem,” Li Yibo coughed.

Pan Lin glanced at Li Yibo in confusion. The TV director’s angry roar quickly made him realize his mistake.

“Oh, it’s not the individual competition. It’s the group arena. I’m sorry friends, a slip of the tongue,” Pan Lin hastily apologized. The Challenger League finals was based on the playoffs competitive format. A 5v5 group arena and a team competition with the points calculated based on the results. Pan Lin had been thinking it was an ordinary regular season game and failed to react in time.

“Excellent Era’s first player will be…” Pan Lin did a clear pause before the introduction. He didn’t recognize this person! So he could only take a look at the lineups and match the name to the position.

“Wen Li.” Pan Lin announced the player’s name and then dully read the information on him. That was all of his understanding of this player. He clearly had no personal opinion on him.

“As for Mysterious Fantasy, their first player is…” After introducing one side, he moved to the next. He knew a bit more about Mysterious Fantasy though. Even if it had been two years since the player had competed in the Alliance, he still had a rough impression of him.

“Okay, the match is starting now,” Pan Lin recited.

But soon afterwards, Pan Lin was sucked into the contents of the match and gradually grew spirited.

After all, the Challenger League finals was an important match for these two teams. Their entire year’s worth of efforts would be put to the test in this one hour. There was no retreat. It was either you die, or I die. Although the level of their fight might not be able to compare with the fights for top eight in the Pro League, their thirst for victory was no less, and it could clearly be seen through their playing on stage. This sort of competition would always be able to move the spectators.

When the fourth player for Team Mysterious Fantasy went up, Team Excellent Era was already at their fifth and last player. Pan Lin was starting to worry for Excellent Era.

“Excellent Era has been making a bit too many mistakes! They originally should have had a good chance at the group arena! What are your thoughts Coach Li?” Pan Lin said.

“Yes,” Li Yibo nodded. “Just from a technical skill perspective, Excellent Era’s players are no worse than Mysterious Fantasy’s. However, in terms of real match experience, the current Excellent Era is lacking. Mysterious Fantasy’s players have at least experienced the Pro League before. On the other hand, Excellent Era’s current members have never participated in a real professional match before. Their match experience is still somewhat deficient, especially in this sort of life and death match. All of them look nervous, and that nervousness is certainly one reason for their mistakes.”

“If they don’t deal with this issue, Excellent Era might not perform well in the team competition either,” Pan Lin said.

“It’s up to Excellent Era’s final player. Right now, the team needs something to boost their resolve,” Li Yibo said.

“Mm, Excellent Era’s final player for the group arena has gone onto the stage. He’s Excellent Era’s current team captain, Qiu Fei. He’s very young actually. The information I have on hand is telling me he’s only 19,” Pan Lin said.

“But he is truly a very talented player. I heard that last year, Tiny Herb tried to recruit him, but he rejected them,” Li Yibo said.

“It looks like he still holds a lot of feelings for Excellent Era. But feelings alone isn’t enough. We all know that what matters in the end is strength,” Pan Lin said.

“Qiu Fei, 1v2! Let’s see how far he can go!” Li Yibo said.

The two team’s characters set out and started fighting in the middle of the map.

“Beautiful!” After a few blows, Pan Lin shouted a word of praise. Qiu Fei’s Combat Form had taken the initiative and was attacking ferociously.

“Very solid foundations!” Li Yibo sighed.

“His opponent doesn’t seem to be able to defend,” Pan Lin said.

“This Qiu Fei. I remember in last year’s Challenger League finals, he produced a combo that even Ye Xiu was helpless against,” Li Yibo said.

“If even Ye Xiu was helpless, that’s truly the peak of what can theoretically be accomplished,” Pan Lin said.

“It’s looking pretty hopeless for this Mysterious Fantasy player,” Li Yibo gave a fairly bold prediction. He could see the difference in skill between the two sides.

His prediction was correct. Qiu Fei won.

“Combat Form still has 68% health left! That was an impressive fight. Qiu Fei truly lives up to his name,” Pan Lin said.

“But next up is Mysterious Fantasy’s captain, Tang Xin. He’s quite skilled too,” Li Yibo said.

“If Qiu Fei can really pull off a 1v2, it’ll be a huge blow to Mysterious Fantasy’s morale. Let’s see how Tang Xin does!” Pan Lin said.

In the end…

“He won, Qiu Fei won again! The last laugh belongs to Excellent Era, and they now have a one point lead. That wasn’t easy at all. Excellent Era sure has a capable captain, even though he’s only 19 years old right now,” Pan Lin yelled.

“Yes, even if it’s only a one point lead, it’s a huge swing for Excellent Era. The blow to Mysterious Fantasy’s morale must be huge. I hope they don’t get discouraged and can bring their spirits back up for the team competition,” Li Yibo siad.

“Neither side will let the other win easily!”

“But there’s only one champion.”

Challenger League, final victor: Excellent Era.

“We’re back!” In the post-match press conference, Team Excellent Era’s new-generation captain, Qiu Fei, faced the cameras and gave a solemn declaration.

Chapter 1361 - Only Two Rounds Remaining

Excellent Era is back!

Even though it was not what it had been before, everyone knew that this Excellent Era was the direct successor of that old powerhouse. It was just that the luxury goods of this house had been sold off, so it seemed somewhat run-down.

But for many loyal fans, as long as this team was still here, that was enough.

The instant that Excellent Era won, Chen Guo clearly heard a racket coming from outside, and even the sound of people setting fireworks. They were celebrating Excellent Era’s victory – Excellent Era’s return.

Excellent Era belonged to this city, in the past, and in the present still. True, Happy was here as well and had even taken over Excellent Era’s former home stadium, earning pretty good attendance at their matches. But it was clear that compared to Excellent Era, who had been rooted here for ten years, Happy couldn’t compare. Respect was won through results in competition, but feelings and passion couldn’t be transferred so quickly.

“What do you think?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“The match was pretty good. Mysterious Fantasy clearly had the advantage in terms of experience, but Excellent Era’s young players had more drive, and they seized more opportunities in the end,” said Ye Xiu.

“Who cares about that,” Chen Guo huffed. “I’m asking you about your feelings on Excellent Era’s return.”

Ye Xiu felt out a cigarette, lit it, took a deep breath and nodded. “Pretty good.”

“Next season, they’ll become our opponents,” said Chen Guo.

Ye Xiu smiled faintly. “We’ve beaten them, what’s there to worry about?”

“What are you pretending for.” Chen Guo was speechless. She knew that Ye Xiu was someone who would never look down on any opponent.

Ye Xiu continued to smile, but he didn’t say anything. He watched the television quietly, watched that new generation Battle Mage, who announced to the world: “We’re back.”

Yes! They were back.

To be able to return after leaving, that feeling was wonderful, wasn’t it?

Ye Xiu thought of that year and a half he’d spent in retirement and couldn’t help but let out a sigh.

Excellent Era’s return!

The next day, this made headlines everywhere. And this new Excellent Era wasn’t a powerhouse, only the remnants of a powerhouse, but they still stood resolutely, they still charged through the Challenger League. This earned much praise for the young army of New Excellent Era, and the media began to report in detail on the players and characters of this new army. The excitement was comparable to how everyone had felt last year when Happy knocked down the powerhouse Excellent Era.

In this year, Excellent Era had experienced both roles.

With the strength of a powerhouse, they’d lost the most critical battle, attracting all sorts of anger and criticism.

At a weakened level, they’d conquered the final obstacle, winning all sorts of praise and support.

Everyone was already indulging discussion on Excellent Era’s future. But they only had half a day of time, because at 8PM that night, Round 36 of the regular season began. Here, the competition would only be fiercer.

This round, Happy was playing their home game, welcoming the second-to-last Bright Green, who was already set to be relegated. In everyone’s eyes, this was basically a gift of points for Happy. And Wind Howl was facing Parade this round. Meanwhile, Hundred Blossoms and Thunderclap faced off, becoming the match that was chosen for broadcast. 301 continued their difficult match schedule, this round playing their away game against Blue Rain.

They had reached a critical point in the season, so even though Happy’s opponent was weak, there were still many fans who came to watch. And this time, they finally watched their fill, without any disappointment.

Happy earned a perfect 10-0 victory against Bright Green, giving their team a valuable point buffer during this fierce point in the competition. Even more valuable, Ye Xiu still didn’t appear in the team competition this match, but Happy’s team was still able to cleanly defeat their enemies. Those reporters who had been ready to tear into Happy could only grit their teeth.

Wind Howl also won their match, 9-1 against Parade. The death match between Hundred Blossoms and Thunderclap entered the typical rhythm for Thunderclap matches. After the individual rounds, Hundred Blossoms had the lead 4-1, but Thunderclap won the team competition, ultimately surpassing Hundred Blossoms 6-4.

And 301 defeated Blue Rain 7-3. Step by step, they were breaking through their difficult match schedule. After their three matches against Samsara, Tiny Herb, and Blue Rain, they won 15 points in total. Even though they were still in ninth place for now, they hadn’t dropped in the rankings. They were only one point behind the eighth place Hundred Blossoms, so a reversal within one round was completely possible. And Round 37 looked to be a perfect opportunity for this.

Round 37, 301 was fighting their home game against the current last place team, Seaside. And Hundred Blossoms was facing Tyranny.

In Round 36, Tyranny had won 10-0 against Seaside, while Blue Rain had lost to 301, so the two teams switched on the leaderboard. Tyranny once again rose to second place, forcing Blue Rain down to third. Second and third place both had the small home field advantage in the playoffs, the only difference was the amount of prize winnings for final placement on the leaderboard. But these two powerhouse teams clearly didn’t need to worry about this small amount of prize money, and of course Tyranny wouldn’t overexert themselves during this time.

They of course wouldn’t throw their match with 301, but it was natural that they wouldn’t play this match with the same perseverance and energy that they would for the finals. The modern competition format was simply this prolonged, and it didn’t make sense to require the full effort of all players at all times.

With all of these factors tangling together, the future situation only grew more complex and confusing.

Just two rounds left!

This is what all the teams were telling themselves. After two rounds, the line between heaven and hell would be determined.

May 29th, Round 37 of the regular season began. Happy’s away game against Wind Howl became the broadcasted match for this round. Wind Howl’s home stadium was completely filled, without an empty seat in sight. Ever since Wind Howl switched to their one-on-one team playstyle and began winning again and again, everyone from players to fans became energized, and even their chant of winning the championship was brought out once more. And this round, their opponent was the team that had previously swept them 10-0, Team Happy. The stadium was filled with hostility, and as soon as Happy’s players entered the field, they were surrounded by booing.

Ye Xiu was once again first up in the individual competition. 35 consecutive wins, the media no longer had the strength to emphasize this incredible feat. This season’s King of Dueling award would undoubtedly go to him, as his individual record this season was so far ahead of everyone else’s. As for who had the second-best score, everyone was too lazy to care, since there wasn’t any meaning in comparing them anyway. Right now, everyone was waiting to see whether Ye Xiu could ultimately complete the feat of 37 consecutive wins, and some were beginning to sigh about how Ye Xiu hadn’t played in the individual round in Round 1. Otherwise, he’d have 38 rounds – that wouldn’t be called consecutive wins anymore, he would have won all of them, every single one. This score could never be surpassed, only tied, unless the Alliance once again expanded and added more teams.

“Ye Xiu is already on the field. This is his thirty-sixth individual battle, and up to now he was already won thirty-five consecutive. Will his record end here? Who will Wind Howl send up to meet him? Will their captain Tang Hao himself face him?” After Ye Xiu came out, Pan Lin began to shift the audience’s attention toward Wind Howl’s player. In the end, Wind Howl’s first player for the individual round: Liu Hao.

“Liu Hao, it’s Liu Hao! Wind Howl’s vice-captain Liu Hao, former vice-captain of Excellent Era. To send him against Ye Xiu, is it because he understands him? Does he have some grasp of this match? Will Ye Xiu’s consecutive win record end by the hand of his former lieutenant Liu Hao?” As soon as Pan Lin saw this player coming forward, he grew excited. This was something to talk about! The media loved this kind of battle, where there was a lot to talk about.

“Mm, it’s no secret that Ye Xiu goes first in the individual competition. So most teams would address this in one of two ways. They could try the Tian Ji Horse Race strategy, and just let Ye Xiu win the first match, or they could send a strong player who actually has a chance of taking him out. No matter what, Liu Hao isn’t a throwaway player for Wind Howl. His appearance now means they have some sort of plan against Ye Xiu,” said Li Yibo.

“Has Liu Hao discovered the way to defeat the unspecialized Lord Grim?” Pan Lin exclaimed.

“Let us wait and see!” Li Yibo hurriedly said, fearing that Pan Lin would want him to make a analytic prediction. This was Ye Xiu’s match. Predict the outcome? Don’t joke around.

Soon, the first individual match officially began.

“It’s not a direct confrontation,” Li Yibo immediately concluded, after looking at the map selected. “This map is pretty typically suited for a Spellblade. The distance between obstacles matches very well the attack range of a Spellblade.”

“As expected, Liu Hao came prepared!” Pan Lin exclaimed.

“Come on! Let me see how much you’ve grown these past two years.” As soon as the match began, Ye Xiu spoke in the chat.

“Haha, I welcome the teachings of my old captain,” Liu Hao replied, polite and modest, in an extremely composed demeanor. In reality, he was about to explode.

I’m not a student in Excellent Era’s training camp anymore. I’m not Excellent Era’s benchwarmer substitute anymore, or Excellent Era’s player at all. I’m not under your authority anymore, Ye Xiu. I’m Team Wind Howl’s vice-captain, an All-Star player this season. But you, you, on what basis are you still acting so high and mighty? You want to see how much I’ve grown? Do I need your comments anymore?

My growth?

I’ll show you how much I’ve grown.

Liu Hao’s Spellblade Absent Sun decisively advanced, without retreat, along the center road.

Stone Forest.

This was the name of this 1v1 map. Stone pillars, each as thick as a person, were distributed quite densely along this map. No clash could avoid hitting them; places for cover were everywhere.

Absent Sun quickly arrived at the center road, but when he looked around, he didn’t see any sign of Lord Grim.

“Old captain, how come you’re not here? This isn’t your normal style!” Liu Hao immediately said in the chat.

“Of course not, my style adapts to local conditions!” Ye Xiu quickly responded.

Where is he?

Liu Hao purposefully acted relaxed in chat, but in reality he was very nervous. Dealing with sneak attacks on this map would be a headache. Liu Hao didn’t let Absent Sun just stand around waiting, and so he also prepared to sneak attack the opponent, and began to move carefully alongside a stone pillar.

Whoosh!

About twenty body-lengths away, a silhouette flashed through the stone pillars, instantly going from behind one to behind another. Liu Hao immediately adjusted his camera view, capturing this rare clue.

Liu Hao stared at that one stone pillar. Lord Grim was right behind it. Absent Sun began to carefully move in that direction. On this map, Liu Hao was unafraid of a direct confrontation.

Chapter 1362 - It's Always Like This

Step by step, Liu Hao carefully approached. Absent Sun moved steadily, his eyes unwavering, with no openings in sight.

The viewers yawned. Lord Grim wasn’t in the direction Absent Sun was moving in. After Lord Grim hid behind that stone pillar, he backed up in a straight line until he reached a different stone pillar and then switched to it as a new hiding spot.

Having an omniscient view sometimes made things quite boring. The viewers all felt bored. They regretfully could not experience Liu Hao’s nervousness and could not sympathize with Liu Hao’s extreme caution.

Earthquake Sword!

Absent Sun threw out a fierce attack, and a wave of earth surged forth. The whirling earth crashed into that stone pillar and sliced it in half. The Earthquake Sword had split into two paths and then converged towards the center of the stone pillar.

Liu Hao had been waiting for this moment. Absent Sun slid to the side to get a better line of sight and sent out an Ice Wave Sword.

“Haa…”

The audience once again yawned. There was no one behind that stone pillar. What was the point of making so much noise? Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was quite a distance away and wasn’t within the attack’s range. A fight wasn’t going to break out. Everyone could see that clearly. It was only Liu Hao alone, with his spirit trembling with excitement, who couldn’t see it. His two skills ended up hitting nothing but air.

He’s not there!

Liu Hao was shocked to discover that Lord Grim wasn’t behind the stone pillar.

However, with his experience and his familiarity with the map, he immediately determined how Lord Grim had disappeared from right under his eyes.

Absent Sun moved precisely along the route Lord Grim had chosen. The audience noticed Liu Hao’s precise judgement and shook excitedly. Applause suddenly poured down.

This time, he was truly closing in. However, this time, Liu Hao wasn’t certain of Lord Grim’s exact location.

The audience didn’t know that though! All they saw was Liu Hao chasing after Lord Grim with extraordinary precision. They thought he had completely ascertained Lord Grim’s position. How could they know Liu Hao only had a rough idea. He was still picking from A, B, or C as his final answer!

Seeing Absent Sun getting closer and closer to Lord Grim, the crowd became increasingly more excited. All sorts of cheers and excited shouts exploded. Then, they watched as Absent Sun sweep out an Earthquake Sword towards a stone pillar with no one there.

Fuck!

What a letdown.

Everyone’s hopes were instantly crushed. The crowd immediately went silent.

Liu Hao did the same two attack maneuver as before and once again saw that there was no one behind that stone pillar.

Okay, so A’s been eliminated. There’s only B and C left.

He should be… behind those two stone pillars, right?

Liu Hao was suddenly unsure again. He had been confident in his pursuit. Even though he hadn’t seen any signs of Lord Grim, he was certain Ye Xiu was dancing in the palm of his hands. If there were any strange movements, he would definitely notice them.

But there were none.

That meant Lord Grim should be in front of him. He just couldn’t confirm whether A, B, or C was correct.

Liu Hao believed choice A was the last likely. He still chose it in the end though. It was actually bait. When he attacked A, his attention was more focused on B and C. He thought Ye Xiu would act as soon as he guessed wrong, so he wanted to beat him at his own game.

But Ye Xiu did not act. As a result, he safely eliminated A as the correct choice and now began pondering over the other two choices.

The audience suddenly became quite lively.

Lord Grim’s over there! If your first guess wasn’t right, try again! Why’d you stop?

Absent Sun raised his shortsword and suddenly started casting a Wave Formation. With just one move, he could cover both options.

At this moment, Lord Grim casually stepped out from pillar B.

Liu Hao was greatly alarmed and hastily cancelled his Wave Formation. Shining Cut! Lord Grim cut across and appeared right in front of Liu Hao.

“You haven’t changed. Your playstyle is always so… fake,” Ye Xiu said as Lord Grim let out two slashes in the shape of a cross. At this distance, a vertical and horizontal slash was truly difficult to dodge. Liu Hao reacted quite fast though. Absent Sun shielded his head with his shortsword, using the Blade Master skill Guard to block Lord Grim’s attack. Borrowing the momentum from Lord Grim’s attack, he slid back.

“You clearly know where I was hiding! Why not directly attack me? Why did you insist on running in circles?” Ye Xiu didn’t have Lord Grim urgently rush over and followed up on the conversation.

“You call that fake?” Liu Hao sneered. “Are you saying you’ve never done this?”

“I have, but no one is so fake through and through,” Ye Xiu replied.

“Do you really think words like those would shake me up?” Liu Hao said.

“If you really did get shaken up, that would be great,” Ye Xiu said.

“Shut up!” Liu Hao was finally unable to hold back. After all, letting it accumulate was quite tiring as well.

“Alright!” Ye Xiu responded. Lord Grim moved again.

Liu Hao sneered. In his eyes, Ye Xiu had made a mistake. Lord Grim suddenly leaping out, while his Absent Sun was casting a spell, came out of nowhere. Lord Grim instantly closed in on him too. It had been such a perfect ambush opportunity. But instead of continuing his assault, he just chattered. Liu Hao was truly laughing from head to toe. He had truly been panicking whether or not he could block Lord Grim’s direct attacks. That distance wasn’t a Spellblade’s ideal distance.

Instead, Ye Xiu stopped, giving him a chance to breathe. This was simply letting a tiger return to the mountains! Liu Hao had adjusted himself. If another attack came, he wouldn’t be afraid. He had originally planned on directly fighting with Ye Xiu. Why else would he have charged directly to the center of the map at the start of the match?

You’ll pay the price for trying to preach to me!

Liu Hao shouted inwardly. Absent Sun raised his sword. A frenzy of fire surged towards Lord Grim. Fire Wave Sword!

Bang!

The raging flames left Lord Grim nowhere to dodge. The fire blazed turning Lord Grim into smoke.

Humph…

Liu Hao laughed coldly. Shadow Clone Technique. Ye Xiu had used this old trick who knew how many times by now.

Absent Sun had already leapt up. At practically the same time as the Fire Wave Sword, he twisted his body in the air and released an Earthquake Sword!

The land quaked and violent sword intent flew forward, but all that it hit was a thread of Lord Grim’s clothing.

Absent Sun had missed. Lord Grim hadn’t been standing directly behind him, but rather to the side a sliver. The Earthquake Sword grudgingly whistled by him.

“Who told you I always went behind my opponents?” Ye Xiu asked as Lord Grim unsheathed his sword.

Sword Draw!

The sword light swept over. The airborne Absent Sun had no way of dodging it. He had just Guarded previously; its cooldown wasn’t up yet. All he could do was swing his sword as a normal attack to parry it.

However, a normal attack had lower priority than Sword Draw. It couldn’t completely block it. The Sword Draw pushed Absent Sun’s shortsword back towards him. Absent Sun crashed to the ground; the flames from his previous Fire Wave Sword had yet to extinguish.

Even though he wasn’t able to completely block it, it still had some effect. Absent Sun didn’t go into a tumble as a result. Liu Hao adjusted his character, so he would land on his feet.

Clack!

The instant he fell, a clack came from beneath his feet. Liu Hao lowered his head and saw spikes through his character’s feet.

Thief skill Spike Trap rooted the target.

Liu Hao’s face suddenly paled. He hadn’t noticed when Lord Grim had placed the trap down. From its location, could it have been the instant he sent out the Fire Wave Sword? Could he have used the light from the flames as a cover?

In any case, Liu Hao had been hit by the trap, and his Absent Sun couldn’t move an inch for the duration of Spike Trap. And this time, Ye Xiu had no plans of chatting with him. Grenade, Sand Toss, Disperse Powder… Lord Grim rushed over and threw a bunch of things. Unable to move, the only thing Liu Hao could do was look away to avoid Sand Toss’s Blind effect. Every other projectile had hit. Then, Lord Grim’s sword glowed dark purple as a ghost soul flashed out. A boundary had appeared on the ground: Sword Soul, or Sword Boundary. All allies within the boundary would have their Strength and Intelligence greatly buffed.

The real offensive had only just begun: Unspecialized Blitz.

With Spike Trap in effect, Absent Sun could only stand there and get beaten. When Spike Trap’s root effect dissipated, Absent Sun could still only get beaten up.

Liu Hao wanted to cry. He had been waiting to use this map for a long time. He had been waiting for the key moment to use it to improve his popularity. This crucial match against Ye Xiu and his 35 round win streak were once in a lifetime opportunities to win huge amounts of fame. Liu Hao had sacrificed his treasure and released his treasure’s full might. He had utilized his familiarity with the map to give a precise chase and received the audience’s applause.

But there was nothing after that.

He received no more chances to utilize this map. Ye Xiu had used a Spike Trap to seal his movements. Then, after making a few setups, Ye Xiu didn’t give him a single opportunity to counterattack or use the map as cover.

Am I going to lose?

Lose like this?

I was so meticulous and precise with my preparations, yet I’m going to lose like this without any chance of retaliation?

IMPOSSIBLE! It doesn’t make sense! I worked hard and put in the effort! Victory? Why can’t I see any shred of victory? Will I truly never be able to beat him?

Liu Hao felt fear.

He had exhausted everything at his disposal in this match. He thought that he had a huge advantage, but he hadn’t even been able to hold the upper hand for even a minute. It was like he still a trainee at the Excellent Era training camp. That Battle God from up above strolled into the training camp, picked a random map, and just casually crushed him.

He thought that he had grown strong, but in the end, he could see no difference from the past. He was easily and casually defeated.

Why?

Why did it turn out like this?

When Absent Sun fell, Liu Hao collapsed in his seat and roared furiously. But no one could hear him.

Chapter 1363 - Hundred Blossoms on the Cliff

Happy vs Wind Howl, 1-0.

The scoreboard in the stadium clearly displayed the two teams’ points after the first battle.

Ye Xiu’s win streak continued. In the live broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo only mentioned this once, almost with an air of resignation. It was simply too repetitive. And with this battle in particular, Li Yibo felt that he had been faceslapped once again. He hadn’t even dared to make any thorough analysis at the start of the match, he’d only said that this map was suitable for Spellblades, and that Liu Hao had chosen it carefully. He felt that he couldn’t go wrong with such an obvious observation!

But in the end, had this map actually been suitable for the Spellblade? If only looking at the actual performance, and not the map, then Li Yibo could only be given a regretful “haha.”

Just from the onstage performance, it was impossible to see that Liu Hao’s Absent Sun had used any special characteristics of the map. But would Coach Li be beaten that easily?

“Ye Xiu played very well!” Li Yibo said. “From the very start, he could tell that the map put him at a disadvantage, so step by step, he drew the opponent into his plan, took control, and ended the match.”

“Yes, yes – what did Liu Hao want to do with this map? We didn’t even get the chance to see!” Pan Lin followed Li Yibo’s thought process.

“This match between old teammates didn’t ignite the fireworks we’d expected. Ye Xiu easily obtained victory,” said Li Yibo.

“Yes, Ye Xiu won easily, and now Happy is 1-0 in the lead. The Wind Howl audience seems somewhat disappointed!” Pan Lin said.

“This outcome probably caught them off-guard as well! The first player in a match is usually chosen to be someone with a tougher style. This kind of player can carry the atmosphere, and even if they lose, they won’t disappoint people too much. Liu Hao is more of a calculating player, but if he miscalculates, then his loss is a bit more ugly,” said Li Yibo.

“Yeah… this match, he seemed a bit off,” Pan Lin said.

While the two of them discussed, the two players had already begun to come offstage. Liu Hao’s face was ugly as he walked along, and he heard a few boos directed at him. Clearly, a number of Wind Howl fans were unsatisfied with his performance. But overall, the Wind Howl audience was still relatively tolerant.

“Let’s get ready to enjoy the second battle!” Pan Lin said. The camera switched back to show the digital display in the stadium, and very soon, the names of the players participating in the second battle of the individual round appeared.

Happy, Mo Fan, Deception.

Wind Howl, Guo Yang, Qi Breaker.

“Another former Excellent Era player,” Li Yibo said.

“Happy sent out Mo Fan, unlike their recent pattern of sending Luo Ji or Wei Chen. It looks like the situation’s getting more tense, so Happy doesn’t dare to continue to let Luo Ji and Wei Chen find their condition,” said Pan Lin.    ( Updated by NovelFull.Com)

“Haha, if they lose points now, they won’t have any more chances to win them back,” said Li Yibo.

Indeed, these were the last two rounds. Every single point was precious. It was very possible that the final standings would be determined by this single point.

Wind Howl had lost one point, but they were still in seventh place, and had a points advantage over eighth and ninth. Meanwhile, Hundred Blossoms, currently in eighth place, was in a greater need of points, but they also lost the first point of the individual round.

Song Qiying, the young general of Tyranny, went first, and ultimately defeated Hundred Blossoms’ old general Zhang Wei to win a first point for Tyranny.

The second Tyranny player instantly provoked boos from all corners of the Hundred Blossoms stadium.

Zhang Jiale, it could only be Zhang Jiale. Every time he returned to this stadium, he was met with this kind of welcome.

It had already been three years since he retired from Hundred Blossoms.

It had already been two years since he joined Tyranny.

Yet Hundred Blossoms’ resentment toward him seemed not to have lessened in the slightest. Even if there were many Hundred Blossoms fans that understood him, their voices would never be loud enough. Those who passionately despised Zhang Jiale had a stronger presence.

This season, Hundred Blossoms’ fans had organized a poll amongst themselves, a contest in which they ranked the various players in Hundred Blossoms history in different categories. The player toward whom they were most grateful, and the player they hated the most, the number one for both categories was Zhang Jiale.

Zhang Jiale, to Hundred Blossoms, was an angel and a demon combined.

Some remembered his many years of contributions, while others hated his final abandonment.

Love and hate tangled together like this, in a never-ending debate. Now that he came onstage, there was some applause, but there was more booing. In the end, Hundred Blossoms desperately needed victory at this time, and Zhang Jiale had become an obstacle standing in their way. Evidently, this would ignite more hatred than gratitude.

And on Hundred Blossoms’ side, when their player name was announced, the crowd instantly hushed.

Zou Yuan, Bright Blossoms.

By coincidence, Hundred Blossoms’ old and new Spitfires stood opposite each other on the battlefield. The very air seemed thick with tension.

But Zhang Jiale was very calm.

Having walked to this point today, he would have no other emotion. All of those feelings and conflicts of the past were now buried deep in his heart. He would reminisce, but not at this moment. Perhaps the points didn’t matter to Tyranny right now anymore, but Zhang Jiale absolutely would not throw the match for Hundred Blossoms. He still hoped he could earn the understanding and support of the Hundred Blossoms fans, but he would not do so through such a method.

He would play this match seriously. It wasn’t a victory that Tyranny needed, but to himself, and to Hundred Blossoms, this was the greatest respect he could offer.

Gunshots.

The two Spitfires were already fighting.

These were perhaps the two best Spitfires in Glory right now, both from Team Hundred Blossoms, both controlling Spitfire characters with the word “blossoms” in their names.

Who was weaker? Who was stronger?

This was not a question that could be answered with one match. In one match, there was only victory and defeat.

Zou Yuan’s playstyle had inherited many characteristics from Zhang Jiale’s, but later on, he had integrated many of his own traits as well. The two’s styles seemed to be similar, but they weren’t the same.

This had nothing to do with which was superior. They simply each used their own abilities to the limit.

Amidst roars, explosions bloomed like flowers. In this instant, everyone forgot all debate, as they were captivated by the sights onstage.

Victory and defeat, that was all there was. No matter what player, what class, what style, what debate – once on the battlefield, only victory and defeat were displayed in the end.

The loser would fall; the winner would remain standing. Aside from this, there would be no other outcome. And when this moment arrived…

Glory!

The display flashed with this large word. The holographic projection, showing the details of the battle, played the final moments in slow motion.

Amidst the fireworks exploding like blooming flowers, Bright Blossoms fell. In the end, Zou Yuan could not defeat his senior. As for Zhang Jiale, he knew very well that this match was just icing on the cake for Tyranny, while it could be fatal for Hundred Blossoms. But he didn’t hesitate, didn’t retreat, as he resolutely controlled Dazzling Hundred Blossoms to fire the final shot.

As for what consequences this would have for Hundred Blossoms, it was no longer his business.

Hundred Blossoms’ core player, ace character, this was all in the past.

2-0!

In Tyranny’s away game against Hundred Blossoms, when Tyranny no longer needed to care too much about victory, they still obtained the first point, pushing Hundred Blossoms to the cliff’s edge.

The news from the other ongoing matches only gave Hundred Blossoms even more of a panic.

301, who had only been behind them by one point, was facing the last-place Seaside this round. By now, they’d already won all three of their individual battles, squeezing Hundred Blossoms out of the top eight.

Thunderclap was playing their home game against Samsara and had already finished two individual matches. Even though Thunderclap was generally weaker individually, they had actually taken the lead 2-0 against Samsara.

In Wind Howl against Happy, they’d finished two battles and were tied 1-1. When two direct competitors were gaining points at an equal rate like this, it was the worst for the other competitors. It would be better for Hundred Blossoms if one team dropped a lot of points, because then there’d be space to pass them.

Not a single piece of good news.

Team Hundred Blossoms, at ninth place right now, had no road of retreat.

Victory, they needed victory! If they weren’t able to earn points this round, then their season would come to an end right here. Hundred Blossoms was facing an away game at Samsara next round. It was truly too difficult to push any hopes onto that match.

“You have to win!”

Carrying all of Hundred Blossoms’ hopes as he walked onstage was their Summoner Zhu Xiaoping. The one he was about to face was the player who quietly demonstrated his strength through positioning and movement, Qin Muyun.

Zhu Xiaoping knew how critical this battle was, but it was a difficult task!

His summoned creatures had no way of completing an encirclement around Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees. Qin Muyun’s precise movement allowed him to thread his way through the army of summons, while his bullets were sent wave after wave toward Zhu Xiaoping’s Wind Carving.

The summons he’d sent to surround the opponent weren’t enough, but Zhu Xiaoping didn’t have anything left to summon creatures to protect himself. Both attack and defense were too difficult, and in the end, he unfortunately lost this crucial third match.

0-3!

Hundred Blossoms was now lagging 0-3. Just when they thought the situation couldn’t get any worse, Tyranny dealt them another blow.

When he came offstage, Zhu Xiaoping’s expression was anguished. He hadn’t been able to manifest the hopes that the entire team, the entire audience, had placed upon him. He knew what this loss implied.

The stadium was deathly silent. No matter how dissatisfied they were by Hundred Blossoms’ performance, the audience was in no mood to boo or jeer.

We have to win!

In everyone’s hearts, there was only this one sound: win!

“We can’t lose any more points. We have to win every single one of the next seven points. This is the most crucial moment of our entire season. Everyone, focus! Win, we must win. Erase every other thought from your minds. Don’t hope that Tyranny will let up, because they won’t, that team never will. We can only bring out everything we have and wager it all on this stage. This is our opportunity, and we can only rely on ourselves to seize it. Win! Win all the way until the end!”

In the short break after the individual round ended, Yu Feng was desperately trying to boost the team’s morale.

“Let’s go!” he roared. “Don’t let the opponents look down upon us, don’t let down our fans! Let’s get them.”

Chapter 1364 - An Extremely Stressful Team Competition

At the brink of disaster, without anywhere else to retreat to, Team Hundred Blossoms finally showed astonishing fighting strength during the group arena. Amongst them, the most praiseworthy performance came from their Assassin player, Zhou Guangyi. He had played exceptionally well, narrowly completing a 1v2. After such a beautiful opening, the following two players didn’t waste the opportunity, finally securing a valuable 2 points for Team Hundred Blossoms in the group arena, somewhat stabilizing the cliff that they were on.

But the news that arrived from other matches made Hundred Blossom’s situation as dire as before.

301 was entering the team competition with an absolute lead of 5 to 0, already putting themselves ahead of Hundred Blossoms by two points. It looked like they wouldn’t have too much trouble securing victory in the team competition, meaning that 301 had secured a full 10 points in this round.

Thunderclap, after seizing 2 points in the individual competition, now suffered against Samsara’s strong retaliation, with the score already changing to 2 to 3 in favour of Samsara. Still, Thunderclap was ahead of Hundred Blossoms by 7 points. Even if they were to lose the upcoming team competition, Hundred Blossoms couldn’t rely solely on beating Tyranny in the team competition to surpass them.

The other match was the one that Hundred Blossoms had pinned the most of their hopes on. Team Wind Howl was only ahead of them by 3 points, so of course, Hundred Blossoms was hoping that the gap wouldn’t increase, or even for them to simply overtake Wind Howl in one move. In the end, after their initial victory in the first individual round, the retaliation that Happy received was even more dramatic than the one against Thunderclap. Team Wind Howl won round after round, with the score after the group arena tallying up to be 1 to 4. Happy with 1 point, and Wind Howl with 4.

If Happy was ahead of Hundred Blossoms by 7 points, and Thunderclap was ahead by 5 points, no matter what the end result of the round was, Hundred Blossoms had no way of surpassing either of these two teams. Unexpectedly, their end result in this round had already been decided halfway through the competition. Ninth place, it could only be ninth place, with no chance whatsoever of entering the top eight. The last round would be their final chance to make it into the top eight, but it was an away game against Samsara, the most difficult opportunity of them all. And in order to have a chance of seizing this opportunity, they had to first defeat Tyranny in the team competition of this round.

They had easily taken back two points in a brilliant performance in the group arena, but after hearing such bad news from other matches, the morale of the members of Hundred Blossoms began to wane.

“That makes things easier.” Unexpectedly, their captain, Yu Feng, had become more relaxed. “We only have one road to take, without any other choices. Let’s put in all our effort and try to make it! No matter what, we won’t have any regrets.”

No matter what, we won’t have any regrets!

As the members of Hundred Blossoms thought about it, their gazes gradually became more resolute. They needed to win this round, so they would fight with no fear. Who cared who their opponents were?

“Hundred Blossoms’ current situation isn’t good, no matter how the match plays out, they’re definitely going to be in ninth place.” Pan Lin and Li Yibo took advantage of the break in the match to comment about the circumstances for Team Hundred Blossoms.

“That’s true, but in the last round, Hundred Blossoms will still have a chance. However, they have to win the upcoming team competition first,” Li Yibo said.

“Mm, if Hundred Blossoms wins the team competition, they’ll have 237 points.” Pan Lin looked at the team rankings and calculated, “If Thunderclap loses the team competition to Samsara, they’ll only have 239 points, and they’ll be ahead of Hundred Blossoms by 2 points; if Team 301 wins the team competition against Seaside and takes 10 points, they’ll also be at 239 points, ahead of Hundred Blossoms by 2 points. As for the match we’re currently broadcasting, if Wind Howl wins in the team competition, Happy will only be ahead of Hundred Blossoms by 2 points; and if Happy wins, then Wind Howl will have the same number of points as Hundred Blossoms. Hundred Blossoms still has an obvious opportunity to make it into the top 8.”

“No matter who wins or loses in the current match between Wind Howl and Happy, one team will be left behind, becoming the target for Hundred Blossoms to surpass,” Li Yibo said.

“I’m sure that they’ve already heard the news from the other matches during this break, so they should be very clear of the circumstances that they’re facing,” Pan Lin said.

“In this round, both teams are shouldering a lot of pressure. But if they lose this round, they’ll face even more pressure in the next round. Wind Howl will face Tiny Herb in the last round, and Happy will face 301. Neither match will be easy for them to deal with,” Li Yibo said.

“Looking at it, Wind Howl has taken 4 consecutive points in the individual rounds, so their morale should be very high, and they have the benefit of being the home team. On the other hand, after their initial victory, Happy has lost 4 points in a row, so they need to collect themselves quickly!” Pan Lin said.

“Yes, that’s right. While these two teams are evidently in a much better state than Hundred Blossoms, they’re still not too far from the edge of the cliff. Whoever loses will move a few steps closer to that cliff, where Hundred Blossoms is desperately trying to claw their way back in. It could very well be that Hundred Blossoms comes back, while one of these teams makes an exit,” Li Yibo said, putting his fists on the edge of the table to illustrate what he meant.

“Let’s wait and see which team can better stabilize their state of mind at this crucial time!” Pan Lin said.

“Mm, the team competition is about to begin,” Li Yibo replied.

“Let’s return to the current match,” Pan Lin said, as the camera moved away from the commentator’s booth and back to the arena. At the same time, a bird’s-eye shot overlooked the player benches for each team, where the players were huddled in a circle, obviously making crucial preparations for the match ahead.

In the arena, the referee walked to the side of the stage, stretching his hand out to indicate that the competitors from the two teams should prepare to go onstage. One by one, the names of the players from each side who would be appearing in the team competition flashed on the large screen in the stadium.

“Fuck!” Pan Lin suddenly cried out, before immediately covering his mouth, but it was already too late. During this whole season, he had been walking on the blade’s edge with the issue of repeatedly swearing, and Pan Lin had put in a great amount of effort to control his repeated urges to curse out loud. Unfortunately, in the second-to-last round, his willpower finally cracked, and he was unable to refrain from swearing. In an instant, his cursing was transmitted to the ears of every single viewer. He could practically already see his bonus for that month flying out of his pocket.

“Happy is really too bold!” Li Yibo was really quite considerate, knowing that Pan Lin’s sudden swearing wasn’t very appropriate, so he hurriedly spoke up, doing his best to cover it up a bit.

“Yeah…” Pan Lin was still somewhat unable to calm himself after his mistake.

“In a match as crucial as this, Ye Xiu still isn’t going up in the team competition?” Li Yibo continued to stare in surprise at the names of the players who were competing in the team competition. Team Happy: Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, Tang Rou, Luo Ji, An Wenyi, Mo Fan.

Not only was Ye Xiu not going up, Luo Ji, a rookie who had only played in a few rounds, was unexpectedly appearing in the team competition roster during such an important match.

“What on earth is Happy thinking!” Pan Lin exploded.

“Could it be that Ye Xiu has really run into some kind of problem?” This time, Li Yibo really couldn’t stop himself from making a conjecture. Even though Ye Xiu had continued his unblemished record in the individual competition, he’d already rested for 4 whole rounds when it came to the team competition. Normally, if a player didn’t appear for 4 rounds, most people wouldn’t think that they were rotating their roster, they would think that the player had been cut from the main roster entirely.

But how could Happy possibly cut Ye Xiu?

“Could he have suffered an injury that prevents him from playing for a long period of time? Like Sun Zheping?” Pan Lin wondered. Until today, Sun Zheping had only played in the individual competition for Team Heavenly Swords. It was no secret that he couldn’t take on a greater burden due to his hand injury. Ye Xiu only appearing in the individual competition for four rounds in a row really did have a few similarities to Sun Zheping’s situation!

No matter whether he was resting, or if it was some kind of deliberate feint, Ye Xiu not appearing in such a crucial competition really didn’t conform to common sense.

But no matter how surprised everyone was, Happy could only have these 6 players who were taking the field. At this time, they were lined up in the middle of the stage next to Wind Howl’s 6 players, taking in the look of astonishment on their faces. Evidently, Ye Xiu not appearing in this round was something that no one had expected, not even Team Wind Howl.

After shaking hands and exchanging greetings, the two sides made their way to the player booths. As they walked away, some of Wind Howl’s players turned their heads in suspicion, as if Ye Xiu was mixed into that group of 6, waiting to catch them off guard.

“Don’t bother thinking about what the other side is doing, it’s irrelevant to us. We’ll mark their players, the same thing as usual,” their captain, Tang Hao, said to the rest of his team.

“Understood.” Wind Howl’s players nodded their heads, but at this time, their vice-captain, Liu Hao, was staring at Happy’s player bench, away from the stage. He was staring at Ye Xiu.

Having being easily beaten into submission during the individual competition, Liu Hao was on the verge of collapse, but he was really too good at hiding his true feelings. After he came out of the player booths, he wore a look of defeat without despair, apologizing to his teammates, encouraging the next player, leaving no room for anyone to say anything much to him.

Only he knew that deep inside, he wasn’t as calm and collected as he looked.

He was about to go insane. He simply couldn’t accept the reality that he had been so easily dispatched by Ye Xiu.

He wanted revenge. He needed revenge.

The opportunity was right in front of him, the team competition. In the team competition, they would face each other again. And in the team competition, where Wind Howl wanted each person to mark an opposing player, Liu Hao’s mark was indeed Ye Xiu.

Liu Hao had clenched his teeth, waiting for this moment the entire time. But in the end, Ye Xiu didn’t appear.

In such a crucial, important match, Ye Xiu actually decided not to play in the team competition.

The energy that Liu Hao had been building up for the whole of the first half of the competition immediately turned to sullenness.

He desperately wanted to take down Ye Xiu, but from the very start, Ye Xiu paid no mind to him. When he should take the stage, he went up, and when he wanted to rest, he would rest. Just because Liu Hao was on the other team, would he have to go up in the team competition to take the reins? Regrettably, Liu Hao never had this sort of worthiness, and Ye Xiu never had such intentions.

Ye Xiu didn’t appear, so Liu Hao’s mark changed. His new mark: Luo Ji. / NovelFull.Com

This was the natural substitute, since Ye Xiu hadn’t appeared in the match. Wind Howl had no intention of rearranging each person’s mark once again. But Liu Hao wasn’t in a good mood, immediately becoming furious with the player that he had to target during the match.

It was actually that noob?

Liu Hao felt as if he was being scorned. Deep down inside, he knew that there was no such thing, it was just a natural result of Happy’s players being swapped. But even then, he couldn’t get rid of the feeling that they were looking down on him.

“Let’s beat them!” Tang Hao roared.

“Yes!” The players shouted back.

The competition began.

Chapter 1365 - The Underestimated Rookie

The match had officially began, but the audience hadn't gotten ready for it yet. No one had recovered from the news that Ye Xiu wasn't playing!

But the first thing each team did when the match began had the entire audience snapping their attention back to the match.

Team Wind Howl, player and account substitution, healer player Ruan Yongbin, Cleric Soul Healer switched out, sixth player Guo Yang, Qi Master Qi Breaker switched in.

Team Happy, player and account substitution, healer player An Wenyi, Cleric Little Cold Hand switched out, sixth player Mo Fan, Deception switched in.

The entire stadium exploded into uproar.

Everyone had gotten used to Wind Howl's new playstyle by now and some even questioned why they even bothered having a healer at all. Of course, this was just sarcasm. Having a healer in their starting lineup added a layer of uncertainty for their opponents. Even though they knew that Wind Howl favored the tactic of switching their sixth player in for a five DPS formation, they would be forced to wonder if the other would really use it.

In addition, a man on man offense was very tiring to keep up. Often times, they still needed a healer behind them to help stabilize the situation, so that was why a lost of people thought Misty Rain too extreme with their six DPS lineup.

In this match, Wind Howl was using their usual play style, but no one had expected that Happy would copy them, throwing their healer out for a DPS the moment the match started.

"Happy… is really too brave!" Pan Lin exclaimed.

Team Wind Howl had rolled through the competition with their playstyle and, until now, no other team had been so resolute, arranging a full DPS formation to counter. This was another huge shock after the first, where everyone realized Ye Xiu wasn't playing.

"But, speaking of, it isn't like Happy hasn't used this playstyle before. Of course, back then their goal wasn't a man on man offense like Wind Howl," Li Yibo brought up.

Pan Lin thought back. It seemed that they really had switched out their healer for their sixth player to maximize DPS before. Happy had utilized this ages ago.

"Then what are they aiming to do this time?" Pan Lin wondered aloud.

"Hm, let's wait and see," Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin rolled his eyes. At a time like this, shouldn't he do some analysis? Li Yibo was just getting worse and worse, pretending that he had nothing to do at times like this.

The two teams charged out. Team Wind Howl split into three groups, two people heading to the left and right flanks. This flank attack was their usual strategy. On their home turf this round, the familiarity of the map had them moving even faster and more decisively.

On the other hand, Happy's five were in a tight group. Never mind scattering, their current position was almost too closely spaced.

"What's Happy trying to do?" Pan Lin's curious and anxious attitude wasn't an act to rouse excitement; he really did want to know. "They switched out their healer for a DPS, but considering this formation, it doesn't seem like they intend to fight man to man!"

"They probably don't," Li Yibo agreed, "If they really were planning on a man on man, then Happy would most likely be at a disadvantage. Team Wind Howl's players are very strong individually, which is what has allowed them to perform so well at this man to man offensive. It's probably not the best idea to face this head on for Happy."

Just as they spoke, the two teams met. For Team Wind Howl, it was Tang Hao, Lin Feng, and Zhao Yuzhe. As for Happy, all their members were present.

Team Happy's movement speed suddenly fell, while Wind Howl continued to charge forward.

Suddenly, there was a poof from Happy and then purple smoke rapidly spread out, immediately enveloping Happy's characters.

"Smoke Bomb! It's Happy's Deception's Smoke Bomb!" Pan Lin yelled. "No wonder Happy's formation was so closely spaced. Were they wanting to use the cover of Smoke Bomb to make their opponents incapable of figuring out the situation?"

Pan Lin yelled out excitedly, as if he had discovered a new continent. However, Li Yibo frowned, deciding against making any hasty judgements. Did they want to break up Wind Howl's man to man with just a Smoke Bomb? That was underestimating their opponents a little too much, wasn't it? That's what Li Yibo thought.

Childish!

On the field, Wind Howl's captain, Tang Hao, looked at Happy's strategy with disdain. Wind Howl had honed their man to man over and over. It wasn't so easy to break.

Smoke Bomb could conceal characters, but it was best for a single character. With five characters, it was a little too much. It was okay if they didn't move, but once they started moving, the smoke would move, too, and then it was a matter if observing the thickness of the smoke to find out where each character was.

Or, they could just ignore the smoke and wait. It wasn't like the smoke from Smoke Bombs would move with the characters. If Happy's five just sat there, by the time the smoke dispersed, they'd still have to fight.

In conclusion, there were too many ways to counter this. If Happy thought that a Smoke Bomb was some sort of amazing counter strategy, then they were far too naive.

"A single Smoke Bomb can't cover for all of them. Destroy them!" Tang Hao ordered, matching their aggressive style perfectly. In addition, he hadn't even bothered to switch to the team chat, sending the message directly into the public chat.

Happy's strategy was honestly embarrassing. Sending the order directly into the public chat would teach them a lesson, and might have them wavering.

Tang Hao didn't rely purely on passion when fighting. As a captain, he knew what he should do.

Wind Howl's team followed his orders, charging forward. By then, Liu Hao's Spellblade, Absent Sun, and Guo Yang's Qi Master, Qi Breaker, had arrived as well, and they acted in perfect sync with the other three. Wind Howl's playstyle was very mature now.

"I'll get rid of their smoke!" Liu Hao yelled into the chat. He was relatively more cautious. Being unable to see Happy's current situation unsettled him a little.

"Together." Guo Yang, on the left, understood his worries as a teammate back from Excellent Era, and coordinated with him. The two mid-range attackers both had AoE attacks, making pincer attacks very satisfying.

Thus, Absent Sun began casting a Wave Sword while Qi Breaker casted to gather Qi energy. Yet that was when a missile shot out of the smoke, trailing flame behind it. Dancing Rain's missile headed straight for Absent Sun, interrupting his cast. On the other flank, the air seemed to have been pierced through by something, leaving behind a chain of transparent ripples.

Qi Blade!

How could Guo Yang not recognize this skill as a Qi Master player? This was Fang Rui's attack, interrupting his.

The two attacks from the flanks had been interrupted, but Tang Hao's Demon Subduer was already charging in from the front, while Lin Feng's Doubtful Demon had activated Stealth, creeping closer. Zhao Yuzhe's Elementalist, seeing the two casts interrupted, didn't bother starting to cast a powerful spell. He jabbed his staff forward and a Raging Flames exploded up amidst Happy's formation. The flames, rising like a volcanic eruption, shot up several meters, but no characters were blasted up by it.

Tang Hao's Demon Subduer had finally gotten within attack range and Lin Feng's Doubtful Demon had closed in successfully with Sealth. Happy's smoke cover now looked like it was boiling over with those attacks, starting to thin.

"Attack!" With Tang Hao's cry, Team Wind Howl began their most practiced divide and conquer!

Ice Wave Sword!

Liu Hao's Absent Sun swept his blade out, frost swept across the ground, tearing into the smoke. The glittering light blue crystals left a clear mark in the purple smoke.

Hit!

Liu Hao saw the crystals hit a target. He didn't know who it was, exactly, but this target would have their speed slowed. Happy's rhythm was, with this, destroyed.

His blade rose once more, this time surrounded by wisps of flame. Fire Wave Sword, the Wave Sword with the strongest attack power, was prepared, but that was when Liu Hao felt something strange with the ground under Absent Sun' feet. He hurriedly stepped away and looked down, yet found that he was unable to take this step. A vine had wrapped itself around Absent Sun' foot.

Devil World Flower!

Liu Hao was stunned for a moment, immediately remembering that one player in Happy's lineup that had replaced Ye Xiu's position. That rookie-like guy called Luo Ji or something, wasn't his class a Summoner?

Summoner...

Summoner

Liu Hao shuddered, suddenly realizing something...

Tyrannical Chain Punch!

Tang Hao's Demon Subduer had lunged into the fray by then. He didn't care who he'd catch. Divide, their goal was to divide, divide up Happy's five characters and isolate them from one another.

Hit!

Demon Subduer crushed his target against the ground with one hand, his other hand crashing forth. The only thing was that it wasn't as satisfying as he thought it would be. This target seemed so tiny.

Spirit Cat...

It was a measly Spirit Cat...

Summoner...

Summoner!

Tang Hao finally realized what was going on, but soon enough, two sets of sharp claws had caught Demon Subduer's shoulders. Frost Wolf was biting down on Demon Subduer with a mouth full of chilling energy.

Zhao Yuzhe's Elementalist Beautiful Light began to cast a high level spell after Wind Howl had fully opened up their offensive.

Absolute Zero!

He wanted to use this powerful control skill to throw one of Happy's members out of their formation.

However, in the middle of his casting, an eagle's cry sounded from amidst the purple smoke. A Thunder Eagle shot out from the smoke like a bolt of lightning, arriving in the air above Beautiful Light seemingly in the blink of an eye. It opened its mouth, spitting out a thunderbolt and Zhao Yuzhe was forced to dodge, cancelling his cast.

Not good!

Zhao Yuzhe had realized, too.

This wasn't good at all.

The true goal of the Smoke Bomb wasn't to cover for Happy's five characters, but to cover for Happy's Summoner's summoning. Wind Howl wanted to fight man to man, but with a Summoner, how could they manage? A Summoner meant that there would always be more characters.

A mistake!

They had made a huge mistake.

No one had expected that Happy's rookie would be the key character in their team competition. Summoner! This class was a rather obvious counter to Wind Howl's man to man style, but Wind Howl had neglected to consider him and forgotten to deal with him.

This was only because he was replacing Ye Xiu. Everyone was shocked, but had forgotten to consider what sort of value the person who had been substituted in might have in this team competition.

Forgetting a rookie could be fatal too!

Chapter 1366 - The Limits of Happy's Summoner

Wind Howl with their man to man offense had neglected to consider the Summoner amongst Happy’s ranks. This was a humiliatingly rookie mistake.

Team Happy’s courage and their confidence in their players had reached an absurd level. For other teams, how many of them would be willing to bet everything on a rookie, even when knowing that Summoners were a counter to Wind Howl’s playstyle? A rookie that hadn’t played many rounds since his debut at that?

That’s what Happy had done. As for the humiliating mistake Wind Howl had made, barely anyone had the heart to criticize them for it, because most people had neglected to consider this as well, just like Wind Howl.

Just as everyone was obsessing over how Ye Xiu wasn’t playing, now many people had stopped to think how Happy would face this match without Ye Xiu?

From their perspective, Happy was just messing around with Ye Xiu not playing.

Unfortunately, with a Smoke Bomb and a Summoner, Happy had used two rookies of theirs that rarely played in official matches to dismantle Wind Howl’s man to man offense.

The smoke had more or less dispersed and Happy’s impressive formation was revealed. Concealed Light’s summons made Team Wind Howl’s man to man seem ever so idiotic.

Liu Hao’s Absent Sun was caught by the Devil World Flower’s vines.

Tang Hao’s Demon Subduer had managed to pin a Spirit Cat, but his own head was in the jaws of a Frost Wolf, a rather terrifying sight. 　 Zhao Yuzhe’s Beautiful Light had been locked onto by a Thunder Eagle. Though there was no way a single summon could be much of a threat to a pro player, he’d have to ask the Thunder Eagle before he could attack Happy.

Was Guo Yang’s Qi Breaker and Lin Feng’s Doubtful Demon in the clear then?

Of course not!

Happy was a team, and Luo Ji wasn’t the only one in it. Concealed Light’s summons had occupied three of Wind Howl’s players, and the other members of Happy had plenty of freedom to act as they wished!

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain engaged Qi Breaker with her artillery. However, the most unfortunate one was Lin Feng. He was a battle Thief and had sneaked over with Doubtful Demon under Stealth, planning to tear a character out of Happy’s formation. However, the smoke dispersed, his Stealth wore off, and then he got surrounded.

Tang Rou, Fang Rui, Mo Fan’s three characters had surrounded Doubtful Demon.

Dismantling an opponent’s strategy didn’t count as a victory. A true victory was dealing a critical blow to the opponent. Strategies could be switched and adjusted. Wind Howl wouldn’t have the rookie mistake of forgetting the Summoner in their opponent’s ranks again.

Thus, Happy would naturally want to use this chance and deal a critical blow to Team Wind Howl first. Otherwise, they would’ve merely tanked past their opponent’s first wave of attacks; without a counterattack, what use was that?

Lin Feng was currently deeply lodged in Happy’s counterattack. Being ganged up on by three people had him incapable of fighting back. Doubtful Demon’s health plummeted, however, there wasn’t nearly enough time to erase Doubtful Demon from the field in one go.

Just a Thunder Eagle wasn’t nearly enough to completely control Zhao Yuzhe.

It might have looked scary with Frost Wolf’s jaws clamped around Demon Subduer’s head, but this was just a game. The damage didn’t increase just because of how scary the scene was. However, the frosty breath of Frost Wolf would give Demon Subduer a slow that could prove annoying for Tang Hao.

Liu Hao’s Absent Sun was only caught by the vine, which only limited his movements. He could still attack from there. The attack range of Wave Swords could still reach Happy.

In the end, the only one who was pinned rather badly was Qi Breaker under Dancing Rain’s assault. Summons, in the end, wasn’t as good as a pro player, not nearly good enough!

“In the current situation, Happy has the advantage, but we can’t determine the victors just from that. We’ll still have to see how well they perform.” Li Yibo could tell that the battle was far from over and commented with this in the live broadcast.

“Indeed. Liu Hao’s Absent Sun might be rooted in place by Devil World Flower, but Happy is still within his attack range. He can definitely still provide Lin Feng with support!” Pan Lin exclaimed.

Earthquake Sword! 　 Liu Hao, as Pan Lin said, soon had Absent Sun provide support for Doubtful Demon.

However, Devil World Flower had become a shield then. Doubtful Demon was dragged behind Devil World Flower and beaten down. Absent Sun’s Wave Sword attacks couldn’t go around Devil World Flower no matter what. Earthquake Sword was all for naught. But Liu Hao did see a missile rocket over, bouncing on the ground twice before landing in front of him after the dust kicked up by Earthquake Sword dispersed.

That bitch!

Liu Hao only had the time to curse in anger before the Heat Seeking Missile descended, spewing fire. Absent Sun, trapped by the vine couldn’t dodge.

Boom! 　 A mushroom cloud engulfed Absent Sun. Su Mucheng, who was primarily dealing with Qi Breaker, managed to divide some of her precious time and focus to send Liu hao a gift.

Tang Hao’s Demon Subduer managed to finally escape by then. 　 Fling!

The Frost Wolf was grabbed by Demon Subduer. Though his speed had been reduced due to the slow, the power of his attack wasn’t reduced at all. The Frost Wolf was thrown right at Tang Rou and co.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

But that was when Tang Rou, attacking even as she defended against his assault, charged out with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks, knocking the Frost Wolf away and stabbing right towards Demon Subduer.

Tang Hao’s reaction speed and mechanics were perfect, but he couldn’t do anything about Demon Subduer’s slow. With Tang Rou’s abrupt and resolute change in targets, his character couldn’t keep up with his attempt to dodge. With a clink, Demon Subduer was sent flying by Soft Mist.

However, Tang Rou didn’t bother pursuing him. Soft Mist turned right back, continuing her assault on Doubtful Demon.

“Happy is doing very well. Their play is methodical, very well paced!” Li Yibo exclaimed in awe.

“But, like this, hasn’t Demon Subduer escaped his pin? Tang Hao will be free to join the fray!” Pan Lin said.

“Really?” Li Yibo smiled.

On the field, Concealed Light’s casting and orders continued relentlessly.

The Four Summon Beasts were what he mained, and this number was also one he was good at controlling. However, right now, Luo Ji didn’t conserve anything. He summoned all and any summons that were available to Concealed Light.

Some low leveled summon creatures had very limited attack power, but Luo Ji wasn’t counting on these summons to finish the battle. All these summons had one job: to stall and pin their opponents. They were like line after line of defense, preventing Wind Howl from engaging with Happy.

To achieve this goal, Luo Ji summoned relentlessly. Luo Ji’s mana was the one thing that was being exhausted the fastest on the field. Normally, Summoners definitely wouldn’t fight like this. Otherwise, they’d use up their mana before they managed to defeat their opponents. However, the task of defeating their opponents had been given to the others in Happy, and Luo Ji’s task was simply to use his summons to continuously harass his opponents.

This was a trade: Concealed Light’s mana for the opponent’s HP. Right now, Lin Feng’s Doubtful Demon’s health was being depleted just like Luo Ji’s mana.

Under the combined efforts of three of Happy’s members, he couldn’t retaliate at all. He could only stall as much as possible, waiting for his teammates to save him, and what Luo Ji was doing was preventing this sort of support. Concealed Light’s summons and Dancing Rain’s long-ranged firepower had become the biggest hindrance to Team Wind Howl.

A measly rookie Summoner had managed to stall their entire team?

This reality was driving Wind Howl crazy.

But what could they do?

Luo Ji’s crazed summoning had creature after creature appear in front of them. He was also giving the summons orders the best he could, not just sending them up to die.

With Luo Ji’s mechanics, he wouldn’t be able to do it perfectly. However, the choice in what details to focus on and which to neglect was something he was accomplishing very well this time. He couldn’t perfect his mechanics, but he would act when needed at the crucial moments.

Those who looked down on Luo Ji, but had some understanding of Glory, snapped their mouths shut. Anyone could tell how important Luo Ji was to this match. Though he wasn’t the main DPS, he was an indispensable part of Happy’s strategy. He was like a healer, barely providing any DPS, but who would say that a healer had no value on the field?

As for those who were a little more skilled, they were shocked by Luo Ji’s performance.

It was true that he wasn’t top notch with mechanics, but he had managed to do what he could, the best he could.

Precise calculations, a carefully executed rhythm.

Happy seemed to have produced another interesting player!

Although his natural talent was limited, he could perform at his limit.

For example, if this were an exam, some had the ability to achieve a 100 percent, but because they would make mistakes out of carelessness, they only achieved 90 percent. As for Luo Ji, he was someone who could only achieve a maximum 90 percent, but in the end that was what he achieved. With that, his actual performance was no different from those who could achieve 100 but only got 90.

“Wind Howl needs to find a way to turn things around. This mess won’t be good for them if it continues,” Li Yibo commented. 　 “Then, Advisor Li, what do you think Wind Howl needs to do to solve this dilemma?” Pan Lin asked. 　 “Cooperate,” Li Yibo replied, “Wind Howl needs to work as a team. Only by cooperating and advancing as a team can they successfully deal with Concealed Light’s stream of summons. Right now, they’re each doing their own thing. It’s far too low-efficiency. This is the root of why Luo Ji has managed to stall them all by himself.”

“As a team…” Pan Lin wasn’t too sure what to say anymore. Everyone knew that Wind Howl had ended up with this man to man style because they performed too terribly as a team. With that, they could brute force a battle of cooperation and teamwork into one on one duels. Yet now, Wind Howl had to work as a team to solve their current crisis.

“That’s probably… a little hard for them now, no?” Pan Lin lamented. He couldn’t lean too much to one side right now, after all!

Chapter 1367 - Wind Howl That Needs Teamwork

To have Wind Howl play as a team…

Everyone who heard Li Yibo’s evaluation went silent.

If Wind Howl could play beautifully as one, would they have needed to resort to their current method? In the end, a man to man full offensive playstyle was on the extreme end. When employing such an imbalanced playstyle, a slight fault in execution could result in the opponents grasping a huge opportunity.

This time, because Wind Howl had neglected Happy’s Summoner, they had fallen into such a crisis.

Lose like this?

No!

No one in Wind Howl was willing to give up. Who was that? Luo Ji? A name they had never even heard of, an unknown noob, was about to be their downfall? How could they live with that?

“Stand firm!” Tang Hao roared in the chat. Who knew if he wanted Lin Feng to persist, or if he wanted the whole team to continue with their current playstyle and look for an opportunity to break through. After he yelled out this order, the Frost Wolf summoned by Concealed Light once again pounced towards him relentlessly. Frost Wolf was one of Concealed Light’s four main summons. Its battle power couldn’t compare to the miscellaneous summons he only added a few points in. In addition to its naturally high defense and health, it wasn’t something that could be dealt with in just a few blows, not even by Tang Hao.

Back Throw!

Tang Hao could use a high priority move to have Demon Subduer throw the Frost Wolf behind him. However, in the blink of an eye, the Frost Wolf had climbed back up and pounced again!

As Wind Howl’s core, a lot of importance had been attached to Demon Subduer, but the enemy summons seemed to be endless; no matter what he did, he could never get rid of them all.

No, it’s not like this!

Tang Hao was still a top-tier God. He obviously knew that although a Summoner had a lot of summons, they didn’t have an endless amount of them. The enemy Summoner had an extremely strong grasp of rhythm, linking attack after attack. His calculations were immaculate.

This guy… Tang Hao realized that Happy’s Luo Ji wasn’t a player that could casually be ignored.

If it was a 1v1, Luo Ji’s annoying tactics were nothing to be afraid of. If one came, he would kill one. If two came, he would kill two. He could just keep on killing summon after summon until Luo Ji ran out of mana. However, in the amount of time it took for him to kill one summon, who knew how much damage Lin Feng’s Doubtful Demon would take. If he didn’t hurry and rescue him, Wind Howl would immediately have one less player the enemy side. Such a wide disparity could not be casually erased.

“Restrict Concealed Light’s summons!” Tang Hao finally gave the order.

When Chen Guo saw this scene, she felt a wave of joy.

Luo Ji seemed to be Happy’s weakest member. He hadn’t been used until the very end of the season, but in this match, the arrogant Team Wind Howl and the overbearing captain Tang Hao had unexpectedly targeted him.

They weren’t focusing on Luo Ji because he was the weakest member, or because he was the easiest to bully, but rather because he was the one putting a halt to Wind Howl’s plans.

He had not only received the acknowledgement of his teammates, but the acknowledgement of an extremely proud opponent. Even if it was just in this team competition, Lou Ji had firmly cemented his place. Chen Guo believed that no matter what ended up happening, Tang Hao would certainly remember the name Luo Ji, this noob who had brought so much trouble to them.

Well done! You have to win!

Chen Guo celebrated quietly.

But Wind Howl had already started acting. Under Tang Hao’s clear orders, they began targeting Concealed Light. And this would be a group effort. In the end, Wind Howl had been forced to change their recently successful playstyle to deal with the situation.

Zhao Yuzhe’s Beautiful Light suddenly Teleported, abandoning his original position. Wind Howl’s formation had reason behind it. Every player’s position efficiently split apart each opponent. But because they were switching up their tactics, Zhao Yuzhe immediately threw his position aside. There was also Liu Hao. His Absent Sun was no longer being restricted by vines. After receiving the order, he immediately moved horizontally, his movements matching Zhao Yuzhe’s. Team Wind Howl’s team play was indeed lacking, but they had built up synergy in a certain places. After all, each player was individually talented. If they truly couldn’t work together at all, they wouldn’t be qualified to be pro players.

Absent Sun and Beautiful Light had joined together despite the blockade of summons. Beautiful Light’s Teleport had contributed greatly towards it. No matter how fast a Thunder Eagle may be, it could not achieve instant movement.

After the two characters met up, Absent Sun moved to the front, while Beautiful Light moved to the back, forming a shield. The charging summons were dealt with by Liu Hao’s Absent Sun, while Zhao Yuzhe’s Beautiful Light began casting in safety.

Then, a Satellite Beam crashed to the ground, sweeping towards them. The two immediately dodged.

This girl again!

Liu Hao’s irritation had reached a peak, and Su Mucheng had kept it there. Dancing Rain’s firepower suddenly shifted towards them, unleashing a fierce assault.

Absent Sun dodged with difficulty, and without protection, Beautiful Light could not continue casting.

Everyone in the audience shook their heads.

This was exactly why Wind Howl could not play well together. They had a certain level of synergy, but it stopped there. Their teamwork was easily broken apart. Not only that, the two had just gotten together, but were separated by a Satellite Beam. The two were now getting farther and farther apart. They had initially intended on coordinating with each other, but in the blink of an eye, their plan was destroyed without a sliver of it remaining.

“Wind Howl may have realized that their top priority is to stop Luo Ji from summoning freely. However, Wind Howl still hasn’t found a good solution to it yet. Liu Hao and Zhao Yuzhe tried to convene, but Su Mucheng easily broke them apart,” Pan Lin said.

“Their teamwork still isn’t good enough! In team battles, Wind Howl’s foresight is rather lacking. Liu Hao’s and Zhao Yuzhe’s coordination was somewhat hurried. They failed to consider the issue of timing,” Li Yibo had the courage to talk about Wind Howl’s teamwork because it was rather weak. Weak meant superficial. Li Yibo could see through them without much effort.

“Then, Coach Li, what do you think they should do?” Pan Lin asked.

“They could have Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe act as bait from one end, while Liu Hao and Guo Yang work from the other end. The two were old teammates in Excellent Era. Their synergy together should be quite high,” Li Yibo was more than bold enough to talk about Wind Howl’s plans.

“Indeed, that would be better. Hm? Liu Hao is…” Pan Lin suddenly noticed something.

“Huh? This is…” Li Yibo also noticed it.

“He’s pretending to retreat, but in reality, he’s looking to coordinate with Guo Yang,” Pan Lin yelled.

“Guo Yang’s Qi Breaker has made a move! Dancing Rain shifting targets gave him an opening, and he grasped that opening well,” Pan Lin shouted.

“Su Mucheng’s attacks were a bit excessive! She should have been able to promptly shift back. This opening shouldn’t have existed,” Li Yibo remarked.

It was already too late though. Guo Yang’s Qi Break was able to complete a cast during this opening.

“Cloud Grasping Fist!” Pan Lin shouted.

Everyone’s hearts leapt to their throats. Could Qi Breaker’s move turn the tables for Wind Howl? The camera zoomed in on Concealed Light.

But…

“Dancing Rain?” Pan Lin was astonished. Guo Yang’s Qi Breaker was just barely able to find an opening to disrupt Happy’s momentum, but he targeted Dancing Rain instead of Concealed Light?

“How calm!” Li Yibo praised, “Grabbing Concealed Light from his position was rather difficult. One slight slip-up, or if the summons got in his way, he might just end up grabbing a summon instead.”

“That’s why grabbing Dancing Rain is actually an excellent choice. Dancing Rain has been Cloud Grasped and is out of the picture. Wait, she hasn’t stopped attacking!” Pan Lin was unable to keep his thoughts to himself and ended with a cry of surprise.

Dancing Rain had been forcefully separated from her team with Cloud Grasping Fist, but she continued to bombard Liu Hao’s Absent Sun with attacks. Despite the forced movements, her attacks were still as precise as ever. Hit, hit, hit, hit after hit! Liu Hao’s Absent Sun was blown up, as if there really was no sun.

“Could it be… Liu Hao isn’t actually intentionally giving away openings, but rather Su Mucheng’s attacks are truly so fierce that he’s being forced into so many openings?” Li Yibo was astonished.

“So you’re saying, Guo Yang’s opening came out of blind luck?” Pan Lin said.

“It’s hard to say…” Li Yibo said. It really was hard to say, but seeing how Dancing Rain had been pulled away, yet refused to let up her attacks, those really were his thoughts.

Dancing Rain bombarded Absent Sun as she moved towards Qi Breaker. Her speed actually increased because of the recoil from her attacks. Her character continued to grow larger and larger in front of Guo Yang’s eyes.

This… why does this feel familiar?

Guo Yang suddenly had a strange feeling rise up. He didn’t have time to think carefully about it. Dancing Rain had already arrived in front of him…

“Behind!!”

Guo Yang saw a warning from the team chat.

Behind?

How could there be anyone behind him? Happy’s players were all in front of him! Wait, no! Isn’t there someone missing? Soft Mist?

Guo Yang suddenly realized where that feeling of deja vu came from.

Launching Spear…

This was a tactic that Ye Qiu and Su Mucheng had once used. What they meant by behind wasn’t behind Qi Breaker, but rather behind Dancing Rain. Behind her was Soft Mist…

Dancing Fire Flowing Flames swept by as the air itself seemed to boil. Guo Yang had the opportunity to strike Dancing Rain, but then the following Battle Mage attacks could not be dodged.

What to do?

This was a question that countless Excellent Era opponents got headaches from, but this time, it was Guo Yang’s turn.

Guo Yang didn’t run away because his memory told him that when this tactic came, dodging would turn out worse than standing firm.

Qigong Blast!

Qi Breaker’s palm slammed towards Dancing Rain as Dancing Fire Flowing Flame swept towards him.

Chapter 1368 - Both Sides Stalling One on Two

Boom!

The Qigong Blast crashed through Dancing Rain’s body, qi buffeting her long hair. Qi Breaker was unable to avoid Soft Mist’s attack either, but Guo Yang’s attention was mostly focused on Dancing Rain.

Launching Spear. This was a rare method of attack of Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng’s where the Launcher was the main attacker. The Battle Mage’s sneak attack from behind the Launcher was just to set up the foundations of the assault. Next, the Launcher would engulf the target in a barrage of close ranged artillery fire.

Guo Yang was an ex-player of Excellent Era’s, after all, so he had seen this technique plenty of times in matches and was taught about it in training as well.

Be on guard against Su Mucheng.

That was what experience told him. However, this time, all Dancing Rain did was turn her back on him. Guo Yang anxiously waited for her to turn around, yet she didn’t, instead slowly moving away from him…

She… she left?  Up.dated b.y B o x Novel. com

Guo Yang was shocked. What the hell was this? This wasn’t how the Launching Spear went. He hesitated, but Tang Rou didn’t. Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flame burned through the air towards him. Dancing Rain was already behind her. Although Dancing Rain didn’t seem to have any intentions of turning around, her attacks hadn’t stopped at all, still bombarding Liu Hao’s Total Darkness relentlessly.

What was this?

Guo Yang was completely baffled. From start to finish, Su Mucheng didn’t even glance over. Was this really the Launching Spear? Resisting the urge to beg for attention, Guo Yang focused on dealing with Tang Rou. After the first strike, Soft Mist’s attacks were raining down on him rapidly. Guo Yang realized that even though it was just this one person, he wouldn’t be able to deal with her offensive that easily. 　 Thus, looking back on the process, the cooperative aspect of the Launching Spear seemed completely nonexistent. Tang Rou merely used this method to help Su Mucheng escape the Cloud-Grasping Fist. And then? Then Tang Rou attacked Guo Yang while Su Mucheng never stopped her assault on Liu Hao. Even when she was dragged away by Cloud Grasping Fist, she didn’t even give Guo Yang’s Qi Breaker a single glance.

“This… what were they trying to do?” Commentator Pan Lin was confused and looked at Li Yibo for an answer.

“This… is probably because she doesn’t want to stop her offensive! Su Mucheng has been very successful in suppressing Liu Hao, after all.” Li Yibo was also filled with confusion, but as a VIP guest commentator, he was here to explain uncertainties and not ask questions, so he had no choice but to answer Pan Lin.

“She seems to be very focused on dealing with Liu Hao…” Pan Lin noted.

“Probably because she has a better understanding of him, since he’s an ex-teammate!” Li Yibo guessed.

“But so is Guo Yang!”

“…” In the end, Li Yibo still ended up lost as to how to answer. However, thinking carefully, Su Mucheng’s performance in this round really was rather strange. No matter if it was back at Excellent Era, or currently at Happy, she generally performed a supporting role in their tactical system. It wasn’t like there weren’t times where she’d open up an offensive, but for her to lock onto a single person and bombard them relentlessly like this, that was extremely rare. Su Mucheng seemed like she was determined to act on Wind Howl’s strategy, trying to tear Liu Hao’s Total Darkness out of Wind Howl’s team.

Boom boom boom!

Boom boom boom!

The broadcast also gave Su Mucheng a lot of focus. Steadily, everyone began realizing that this was rather uncharacteristic. Su Mucheng seemed to have left Happy’s tactical system and went to 1v1 Liu Hao.

Was this girl crazy?

Liu Hao frantically had Total Darkness dodge, feeling rather surprised. He was pretty sure he wasn’t a key figure in Wind Howl’s strategy, no? It wasn’t like he was Happy’s Luo Ji. Why was Su Mucheng so focused on him? Had she gotten something wrong?

Roll, jump, run… Liu Hao’s Total Darkness acted like he was here to attend a sports competition, only able to execute these technical actions. Counterattack? His Spellblade didn’t have the range of a Launcher. If he wanted to counterattack, he had to be able to actually reach her first!

Generally speaking, the further the distance, the weaker the control on the target. However, Dancing Rain’s attacks were so well spaced that Liu Hao couldn’t see any of the openings that distance should’ve given him.

He slowly began to panic. He had known and fought beside Su Mucheng for years, and never once had he noticed how aggressive she was. What was with this feeling? It was like he was prey with a predator staring down his neck.

He wasn’t the only one who was surprised. All those who knew Su Mucheng well enough were all shocked at her uncharacteristic actions.

Did… she have a grudge or something?

That was what many people were thinking by then. Su Mucheng’s playstyle wasn’t at all like a tactic that Happy had planned for, but more like cathartic venting.

Su Mucheng’s burst of strength had the match twisting in another direction. Currently, Tang Rou and Guo Yang were fighting 1v1, Fang Rui and Mo Fan were ganging up on Lin Feng, while Luo Ji was stalling both Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe at once. As for Su Mucheng and Liu Hao, the former was completely suppressing the latter.

From this perspective, the match didn’t seem much different from a man to man. It was just that this situation had a 1v2 and a one 2v1, and it was all with Happy at an advantage.

Lin Feng’s Doubtful Demon, after being bullied by three people for so long, was still helpless against the two that remained. Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe, the two that were viewed as the cores of their team now, were being stalled by a single rookie Summoner.

However, they hadn’t lost much health, and instead, Concealed Light had expended a huge amount of mana. Yet anyone could see what Concealed Light was trading this mana for.

Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe were both very confident in themselves. Currently, being stalled by Luo Ji 2v1 for so long, the mental blow that this dealt to them was more significant. As for Luo Ji? Originally, he had to have his summon creatures stall several targets and now, suddenly, that number had fallen to two. His mechanics became more focused and active. This 90 point student was performing exceptionally this time, reaching a score of 95. 　 However, the one who had been in the worst situation this entire battle was still Lin Feng.

From the very beginning, he had been encircled and beaten. He had no choice but to watch and wait for help. He waited, and waited, yet Wind Howl’s actions were like thunder without the rain or lightning. They had fought up till now, and although his opponents had fallen to just two, he still couldn’t hold up against them!

On some level, Lin Feng, at first, could be considered to be holding off 1v3, and now 1v2, but his teammates had to deal with the problem at hand while he held them off! Unfortunately, Wind Howl couldn’t deal with the problem at hand, and Lin Feng was slowly being dealt with by their opponents.

“It seems like Wind Howl still hasn’t found a solution.” Pan Lin had said this who knows how many times already.

“However, they’ve at least managed to increase Concealed Light’s mana expenditure. This way, if Concealed Light’s mana runs out when Doubtful Demon is defeated, then they’ll still be able to fight this match. A Summoner without mana is more or less equal to a dead character,” Li Yibo analysed.

“Could this be the solution Wind Howl has decided to go with?” Pan Lin asked.

“Perhaps!”

“How brutal!” Pan Lin exclaimed.

“Hahaha…” Li Yibo laughed weakly. Brutal? More like helpless! Did Wind Howl really plan this or get into this situation by chance? Who knew? Either way, Wind Howl wasn’t in a good position.

Would Doubtful Demon’s health be depleted first, or Concealed Light’s mana?

The live broadcast displayed the two’s health and mana side by side, reminding the audience of the crucial point to this battle. The playing on the field seemed to have realized this as well. Lin Feng hadn’t given up, still stubbornly struggling against the two person pincer. As a Battle Thief, he’d occasionally use some dirty tactics. After all, playing dirty was better for survival than tanking through. As for Luo Ji, he really didn’t have any further ideas. Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe were putting even more pressure on him. He could only face them head on; he couldn’t let his guard down at all.

If only his mechanics were a little better! Luo Ji, even doing his absolute best, still didn’t feel like this was enough. However, this was already the ceiling of his ability. He was already performing past his limit, and no one doubted his skill any longer. However, Luo Ji wasn’t satisfied with himself. If he could do even better, then Happy wouldn’t have fallen into this situation in the first place. It was because he wasn’t good enough that he had to deplete his mana and throw his summons out like cannon fodder in order to stall the opponents.

Their current situation wasn’t so good!

Just in terms of calculation, Luo Ji’s ability was cream of the crop. Even when everyone else only had a vague judgement, he had already managed to calculate the rate at which the two gauges were going down. 　 Not good, not good at all!

If this continued, his mana would be depleted first. Then, if he was unable to stop those two, Doubtful Demon might even be saved, and everything would’ve been for nothing.

They needed support!

Luo Ji was desperate. He wanted to notify his teammates, but Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe were on him too hard. He didn’t have any time to type.

No voice, what a shitty rule!

Luo Ji was even cursing the Alliance match rules now.

“Hurry, we gotta hurry!” Fang Rui, by then, had also realized that he and Mo Fan might not be efficient enough. However, he had the the time to spare to send a message. On one hand, this was to tell Mo Fan to hurry. On the other, it was also telling the two 1v1 fighters that they might need some support, and to provide it if they could..

Tang Rou understood what Fang Rui was trying to say, and had the intentions of pulling her battle over. However, the experienced Guo Yang was clear on the situation of the battle and knew that Lin Feng definitely couldn’t take more damage. He immediately clung to Soft Mist with everything he had.

Just a little bit more! A little bit longer!

Everyone was staring at the two’s HP and MP. As the two numbers fell, the situation became clearer and clearer. It wasn’t looking good for Happy! Summoners were mana hungry classes in the first place, and with this playstyle, the player was doing all he could to the best he could, there was no reason to criticise this sort of performance.

Was Happy’s spectacular arrangement and performance going to be brute forced through by Wind Howl like that? Apart from Wind Howl fans, everyone felt that this was quite a shame for Happy.

“We need some artillery support!!” Fang Rui finally yelled for help directly. He wasn’t Tang Hao or Zhao Yuzhe. When it was time to call for reinforcements, he wouldn’t hesitate at all.

Boom!

An explosion immediately enveloped Doubtful Demon, which surprised even Fang Rui, who was right nearby. Support came right when he asked for it. Did he have some sort of superpower?

“Sorry, I’m late,” Su Mucheng sent into the chat.

That was when everyone suddenly remembered that there was another set of players on the field. Su Mucheng had returned, and what about Liu Hao?

Liu Hao… had already been defeated?!

Spellblade Total Darkness was the first to be wiped off the field. Defeated by Su Mucheng, Dancing Rain, alone?

Nomyummi She definitely has a grudge.

Chapter 1369 - Who’s the MVP?

Liu Hao was killed?

Once everyone realized that this was true, they were all stunned.

That was absurd! Lin Feng was still holding on after being ganged up on for so long, but Liu Hao’s Absent Sun had been crushed by Su Mucheng on her own?

No one had expected that the 1v1 duels would be the first to end, so in this time, no matter if it was the live broadcast or the audience’s attention, they were all focused on Lin Feng and Luo Ji’s 1v2s.

Lin Feng was forced into a 1v2, while Luo Ji had the initiative for his 1v2. This indirect face off between the two seemed to be coming to an end with Concealed Light’s mana running out, but no one had ever expected that the 1v1 on the other side would see a result first.

How did Su Mucheng destroy Liu Hao so quickly?

The battle was tense and the live broadcast couldn’t possibly replay that section. Everyone could only watch dumbly, as the battle raged on.

With Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain back, she helped Fang Rui and Mo Fan turn their battle into a 3v1 even as she sent some firepower support towards Luo Ji’s side of things. The situation immediately turned, and soon enough, the face off ended with Doubtful Demon’s death. Instantly, the 5v5 situation became a 5v3, and Wind Howl’s Cleric hadn’t even managed to rush over yet.

It was over.

That was what everyone was thinking. Wind Howl had lost two people at once, so man to man wasn’t an option anymore. Fight as a team? Could Wind Howl beat Happy with a number disadvantage? Even if Happy didn’t have Ye Xiu, they had proven their strength as a team in the three consecutive rounds of Ye Xiu-less team competitions. A team that could fight Thunderclap’s to the bitter end, who dared underestimate them?

They were going to lose…

A lifeless silence engulfed Wind Howl’s home stadium.

This loss was a crisis for Wind Howl. With this result, they might fall to the same number of points as Hundred Blossoms, meaning that they’d both have to fight for that extra boost in points in the last round. With the tiebreaker in their favor, Wind Howl wasn’t afraid of tying in points, but if they had even a one point disadvantage, then they’ll be kicked out of the playoffs.

“How is Hundred Blossoms doing against Tyranny?” Li Yibo asked after this problem for all those who were curious.

“Er, it’s still ongoing.” Pan Lin looked over the information sent over from the other stadium.

“Ah!” Pan Lin suddenly cried out after looking more closely at the contents, “They’re in the lead. Team Hundred Blossoms is currently in the lead in terms of numbers. They managed to get the advantage in numbers in their home game.”

An advantage in numbers was generally how team competitions were judged while ongoing. If the other side couldn’t mitigate this imbalance in time, then the final result would be exactly what they didn’t want to see.

“If Hundred Blossoms wins, then they’ll be tied with Wind Howl in the final round,” Li Yibo noted.

“The match between 301 Degrees and Seaside is about to end. 301 Degrees should be able to win without much trouble,” Pan Lin continued.

“Then 301 Degrees will be 2 points ahead of Hundred Blossoms and Wind Howl,” Li Yibo concluded. “And the other matches?”

“Thunderclap currently has the advantage in numbers as well,” Pan Lin replied.

“It seems like they really do have a chance to beat Samsara!” Li Yibo’s tone was filled with admiration.

“If so, then Happy and Thunderclap will both have a 7 point advantage in the last round,” Pan Lin said.

“But they still shouldn’t let down their guard! Especially Happy, their opponent for the last round is 301 Degrees. 301 Degrees only has a 2 point lead. They’d definitely go all out in the last round. If Happy really does slip up and lose by a little too much, and if Hundred Blossoms and Wind Howl manage to win big, they might be left behind!” Li Yibo said.

“The… the chances of that are a little too low…” Pan Lin said.

“Ha. It’s true that there are a lot of requirements to meet, but Happy really can’t let down their guard. In contrast, Thunderclap’s last opponent is Miracle. I think they’re completely in the safe zone now,” Li Yibo said.

The two’s discussion was already on the next round, not giving any attention to the ongoing match. In their eyes, Wind Howl, down two people, had no way of turning the tides. The match was already at its end.

However, Wind Howl clearly didn’t want to give up. After a moment of silence, the in-venue audience exploded with cheers and shouts of encouragement. On the field, Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe weren’t the kind of people who gave up when they fell behind. They were still giving it their all, trying to use their skill to overturn the match.

However, Happy had become cautious, their entire team drawing back, heading towards the support zones and clearly aiming to switch in their healer. With Wind Howl’s disadvantage in numbers, they couldn’t stop Happy’s retreat even with their Cleric’s arrival.

Yet, once they arrived at the support zones, Happy didn’t directly switch their players, they first set a trap. When Wind Howl arrived in their relentless pursuit, they were struck full force by Concealed Light’s final Elemental Beast King Formation.

The requirements for activating the Elemental Beast King Formation was to have all four summon beasts on the field and standing in the required positions. After activation, the four summon beast’s combative ability would dramatically increase. Thunder Eagle and Young Wyvern’s thunderbolts and fireballs shot out like bullets from a machine gun. The chill that spread when Frost Wolf opened its maws and howled spread a layer of frost across the field. Spirit Cat, originally very agile, had its speed raised another level, it’s form darting from one place to the next leaving broken after images behind.

Being able to control such powerful summons was a delight for any Summoner, but this delight wouldn’t continue on forever. The powered up four summon beasts still had health and could be killed, and their active time would be calculated according to the active time of the Elemental Beast King Formation. When the skill ended, the four summon beasts would all disappear. In addition, during the time the Elemental Beast King Formation was active, the summoning of the four summon beasts were deactivated. They couldn’t be resummoned.

Luo Ji, an underestimated rookie Summoner, had become the star of this show. It was only after the Elemental Beast King Formation ended that An Wenyi and Little Cold Hands were switched in. Happy then fought steadily while Wind Howl’s Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe, unwilling to give up, continued to struggle. But their struggles were futile.

“Alright, now Wind Howl’s last character, Tang Hao’s Demon Subduer, has fallen. In the end, Wind Howl still lost this team competition,” Commentator Pan Lin announced.

“With that, the results of this match are 4 to 6, Happy with a total of 244 points, while Wind Howl had 237. The two teams will enter the last round of the regular season with a seven point difference,” Li Yibo said.

“Coach Li, what do you think about this match?” Pan Lin asked.

The match had finished and the results were out, meaning that Li Yibo was much freer to comment as he wished, “Hm, well, although Ye Xiu didn’t fight, they clearly made ample preparations for this battle. Their strategy was executed very well, and a great counter to Wind Howl’s playstyle. They managed to grasp the initiative from the very start.” 　 “Indeed. Team Happy’s Luo Ji was the greatest surprise and delight of the match. It was truly unexpected, but also a very reasonable coincidence,” Pan Lin agreed.

“That’s right. On the other hand, for Wind Howl, neglecting to consider Luo Ji was a fatal mistake they made at the very beginning. No matter what kind of player the opponent is, just the fact that there was a Summoner meant that Wind Howl should utilize the appropriate countermeasures. Though Wind Howl only knew of Happy’s player switch when the match was about to begin, they should have adjusted accordingly, but they didn’t. They didn’t even think to counter Luo Ji’s Summoner until halfway through, and afterwards, they didn’t execute that counter well either,” Li Yibo analysed.

“Despite that, Wind Howl actually still had a chance, right?” Pan Lin asked.

“Yes. Even if Luo Ji’s Summoner dismantled their man to man playstyle, this dismantling came at a huge cost to Luo Ji. Using their willpower and individual abilities, they might not have been able to break through Luo Ji’s summon creature wall, but they could deplete Concealed Light’s mana. Unfortunately, that’s when a major problem appeared. I believe everyone noticed this,” Li Yibo said.

“Liu Hao, right?” Pan Lin questioned.

“Yes. Just as Wind Howl’s entire team was holding on, waiting for Concealed Light’s mana to be completely depleted, Liu Hao fell to Su Mucheng. This is another immense surprise in this match. In reality, Wind Howl’s eventual loss was because of this one event. If it wasn’t for this, then even with Happy’s arrangements, Wind Howl would still have a chance. However, Liu Hao’s defeat pretty much killed all of Wind Howl’s hopes,” Li Yibo explained.

“Uh huh. We still have some time left so, next, let’s look back at what really happened and how Liu Hao was killed so quickly by Su Mucheng.” As Pan Lin talked, the shot in the broadcast switched to Dancing Rain’s barrage against Absent Sun.

As the battle raged, Pan Lin and Li Yibo waited to comment, and the blasts of the Launcher’s cannon resounded in the audience’s ears.

“Su Mucheng’s style is very resolute this time. What do you think, Coach Li?” Pan Lin finally spoke up.

“Yes, we’ve never seen such resolution from her. Su Mucheng accurately grasped the match point. Look, she had completely stopped the wide range support she’d usually provide in matches, focusing all her attention on Liu Hao’s Absent Sun. Her performance is impeccable and Liu Hao was completely suppressed. He was completely helpless, and she crushed him, otherwise how else would he have died so fast? Over there, Lin Feng’s Thief fighting 1v3, then 1v2, had managed to hold on for longer!” Li Yibo commented. 　 “Liu Hao’s performance definitely wasn’t the best this time!” Pan Lin exclaimed.

“Indeed. Being steamrolled like that in a team competition, never mind in a match like this, in any match, it would definitely break the balance of the situation,” Li Yibo said.

“Su Mucheng’s performance was truly exceptional,” Pan Lin sighed in admiration.

“I agree! She’s given this match a dilemma, and I’m curious about it as well. Will the MVP of the match be given to Luo Ji or Su Mucheng?” Li Yibo wondered aloud.

“I think it’ll probably go to Su Mucheng. After all, it was her exceptional performance that allowed them to grasp the match point and ascertain Happy’s victory. Otherwise, with just Luo Ji’s playstyle, the way the match would go would still be uncertain!” Pan Lin explained.

“However, Luo Ji played a crucial role in breaking the balance on the field as well. In addition, he’s a rookie that hasn’t played many matches. I think the Alliance will take that into account, too, so I think it’ll be Luo Ji,” Li Yibo countered.

“Then, Coach Li, let’s make a bet. Whoever loses has to treat the other to a midnight snack, yeah?” Pan Lin joked. This clearly wasn’t anything harmful.

“Alright then. The statistical data should be announced soon,” Li Yibo played along.

“Let’s use this time to take a look at the other matches,” Pan Lin suggested.

Chapter 1370 - You Played Pretty Well

By this time, the players from Wind Howl and Happy had emerged from their competitor booths. The large screen in the stadium displayed the final score as the players came onstage. They followed the typical post-match protocol, acknowledging the crowd, and greeting their opponents.

Each and every one of the Wind Howl players looked numb, robotically shaking hands with Happy’s players. The typical niceties like “you played pretty well,””keep working hard,””congrats,” and so on, were left out this time. These were all just for politeness, so no one really cared too much whether they were actually said or not.

Their players were still lined up in an orderly fashion, though, with Captain Tang Hao at the head, and the rest arranged in order. Lined up second was Vice-captain Liu Hao, who quickly arrived in front of Su Mucheng with a resentful expression on his face.

But Su Mucheng seemed to be in quite a good mood, as she looked at him with a bright smile.

Liu Hao gave a cold humph and didn’t pay attention to it. He just stuck out his hand automatically, wanting to get this over with. Su Mucheng, however, didn’t extend her hand.

“You played pretty well,” Su Mucheng said, smiling.

“You…” Liu Hao was enraged. In this match, everyone else could be praised as “playing pretty well.” Tang Hao, Zhao Yuzhe, even Lin Feng, they had all worked hard in the match, and even though they’d lost, they’d displayed their skill level. Only Liu Hao hadn’t.

He’d been completely wiped out by Su Mucheng, which had destroyed Wind Howl’s chance of success. He was absolutely the one person on the field that had disappointed the most. If there were an award for Least Valuable Player, Liu Hao would have earned it with no contest. Su Mucheng’s “you played pretty well” to him was a statement filled with mocking irony.

Liu Hao felt powerless to argue and just wanted this all to end quickly. But Su Mucheng still did not shake his hand.

“I’m not like a certain person, who can’t bear to waste time caring about all of the despicable things that you’ve done. Unlike him, I object greatly.” Su Mucheng was still smiling, but after dropping those words, she completely ignored Liu Hao’s outstretched hand and walked right past him.

Liu Hao stood there, stunned.

What grasping the key point of the match, resolutely attacking, going all-out on the offensive, beautiful performance…

It was none of that!

She just wanted revenge! She searched for an opportunity on the battlefield and ferociously opened fire upon him.

That fucker!

Liu Hao clenched his left hand into a fist. His right hand had been ignored by Su Mucheng, and now it seemed like even he had forgotten about it as it remained stiffly extended.

After Su Mucheng, the next Happy member to walk by was Mo Fan. He didn’t pay attention to Liu Hao’s state at all, and, seeing the extended hand, he simply took it and casually shook.

“You played pretty well,” he said.

What?

This sentence struck Liu Hao awake like a bolt of lightning.

You’re here to humiliate me too?

Liu Hao was furious, but Mo Fan didn’t pause. After speaking, he was already swiftly walking past.

“You played pretty well.”

“You played pretty well.”

“You played pretty well.”

Mo Fan mechanically shook hands with all of the Wind Howl players, giving all of them this same sentence. This was what he had learned was necessary to do after a match. Without any change, he delivered this message to every opponent. But for Liu Hao, after what Su Mucheng had just said, this was just rubbing salt in the wound.

Liu Hao felt faint.

You played pretty well. The sound of these mocking words seemed to reverberate around the whole stadium. It was as though all of the audience members, and his Wind Howl teammates, and all of the media reporters and commentators, were all gently smiling as they looked at him, and said: you played pretty well.

The world spun.

Liu Hao suddenly crashed to the ground.

Immediately, the stadium was in an uproar, and the players still onstage were in even more of a panic as to what to do. The stadium workers rushed onstage to carry Liu Hao away, and they swiftly looked for someone to treat him. Just like this, the post-match greetings came to a hasty close.

But the post-match press conference would go on as usual. Liu Hao instantly became the center of discussion, but it wasn’t just because he’d fainted after the match. As the single largest contributor to Wind Howl’s loss, this press conference would have been very difficult for him. Some reporters even questioned whether he’d pretended to pass out just to avoid this. Of course, such doubts couldn’t be directly voiced, as it would be somewhat heartless. What if he really had fainted?

And so the press conference opened with everyone expressing false concern. After hearing that Liu Hao was not in any serious condition, the question “what are your thoughts on Liu Hao’s performance this match” was naturally pulled out.

In the individual competition, Liu Hao had been defeated by Ye Xiu; in the team competition, he was wiped out by Su Mucheng, which directly orchestrated Wind Howl’s defeat. He had been the biggest reason why Wind Howl had lost six points. Most teams, in a situation like this, would try to protect their players who had performed poorly, even if it was just for appearances. But Wind Howl’s Captain Tang Hao wasn’t that kind of person. He very bluntly used “disaster” to describe Liu Hao’s performance today.

What a shame.

This is what everyone was thinking, but they weren’t pitying Liu Hao’s disappointing performance today. No, they were thinking that it was a shame that Tang Hao had given such a blunt answer, breaking from what most other teams would do, but Liu Hao wasn’t here to hear it. Otherwise, what sort of fireworks would have resulted?

This sort of merciless criticism was extremely rare to see. The reporters were all excitedly wondering how they should write their articles.

At this time, the results of the other matches this round had already been released.

301’s match had ended the earliest. To no one’s surprise, they took down Seaside in an easy 10-0 victory. They now had 239 points, 2 points ahead of Wind Howl and 5 points behind Happy.

Team Hundred Blossoms, at this critical moment, withstood the pressure. After lagging behind Tyranny 0-3, they furiously chased their points, and managed to win both the group arena and the team round, resulting in a final score of 7-3. With 237 points, they were now tied with Wind Howl. However, because they lost to Wind Howl in terms of their head-to-head score, they were still in ninth place for now. Still, they were able to carry their hopes into the final round.

Hundred Blossoms’ fans were beyond excited. Their team’s strong fighting spirit and refusal to give in gave them strong feelings of loyalty and pride. They held faith that this kind of team could definitely fight until the last moment, and achieve results that would make everyone happy.

Aside from this, Thunderclap had also managed to obtain victory in the team round against Samsara, ending the match 7-3. Right now, Thunderclap was tied with Happy at 244 points, but because they lost to Happy in terms of their head-to-head score, they were at sixth place for now. But in the final round, Thunderclap was facing Miracle. In terms of opponent, their final round was pretty relaxed, so everyone figured that Thunderclap had secured their spot in the playoffs. The celebrations in Thunderclap’s home stadium were much more relaxed than those at Hundred Blossoms’ stadium.

After seeing the results of all the other matches, Pan Lin and Li Yibo were still eagerly waiting for the final statistics of the match between Wind Howl and Happy.

Finally, the statistics were announced, and the MVP award for this match went to Luo Ji. The official analysis affirmed his outstanding performance and important role in this match.

“As expected of Coach Li.” Having lost the bet, Pan Lin had to express his regret.

“Haha, time for you to pay,” said Li Yibo.

“I know this one place that serves good dapanji

“Even though it’s this late?” said Li Yibo.

“Let’s go, let’s go!” Pan Lin prompted him. The match broadcast announced its conclusion in the middle of the off-topic conversation of these two. By this time, all matches of Round 37 of Season 10 of the Pro League had ended. Aside from these five teams who were fiercely competing for playoff spots, the other teams dutifully played their matches well.

The biggest change on the leaderboard was that 301, after sweeping Seaside, finally returned to the top eight, while Hundred Blossoms was squeezed to ninth place. Which eight teams would make it to the playoffs? This would only be decided with the final round.

Aside from this, Blue Rain won 8-2 against Void, allowing them to once again surpass Tyranny to sit at second place. This competition of rankings would impact the playoff matchups, and so there were a number of people paying attention to this.

In Wind Howl’s post-match press conference, Liu Hao earned the public criticism his captain made to the media. Meanwhile, in Happy’s press conference, Luo Ji appeared for the first time. He was bombarded with questions from the reporters, enough to make his head spin. He pitifully looked to his seniors to save him, but no one was paying attention to him – Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were calmly chatting over to the side!

“You beat Liu Hao so hard that he actually fainted,” said Ye Xiu. “So ferocious of you.”

“As soon as I see him, I can’t help but explode,” said Su Mucheng.

“You have to stay calm!”

“We won’t see him again.”

“That’s not for sure, there’s still one round left,” said Ye Xiu.

“God Ye, could you talk about why the team chose to make such bold arrangements against Wind Howl this round?” At this time, Su Mucheng had actually taken out a handful of sunflower seeds and was munching on them right there on the press conference stage, and a reporter, feeling that this was just too much, finally interrupted the two’s conversation to ask this question.

“Oh? Was it bold?” Ye Xiu immediately adjusted his attitude to respond to the question. “I don’t think so. Wind Howl’s extreme tactics could be used for a while, but not forever. To get such excellent results in so many rounds, their luck is quite good. But if they really wanted to rely on such tactics to defeat every opponent under the sky, then they’re truly underestimating everyone far too much.”

“That’s to say, you don’t think Wind Howl’s prospects are good?” the reporter asked.

“Who’s Wind Howl’s opponent in the final round?” Ye Xiu asked.

“It’s Tiny Herb,” the reporter answered.

“Oh. If Wang Jiexi is killed by strategy like this, I think that he should just give up and retire,” said Ye Xiu.

“Uh… this…” The reporter felt awkward and had no idea how to continue.

“Didn’t you just say that nothing was for sure with the final round?” said Su Mucheng.

“The rankings aren’t for sure, but that doesn’t mean Wind Howl can win!” Ye Xiu said to her.

“Can you talk about Su Mucheng’s performance today?” the reporter asked.

“She astutely grasped the the key points of the match and decisively attacked. A beautiful performance,” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what do you think about Luo Ji’s performance?” the reporter continued to ask.

“We were able to achieve victory largely thanks to the foundation he laid down,” Ye Xiu said.

“Then will Luo Ji participate in the playoffs?” the reporter asked.

“That’s a secret we can’t announce beforehand,” said Ye Xiu.

“Then, can we ask, which team does Happy hope to encounter first in the playoffs?” asked the reporter.

“The season hasn’t ended yet, and Happy hasn’t entered the playoffs for sure. Answering that question now would be too improper,” Ye Xiu said, serious.

The reporters were speechless. Fuck, who was the person who’d announced, fresh out of beating the Challenger League, that they would be the Season 10 champions? It was you, wasn’t it?

Chapter 1371 - Endgame Preparation

With Round 37’s match, Luo Ji had truly become a protagonist.

“How about it? Feels pretty good, doesn’t it, kid?” After returning from the press conference, Wei Chen came up to Luo Ji and tousled his hair.

“It’s great, it’s great,” Luo Ji said excitedly. MVP? Just a few rounds ago, he’d been worried about not dragging down the rest of the team, but now, he’d actually become the match MVP, the crucial piece in the team’s victory… Luo Ji was truly thrilled, and even though the reporters had hounded him like wolves, he didn’t really mind. All that mattered was that he could be useful to the team.

“Keep it up, your future is filled with light!” Wei Chen said.

“Yes, Boss Wei!” Luo Ji happily answered. Soon after, the other young players like Qiao Yifan and An Wenyi surrounded him with congratulations, and Steamed Bun took on the role of a boss as he gruffly warned Luo Ji against becoming too arrogant.

How good it is to be young…

Watching Happy’s vibrant young members, Wei Chen was filled with emotion.

In Wei Chen’s eyes, Luo Ji’s skill truly wasn’t all that much. The professional circle was overflowing with talent. But Luo Ji had what Wei Chen admired and envied the most: his youth.

If only I could be ten years younger… Even if I lost all the technique and experience I have now, and started over from zero, that would be fine!

Technique could be trained, experience could be raised. Only youth, once lost, could never be regained.

Luo Ji still had the future. He had chance after chance to be useful in Happy’s matches. But what about Wei Chen himself?

Wei Chen lit a cigarette, and took a deep breath.

For him, there was perhaps only this handful of battles remaining.

One match left of the regular season. If they made it to the finals, if every round of the playoffs became three matches long, that meant nine matches. Ten matches total.

Ten matches…

Even if he went on in every single match, his professional career would have no more than ten matches left. Next season? Wei Chen didn’t dare think any more. If he stubbornly clung on, then he would only become dead weight for the team.

Back then, why had he retired?

Wei Chen suddenly felt regret swelling in his heart.

If his thirty-year-old self could still hold on now, then back then, why couldn’t he have held on in the first place? Even if he had simply joined some random team, he always could have found a position.

Six years… Why in the world had he wasted those six years?

As the young members talked and laughed, Wei Chen let out a sigh. They felt joy at making it to the playoffs in their debut year, while Wei Chen felt melancholy as he thought of his rapidly dwindling professional lifespan.

“Look at these young ones, how nice.” Ye Xiu suddenly appeared out of nowhere, slapping a hand on Wei Chen’s shoulder.

“Fuck!” Wei Chen hadn’t been holding his cigarette securely, so when he was startled, it almost flipped into his eye, giving him a second scare.

“Just ten rounds left,” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” The fact that Wei Chen only had ten professional matches left was, for a pro player, an extremely tragic and cruel thing. No matter how shameless Ye Xiu was, he wouldn’t deliver this kind of jab, would he? For him to say this…

Were these the last ten rounds for himself, as well? Was this guy also planning to retire?

“Don’t regret it!” Wei Chen finally said.

“Haha.” Ye Xiu only chuckled.

All sorts of discussion emerged after Round 37. The five teams struggling for a spot in the top eight were the hot topic, of course. Hundred Blossoms dropping three points to Tyranny before successfully counter attacking, Thunderclap winning seven points from Samsara, 301 earning a perfect victory against Seaside, all earned praise. And the final score of Happy against Wind Howl was 6-4, relatively close, so they couldn’t say one side was particularly disastrous. In the individual rounds, Wind Howl fell behind one point and then earned four in succession, which was quite a strong performance. As for the team competition, Su Mucheng and Luo Ji of course earned much praise, and Liu Hao became the only player in the crucial Round 37 who performed terribly, and thus the sole target of critics.

And even Tang Hao had expressed dissatisfaction over his performance in the post-match press conference by calling him a disaster. This only further supported the point.

A few less professional media directly took this out of context. Tang Hao had clearly just been speaking fact, that Liu Hao’s performance in this one match had been too subpar, like a disaster. But these reporters took this to mean that Wind Howl overall had met disaster, and described Liu Hao as cancer for Wind Howl. Clearly, Liu Hao’s performance in Wind Howl this season had been fairly strong. The team trusted him, the fans liked him. Otherwise, how could he have become vice-captain and an All-Star?

But in this round, no matter how upright the media, couldn’t find anything good to say about Liu Hao.

As far as the eye could see, there was nothing but negative reviews. Liu Hao felt that all he had endeavored to build up over this entire season was collapsing because of this one disastrous performance.

Next round, I have to redeem myself. Liu Hao grit his teeth.

June 5th, Season 10 of the Glory Professional League finally arrived at the final match. For half of the teams, this was the end of a season, but ten teams would step onto a new journey after this. Some would go on to fight for the highest glory, while others would now fight for salvation.

There were three matches in this final round that were attracting the most attention: Happy playing their home game against 301, Samsara home game against Hundred Blossoms, and Tiny Herb home game against Wind Howl.

Three matches would determine which three teams would enter the top eight and earn the right to compete in the playoffs. 301, Hundred Blossoms, and Wind Howl couldn’t slack off one bit. Every point might determine their ultimate fate. And because of these teams, Happy had to continue to fight as hard as they could. They, too, couldn’t afford to grow careless.

“Let me go on!” As Team Happy prepared, someone was begging to play in the match.

But others all told him, “Rest, rest!”

“Leave it to us, it’s no problem,” everyone said.

“Don’t! I haven’t played in the team competition in a whole month! Please, I’m begging you, give me the chance to keep my hands warm.” Ye Xiu struggled to obtain a chance to go onstage.

Actually, for both Round 35 and Round 37, Ye Xiu had originally intended to play. But everyone in Happy had very firmly shoved him back down onto the bench.

“With all your experience, do you still need to train your hands?” Tang Rou said.

“Right right, if it’s Boss, he doesn’t need it at all,” said Steamed Bun.

“Rest, rest!” everyone continued to say.

“I still need this! Hurry and let me go onstage!” Ye Xiu shouted.

Chen Guo was at a loss. With all of the commotion, she also couldn’t tell whether Ye Xiu really needed to play a match to keep his hands warm, or if he was just lonely.

“Do you really need it?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu was about to cry. “How could I not need this? I haven’t played in a month.”

Chen Guo looked at Su Mucheng and Fang Rui, for confirmation from those who had professional experience.

“Let’s follow his plan!” Su Mucheng laughed.

At last, Ye Xiu began planning out the next round. He began by confirming that he would have a starting position in the team competition, which was instantly met by a room full of boos.

“This is an abuse of power.”

Ye Xiu heard someone say this, and he began to question whether these guys genuinely wanted him to rest, or if they were trying to squeeze him out of his position.

After that, they progressed with the planning. Everyone finally put away their joking attitudes, and listened to Ye Xiu’s match arrangements seriously.

“Three points. That will guarantee our entry into the playoffs. But we can’t set our goal that low. Fight for victory with everything you have! Don’t worry about 301’s survival,” said Ye Xiu.

“Understood!” everyone answered.

“Let’s start practice!” Ye Xiu waved his hand, and everyone began their tense training for the next round’s match.

The R&D department was also making the final sprint to the playoffs. Everyone hoped that they could complete equipment upgrades before the playoffs began. In the playoffs, one mistake could lead to a complete loss, and to suddenly switch to unfamiliar equipment in the middle of the playoffs wasn’t a wise decision. The differences brought by changed equipment could lead to miscalculations or misjudgments in the middle of a match. To some extent, the playoffs were a competition of which side could make fewer mistakes.

“36 pieces of pseudo-Silver equipment, and the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella has been completed. Do you want to upgrade now?” Seeing Ye Xiu come over, the R&D workers asked him excitedly. They were also looking forward to see their own handiwork equipped on characters to give the entire Alliance a shock. Although the stats of the Silver equipment wouldn’t be displayed, the equipment level would be shown. The sight of Happy’s characters clad in Level 80 equipment, what kind of shock would that bring to the Glory circle? Just thinking about it was enough to cause excitement.

“We’ll upgrade after this match!” Ye Xiu said. “Can there be more?”

“For now, it’ll probably just be this much,” the R&D worker answered. “Most equipment can’t manifest this kind of complex, redundant structure.”

The R&D called the structure used by the Level 80 pseudo-Silver “redundant addition.” If they were simply making the equipment, they wouldn’t need nearly this many materials. But to raise it to Level 80, they had to forcefully add on more materials, while ensuring that these materials didn’t change the original properties of the equipment. Many equipment couldn’t take this additive modification, and these were the failed products that had no way of reaching Level 80.

The recent research of Happy’s R&D had been focused on determining which equipment could be upgraded and which couldn’t, and this process had used up a large amount of materials. Fortunately, because they were only aiming to make Orange-level Silver equipment, they didn’t need as many rare materials. And there was always a surplus of dungeon materials, so they could almost always get them from the in-game marketplace. The rarer ones would be the drops from the highest-level dungeons, but on the guild side of things, Wu Chen had coordinated teams to increase their acquisitions, and they were able to meet the demands of the R&D.

Even as they continued their development of pseudo-Silver, they didn’t forget about their research of real Silver, either. After all, they only needed pseudo-Silver for now. This batch was directly jumping to Level 80, but when the overall level cap was updated to 80, it was unknown whether they could still use the method of redundant addition to upgrade to Level 85. Only real Silver equipment would be the true path to sustainable development. Happy could expend effort on pseudo-Silver largely because there wasn’t much conflict with the materials required for real Silver. Because the two goals didn’t interfere with each other, Happy could grab both.

Chapter 1372 - Playing Too Honestly

Round 38 of the Alliance was rapidly approaching. Given that it was the final round, it was inevitable that there would be a of publicity surrounding it. After this round, voting for the awards of the current season would begin. The awards would be based on the performances of the regular season, with the playoffs having their own set of awards afterwards.

Amongst the various awards, the one that caught the most attention was naturally the MVP award. There were many players who had been raised as possible MVPs, to the point that even Bai Shu, who had only joined 301 in the winter transfer window, was also part of the list.

Other than that, there were Samsara’s Zhou Zekai, Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian, Tiny Herb’s Wang Jiexi, Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie and other All-Star players were frequently raised as possible candidates. Apart from these players, there the was the player with the strongest return to the Alliance: Happy’s Ye Xiu.

Team Happy’s performance may not have been as outstanding as Samsara or the other powerhouse teams, but as a new team, achieving such results was already entirely unprecedented, and within the team, the role that Ye Xiu played was something that anyone with eyes could see. If the Alliance were to take into account Happy’s difficulty in achieving such results, Ye Xiu’s inclusion in the list of MVP candidates was indisputable. If there was anything that was disadvantageous to Ye Xiu, it was his continued “ceasefire” for the last 4 rounds. Missing out such crucial competitions would have a negative impact on his assessment for the MVP award.

The MVP award was something that had various different considerations and factors. In comparison, some of the other awards that only looked at results or numbers were more easily decided upon.

The King of Dueling title was based on the results of the individual competition. The award would definitely go to Ye Xiu without much suspense, given his 36 consecutive victories in the individual competition. Looking at the statistics, One Hit One Kill, the award based on the number of killing blows accomplished within the team competitions, was already in Zhou Zekai’s hands one round early.

Then there was the Arena Star, the award based on how much damage a player had dealt throughout the course of the group arena competitions. Similarly, the holder of this title had been convincingly decided one round early: Team Samsara’s Sun Xiang.

Other than that, awards like Best Partners, Best Rookie or Best Sixth Player were also like the MVP award, and wouldn’t be decided purely by numbers or statistics, instead needing careful consideration of the various player’s performances after the end of the 38th round.

Everything was waiting for this final round.

On the evening of the 5th of June, the 20 teams in the Alliance gathered in 10 different team’s stadiums, marking the beginning of the 38th round of competition.

In the end, the broadcasters decided to show the match between Samsara and Hundred Blossoms. Hundred Blossoms was temporarily in 9th place, and if they wanted to enter the top 8, they could either win 1 more point than Wind Howl or 3 more points than 301 in this round. In the previous round, after falling behind by 3 points against Tyranny, they had valiantly snatched back 7 points, lighting the expectations for them to produce a breathtaking performance in their away-game against Samsara. The Glory community hadn’t forgotten that Team Samsara’s crazy streak of wins in the first half of the season had ultimately been put to a stop by Team Hundred Blossoms. This final match would be Team Hundred Blossom’s most important match of the whole season.

In this final round, every stadium was packed to the brim, including the stadium for Seaside and Bright Green, the two teams in the relegation zone. Next season, they wouldn’t be able to compete in this stadium anymore, so the heartbroken fans had come to accompany their teams in battle till the very last moment, even though it was already too late to change anything.

At 8.30 in the evening, the final round of the competition punctually began in all ten stadiums.

In Happy’s stadium, Ye Xiu appeared in the individual competition for the 37th time, taking another shot at breaking his own record. This time, the player attempting to snipe his streak was someone who had garnered a lot of attention in the second half of the season: Team 301 Degrees’ Knight player Bai Shu, hailing from Europe.

The competition quickly began. Until the very last round, Ye Xiu had persisted in choosing the same style of maps: clean and minimalistic maps meant for a head-on battle. The two characters loaded in, appearing at two opposite ends of the map.

Bai Shu’s Knight character, Tide, was clad from head to toe in Silver equipment. In this small map where sunlight was shining brilliantly, the reflections off Tide’s metal armor was dazzling, and his shield, Silver of Life had practically become a mirror.

“Ah, this map choice is a little unfortunate!” Fang Rui said, sitting on Happy’s player bench.

“Wait, why?” Chen Guo asked frantically.

“It’s too bright, it dazzles the eyes,” Fang Rui said.

“Are you talking about the reflections from Tide’s equipment?” Chen Guo asked.

“That’s right. In the context of Glory, things like this will all become disturbances to the opposing player,” Fang Rui replied.

Chen Guo immediately felt a sense of apprehension. Losing 1 point was nothing to fear, but she really didn’t want to see Ye Xiu’s streak of consecutive victories come to an end. In fact, she was still brooding over the fact that Ye Xiu didn’t play in the first round! That meant that he could at most have 37 wins in a row, not a complete sweep of all 38 rounds. The tiny bit of imperfection was extremely regrettable.

As they spoke, the two characters on stage had already started to charge towards the center of the map.

Boom boom boom!

Ye Xiu used Lord Grim’s long-ranged superiority to open fire first, sending three Anti-Tank Missiles flying out.

Charge!

Bai Shu surprisingly didn’t dodge, instead choosing to have Tide press the assault. His shield was raised in front of him, and all three Anti-Tank Missiles exploded on it in succession. In a moment, Tide had left the cloud of smoke and the sound of explosions behind him, the gap between the two shortening in the blink of an eye. Tide’s shield, Silver of Life, was shining brightly. On the large screen in the stadium, everyone could see from Ye Xiu’s player perspective, and all they saw was a field of dazzling radiance, similar to the effect from a Spitfire’s Flash Bullet.

“Look!” Fang Rui had long been watching Ye Xiu’s player perspective, and at this moment, he immediately pointed at the screen for everyone to see.

Heroic Leap!

Tide leapt into the air, but the only thing that Ye Xiu could see in his vision was a flash of brilliant light, and then nothing.

Shining Cut!

Ye Xiu used the skill to dash out.

This was an instinctual reaction that he made based on his experience. When the opponent disappeared, no matter where he went, eventually he would want to continue his assault. At this time, the best thing to do was to keep moving, and figure out where the opponent was afterwards.

Tide descended from the air, and Lord Grim fled from his original position. The two of them had more or less completed a swap of positions. After Shining Cut, Lord Grim immediately twisted his body in mid-air, and the moment he saw Tide in his field of view, the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella changed back into Gun Form, and Lord Grim opened fire!

Bang!

A single bullet flew out.

But this time, Bai Shu didn’t have Tide use his shield to block the attack.

This single bullet was the Spitfire’s Burning Bullet, which would create a fiery blaze as it fell to the ground, something that the shield couldn’t prevent.

Tide jumped out of the way, dodging the Burning Bullet. As a sea of fire immediately began to spread on the ground, he had already stepped out of the range of the attack.

Gatling Gun!

Lord Grim used yet another skill, sending a torrent of bullets towards Tide. This time, Tide raised his shield, forcefully advancing under the rain of bullets. Tide’s Silver of Life wasn’t as large as the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s Shield Form, so it couldn’t possibly shield his whole body. As such, Ye Xiu adjusted the angle of the Gatling Gun, attempting to send the bullets to the gaps that weren’t being protected by the shield. Despite that, all the bullets were blocked by Tide, as Silver of Life’s position was adjusted non-stop, unexpectedly blocking the Gatling Gun bullets that were coming from continually shifting angles.

“This guy!” Fang Rui exclaimed in surprise. Team Wind Howl’s original lineup also had a Knight, so he had a fairly impressive understanding of the class. Being able to use his shield in such a way to completely block Ye Xiu’s gunfire meant that his fundamentals were far more solid than normal.

Atr this moment, in Ye Xiu’s field of vision, Silver of Life became dazzling once more. Evidently, they had once again entered an angle in which the shield could reflect sunlight.

“Eh? This time…” This time, Fang Rui was bewildered.

“What is it?” Chen Guo frantically asked again.

“His timing of the sunlight was a bit sub-par,” Fang Rui expressed.

On stage, Ye Xiu slightly adjusted Lord Grim’s position, easily avoiding the reflection of the sunlight this time around, before continuing to assault Tide from a distance.

“He isn’t doing it on purpose.” At this time, Wei Chen spoke up.

“Who are you referring to?” Chen Guo asked.

“Bai Shu. He didn’t think of using his equipment to reflect the sunlight, it was actually all accidental,” Wei Chen replied.

“Really?” Chen Guo looked at Fang Rui, but he was deep in contemplation, so he didn’t respond.

“This player from abroad seems to disdain these kinds of dirty tricks!” Wei Chen said.

“Do you think he’s like all of you?” Chen Guo snorted at Wei Chen, and then shifted her gaze to Fang Rui. These two played in an especially wretched way, with an innumerable number of dirty tricks up their sleeves.

“I’m looking down on him, can’t you tell from my tone?” Wei Chen replied.

“…”

“In order to win, I would be as unscrupulous as I need to be. These kinds of players who pretend to be upright and not use the tricks they have access to are the kind I hate the most,” Wei Chen said.

Chen Guo didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry. This wasn’t about pretending to be upright, couldn’t a person just prefer not using these kinds of methods to fight?

“Lose, he’s definitely going to lose!” Wei Chen cursed.

“That I can agree with,” Chen Guo nodded.

At this moment, Tide had already drawn closer to Lord Grim by quite a bit, raising his hand and gesturing towards him: Provoke.

Lord Grim promptly charged towards Tide without hesitation, and sent out a Collapsing Mountain! Ye Xiu straightforwardly used this skill, and Lord Grim jumped up, sending his blade chopping downwards.

Clang!

An ear-piercing noise rang out. Surprisingly, Bai Shu had let Tide raise his shield to block the powerful Berserker skill, Collapsing Mountain, before using his other hand to brandish his sword for a counterattack.

“I have no words left,” Wei Chen said.

“What is it now?” Chen Guo asked.

“Couldn’t he just have avoided this attack?” Wei Chen said.

“Is using the shield to block not good enough?” Chen Guo asked.

“Using the shield to block still costs HP. If he’s able to avoid losing HP altogether, does he still need to be so unyielding?” Wei Chen replied.

“He can… counterattack a bit faster?” Chen Guo’s answer sounded quite professional, her standard was improving!

“If he can’t take the initiative from the counterattack, what’s the point of counterattacking at all?” Wei Chen continued to look down on him.

After blocking Collapsing Mountain, Tide’s counterattack indeed wasn’t able to help seize the initiative, and the two of them continued to trade hits, countering each other’s every move.

“That Taunt usage was also baffling, this is a 1v1, and the opponent doesn’t want to run away, what’s the point of taunting him? Taunting him only results in close-range combat, but that’s what Lord Grim’s good at,” Wei Chen continued.

Chen Guo was puzzled. According to Wei Chen’s analysis, this Bai Shu was really full of problems! But looking at the match, he didn’t show any signs of faltering when fighting against Ye Xiu! In this match, she couldn’t see any sign of who was going to win or lose.

“You’d best ignore him.” Su Mucheng saw Chen Guo’s bewilderment and laughed, “They have completely different styles, so of course they can’t stand the sight of each other.”

“Is he playing too honestly?” Chen Guo consulted Su Mucheng, and ended up being viciously stared at by Wei Chen, causing her to momentarily not dare to say anything more.

“In this confrontation, it’s exactly this kind of upright and frank play that’s needed to determine victory or defeat!” Su Mucheng replied.

“It’s boring as hell,” Wei Chen and Fang Rui said in unison.

“I believe that Ye Xiu won’t give him that kind of opportunity,” Wei Chen said sincerely, “That guy has no limit to his shamelessness!”

Chapter 1373 - Peak Skill

Fight justly and fairly?

Chen Guo trusted Su Mucheng’s words more than Wei Chen’s. Then again, she really couldn’t tell the difference between fair and shameless in a match.

Crusader’s Trial!

At this moment, Bai Shu suddenly cast a powerful high-level skill at an extremely close distance. Tide crashed forward with a Charge, his sword and shield brandished.

Shining Cut!

Lord Grim flashed by with a cold light.

The direction of Crusader’s Trial could be controlled though. The moment Lord Grim flitted to the right, Bai Shu had Tide cut across from the left.

Charge and Crusader’s Trial moved at the same speed, which didn’t lose to Shining Cut. Even though the first stage missed, the second stage of the skill smashed towards Lord Grim.

Charge!

Ye Xiu used another movement skill. Lord Grim switched directions, dodging the second stage.

Colliding Stab!

Shadow Clone Technique!

Slide Kick!

Ye Xiu used multiple movement skills in a row in an attempt to escape from Tide, but in the end, he failed. Bai Shu’s controls were extremely fast and precise. He immediately adjusted his Crusader’s Trial with every escape attempt from Lord Grim. The viewers were dumbstruck as they watched these two characters shuffle around a small area in a blur. Ye Xiu was clearly using a variety of skills from different classes, but by chaining them together in a single breath, it was hard to believe that there were multiple skills being used; it looked like one smooth yet messy movement. On the other hand, Bai Shu was using just a single skill, so his movements were naturally smooth. However, he was the one reacting to Ye Xiu’s actions. Being able to stick so tightly to Ye Xiu despite these circumstances was truly a terrifying display of technique.

Multiple movement skills had been linked together in an instant. Sometimes, a skill wouldn’t even complete before the next skill began. But after the Slide Kick, the attentive viewers noticed Lord Grim’s skill bar. The first skill he had used, Shining Cut, was still on cooldown.

Players had already figured out which low-level movement skills Lord Grim possessed. He had the Assassin’s Shining Cut, the Kinght’s Charge, the Berserker’s Colliding Stab, the Sharpshooter’s Slide Kick, and the Ninja’s Shadow Clone Technique.

Five skills on rotation was usually more than enough. But today, Ye Xiu had been forced by Bai Shu to use all five skills consecutively, yet he still couldn’t escape. The Level 75 Crusader’s Trial had a maximum of nine stages. Tide had only used five stages so far and still had four more stages to call upon.

This time, what high-level skill had Ye Xiu added onto his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella? Perhaps a Teleport? People began thinking of the possibilities. However, those who had noticed Lord Grim’s skill bar suddenly realized that apart from these five movement skills, Lord Grim also had Spike Trap on cooldown.

If it was on cooldown, it meant it had been used. But when?

No one had any time to ponder over this question. The pace of the battle was extremely fast. Tide had chased Lord Grim to the sixth stage of Crusader’s Trial, when a sudden “ka” sounded. Tide could still swing his weapon, but his feet wouldn’t budge an inch.

Spike Trap was triggered just like this. Everyone was dumbfounded. Besides those who had been paying attention to Lord Grim’s skill bar, everyone else had been caught off guard. Judging from the position of the Spike Trap, Lord Grim must have placed it while Slide Kicking.

Spike Trap only restricted movement. It did not interrupt skills. Tide could continue his Crusader’s Trial, but he could only do it in place. Lord Grim jumped back nimbly, and Tide’s attack could no longer reach him. Ye Xiu was just about to counterattack, when Tide’s sword suddenly flew out towards Lord Grim.

Spirit Guidance!

The Exorcist’s Spirit Guidance gave the ability to throw your weapon. Exorcists and Knights were both Priest classes and could learn each other’s low-level skills.

This attack had been quite sudden. Happy’s home crowd cried out in alarm. Lord Grim promptly rolled though, and evaded the attack.

Grenade, Shuriken, Mechanical Seeker. As Lord Grim rolled, he threw a bunch of things at Tide, who who had no way of dodging due to the Spike Trap. However, he still had his shield. Tide immediately crouched down and raised his shield, Silver Life. The Grenade and Mechanical Seeker exploded on his shield, while the Shuriken was deflected.

“See, dirty!” Wei Chen shouted excitedly.

He wasn’t talking about Tide and his shield, or Lord Grim’s chain of attacks. These were far from being qualified. Wei Chen was talking about how Ye Xiu was having his Lord Grim approach while sticking close to the ground.

When Bai Shu used his shield, he made sure to give himself an open line of sight. But with Lord Grim crouching down, the line of sight that the shield allowed him to have wasn’t quite enough. He couldn’t see the target, so he subconsciously lowered his shield a bit. Right after he did so, he heard a gunshot.

Bai Shu reacted extremely fast and hastily lifted up his Silver Life again. However, he then heard a “pu”, a hit.

Bai Shu looked down in disbelief and saw a bullet wound at his feet. This opening hadn’t been there originally. When he raised his shield instinctively to protect his head, a small crack had appeared in his defense. To think his opponent could grasp that tiny opening…

No, it wasn’t his opponent grasping an opening. Bai Shu had clearly heard the gunshot before lifting his shield. In other words, the other side had shot at his feet, predicting that he wouldn’t be able to see the attack and would lift his shield thinking it would be a headshot…

To think there was someone who could calculate this many steps ahead.

Bai Shu was amazed.

He had only started playing Glory after going abroad. He had played in the European servers and then joined England’s Pro League. As a pro player, he could be considered a locally born and bred European player. However, his homeland was still China, so he paid some attention to the Glory scene there as well. But because of China’s mediocrity at popular sports like football and basketball, he didn’t think very highly of the skill level of China’s competitive Glory scene. As a result, he mainly followed the scene out of curiosity and didn’t take it seriously.

When Team 301 sent out a formal invitation to him, he had been both surprised and proud. To think I could receive attention from a competitive league on a completely different continent, it looks like my skill and fame is quite high!

Along with a feeling of intimacy for his homeland, in the end, Bai Shu was moved by Team 301’s detailed plans for him, especially after knowing that Team 301’s situation wasn’t too great. Instead of disappointment, he was rather excited to be the savior for a team.

As a result, he returned to his home country and joined Team 301. He began adapting to China’s competitive league and helped Team 301 form a new tactical system.

Much of this came from the strategies and techniques that Bai Shu had learned from his career in Europe. After combining these with Team 301, the team’s win record improved drastically. Win after win, the spotlight shone on him.

Bai Shu felt great. Sure enough, Europe was the superior region. After joining the Alliance, Team 301 became like a fish in the water. They had originally been dozens of points away from top eight, but they quickly squeezed their way in a huge reversal.

However, near the end of the season, Team 301 had been caught into an intense struggle for playoffs, a bit far from Bai Shu’s goal of sweeping through the league. Bai Shu wasn’t discouraged though. After all, he had only been a part of 301 for half a season. Both sides needed more time to synergize to reach their peak condition. Team 301 had made a huge comeback within this half a season. To be able to do that was more than enough for Bai Shu. After his arrival, 301 had only lost to two opponents. One was Wind Howl and their sudden improvement. 301 hadn’t been prepared and lost. The other one was the Alliance’s current number one, Samsara. Bai Shu very much recognized their strength. It would truly be quite challenging for Team 301 to win over them.

Apart from those two though, the powerhouses in the Alliance such as Tyranny, Blue Rain, and Tiny Herb had all fallen to 301. From Bai Shu’s perspective, those teams were on par with each other. Neither team was better than the other by much.

Their teams were like so, the individuals were like so. Bai Shu hadn’t noticed anyone who could make him feel fear. The so-called number one Knight, Xu Bin, had apparently come from 301. But in their 1v1 match, Bai Shu won quite easily. He was nothing impressive.

Finally, in this last round, Team 301 would meet Team Happy.

Ye Xiu had won 36 individual rounds in a row. Just this win record alone made it so Bai Shu could not underestimate him. After doing some research on him, he learned about his legendary history.

But isn’t he a bit old?

Whether it was in China or Europe or anywhere else, the pro players were all around the same age. Ye Xiu’s 27 years of age was a genuine old general in any competitive scene.

To let such an old general keep winning in the individual competition?

When Bai Shu first came over and heard about his win streak, he had a hard time understanding. Then, he heard about the unspecialized’s playstyle as well as his strange weapon, which made him quite curious.

At that time, he had made a decision. This Ye Xiu needed to be taught a lesson. However, Team 301 and Team Happy would only be meeting each other again in Round 38, at the end of the regular season. It would only be then would Bai Shu be able to realize his long-cherished wish.

During this half a season, he had personally watched quite a few of Ye Xiu’s and Lord Grim’s matches, and made ample preparation. That ultra fast speed made many people’s heads hurt, but wasn’t he keeping up with it just fine?

But in the process, he had fallen for a trap that had been placed who knew when.

Then, he was hit by a bullet that had completely seen through his thoughts.

So this is someone who won 36 individual rounds in a row… China’s peak skill?

Chapter 1374 - Thirty-Seven Consecutive Wins

A shot that Ye Xiu had so precisely calculated and fired of course wouldn’t just be an ordinary attack. This was a Spitfire skill: Stun Bullet. The instant it hit, Lord Grim was already pulling back and circling around. Then, he began his offensive.

Unspecialized Blitz!

This was a term that had circulated for a while now. Bai Shu had heard of it before, and he had studied it. He had felt that he wouldn’t give Ye Xiu that kind of opportunity during the match. But now, he understood, it wasn’t that he would give an opportunity, it was that the opponent would create the opportunity himself. After being hit by the Stun Bullet, Tide could no longer move, and so when Lord Grim charged over, circled around to his back, and began attacking, what could he do?

The Paralysis status wore off fairly quickly, but Lord Grim’s offensive was far from over. Bai Shu tried to control Tide to block with his shield, because he just needed to block one attack to rebalance the situation. But Ye Xiu had clearly considered this point from early on. Tide was a Knight, which was a class that had a shield that gave them a natural advantage in interrupting the opponent’s attack. This was why Ye Xiu had begun his attack from behind, preventing Bai Shu from controlling Tide to pull out his shield to block. Just like that, the famous Silver of Life became mere ornamentation.

Thirty-seven!

The fans in Happy’s home stadium were already cheering.

A win streak lasting thirty-seven rounds. How incredible of a record was that?

It had never been done before, and it would likely never be repeated again. Right here, right now, this miraculous record was about to be born. Countless fans in the audience were rising from their seats, and Happy’s diehard fans had already made preparations beforehand. They were just waiting for the instant that Lord Grim killed Tide for good, and then they would begin their celebration ceremony for this record.

“Ten!”

“Nine!”

“Eight!”

“Seven!”

“Six!”

There wasn’t much remaining of Tide’s health. From some corner of the stadium, this countdown suddenly began, gradually spreading through the audience. By the time they reached six, aside from a few depressed 301 fans, the entire stadium was chanting along.

“Five!” Everyone stared at Tide’s dwindling health bar.

“Four!” Everyone watched Lord Grim attack.

“Three!” Everyone calculated the damage that was dealt by this attack.

“Two!” Everyone once again checked Tide’s remaining health.

“One!” Another attack from Lord Grim arrived, and everyone prayed, fall, you bastard! They didn’t have any particular enmity toward Bai Shu, but in this moment, they cursed him with all their heart.

“Zero!” The cheers reached their peak, Lord Grim’s Sword Draw flashed out, and the blade scattered blood as it swung to the sky. And finally, Tide’s health reached zero!

“Thirty-seven!!!” After zero, another number surged forward, but no one was surprised. This was what they had been waiting for.

Bang bang bang bang bang!

The stadium erupted with fireworks, colorful confetti bursting forth to surround the whole stage. This was all clearly something that Happy fans had planned in advance. The fans who had the fireworks had arranged themselves in a ring all around the stadium, to allow the celebration to spread to all corners. Even in the middle of the away team’s fan section, a spy had somehow infiltrated their midst and set off a firework, although it was only round. Probably that fan was soon forcibly stopped by the surrounding 301 fans.

“Thirty-seven!” In the midst of the confetti, the fans cheered with all their might, and Chen Guo felt the tears beginning to stream down her cheeks. That guy, he had actually done it. He had started as an overnight manager at Happy Internet Cafe and established this team from scratch. He personally defeated Excellent Era, the team he had spent seven years fighting for. He returned to this stage, and then he established this shocking record that perhaps no one would ever surpass, permanently carving his true name onto this homeland of Glory.

“Too incredible!” Chen Guo exclaimed, wiping at her tears.

“It is!” The shameless Wei Chen, for once, didn’t have any words of mockery, and his voice was sincere and heavy as he answered Chen Guo. Yes, it was really too incredible. How was this bastard so strong? Was he even stronger than he was ten years ago?

“I can’t believe him!” Fang Rui yelled. “What about all the players in the future? This record is so ridiculous, it’s disgusting!”

“To surpass it, you’d need thirty-eight consecutive wins?” Tang Rou still saw that tiny thread of hope.

“Boss is powerful, Boss is dominating,” said Steamed Bun.

“As expected of Senior,” said Qiao Yifan.

“It’s amazing, I could never do that,” Luo Ji said.

“This is really our captain…” An Wenyi was originally a Tyranny fan, and Ye Xiu had always been the person he could never like too much, but now, he had essentially been converted into his fan.

“…” Mo Fan didn’t say anything, but his eyes, like those of the others, were filled with marvel.

Su Mucheng didn’t say anything, either. She knew the hardships Ye Xiu had endured these past two years, and she knew that this insane win streak wasn’t just for himself, but for another legacy. That character, Lord Grim, should have been controlled by another person to shine onstage with power unstoppable. But unfortunately, that could never become reality.

Now, Ye Xiu had completed this season for him. He used the character Lord Grim to leave behind a record that could never be erased. Perhaps no one would ever learn that other person’s name, but Lord Grim, this character he created, would forever remain in Glory’s history.

It was amazing.

Su Mucheng stood and clapped. She didn’t cry, because she had always believed in Ye Xiu.

He said he would return, and so he returned.

He said he would establish a win streak, and so he won thirty-seven in a row.

He said they would aim for the championship this season, and Su Mucheng believed that this championship would undoubtedly belong to Happy.

The door to the competitor booth was opened. Ye Xiu walked out, walked onto the stage, and the cheers of the crowd instantly grew even louder. Bang bang bang, another ring of fireworks was set off. The fans had planned to do another round at this moment, although the fireworks from the away team’s seating came a fraction later. Still, even when surrounded by the strict monitoring of the 301 fans after the last round of fireworks, this brave man still managed to suddenly break through and fire again. He could be called the hero of the fans.

“Thirty-seven!” Everyone continued to holler. Ye Xiu waved to the audience, expressing his thanks, before walking offstage.

“What an incredible record!” At this moment, although the live broadcast was set to show Hundred Blossoms’ match against Samsara, they suddenly took advantage of the break between battles to show the scene at Happy’s stadium. This, too, was something the broadcasters had arranged beforehand. They didn’t choose to show this Happy versus 301 match, but they didn’t want to miss the moment that this powerful record was born. They had to record this in video.

Fortunately, when Ye Xiu defeated Bai Shu, Samsara and Hundred Blossoms had also just finished their first battle. The broadcast didn’t care too much about how difficult it must have been for Hundred Blossoms, as the away team, to earn a point against Samsara. As soon as they saw how perfectly the timing was, they didn’t hesitate to switch the cameras over to Happy.

The commentators Pan Lin and Li Yibo also couldn’t be bothered to compliment the old general Zhang Wei or acknowledge how difficult it must have been for him to defeat Samsara’s All-Star Lu Boyuan. The two swiftly began to sing their praises for this terrifying win record that Ye Xiu had established.

“An incredible record, an incredible record.” Pan Lin repeated this phrase three times, because he truly couldn’t find any other words to describe it.

“Thirty-seven consecutive wins, Ye Xiu is really…” Li Yibo also couldn’t find the words.

“Amazing!” Pan Lin found it.

“Mm.” Li Yibo nodded, but he didn’t echo it too much. Because of his Tyranny background, it was already somewhat difficult for him to give impartial commentary on Ye Xiu. To extol him now, to proclaim him the greatest, Li Yibo suddenly felt somewhat uncomfortable.

“Happy’s fans are very excited. These are all fireworks that they’ve set at the stadium, to celebrate this birth of this extraordinary record,” Pan Lin described the scene at the stadium.

“Right now, Ye Xiu is walking offstage. The audience is giving him a standing ovation – oh, and the players of the two teams as well! 301 is very dignified, even though this record was ultimately built from their defeat. Haha, even the judge is coming over, standing at the side of the stage and applauding, this record is truly too moving. To be able to experience this moment in person is also a very fortunate thing!” Pan Lin continued.

“The judge has finished clapping, it looks like he’s saying something. Hm? He’s insisting that the match continue? This judge is a bit strict. At such a historic moment, what’s the harm in letting everyone be happy a little longer?” said Pan Lin.

“This is the final, most critical match, after all!” Li Yibo said.

“Mm. The display screen is already showing the players for the next battle, Happy’s Luo Ji, the MVP of last round, the rookie who’s earned the respect and notice of us all. What about 301? Oh, it’s the Blade Master Gao Jie! Let us… Oh, let’s return to Samsara versus Hundred Blossoms.” Pan Lin wiped at his forehead. He had almost begun to start commentating the match of Happy against 301.

At Samsara’s home stadium, the match had progressed to the second battle of the individual competition. Hundred Blossoms had won the first battle, earning a first point, so this match was off to a good start for them. And 301 had lost a point first, which was good news for Hundred Blossoms. But their primary competitor right now was still Wind Howl, and news from Tiny Herb’s home stadium said that Wind Howl had also won their first battle. Having won one point, they continued to suppress Hundred Blossoms by their superior head-to-head score.

“Don’t worry about everyone else. We’ll only have the right to seize our chance if we play our own matches well!” Hundred Blossoms Captain Yu Feng encouraged his teammates. In the second battle of the individual round, they would be sending Zhou Guangyi against Samsara’s vice-captain, Jiang Botao.

Another win!

A few minutes later, Hundred Blossoms once again received good news. Zhou Guangyi defeated Jiang Botao, helping Hundred Blossoms earn another point.

“Hundred Blossoms is in excellent condition today!” Pan Lin and Li Yibo both exclaimed. In these two consecutive matches, the Hundred Blossoms players had performed exceptionally.

And after the end of each match, everyone would immediately worry about the points of their direct competitors.

“301 won the second individual battle against Happy,” Pan Lin said, checking updates from the other matches.

“In Tiny Herb vs Wind Howl, Wind Howl also won the second battle,” Li Yibo added, looking in on that match.

“Well, it looks like Hundred Blossoms is still behind!” Pan Lin sighed. Even though they’d managed to win two points from the powerful Samsara, they still hadn’t been able to change the situation. This could be quite a blow to morale.

“Hopefully Hundred Blossoms won’t be disrupted. They need to adjust their mentality and play their next battles well. This is only the beginning,” said Li Yibo.

Nomyummi Bad news folks, updates are going to slow down to maybe 1 chapter every 2 days for the next twoish weeks. I will be going on vacation to Japan from 12/12-12/25. Our other two main translators (Syncogon and Jouissance) are also very busy around that time and cannot translate either.

Chapter 1375 - Seeking Victory

Reality was cruel.

Hundred Blossoms had taken 2 points from Samsara with great difficulty, yet they were still in a predicament. It was a huge blow to their morale. Although their captain Yu Feng was constantly trying to encourage them, every player had a different personality. Not everyone was so tenacious.

Team Hundred Blossom’s third player in the individual competition, their Summoner Zhu Xiaoping, was downcast. Knowing that Hundred Blossoms could not afford to lose a single point, the pressure bearing down on him was enormous. In the end, he performed poorly and lost to Samsara’s Assassin, Wu Qi.

At the same time, news from two other matches came, which only added hail to snow for Hundred Blossoms.

Team 301 had won against against Happy, taking a 2-1 lead with the individual competition.

Wind Howl had swept the individual competition against Tiny Herb, taking all three points. If Hundred Blossoms wanted to surpass Wind Howl, they would now need to win 2 more points over them instead of 1.

After Zhu Xiaoping, who had just gone down from the stage, heard this news, the color on his face became even paler. He wanted to apologize to his teammates, but he didn’t know what to say. He just stood there like a statue, unable to even find his own seat.

“We’re going to need to win 2 more points than Wind Howl, or win 3 more points than 301. What are your thoughts everyone?” Captain Yu Feng said.

Everyone was dead silent.

“Uh, or to be more precise, it should be what are your thoughts, and what are your thoughts?” Yu Feng looked over two players.

Zou Yuan and Zeng Xinran.

They would be the players going up in the group arena. Yu Feng ignored the rest of the team and only picked out the two players, who would be fighting for the points.

“I won’t give up!” Zou Yuan spoke firmly.

Yu Feng nodded his head and fet gratified. In fact, Zou Yuan held more seniority than him in Hundred Blossoms. He was the successor of Hundred Blossom’s Spitfire, the core of the team for many years. But after his arrival, Zou Yuan was perfectly happy to give him full authority in the team. This sort of trust and acceptance made Yu Feng even more confident that he had made the right choice. Right now, with their backs to the walls, Yu Feng trusted that Zou Yuan would not let him down, and he would put in his utmost as well.

Yu Feng and Zou Yuan both turned to Zeng Xinran.

“Fight! What’s there to be afraid of!” Zeng Xinran responded. In his very first match on the professional stage, he had been so nervous that his entire body had froze. To Zeng Xinran, that was his most shameful moment. From then on, he carried the attitude that it was impossible to ever do worse than that time. In fact, he became braver and braver on stage until he gradually rose to his position in Hundred Blossoms, a position high enough such that in this crucial match, the team had sent him up for the group arena.

Seeing the determination of his two seniors, Zeng Xinran found no reason to retreat and boldly stood together with the two of them.

“Good!” Yu Feng said in a voice loud enough for the entire team to hear.

“What’s there to be afraid of? If we win the group arena and Wind Howl loses there’s, we’ll take the lead,” Yu Feng said.

“Watch us!” Zou Yuan was Hundred Blossom’s vice-captain. In this crucial moment, he would bear the burden together with Yu Feng.

“Let’s go!” Yu Feng said.

“Yes, captain!” Zeng Xingran replied loudly. At age 17, he strode forward at the very front.

This was Samsara’s home stadium. They would receive no encouragement or support, but their hearts were firm. They knew that in City K countless Hundred Blossom fans were waiting for them to grab the ticket to playoffs, and there was only way to get that ticket — win.

The other matches were taking place at roughly the same pace.

When the group arena between Hundred Blossoms and Samsara began, Wind Howl’s three players, their fighting spirits burning, were continuing their charge towards Tiny Herb.

Zhao Yuzhe started the group arena, facing Tiny Herb’s Gao Yingjie.

The two were rookies of the same generation. Gao Yingjie joined the champion Team Tiny Herb as soon he began and received countless attention. It seemed as if it had already been predetermined that he would be Best Rookie that season. However, in Season 8, the Best Rookie title was given to Zhao Yuzhe. Why not Gao Yingjie? It was because he had played in too few matches and didn’t qualify for the Best Rookie contention.

The title had been awarded to Zhao Yuzhe, but in response, many people simply sighed – it was a pity that Gao Yingjie hadn’t been given enough chances to play this season.

Zhao Yuzhe was very unhappy, extremely unhappy.

If he wasn’t given enough chances to go on stage, then it meant he wasn’t ready yet. However, everyone seemed to think that if Gao Yingjie had played in enough matches, the title of Best Rookie wouldn’t have been given to that Zhao guy.

Peh!

Zhao Yuzhe didn’t believe it. He didn’t believe that this so-called genius was anything incredible.

But in Season 9, Gao Yingjie, who had failed to qualify for Best Rookie, had directly been chosen into All-Stars. And Zhao Yuzhe? He still carried the title “rookie” and was “still maturing” in Wind Howl! Even more infuriating was that season, a little demon had popped out of Blue Rain, taking the title Best Rookie and voted into All-Stars.

In the Glory Alliance, the title Best Rookie had first been awarded in Season 3 to Wang Jiexi.

Zhang Xinjie in Season 4. Zhou Zekai in Season 5. Yu Feng in Season 6. Sun Xiang in Season 7. Him in Season 8. Lu Hanwen in Season 9…

Every player who had been awarded the title Best Rookie became All-Stars or even Gods. In comparison, the name Zhao Yuzhe seemed pitifully pathetic among them. He was often nicknamed the Worst Best Rookie by some.

I’m definitely not trash!

Zhao Yuzhe really wanted to prove himself, and Gao Yingjie, the same-generation rookie who many believe should have received the title of Best Rookie, was an eyesore to him.

I’ll definitely give you a good beating!

Zhao Yuzhe made a firm decision.

“Come! Genius!” After the match began, Zhao Yuzhe called out into the chat. He was going to tell everyone that a genius was nothing special.

Gao Yingjie didn’t reply. He simply had his Kind Tree quickly move forward. The group arena map was neither complicated nor simple, a balanced map. Gao Yingjie flew directly towards the center of the map. Zhao Yuzhe didn’t want to show fear either. His Elementalist, Beautiful Light, also moved swiftly. Not long afterwards, the two sides met.

Piercing Lightning!

Zhao Yuzhe wanted to make a show of his strength to Gao Yingjie. As soon as Kind Tree entered Beautiful Light’s range, he immediately acted.

Lightning flashed, but at such a distance, no matter how fast the attack, it wouldn’t be able to threaten Gao Yingjie. He easily shifted to the side, dodging the Piercing Lightning.

Forward!

Kind Tree moved like the wind towards his opponent. Team Tiny Herb was currently in 4th place, but it would be difficult for them to move up or down from 4th, unlike Wind Howl and Hundred Blossoms who were placing their entire season’s hopes onto this single match. However, Tiny Herb definitely wasn’t a team that would just simply give away a free win.

The first day Gao Yingjie came to Tiny Herb, the first word he heard was “champions”.

They were a champion team. They existed to be the champions, and champions were always built upon victories.

They would never give up on the pursuit for victory. A team that aspired to be the champions should never let up.

Boom!

The spells by the two mages collided into brilliant lights. Gao Yingjie did not have Kind Tree stop though. These were the steps to victory, the steps to become champions.

Zhao Yuzhe was astonished.

He could clearly feel Gao Yingjie’s determination in a match that didn’t even matter to Tiny Herb.

Was it because he felt it was embarrassing for Tiny Herb to lose all three matches in the individual competition?

Zhao Yuzhe always thought about things from this perspective. He looked at himself and the team in this way. He also wanted to win, but his reason for winning was to show off his skill, to let everyone know his might. Even at the bottom of his heart, winning the championships was simply a way to show off.

This was Glory, not flaunting.

Zhao Yuzhe clearly didn’t think so, so he couldn’t understand Tiny Herb; he couldn’t understand Gao Yingjie’s pursuit for the championships, nor his heartfelt pursuit for Glory.

“I won’t let your arrogance run rampant!” That was all Zhao Yuzhe could think about.

In terms of spirit, he had already lost.

What about skill? Gao Yingjie was called a genius, and that wasn’t a title just anyone could have.

Boom!

The Witch’s spells gradually suppressed the Elementalist’s. Kind Tree finally made his way to Beautiful Light, and Elementalists could not match Witches in close combat capabilities.

“Shit!” Zhao Yuzhe hastily tried to Teleport. Beautiful Light shifted away, creating distance between them.

But who didn’t know how to use Teleport?

Kind Tree was a mage subclass. He had added the Teleport skill to his weapon, Morning Dew.

With a flicker, Kind Tree puller closer to Beautiful Light. His Teleport was only Level 1 though, so his Teleport distance wasn’t as far as Beautiful Light’s. But with just a sweep of his broom, Morning Dew, he instantly closed that remaining distance.

“How annoying!” Zhao Yuzhe refused to admit defeat. As he shouted, Kind Tree’s Morning Dew swung downwards.

Beautiful Light hastily dodged, but that swing had been exceptionally fast.

Gravity Accelerated Sweep!

Magic was used to increase the gravity and thus the speed of the swing to strengthen the strike.

Bang!

Morning Dew didn’t hit Beautiful Light, but rather the ground. With a loud bang, the force from the Gravity Accelerated Swing produced a shockwave. Beautiful Light had just jumped away to dodge the swing was hit by the shockwave and shot up even higher.

Kind Heart leapt onto his broom and flew towards the airborne Beautiful Light.

Pa pa pa.

Morning Dew struck Beautiful Light again and again.

These simple attacks didn’t contain any other meaning. Gao Yingjie and Kind Tree would always only have a single goal: victory.

GLORY!

The word “GLORY” flashed onto the big screen.

Any pro player, any Glory player would see this single word who knew how many times every day. For some, it was a word that was rooted deeply in their hearts. For others, it was simply a symbol of victory.

Glory only belonged to those who truly cared.

Chapter 1376 - So-called Talent

“In the Tiny Herb versus Wind Howl, Tiny Herb has taken the first round of the group arena!”

As the match between Samsara and Hundred Blossoms continued in the live broadcast, Pan Lin also stayed alert for updates from other matches. If the other matches had developments, the people there would also prioritize sending the information to the live broadcast.

“Oh, this is good news for Hundred Blossoms. Although Hundred Blossoms themselves…” Li Yibo cut off mid-sentence.

On this side, the first round of the group arena had not yet finished, but Hundred Blossom’s situation didn’t look too good. Zeng Xingran entered the stage with a fearless attitude, and played quite courageously. However, Sun Xiang, who was first up for Samsara, was not merciful in the slightest. In a head to head, Zeng Xingran still fell short in terms of technical skill. Zeng Xingran really didn’t have many options open to him in this situation, since he did not have the experience to compensate. He desperately fought with nothing but his stubborn refusal to accept defeat.

Zeng Xingran was at his limits and did all he could, but unfortunately, he still ultimately lost to Sun Xiang.

“Can Hundred Blossoms not seize this opportunity, when it’s finally a new era for them?” Pan Lin said.

All the Hundred Blossoms fans sitting in front of the TV wiped the sweat from their brows. It was one thing if they claimed a big victory, but were still knocked out of top eight because their competitors also won hard. However, if their competitor’s match was already falling apart and Hundred Blossoms didn’t seize this opportunity, the regret would probably be harder to endure.

Fight on!

Every Hundred Blossoms fan cheered for their team wholeheartedly. They still had two players, and they happened to be Hundred Blossoms’ core players. The fans believed that they wouldn’t lose so easily.

Fight to the last breath!

Zou Yuan entered the stage with such conviction.

He wasn’t some prodigy. His current core position was already a fluke. Hundred Blossoms had been looking toward the future when they hyped up his talent with the public, but Zou Yuan knew, deep down, that it was simply a public relations move to appease the fans. He was pushed into the core position by Hundred Blossoms because they really had no other choice. Talent? Zou Yuan didn’t know what talent he possessed back then. He was confident that Hundred Blossoms didn’t know either.

But he was very grateful.

He was grateful that Hundred Blossoms used this kind of helpless and senseless method to promote him. He was grateful that the team actually kept their faith in him patiently. He did not perform well in seasons 7 and 8. In season 9, instead of abandoning him, Hundred Blossoms instead measured him up and tailored a character to his style.

In the pro circle, there was a joke that the previous Spitfire of Hundred Blossoms, Zhang Jiale, possessed upstanding moral qualities. Thus, his successor possessed outstanding fortune…

This was a joke, but Zou Yuan had to admit that he really was fortunate.

He wasn’t some eye-catching prodigy. He could not forge a path to a core position himself. He was just an ordinary player, who somehow became a core player of a team as soon as he entered the professional circle. He actually came across this kind of dumb luck. Zou Yuan had felt hesitant, perplexed, and overly pressured.

But when he came to, he realised that he was like the child of a rich parent: he was given something that others would chase for a lifetime and still not obtain, without doing anything himself.

At this point, how could he still yell out “This isn’t what I wanted!”? He would probably be beat up by a group consisting of the whole Alliance’s regular players, rotating players, substitutes, and even those who wanted to get into the Alliance but who couldn’t. If you didn’t even want this, then what the hell did you want?

As a result, Zou Yuan started working hard. Because he knew this was a rare opportunity.

He didn’t have a gift and also didn’t know what his so-called talent was. He could only double down and train hard. He would forge his talent by grinding.

In Season 9, Hundred Blossoms acquired Yu Feng. The additional core took a lot of pressure off Zou Yuan. And this season, he had made great progress.

Now in Season 10, he managed to get himself into All-Stars with his own skills.

However, up until now, Zou Yuan still didn’t know what his so-called “talent” was. He just knew to display his hard-earned skill on the battlefield, to find more paths towards victory. Every player probably did this. While honing their own skills, they would slowly develop their own “talent”. Zou Yuan always thought of it that way.

Now, Hundred Blossoms faced a do-or-die match.

He needed to use his yet to be awakened “talent” to battle someone who was dubbed a genius in the Alliance.

But Zou Yuan did not feel fear.

He was no longer that newbie who struggled to shoulder a character like Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

He snatched up his outlandish luck, he possessed his own tailored character, and he nurtured his own confidence.

Charge!

Bright Blossoms rushed forward.

Bullets, explosives. He created a dazzling scene of his own.

He was the successor to Zhang Jiale, but had a different style to him. Zou Yuan controlled Bright Blossoms to tangle with the renowned One Autumn Leaf in combat from the get-go.

I don’t know what talent I have, but I can defeat any opponent!

“Beautiful play! Hundred Blossoms’ Zou Yuan seems to be unfazed by the current situation. He’s proactively launched an offensive and currently has Sun Xiang firmly suppressed!” Commentator Pan Lin yelled excitedly.

“He’s playing resolutely but also clear-headedly. His attacks are strong, and he’s defending well too. The group arena isn’t just defeating the opponent in front of you; there are still two opponents after Sun Xiang,” Li Yibo said.

“Especially when one of them is currently the number one in the Alliance, Zhou Zekai,” Pan Lin added.

“Even though Hundred Blossoms won against Samsara last time 7 to 3, I recall that they didn’t win the group arena,” Li Yibo said.

“Yes, last time Hundred Blossoms got two points in the individual competition,” Pan Lin agreed.

“Well, what about this time!” Li Yibo said.

This time, after sending off Sun Xiang, Zou Yuan welcomed his second opponent, Samsara’s blademaster Du Ming.

“Two more!”

Zou Yuan counted in his head calmly and continued to charge forth.

“Zou Yuan is in fantastic condition right now!” Pan Lin yelled. Zou Yuan again proactively launched an offensive this battle, and quickly gained the initiative.

“It really is fantastic,” Li Yibo also exclaimed.

It must be good, there’s no reason for it not to be.

I had this kind of luck and hit the ground running. If I don’t cherish this opportunity, what kind of future would I still have? What future would be even more brilliant than that I already had when I first started?

Having an iron grasp on my fluke, fighting tooth and nail to not let the opportunity slip away. That is probably my so-called talent!

The talent of not letting go of an opportunity that presented itself.

Because I’m the pro player who was given the best opportunity in Glory history!

Boom boom boom! As the bright flashes on the battlefield died down and the smoke cleared away, Du Ming’s blademaster was already on the ground.

“He won again!” Pan Lin was astonished. Even though he felt Zou Yuan was in great condition, he didn’t expect Zou Yuan to go that far. He managed to defeat Sun Xiang and Du Ming, while still having 41% health left on Bright Blossoms.

“Is this guy preparing for a 1v3?” Pan Lin yelled.

“…” Li Yibo was silent. His gut tells him that this would be impossible. 1v3 was hard enough, and their current opponent was Samsara… However, Li Yibo could also see that Zou Yuan was insanely fired up. A Bright Blossoms with 41% health remaining, under the control of the currently unleashed Zou Yuan, might just be able to beat the current Glory number one Zhou Zekai!

How’s it going on Wind Howl’s side?” Li Yibo suddenly asked for information from the other matches. He wanted to calm himself a bit. Zou Yuan’s sudden unleashing defeating two opponents in a row had the commentators very tense.

“Tiny Herb is leading, 2 against 1. Wind Howl only has Tang Hao remaining,” Pan Lin said very excitedly, even though he was a commentator and should not be biased. This was because he saw the amazing opening by Hundred Blossoms falter, followed by their hush and hesitancy after the loss of a point, and now their struggle to claw back two points. Humans had emotion; how would Pan Lin not be moved after seeing this struggle? He was really unwilling to see Hundred Blossoms’ season come to an end by losing this match, even after they gave it their all. That would be too cruel. Even though this kind of feeling would be unfair to Wind Howl, Pan Lin’s heart was with Hundred Blossoms right now. Li Yibo also had to take a deep breath. Why shouldn’t he feel like this? Why shouldn’t Hundred Blossoms deserve an outcome they worked so hard for?

“What about Happy versus 301?” Li Yibo asked again.

“On that side, 301 is in the lead,” Pan Lin said.

“If 301 wins the group arena, then they would be up 4-1 against Happy,” Li Yibo said.

“Indeed,” Pan Lin nodded.

“In that case, if Happy lost the team competition as well, they would only get 1 point this round,” Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin started. Happy only getting one point… This possibility was analyzed way before the matches started. Under these circumstances…

Pan Lin hurriedly counted the points using the current results in Hundred Blossoms’ and Wind Howl’s two matches. “Happy initially led Hundred Blossoms and Wind Howl by 7 points. If they only got one point, they would be ahead by 8. If Hundred Blossoms won this group arena and went on to win the team competition, they would have 9 points and overtake Happy! Wind Howl already has three points from the individual competition. The group arena looks bad for them, so let’s say they lose these two points and go on to win the team competition, They would get 8 points and have the same points as Happy!”

“Happy has a chance to be pushed out of the top 8??!” Pan Lin said with great alarm, and hastily checked the previous results. If they had the same points…

“Oh, no they wouldn’t. Happy would have the advantage if they had the same points as Wind Howl. Happy has already secured their spot in the Top 8. If this happened, Wind Howl would be pushed to 9th because they lost to Happy twice,” Pan Lin said.

“If Happy won instead, 301 would get 4 points added to the 2 point lead they had. With only 6 points, they would be pushed out of the top 8 if Hundred Blossoms and Wind Howl both managed to win their respective team competitions,” Li Yibo said.

“Ah, so it’s like this huh,” Pan Lin nodded.

“So in conclusion, the team competition is crucial. Whoever loses the team competition out of these three teams could then potentially lose their spot in the play-offs,” Li Yibo said.

Chapter 1377 - Grasp the Initiative

Pan Lin and Li Yibo calmed their frayed nerves with an analysis of the current situation. On the field, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had already loaded into the map. Zou Yuan once again charged forth heroically. Even against Glory’s Number One, he showed no fear and no intention of backing down at all.

The sound of gunshots didn’t stop.

Gunfire flashed from the two muzzles, bullets flying, carving trails into the air.

Zou Yuan had initiative, but Zhou Zekai was no slouch either. After seeing two rounds of Zou Yuan’s performance, Zhou Zekai had figured out how to deal with him.

Be faster!

Be more precise!

Zou Yuan’s Hundred Blossoms Style required the successive use of skills to overwhelm his opponent. His previous two opponents, one a Battle Mage and the other a Blade Master, were both melee fighters and gave the mid to long ranged Spitfire plenty of openings to use these skills. They had to charge head on into Zou Yuan’s Hundred Blossoms Style.

But it was different for Zhou Zekai.

His Sharpshooter had an attack range that didn’t lose to and could even overwhelm a Spitfire’s. From the moment they engaged, Zhou Zekai had Cloud Piercer maximize his firepower, not giving Zou Yuan a chance to build up his Hundred Blossoms Style.

Though the two characters were ranged fighters, they looked like two melee characters, entangled in a brawl. The bullets were a chain between them, the trails they carved through the air, connecting the two characters intimately.

Neither of them could back down even the slightest, attacking relentlessly, bullets flying, trying to see whose predictions were more precise, whose mechanics were more flawless.

Flowers of blood bloomed on Bright Blossoms’ body, signs of bullets disturbing his flesh.

Cloud Piercer would sway and stumble every now and then, knocked about by the effects of the grenades Bright Blossoms threw.

Both of them were doing their best to overcome this through their mechanics.

At a time like this, whoever stepped back, whoever hesitated, would fall behind.

The gunshots didn’t stop until one of the two characters fell.

Cloud Piercer. In the end, it was Cloud Piercer that stayed standing on the field. Zhou Zekai, in the end, was the one to claim victory, and prevented Zou Yuan from achieving a 1v3. However, this victory had cost him. Cloud Piercer still had 59 percent of his health remaining, having spent 41 percent of his health. As for Bright Blossoms, the amount of health he had at the start was also 41 percent. The two characters had managed to tie in the amount health they had spent.

Zou Yuan had really done the best he could. Against Samsara’s group arena, he was probably the one who had done the best in everyone that had tried this regular season.

We can’t waste the chance Zou Yuan has fought to give us!

Yu Feng stepped onto the stage with this resolve.

That guy who had done all he could had given up the position of core to him. Since he had accepted this responsibility, he couldn’t lose to that guy on the field! Otherwise, what right did he have to call himself their core?

“Come on!” Yu Feng yelled into the chat. After years of being sealed away, Blossoming Chaos, the once Number One Berserker, had finally returned to his throne with Yu Feng’s arrival at Hundred Blossoms and now charged fiercely up towards Glory’s current number one.

If he couldn’t even take out 59 percent health, then how could he face his fellow teammates?

Greatsword Blossoms Burial slashed forth.

Slashing forth, determined, through Cloud Piercer’s rain of bullets.

Would they win?

All the Hundred Blossoms fans were anxious, hoping like never before. Even if the one blocking their way was Zhou Zekai, a person who’d make people think “there’s no way we can win” reflexively when on the field.

Win! 　 They had to win!

They absolutely must win!

Practically no one paid the details of their battle any mind; everyone’s focus was on the health of the two characters. This was the most alluring aspect of competition. Victory, it was victory, everything was to win. When victory and defeat were a hair’s breadth away, no one had the mind to care about what spectacular techniques were being used. Health, that was the clearest indicator of the line between victory and defeat, so everyone focused on the characters’ health. The changes in these two bars, representing the lifeforce of each character, were the clearest, most intense footnotes of the battle.

Whose health bar was depleting faster?

Whose health bar was depleting slower?

Cloud Piercer?

Blossoming Chaos?

The audience’s gazes flashed between the two, and occasionally, when the shot cut to one without the health bars, the audience practically had the mood to jump up and curse. The live broadcast knew that this was a moment of tension as well, and made sure that the health bars were clearly displayed, no matter what shot it was.

They’d win, right?

They wouldn’t lose again, right?

On the health bars, Cloud Piercer had only 5 percent of his health left, while Blossoming Chaos had 32 percent.

A very large advantage, but there was no relaxing until the very last minute.

Hurry and die already!

That was the only voice in the hearts of the Hundred Blossoms fans. Finally, greatsword Blossoms Burial struck down like a whirlwind, dealing the final blow in this battle. 　 “We won!!!” 　 Samsara’s home stadium erupted in cheers. Of course, this wasn’t that even the Samsara fans had been moved, it was just that the long-suppressed in-venue Hundred Blossoms fans exploded with emotion just as Blossoming Chaos finally killed Cloud Piercer.

“Oooooohhhhhhhhh!!!”

In that moment, the Hundred Blossom players on the player bench all jumped up like they were going crazy, as if they had already won the championship.

They had won. Under these trying circumstances, they had managed to win the group arena at Samsara’s home stadium.

“How are things going over there?” Immediately, someone asked after Wind Howl. Once this question was out in the open, the atmosphere tensed once more. If Wind Howl also won their group arena, then Hundred Blossoms would still be behind.

“Wind Howl…” Someone started looking up the match status, and then burst out in excitement, “They lost! Wind Howl lost to Tiny Herb in the group arena!”

“That means, right now, we…” 　 “Have a one point lead!”

“Yesssss!!!!” 　 The Hundred Blossoms players and the fans that came with them now all knew Wind Howl’s current status. Wind Howl had lost the group arena, so they currently only had three points. Meanwhile, Hundred Blossoms had won two individual matches and then the group arena, gaining four points and finally overtaking Wind Howl.

Though the match hadn’t completely finished yet, Hundred Blossoms had finally grasped the initiative. They didn’t need to act and plan around others anymore. So long as they did their best, so long as they won the following round as well, then they’ll have a hundred percent chance of entering the playoffs.

That unsteady feeling of knowing that even if they did everything they could to win they still might be knocked out by an opponent who was doing the same finally disappeared. Hundred Blossoms could finally put all their focus and hard work on the playoffs without caring about other teams.

“Hundred Blossoms’ dedication has finally allowed them to hold onto the initiative! Now, their fate is completely up to their own efforts. On the other hand, after being defeated by Tiny Herb in the group arena, Wind Howl’s survival will depend on how well their opponents do. Even if they manage to defeat Tiny Herb in the last round, their rival will have to lose to give them a chance,” Pan Lin said.

“Indeed. The last round, whoever loses the team competition will end their summer here,” Li Yibo agreed.

“Just one step away. That’s a very cruel result for anyone. But, there’s nothing to it. Today, one team must taste such a bitter end. Who will it be? 301 Degrees? Hundred Blossoms? Or Wind Howl?” Pan Lin’s words were no longer just commentating on this one match, but on three matches at once.

Hundred Blossoms and Wind Howl’s results had reached Happy and 301 Degrees as well. Chen Guo did a quick calculation with her fingers and delight appeared on her face.

“We’re in. We’re in the playoffs for sure now.” Chen Guo was excited, because now, their place in the playoffs was 100 percent certain. Happy would enter the playoffs and set out on the road to the championship.

“So it won’t matter even if we lose all our remaining battles?” Wei Chen asked.

“Yup.” Chen Guo nodded, but then added, “But everyone still has to do their best!”

“Of course. Who wants to walk into the playoffs with defeating hanging off of them?” Ye Xiu retorted.

“You don’t want to, but 301 Degrees wants to even less!” Wei Chen exclaimed. 301 Degrees had to win to ensure their place in the playoffs. Though they had won two individual matches and the group arena, they still had the danger of being knocked out of the playoffs if they lost their team competition. They had to do their absolute best in this last round of the regular season.

“Who cares about them?” Ye Xiu said, “They dared to win a consecutive four points off of us. We’ve got to teach them a lesson, right, Little Tang?”

“Definitely!” Tang Rou was still angrily waiting to venting her loss in the group arena!

“Alright then, let’s go! Let’s end the last round of the regular season with a bang,” Ye Xiu said.

“Best if they get eliminated because of it. That way we’ll be in their nightmares the entire summer, hahahaha,” Wei Chen laughed.

“Okay, let’s go and give them a nightmare!” Ye Xiu waved his hand, and Happy’s team competition lineup stood.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi and sixth player Tang Rou. This was the most common lineup of Happy’s this regular season, and they would pull the curtain on Happy’s regular season this match. 　 As for 301 Degrees, their players also stood after their captain, Yang Cong, gave them all a pep talk.

Yang Cong, Bai Shu, Gao Jie, Li Yihui, Sun Mingjing and then sixth player Qian Wenju was also their core lineup for the latter half of the regular season, after Bai Shu’s addition. It was with this formation that 301 Degrees managed to turn their situation around and become a powerhouse that charged towards the playoffs. In the latter half of the regular season, they had used this formation to defeat Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, and Tyranny. It was only because they lagged behind in the first half of the season that they were pulled into such an intense and anxious chase for the positions in the playoffs.

The people had all the reason to believe that if 301 Degrees could enter the playoffs, then they might get even further. They had already proven that they had the strength to compete with powerhouses in the regular season.

“Let’s win this!” 301 Degrees’ players cheered as the six core members entered the stage. After getting four points consecutively in the one on one matches, their morale was at an all time high.

Chapter 1378 - Playoffs Experience

The team competition of the very last round of Season 10 of the Glory Pro League began one after the other in the home stadiums of ten teams. Twenty teams, six players per team, a total one hundred and twenty players. Sixty of them would end their season here with this last battle. Fourty-eight of them would step from here to a more intense journey called the playoffs. And the last twelve would be bidding this stage a farewell after this match.

Happy’s home stadium, two teams…

One had already confirmed that they would be continuing their journey. The other was still working hard to reach that point.

They had to win.

301 Degrees had no other choice. Only by winning, could they make sure that their efforts this year weren’t wasted.

As for Happy…

“It’s the last round of the regular season. Let everyone see how much you’ve all grown this year!” Ye Xiu exclaimed.

All the players gazed back in silent determination.

“Especially you, Fang Rui,” Ye Xiu called Fang Rui out.

“Fuck off!” Fang Rui bristled. As an All Star player, hearing a word such as “growth” used on him pissed him off. Even though he was still transitioning between classes, Fang Rui felt that “integrate” was a much more appropriate word than “growth”.

“Let’s crush them. This is a rare chance to warm up for the playoffs. 301 Degrees definitely has the determination and lust for victory as a playoffs team. Take this chance to familiarize yourself with this rhythm!” Ye Xiu said.

This wasn’t just a pep talk.

Playoffs experience, finals experience, these things were a whole new level in and of themselves. The playoffs were engulfed in a far more tense pace and atmosphere, and this tension would peak at the finals. Under these situations, a player’s mental fortitude would be tested. Some inexperienced players might get too nervous or too cautious, resulting in careless mistakes.

Those with experience knew how to face the playoffs, and even the finals, allowing them to adjust their mood and mental state. They would be cautious when required, and strike without mercy when necessary. Many players might not be noticed much during the regular season, but they would shine during the playoffs. These were clutch players who had laudable mental fortitude. The more stressful and critical the situation, the better they performed.

Amongst Blue Rain’s current players, Qi Master Song Xiao was a renowned tough hearted player. From his performance and the statistical data gathered in the regular season, he was nowhere near god level, but during the playoffs, his combative ability would rise dramatically. Having debuted during the fifth season, he became a core member of Blue Rain after his debuting season, helping Blue Rain achieve the championship in the sixth season and earning himself the title of “Mister Clutch”.

Team Blue Rain’s lineup had gone through many changes these years, but Song Xiao had retained his position throughout all of that. He was usually in rotation during the regular season, but during the playoffs, his match time would greatly increase. It was clear that Team Blue Rain knew where his value lay.

Song Xiao was a player that had natural talent in this area. Most clutch players were born through accumulating playoffs experience. These experienced, composed veterans might not play much in the regular season, but they shone bright in the playoffs, and that was were the value in playoffs experience lay.

Team Happy’s rookies naturally didn’t have such experience. Though, from Ye Xiu’s observations, it was clear that Happy’s rookies had shockingly powerful mental fortitude, there was no saying if they would be able to last through the playoffs. This match was a rare opportunity. 301 Degrees would definitely be playing with the same energy that they would in the playoffs, so Ye Xiu hoped that his teammates wouldn’t let themselves relax. They should find the appropriate attitude to face the intense atmosphere of a battle to the death. Though the previous few rounds were very intense, it was nowhere close to a match like this that would decide a team’s survival. After all, they couldn’t compare to the intensity of the playoffs matches.

“Understood.” Once Happy’s onstage players replied, they each went into their own player booths. On the other side, 301 Degrees had finished preparations as well. The map loaded in, and the two sides soon began the match.

Happy’s map choice: Paulownia Tower

A map with a high point, clearly considering 301 Degree’s current preferred strategy. So long as there was a high point, then Happy could use it to observe 301 Degree’s movements and prevent their Life Risking Strike from hitting.

Thus, their strategy became clear and straightforward: fight for the high ground!

301 Degrees naturally wouldn’t be clueless about this map and they didn’t take any long routes, all of them charging out as soon as the battle began.

As such an important strategic point, Paulownia Tower naturally wouldn’t be closer to one spawn point or the other. Whoever arrived first would depend entirely on movement speed.

301 Degrees had charged out as a team but soon enough, the characters pulled away from one another.

Scene Killer!

301 Degree’s captain, Yang Cong’s Scene Killer charged at the head, having no intentions to move with the team. He sped up ahead of the rest and charged out towards Paulownia Tower first.

Team Happy’s Silver equipment was relatively few in number, making their stats more transparent. It was already Round 38, and Happy had garnered enough attention for their characters to be researched thoroughly. Movement speed wise, Yang Cong had confidence that he wouldn’t lose to any of Happy’s ordinary characters. Unfortunately, Happy had a very much extraordinary character.

Lord Grim.

If this unspecialized character used movement skills, then his movement speed would probably top Scene Killer’s.

However, Yang Cong predicted that Happy wouldn’t have Lord Grim stand guard over the high ground. In Happy’s core lineup, Lord Grim was a core melee DPS. The one to stay on the high ground would naturally be Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain.

However, Dancing Rain couldn’t outpace Scene Killer in speed. This, Yang Cong was certain, that Happy knew as well. Thus, having Lord Grim temporarily stand guard here before switching with Dancing Rain when she arrived was their most stable plan of action.

Yang Cong’s thoughts were clear and thorough.

Although 301 Degrees had never gotten a particularly good result in the playoffs before, they had participated enough times. As a player who debuted in the third season, Yang Cong had plenty of playoffs experience and knew all too well the suffocating atmospheres that surrounded these battles to the death. He didn’t lack playoffs experience, and so he was able to analyze the situation calmly and carefully.

Heading out alone with Scene Killer wasn’t just to fight for the high grounds, but also to do reconnaissance. Happy’s Lord Grim was slightly faster than he was. It wasn’t a good idea to engage while he had the initiative. The playoffs rhythm was to work towards a position of absolute advantage, so Yang Cong currently had no intentions of engaging.

He was just here to observe Happy’s arrangements and see what Happy was planning. If he had a chance, he’d strike. If not, then he’d wait. In any case, before his hand was forced, then he’d only come out when he had a solid grasp on the situation.

Paulownia Tower soon appeared in Yang Cong’s view. He took a look at the terrain around it and then had Scene Killer begin to circle closer.

From his understanding of Lord Grim’s speed, if the other went all out, he’d have arrived by now.

It didn’t appear that anyone was on the top of the Paulownia Tower. Where would Lord Grim be hiding? Under the tower? Inside the tower? Or somewhere close by? Was he planning to ambush Yang Cong?

Even as Yang Cong calculated his opponent’s movement speed, he trusted that his opponent also had a clear understanding. Though his Scene Killer was donned entirely in Silver equipment with his stats hidden, after fighting in this circle for all these years, Scene Killer’s stats had probably been figured out ages ago even if there was no exact data. Happy had a few veterans amongst their midst, so they had an idea.

He was circling to make certain that Lord Grim wasn’t hiding around.

However, after making a complete circle, he didn’t see anyone.

Yang Cong took a look at all the hiding spots around Paulownia Tower. Lord Grim wasn’t anywhere to be seen. If Lord Grim had arrived, then there was only one possibility: he was hiding inside Paulownia Tower.

Paulownia Tower’s interior comprised of a spiral staircase going all the way to the top. There were no open windows in the tower, so if Lord Grim wanted to hide inside, then Ye Xiu wouldn’t have any way of figuring out if 301 Degree’s people had arrived or not. He could onlt sit there and wait.

Yang Cong didn’t bother with further confirmations. After circling around, he had a new plan. He had found a good hiding spot next to the Paulownia Tower, so Scene Killer moved over and prepared to ambush.

He didn’t dare bet on if Lord Grim had arrived or not.

However, was certain that Dancing Rain had yet to arrive, and if she wanted to gain that high spot, then she’s soon come. As for the place Scene Killer was currently in, it was perfect for ambushing and killing Dancing Rain. If he managed to stall Dancing Rain, then he would’ve dismantled Happy’s plans. Yang Cong’s Assassin wouldn’t be at a disadvantage at all in a melee fight against a Launcher. If he made it so that the rest of Happy was forced to come and assist, then he would have managed to cause their formation to break up entirely.

Yang Cong’s plans were detailed and precise. This was exactly what an experienced veteran should be like.

Thus, Scene Killer hid there. This position was perfect. It was good for ambushing anyone that arrive in the direction of Happy’s spawn point and it was also out of range of an ambush from the top of or under the Paulownia Tower. This was a blind spot from any direction.

Yang Cong had only just hid Scene Killer away when he heard the sound of cannonfire.

She’s coming!

Yang Cong knew it this was Dancing Rain, heading over with Aerial Cannon.

The sound approached steadily and Yang Cong was already counting down in his head, aiming to attack at the optimal time. 　 Boom! 　 Boom!

Boom!

Yang Cong could practically see Dancing Rain jumping and firing to glide over!

Boom!

She’s here!

With another boom, Yang Cong had this clear idea in his head. This was the result of years of experience. He didn’t need to calculate. He could feel it.

Scene Killer jumped up, Dancing Rain’s figure immediately flashing by.

Shining Cut!

Scene Killer charged out.

Chapter 1379 - No Other Choice

A chilling light flashed out!

The Shining Cut of the Number One Assassin, Scene Killer, was clearly much fiercer, much swifter than one executed by an unspecialized like Lord Grim. In addition, Scene Killer was wielding dual swords. Though the attack speed couldn’t compare to a dagger, its attack power and range was much stronger. Different weapons also executed Shining Cut differently. For daggers, there would only be a single flash of chilling light. Scene Killer held dual swords, so the chilling flashes of light crossed into an x shape before slashing down to either side.

Two streams of blood trailed after the cross of chilling light, but at the same time, with three thunderous booms, explosions erupted between the two characters.

Su Mucheng’s reaction speed wasn’t slow. She had noticed movement from the corner of her eyes and knew that a character in the middle of Aerial Cannon couldn’t dodge, so she could only hurriedly turn her cannon around and blast back.

Although Shining Cut had hit Dancing Rain, it couldn’t stop Anti-Tank Missiles from activating.

The explosion threw Scene Killer to the side and the powerful recoil changed the pathing of Su Mucheng’s Aerial Cannon. Scene Killer had managed to close in with one skill, but he was soon left in the dust. Yang Cong wouldn’t let this chance escape and quickly readjusted his position and view. Just as Scene Killer landed, he lunged towards Dancing Rain.

Dancing Rain blasted the other with her cannon. Although it was all normal attacks, she comboed them with backward jumps, allowing her to attack Scene Killer even as she pulled away.

However, Yang Cong was prepared for this. After all, Su Mucheng was a skilled and experienced top player. It was hardly surprising that he wasn’t able to close in with just that. Yang Cong had left other tricks up his sleeve.

Swift Movements!

This skill didn’t have a short cooldown, so Yang Cong had saved it for this moment. It was clear that he had gotten to the point of thinking three steps ahead for every step he took for this match.

Swift Movements and then sprinting, that was the fastest your movement speed could get in Glory. Scene Killer’s form was so fast, he was practically a blur. He dashed past Dancing Rain’s missiles, and those who couldn’t see as well almost missed his dodge.

Heart-Piercing Stab!

Scene Killer caught up to Dancing Rain in the blink of an eye. His dual sword swept out with two more flashes of chilling light.

Boom!

Yang Cong really hadn’t expected that Su Mucheng would play the same trick twice. After that normal attack she had sent, she had time to attack again to try and hinder him, but she purposefully didn’t, letting her hand cannon droop like she was printing backwards. In reality, she was hiding the muzzle to secretly load a Cannonball.

Scene Killer’s approach was swift, and with that, he didn’t have the time to notice such an insignificant detail. By the time his dual swords Dancing Shadows stabbed out, Dancing Rain’s hand cannon Devouring Sun was set against Scene Killer’s chest like a knife.

A normal attack?

Of course not.

For gunners, their normal attacks were gunshots, so wacking someone around the head was actually a skill. For example, a Launcher’s knock-up skill, Swing, swung their cannon and knocked their opponent into the air. However, that clearly wasn’t what Dancing Rain was doing. The muzzle seemed to retract into the barrel, causing the hand cannon to shorten. In that moment, Yang Cong knew that this was a charged Cannonball and by then it was far too late to dodge. Devouring Sun’s muzzle bounced back out and flung forth a cannonball, which then rather unrealistically exploded between them upon hitting its extremely close ranged target. The recoil and blast power of the charged Cannonball was stronger than all three Anti-Tank Missiles added together, throwing Scene Killer far back while allowing Dancing Rain to retreat even further.

He had once again failed to stick close to Dancing Rain, but Yang Cong was relatively satisfied with the current situation. He had, at least, managed to stall Su Mucheng. If Happy couldn’t get the high ground, then their strategy…

“We’ve met the enemy!”

That was when a sudden messaged jumped out in the 301 Degrees chat. It came from Paladin player, Sun Mingjing.

Yang Cong felt his heart jump. He had the gist of this map down in his head. If 301 Degrees had met the enemy before they even got to the Paulownia Tower, then there was only possibility: Their opponent’s goal was never the Paulownia Tower. Instead, they had predicted 301 Degrees’ actions and took a shortcut over to catch them off guard.

So, if Happy never wanted to get the high ground, then that meant his stalling of Dancing Rain was meaningless.

However, Dancing Rain still appeared here as if she wanted to take the high ground.

This was…

“How many!” Yang Cong hurriedly asked in the chat.

“4” The reply was just a single number, with no coordinates or punctuation. Clearly, they were already in an intense battle.

Luring the tiger from its mountain!

The name of that stratagem filled Yang Cong’s mind.

He had tried to block Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain in order to destroy Happy’s plan of taking the high ground.

However, what was the point of Happy getting the high ground in the first place? Clearly, it was to better observe 301 Degrees’ movements as a whole and prevent them from successfully executing their favored Life-Risking Strike.

Thus, now, Yang Cong had successfully blocked Dancing Rain, but at the same time, where was their favored strategy? Without his Assassin, how would they manage to use Life-Risking Strike to kill their opponent’s key character?

Turning their trick against them!

Glory Textbook, Master Tactician Ye Xiu’s most practiced playstyle. This wasn’t the first time third season debuter Yang Cong had seen it, or experienced it personally.

But even now, no matter how on guard you were, you couldn’t defend against it.

It was as if, from the very first day Ye Xiu joined the Alliance, he had skills better than everyone else’s, a more comprehensive understanding, deeper and more meticulous strategies. He was like a time traveller from the future, able to stand at the front of everyone else no matter what. He had created countless playstyles, designed countless strategies, proposed countless theories.

Who could possibly be better at turning others’ strategies against them than this forerunner of Glory ?

It was like he had an absolute grasp over everyone’s thoughts and schemes and would easily stay one step ahead, always in the lead. By the time you noticed and realized, when you looked back, everything seemed so simple. But in reality? You had no way of thinking so deeply before, and you couldn’t predict the convoluted path he had chosen to walk.

301 Degrees had to cover for him to help him successfully execute Life-Risking Strike.

So Happy had to break this Life-Risking Strike strategy.

So Happy had to get the high ground.

So 301 Degrees, in order to protect their strategy, couldn’t let Happy get the high ground.

So 301 Degrees’ fastest character Scene Killer came here.

And the one most suited to standing guard at the high ground, Dancing Rain, also arrived.

Scene Killer had successfully blocked Dancing Rain, but at the same time, without Scene Killer, how was 301 Degrees supposed to get a Life-Risking Strike off?

If 301 Degrees couldn’t use Life-Risking Strike, then was the high ground even important anymore?

After this whole convoluted mess, it was 301 Degrees at a disadvantage.

They couldn’t use the strategy they had gotten used to, the strategy they had managed to defeat all those teams with.

Yet, Happy’s counter was built on such a simple idea.

If the person who could use Life-Risking Strike was no longer there, then they naturally couldn’t use Life Risking Strike. This was so simple, a young child could easily figure it out, yet that was exactly where 301 Degrees had fallen into the trap; Yang Cong had charged right into it.

Scene Killer wanted to turn and flee, but this time, the one stalling became Dancing Rain.

A melee class being chased down by a ranged class was a very painful process.

This was because you could only run like hell, dodge, flee, until you escaped the opponent’s attack range. You had no way of counterattacking. If you wanted to counterattack, then you had to close in, and closing in and fleeing were clearly opposites.

All these years, Yang Cong’s Assassin maintained the image of a heroic warrior that charged at the frontlines. This year, he had switched to kamikaze warrior. The art of escape really wasn’t Yang Cong’s forte. No matter what style he chose, he relied on passion. Dirty play, something that Nightwalkers usually relied on, wasn’t something that he really used.

Gunfire pursued Scene Killer, hindering Yang Cong’s escape.

He had already given up on throwing Dancing Rain off. He just ran and ran, hoping to regroup with his team as soon as possible and execute their favored strategy.

Under the relentless attacks, Scene Killer’s movement speed plummeted. Eventually, the battle appeared in his view. His brothers at 301 Degrees and Happy, their opponents.

Almost there!

Comfort filled Yang Cong’s heart, but soon enough, seeing the large swaths of shadows in his view, he wasn’t able to keep up his smile.

Yang Cong raised his view, looking up behind him.

This was the shadow of Paulownia Tower, lying on the ground. Not long in front of it was the battlefield.

He could have Scene Killer dash over and regroup with his teammates, but then? Then he knew that Su Mucheng, who had been pursuing him all this time, would let him go, because then she’d have Dancing Rain ascend the Paulownia Tower, and observe 301 Degrees’ tactical system from up high.

He had ran like hell all the way back, yet he was faced with such an awkward situation. Had their opponents planned to this point, too?

So, from the start, ever since he had the idea to block Su Mucheng, he only had one option.

Get rid of Su Mucheng!

Only then, could they resolve the dilemma they were in, allowing him to regroup with his teammates and execute their favored strategy.

Apart from that, there was no other choice.

Yang Cong had settled on this, yet Scene Killer still ran towards the battlefield, as if he hadn’t realized their plot.

As expected, Su Mucheng soon let him go and went into the Paulownia Tower.

Yang Cong purposefully slowed down, calculating the speed at which Dancing Rain could climb the tower before resolutely turning back and charging over!

He wanted to trap Dancing Rain inside the tower. Otherwise, if he just turned around and pursued his target directly, who knows where Dancing Rain would kite him to.

Yet, just as Scene Killer was about to arrive at the bottom of the Paulownia Tower, Yang Cong suddenly paused. He realized that he had made a mistake that he really shouldn’t have.

If he caught up, then could he manage to trap Dancing Rain inside the tower? Once she got to the top, she could just jump down.

He had really been led in circles!

Chapter 1380 - Repeat Effect

He couldn’t pursue, but he couldn’t not pursue either.

This wasn’t the first time Yang Cong had been met with an awkward situation like this in a match where no matter what he chose, it wouldn’t help. Was there a third option? Yang Cong didn’t know. Perhaps there was, but he couldn’t see it, so he could only pick one of two actions. Even if neither option was optimal, he had to make a choice. For every moment he hesitated, the worse the situation became.

After her!

In the end, Yang Cong decided to pursue Dancing Rain. Letting Happy take hold of the high ground would throw them into even worse straits. This was why when they saw the map, 301 Degrees’ players all felt their heart stutter, and they ended up sending Yang Cong forth to perform reconnaissance. Yang Cong noticed that their mistakes started from here, from letting their minds focus on the high ground of this map. As for him realizing that he wouldn’t be able to trap Su Mucheng, this was a very minor mistake. Even if he didn’t make this mistake, he’d had turned back to try and close in on Dancing Rain anyways, and then Su Mucheng would have Dancing Rain kite him, which might lead him in circles using the tower anyways.

They hadn’t been prepared enough from the beginning and hadn’t considered that Happy could use this high ground to trick them and counter trap them.

What would they do if they were met with such a situation again?

This thought flashed through Yang Cong’s head, but was soon pushed to the side.

This wasn’t the time for think about that. First, he had to focus on dealing with the current situation. If they managed to get into the playoffs, then it wouldn’t be too late to resolve this issue then.

Scene Killer ran like the hounds of hell were at his feet, charging right up the tower. He could clearly hear the sounds of cannonfire; who knew how much ranged support Dancing Rain had been able to provide already? In addition, the entrance to the tower was clear in her view. Su Mucheng immediately saw Scene Killer when the other charged up. Then, despite there being no voice, Yang Cong felt like he could hear Su Mucheng giggling; despite characters having no expression, he felt like he saw Dancing Rain flash him a smile.

Without any hesitation, Dancing Rain jumped off the tower roof.

Yang Cong didn’t hesitate. He had been expecting this. He too jumped off the roof without hesitation.

Diving Arrow!

Anti-Tank Missiles!

Scene Killer stomped on Dancing Rain in midair, but, at the same time, he was struck close range by Dancing Rain’s cannonfire.

Light and fire exploded in the sky. Below, Happy and 301 Degrees’ eight were deep in battle and didn’t have the time to pay any attention to it.

They knew what was happening over there. In comparison, 301 Degrees was naturally under more pressure. Without Yang Cong, their strategy lacked the most important aspect. They didn’t have to use Life Risking Strike, but after demonstrating their success in using it these few times, Yang Cong’s Scene Killer’s presence in and of itself became a huge hindrance to their opponents. So long as he was here, then their opponents would have to keep a careful eye on his movements, on what he was planning to do.

Team 301 Degrees would expand on this to claim victory. The ultimate goal of the match was victory. Using Life-Risking Strike was just a means to an end, but not the only means. It was just that this means had too large of an impact, making the opponents wary and making 301 Degrees’ openings successful. However, this time, Yang Cong’s Scene Killer wasn’t even there, so Team 301 Degrees couldn’t use the strategy they had been using for the latter half of the season. The remaining four weren’t performing so well against Happy right now. However, Bai Shu’s performance in the team competition was more striking than his performance in 1v1s. Protecting his teammates, synchronizing with them, even charging at the forefront, no matter what, he performed excellently. It was clear that he had already become an integral part of this team.

Unfortunately, a 301 Degrees with only him had still lost its sharpest sword. They could stall and stand up against Happy, but they couldn’t find a way to win.

As for Happy’s four? Under the mix of offensive and defensive maneuvers performed by Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash set ghost boundary after ghost boundary.

Ghost boundaries were inanimate, and players had life. A noob would probably think that ghost boundaries were easy to deal with: I’ll just stay far, far away from it, then my opponent won’t have any way to get to me.

It wasn’t that this was incorrect, but when a pro level Phantom Demon started setting ghost boundaries, they were also weaving a tight web. If they wanted to struggle out of it, if they wanted to get through it, then just staying far away wouldn’t be nearly enough, especially in a team competition.

Ghost Boundaries were inanimate, players had life, but these living players included a Phantom Demon’s teammates.

In a team competition, if you wanted to retreat, then you had to make sure that everyone on your side could retreat successfully. This clearly wasn’t as simple as escaping on your own in a 1v1. In a team competition, Phantom Demons would cooperate with their teammates to capitalize on this. There was no need to trap everyone on the other side. Just trapping one person was equal to trapping everyone. After all, they couldn’t just leave one of their teammates here to die.

Not good!

Seeing the ghost boundaries appear one after the other around them, 301 Degrees’ players knew that things weren’t looking up for them. They desperately needed Yang Cong’s support, but Yang Cong couldn’t come over.

What should they do?

“Here” a single word suddenly popped out in the chat. It was Bai Shu.

Here? What’s here?

301 Degrees’ team members knew that it wasn’t the time to ask, and all turned their gazes towards Bai Shu’s Tide.

Knight’s Spirit!

Bai Shu’s Tide activated the Knight’s awakening skill and then bellowed, waving his sword and shield in the air.

Sacrificial Roar!

Bai Shu had finally gotten a chance where he’d be able to take control of all four of Happy’s characters at once. He swiftly grasped this chance and then released this Sacrificial Roar, which just so happened to reach all four of Happy’s members.

He had waited a long time for such a chance. From the beginning, he had realized that Happy was on guard of his taunt skills and the occasional chance that appeared were all traps.

As expected of Ye Xiu!

Bai Shu’s opinion of Ye Xiu had gone through a huge metamorphosis by now. Not only did the other have skill that not even he could rival, his team worked together like a well oiled machine. However, Bai Shu believed that there would be an opportunity. No one could work flawlessly like a robot, so he waited patiently, endured patiently, observing the situation and preparing to grasp this opportunity.

It had come.

Under the effects of Sacrificial Roar, Happy’s four all forcibly turned to attack him. However, Roar and Provoke were different. Provoke inflicted a Taunt that had a time limit on a single target. Roar would affected everyone within range, but only lasted until the taunter was attacked once.

For ranged fighters, it was easy to get rid of Roar’s effect. All they had to do was attack the target once. It was more troublesome for melee fighters. If they were far away, then they would have to close in first, and the skills unleashed while not closed in would be judged by the system to see if they counted as attacking the taunter. Currently, it seemed that the system wasn’t so easy to trick. It would make a judgement using the range of the attack to see if it posed a threat to the Knight or not.

Ye Xiu and Fang Rui both had ranged attacks, so within a second after Sacrificial Roar, Lord Grim and Boundless Sea immediately sent attacks at Tide and resolved the effect. Yet, even so, their original offensive was interrupted for a moment, allowing 301 Degrees’ other three members to do as they pleased without hindrance for a moment.

For Happy, the one most affected was Qiao Yifan. Ghostblades could use the power of the Phantom Ghost to execute attacks of a longer range than Blade Masters and other Swordsmen. However, right now, he wasn’t close enough to reach Tide with his attacks, so Qiao Yifan had no choice but to have One Inch Ash rush after Tide. Unfortunately, Bai Shu’s main target was this Ghostblade of his. He wanted to pull away, making it so that One Inch Ash couldn’t strike, and thus destroying his Ghost Chaining technique.

From this point of view, Roar’s effect really was rather disgusting. If the opponent couldn’t execute an effective attack, then the taunt would remain forever.

However, it wouldn’t be that easy to maintain this effect because Happy had two characters that could cleanse it.

The Qi Master’s Calm and Composed.

The Cleric’s Focus.

These were both skills that could remove the taunt status, and Happy just so happened to have both classes.

By now, if 301 Degrees’ players didn’t think to support Bai Shu, then they might as well retire.

Triple Slash!

The moment Sacrificial Roar was executed, Gao Jie immediately understood what Bai Shu was trying to do. Stellar Sword swung his white lightsaber, carving a brilliantly white sword light into the air and dashed towards Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea, not giving him a chance to use Calm and Composed.

Bai Shu, on the other hand, used Knight’s Spirit to charge at An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands with a Heroic Charge.

Li Yihui’s Grappler, Moving Mountains, charged towards Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

Normally, an unspecialized wouldn’t have any skills that could remove taunt, but Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could have a skill equipped to each form, so they had to be wary of the possibility.

As expected!

Seeing Lord Grim’s movements, 301 Degrees began to panic.

His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had been folded into two parts, a tonfa in each hand, his palms held towards each other, qi flowing, it was the Qi Master’s Calm and Composed.

Don’t even think about it!

Li Yihui was desperate. His Grappler’s attack range was absolutely appalling, and he most likely wouldn’t make it in time. However, an ex All-Star level Grappler player wouldn’t give up so easily.

Circle Sweep Kick!

Li Yihui’s Moving Mountains leaped into the air, shooting forwards. He seemed to grab for an opponent in midair with his legs, but there was no target within range. However, with this leap forward, he managed to catch up with One Inch Ash’s movement, blocking Lord Grim’s target for Calm and Composed and making him unable to target One Inch Ash.

This was a small trick, but it was effective.

Lord Grim’s Calm and Composed failed, in the end, and he used it on himself in order to not waste it. Li Yihui sighed in relief, yet that was when he saw Lord Grim’s tonfas reconnect and then, with a click, it turned into a scythe.

A Priest weapon!

Li Yihui paled again.

There were too many Taunt removers for Priest skills. The Cleric’s Focus, the Knight’s Immovable Mountain, the Exorcist’s Calming Talisman, the Paladin’s Purify. All four classes had a skill of this kind and apart from the Knight’s, which could only be used on oneself, the other three could all be used on other targets.

After setting a Calm and Composed on his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, had Ye Xiu then added a skill with a repeat effect?

Chapter 1381 - So It Ends Here?

It wasn’t just Li Yihui, Bai Shu’s expression turned heavy too.

Adding on a skill with the same effect? It sounded wasteful, but to 301, it was their biggest bane. 301’s strategies had been brought back by Bai Shu. He knew better than anyone else how it should be played, as well as all the tricks and techniques involved.

In these strategies, the Knight was undoubtedly crucial. Provoke and Roar, the two Taunt skills, were essential for letting the Assassin complete a Life-Risking Strike and were incredibly valuable for other tactics too. It could be said that these were the two most important skills for their strategies.

These strategies weren’t used in China’s competitive scene. Bai Shu had confirmed it. And after 301 started using them, they became a force to be reckoned with. Their execution wasn’t perfect yet, but 301 had already achieved great results. A major reason for their success was the Alliance’s unfamiliarity with these foreign tactics.

However, Happy’s Ye Xiu had attached two skills with the same effect onto his weapon, most likely to target Tide’s Provoke and Roar. It was enough to say that he had grasped the key points of this set of strategies.

Luring away Yang Cong and his Scene Killer was only a part of Happy’s set-up. The other part was restricting the enemy Knight’s two Taunt skills.

With a Qi Master, a Cleric, and who knew how many skills Lord Grim had added onto his umbrella, Happy had numerous ways to achieve this goal.

What a guy. He’s even better than I imagined.

Bai Shu was shocked.

Ye Xiu had seen through his techniques, his thoughts, and even the strategies he had brought back from outside of the scene.

The Glory Textbook.

Bai Shu had heard of this nickname. Now, he was convinced, truly convinced. Was there anything this guy didn’t excel at? He was top-tier at every aspect of Glory? And that weapon his character possessed, Bai Shu had never even heard of it before. The European scene obviously had self-made equipment, but to create one that could transform, wasn’t that cheating? Wasn’t that changing how the game was supposed to be played? Bai Shu had questioned it at one point.

But now, he had nothing to say.

For such a freakish weapon to appear in such a freakish player’s hands, there was nothing he could say.

Lord Grim flickered, avoiding the flying Circle Sweep Kick from Moving Mountain. The scythe form Myriad Manifestations Umbrella arced in the air, drawing out a Rising Emblem, suspending Moving Mountain in the air. Instead of falling down, Moving Mountain shot into the air.

Lord Grim rushed forward, holding a talisman in his other hand, the Exorcist’s Meditation Talisman, which could dispel Taunt effects.

No one could be faster than Lord Grim, and no one could block him. Team 301’s current team comp had a very obvious weakness: no ranged.

Before 301’s sixth player Qian Wenju came onto the stage, 301’s starting team comp consisted of an Assassin, a Knight, a Blade Master, a Grappler, and a Paladin, all melee.

An all melee team was a viable team comp though, unlike all ranged team comps. Even though they would have some trouble against ranged attacks, all melee teams had the numbers advantage in melee brawls. This was the goal of all melee teams. Defense first, and then once an opportunity appeared to fight the opponent melee characters, jump at it and never let go.

However, oftentimes, without a long-ranged class, they could meet situations where there was nothing they could do. For example, trying to interrupt a skill was exceptionally difficult. Lord Grim was getting ready to attack, but without long-ranged firepower, they had no suitable ways of stopping him.

Pa!

Lord Grim’s Meditation Talisman was stuck onto One Inch Ash. The Roar effect was finally dispelled. Qiao Yifan immediately had One Inch Ash place down a ghost boundary. The timing of the dispel was immaculate. The ghost boundary could continue to remain.

At this moment, Bai Shu turned around and lifted his hands. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim made his way over to him in a single step. Bai Shu was shocked. With just one press of his finger, Tide would have let out a Glorious Provocation, but Lord Grim stood in his way. This was the method that Li Yihui had used to block Lord Grim’s Calm and Composed.

Lord Grim moved towards Tide, but was Ye Xiu afraid?

Tide had reached Little Cold Hands. Even if Bai Shu hadn’t Provoked him, Ye Xiu would have went over anyways to rescue their healer. Now, with the Provoke, he didn’t even need to press any buttons to move. He could focus solely on using skills as he rushed over.

Bai Shu was helpless.

Provoke and Roar had been used, and under Knight’s Spirit, their might had even been buffed. However, the opponent had blocked them. Could he still escape?

No tricks would work. His only choice was to brute force his way out. If it was just himself, he could have ran long ago, but the goal was to get the rest of the team to retreat too. One Inch Ash’s ghost boundary needed to be put under control. 301’s objective hadn’t changed.

Just Heroic Leap!

Tide jumped over Lord Grim’s head and smashed towards One Inch Ash. Lord Grim was still under Provoke’s effects though. The system forced him to follow, so his reactions were perfect. Tide had quickly leaped over his head, but Lord Grim instantly turned around. Ye Xiu followed in his steps and also jumped. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear, Circle Swing!

Pu!

Tide was stabbed in mid-air. Bai Shu turned his head in disbelief. To be able to attack in this situation, what were his limits?

Bang!

Tide had been thrown to the ground by Circle Swing. The weight of a fully plated Knight wasn’t light. He formed a crater in the ground as the earth trembled. Bai Shu immediately had Tide get up, but his skills were locked. Happy’s Cleric had probably thrown down Sacred Fire when Lord Grim threw him, sealing his skills.

In the blink of an eye, Qiao Yifan completed a chain of ghost boundaries. He didn’t need to trap all of 301, just a single character was enough. Unless their opponents were crippled, how could they not go rescue their ally?

Gao Jie was unfortunately the one to be captured. He was wildly attacking to stop Fang Rui, but he didn’t realize that it was actually him being locked down by Fang Rui. One Inch Ash’s ghost boundary chain linked together with him in the center of it.

Gao Jie was dumbfounded. Then, he watched as the rest of Happy rushed over, each of them with sinister expressions.

Not good…

Team 301 could do nothing. They couldn’t help but look towards the other side. Their team captain, Yang Cong and his Scene Killer, should be back by now. But, no. Yang Cong was currently fighting with Su Mucheng, who was patiently kiting him. In short, she was doing one thing: stalling.

Yang Cong completely understood Su Mucheng’s intentions, but he had no way of resolving the issue. In fact, he was hoping Bai Shu and the others could find a way to come over and group back up. If everyone lockedd Su Mucheng outside of Paulownia Tower, their tactics would be able to open up. How could he know that Happy had locked up the other four, stopping them from leaving. Both sides were hoping for one another to save them, but right now, neither side could help the other.

In the end, the trapped Gao Jie was unable to be rescued.

When Yang Cong saw Stellar Sword’s name suddenly turn gray, his heart sunk.

He knew that the other side had lost, and in the end, he wasn’t able to get rid of Su Mucheng and rush back to help. Despite knowing the other side’s intentions, he could do nothing but be led around by the nose into a losing situation.

Gao Jie had fallen. Who was next? Yang Cong clearly knew that the death of an ally was the most dangerous moment. The remaining players would instantly feel the pressure multiplied. Before their sixth player arrived, everyone would need to put in even greater effort to hold on in order to last while their side had a numbers disadvantage. If any teammate was unable to persist, the opponents would utilize their numbers advantage to quickly sweep everyone.

I need to group back together with them. Yang Cong made his decision. Scene Killer tossed Dancing Rain aside to return. Su Mucheng continued to give chase with her Dancing Rain, but this time, Yang Cong’s retreat was more decisive. When Dancing Rain entered Paulownia Tower, he didn’t even look back.

In this live or die moment, tactics could only be thrown aside for now. To group up, even if they had Su Mucheng above breaking their tactics, it could be considered as a method of intimidation. Afterwards, they could go on the offensive. Either way it was still better than letting Happy lead them around by the nose.

Scene Killer finally grouped together with everyone, and 301’s sixth player had quickly arrived as well. But it was too late.

When Yang Cong got closer, he saw that Bai Shu’s Tide no longer had much health left. At a numbers disadvantage, he had relied on his sturdy plate armor and his own body to protect the other two members. As a result, he took huge amounts of damage.Their healer, Sun Ming’s Paladin 007 had been focused by the other side as well and could not provide any assistance.

Yang Cong was only an Assassin. He wasn’t a healer. His return could help relieve some of Bai Shu’s burden, but at this point, Happy was trading health for health. At this rate, Tide would certainly be killed.

The Knight Tide was perhaps had the most health out of any Knight in all of Glory, but in order to protect his team, he fell as well.

Boom boom boom!

Dancing Rain had climbed up the Paulownia Tower and was providing help. Yang Cong lifted his head and saw the dazzling yet harsh gunfire.

We lost!

Yang Cong knew that the fight was over.

But was it the end of this match, or the end of their summer?

How bitter! No matter what, losing would always make one feel bitter!

I don’t have many too chances left!

Reality was cruel. With this team competition, Happy beat 301, the final score 6-4. Team 301 would have to wait for the results of the two other matches before they could know their final fate.

As for Happy?

“To think they didn’t even let me play, or could it be a mark of how much we’ve improved?” Tang Rou wrinkled her brow in complaint.

Chapter 1382 - It’s All Over

"Happy and 301 Degrees' match has come to an end. Happy won."

In the live broadcast of Samsara and Hundred Blossom's match, Pan Lin immediately announced the results of the other match once he received them.

"Happy won, huh?" Li Yibo sighed, his tone filled with sorrow. Pan Lin didn't respond, and let out a sigh of relief as well, before focusing on the match again.

Happy had won. Originally, this was great news for Hundred Blossoms, but unfortunately, they hadn't managed to grasp their chance this time. In the team competition against Samsara, Hundred Blossoms was clearly at a disadvantage. Currently, it was five against four on the field, with Hundred Blossoms down one person. It looked like they weren't going to be able to defeat Samsara twice in the regular season after all.

Would they have a chance to turn the tables?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo both silently watched on. If there wasn't any miraculous save, then there was little need for them to commentate.

"How is Wind Howl's match going?" Li Yibo suddenly asked.

"It's not over yet." Pan Lin was also, in fact, checking up on the other match every now and then. However, the only information he had gotten so far was that the match wasn't over yet, but no details.

The match continued. With the fall of each Hundred Blossoms character, the hope for a miracle dimmed a little more.

Pan Lin sighed again.

Hundred Blossoms had done everything they could. Even in front of a powerhouse like Samsara, they maintained hope. Finally, they were able to gain two points in the group arena and overtake Wind Howl, grasping the initiative.

But fate had once again played a cruel trick on them. They had gotten the initiative, but it had slipped out of their grasp again. Right now, all they could do was wait for the results of the Tiny Herb and Wind Howl match.

But by the time Samsara and Hundred Blossoms match ended, the results still hadn't come out.

6-4. To Samsara, this wasn't any spectacular victory, but the venue had exploded into a sea of cheers.

The thirty eight rounds had finally came to an end. Samsara had obtained a total of 319 points. They had started in the lead and had never once been overtaken. Their entry into the playoffs had been guaranteed four rounds ago. However, out of respect, they didn't celebrate too much. But now, with all thirty eight rounds over, there was no need to hold back any longer, and this was Samsara's home stadium as well. They had long since prepared a celebration ceremony, and some hadn't even managed to wait until the end of the match to start.

Team Hundred Blossoms shook hands with Samsara's members amidst this joyful cacophony. Samsara's members were courteous enough to wait until after these procedures were over to wave their fists in celebration with the Samsara fans in-venue, a celebration of thirty eight rounds of victory.

"We are the champions!"

This classic by Queens blared through the stadium speakers. The fans in the stadium all roared along with this line. This was a truth in the regular season and a beautiful blessing for their playoffs journey.

Team Hundred Blossoms left the stage disappointed, surrounded by this sort of atmosphere. No one would care much about the losers, and it wasn't the first time Hundred Blossoms had been filled with disappointment in a celebratory situation. Their seniors had walked off the stage of the grand finals in disappointment like this thrice.

"Has it ended?" The players that had just finished playing in the match didn't know the results of the other match. After asking, they found out that Tiny Herb and Wind Howl's match was still ongoing.

"Is there any hope left?"

Everyone held hope, but this feeling, how they couldn't grasp this hope with their own two hands, was terrible. They felt like a grounded fish. They could do nothing but wait.

What would it be?

Their eyes held hope and anxiety, and a mess of similar emotions.

All until the news came.

"We're in," The person who obtained the news said.

"Is that so?" Yu Feng gave a long sigh and sat down on the player bench. The tension in him finally drained out.

"We're in?" Some others still needed confirmation.

"Yes, we're in. We're in. Wind Howl lost to Tiny Herb. We're one point in the lead, we're in for the playoffs!" The person who had got the news burst out in excitement.

Hundred Blossoms' members looked at each other.

Excitement? Delight?

They didn't seem to be feeling any of that.

After all that had occurred, all they felt was a sense of relief, like they had managed to escape death.

In the yet unfinished live broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo had naturally also received the news.

"I didn't think it there would be such a dramatic ending to all this," Pan Lin commented.

"Yeah, in the last team competition, the three teams that needed to win didn't manage to win any of them. Thus, the points remain unchanged," Li Yibo said.

"We can't really say it's completely unchanged," Pan Lin laughed, "One round ago, Wind Howl sat at eighth and Hundred Blossoms was at ninth. However, Hundred Blossoms gained four points this round, overtaking Wind Howl and squeezing into the top eight."

"Unfortunately, Team Wind Howl wasn't able to enter the playoffs," Li Yibo lamented.

"But they're still young. They can try again next year!" Pan Lin said.

Thus, the regular season ended just like that...

Tiny Herb's stadium wasn't as lively as Samsara's. After all, for Tiny Herb, they had merely finished a match that had little to no effect whatsoever on their points. There was no need to celebrate getting into the playoffs either. They acted like this was all a very normal match, with an applause given to the two teams. However, under the applause stood the most disappointed team of the round.

They lost. It was over.

In the moment the match ended, Wind Howl knew that this would be the result. They were the ones who needed to win this round. The team that wouldn't have any chance whatsoever if they didn't win. However, in the end, they lost.

Especially knowing that 301 Degrees and Hundred Blossoms had both lost, Wind Howl were even more frustrated. A chance had appeared but unfortunately they weren't able to make use of it.

With Round 38 of the regular season, Team Wind Howl's journey fpr Season 10 had come to an end. They weren't able to get into the playoffs and, for a team that had set its goal as the championships, this was a complete failure. They had never expected that their summer would end so soon. They didn't know what they would do next. Everyone felt lost, and silently left the stadium just like that. A season of hard work, a season of their efforts, all dispersed in the wind.

The results of the matches of Round 38 were out one after the other. This would decide the teams final rankings and also the teams' first opponents in the playoffs.

The live broadcast still hadn't ended. It was waiting for this moment, the moment the final match results came out. Pan Lin and Li Yibo swiftly organized the materials at hand, giving a simple report on this season's final results.

Team Samsara was the regular season champions at 319 points.

After them was Tyranny in second with 278 points. They weren't as impressive as last season, and even began the season under doubt from all sides. However, after thirty-eight rounds, they had silently managed to climb over the other teams into second place.

Blue Rain was third, just a point away from Tyranny. They had switched places several times with Tyranny, and in the last round had ended things with a one point disadvantage.

Team Tiny Herb was at 270 points, placed fourth. Fifth was Thunderclap with 254 points, then it was Happy, 301 Degrees, and Hundred Blossoms, whose places were only confirmed with the last round.

Team Wind Howl, unfortunately, falling short by just one point. Void was tenth and Misty Rain was eleventh. After that, it was Miracle, Royal Style, Parade, Heavenly Swords, Lightly, Conquering Clouds and Radiant. Bright Green and Seaside were the only two teams of the season whose points didn't manage to reach the hundreds, and they were both relegated.

It's over!

For the teams not in the top eight, Season 10 was done. As for the top eight, they would enter the final war of the season. Considering the matchups the Alliance had always used, everyone could draw the matchup situation of the playoffs from the rankings.

"The ranked first Samsara will be up against Hundred Blossoms in the first match of the playoffs," Pan Lin announced the first set of opponents.

"This… the teams have just finished playing a round against one another, and now they're going to fight two more rounds in the playoffs, or maybe even three," Li Yibo pointed out.

"Then it's Tyranny versus 301 Degrees, Blue Rain against Happy, Tiny Herb against Thunderclap," Pan Lin continued.

"Yup. And then the winner of Samsara and Hundred Blossoms will fight whoever wins between Tiny Herb and Thunderclap, while the victor of Tyranny versus 301 Degrees will go up against whoever wins between Happy and Blue Rain. Then the winners of these two battles will go up against one another in the grand finals," Li Yibo announced the rest of the matchups for the playoffs.

"Coach Li, can you give a prediction of how the playoffs might go?" Pan Lin asked.

"Haha, the results are hard to say. In the playoffs, what's gained from the regular season loses its value, especially with the new rules in place. This makes it even harder to predict from the results of the regular season. For example, for Team Tyranny, they were a subject of doubt in the regular season, but now everyone's realized that they were saving up strength for the playoffs. Under these circumstances, it's hard to say how well Tyranny will perform in the playoffs," Li Yibo replied.

"Then what about Team Happy? What do you think of them, Advisor Li? This team managed to enter the playoffs as a new team. This is something that has never happened before. Where do you think they'll be able to get to, Advisor Li?" Pan Lin inquired.

Li Yibo could feel his insides clench. Happy was a team he didn't dare make predictions about!

"Er, Happy… well, they might count as a new team, but this new bottle holds old wine. Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, just the three of them alone have plenty of playoffs experience, comparable or even more than the other seven teams. Apart from that, it's all rookies. Such a conflicting team composition has never been seen before. I'm eager to see how they'll perform, as well," Li Yibo said.

"Haha, Happy's just finished their post match press conference. The reports asked about the playoffs, and guess how Ye Xiu replied."

"How?" Li Yibo asked.

"He said, now that they've gotten here, he won't be thrown off again," Pan Lin said.

"Ha! Let's hope that's true!" Li Yibo laughed.

Chapter 1383 - Regular Season Awards

The regular season finally came to a close.

At the Round 38 post-match press conferences, the teams that managed to get into the playoffs were asked questions on how they planned to face the playoffs. Each team’s response was rather reserved, at most expressing their determination. No one expanded on it too much.

The first round of the playoffs was set to beginning on June 14, the start of the new week. The playoffs would open with Samsara versus Hundred Blossoms. After resting for a mere eight days, the two teams would once again meet on the battlefield.

Eight days, no team would really spend these eight days resting and relaxing.

After confirming their opponents for the first round, each team entered a high tension state of preparations. It wasn’t just the teams that grew busier. The Alliance, the media, and sponsors were all rushing to make arrangements for this season’s climax.

The reporters sent out by different media outlets hoped to obtain the situations of each team’s preparations. Some teams would use this as a chance to set a smokescreen. The war that was the playoffs had started ever since Round 38 ended, from on the stage to outside the stage, from mental fortitude to mechanics and strategies. This war wasn’t just one on the battlefield.

Happy, because of their unique origins, had plenty of people keeping an eye on them. However, the day after the last round, Happy announced that they were going into isolated training. Even the Esports Home reporter Chang Xian, who was the closest to them, was sent away politely.

They weren’t the only ones though. Happy’s opponent for the first round, Blue Rain, had also closed itself from the outside world. Their PR gave the media a few courtesy words that were common in the playoffs.

The other six teams didn’t seem to treating this as solemnly as Happy and Blue Rain.

Samsara openly expressed their determination and confidence in accomplishing a consecutive three championships.

Tyranny kept a low profile like they had the entire season, not revealing anything.

Tiny Herb’s roster had undergone great change since their two championships, and captain Wang Jiexi expressed his hopes for Tiny Herb’s future. 　 Thunderclap’s captain Xiao Shiqin mentioned the awkward situation of how Thunderclap had never succeeded in advancing to the second round of the playoffs. This time, he expressed his hope that they would breakthrough. “We’ve gotten here, and we only have one goal: the championship!” Xiao Shiqin displayed an ambition that Thunderclap hadn’t dared display all season. 　 301 Degrees had only managed to charge into the playoffs with Bai Shu’s arrival in the latter half of the season. They might not have a high point score, but the combative power they had displayed in the latter half of the season was nothing to joke about. Thus, Team 301 Degrees was very confident about the playoffs. “This is a completely new 301 Degrees,” was what 301 Degrees expressed in their interview.

In eighth, Hundred Blossoms who had narrowly beaten Wind Howl by one point, first expressed, self-mockingly, that they really were quite lucky. “The playoffs is a new beginning. We won’t waste this rare fortune.” When Hundred Blossoms talked about luck, it would always make people sigh over it, but now they kept talking about their fortune and good luck; their attitude was most certainly very enthusiastic.

Let’s wish them a good luck in the playoffs.

All the reports on the teams were, in the end, about such words. After that, there were analyses and predictions for each team flooding in. Team Samsara was undoubtedly the one people had the highest hopes for. They had managed to leave everyone in the dust in the regular season. Even the Four Heavenly Kings of Tyranny in Season 9 hadn’t given such a dominating performance.

All sorts of reports, all sorts of comments, all sorts of debates.

The matches hadn’t even begun and the normal players were all in a tizzy, all talking about their reasons and opinions.

The esports sites had also began all kinds of polls, to calculate each each’s support ratio.

On June 8, six days before the beginning of the playoffs, the Alliance announced the rewards for the regular season.

King of Dueling, Happy’s Ye Xiu.

Arena Star, Samsara’s Sun Xiang.

One Hit One Kill, Samsara’s Zhou Zekai.

These three were calculated purely through statistical data with no subjectivity. The final results weren’t anything that could be argued over anyways. There were people who’d pick out needles in the haystack and even complain that Ye Xiu’s flawless record was built on a God, of all players, playing in the individual competition. These people who were just looking for trouble had nothing they could actually use against a record like this. The occasional nitpicker would be ganged up on and insulted into submission.

After the three statistically calculated awards, it was time for the other awards decided by the Alliance. Since different people had different opinions, these awards would elicit an intense debate each year. This year followed that trend, and the argument was the most intense yet because the Best Rookie went to Tang Rou.

The Alliance, in the end, decided to respect the fact that this was a competition of skill. Speaking solely in regards to performance, Tang Rou, a core member of Team Happy, held an impressive record of group arena wins and admirable performance in the team competition. No other rookie in the tenth season had a chance against Tang Rou for this award. The most impactful statement on her report was: a player that has managed to smash through Rookie’s Block 1 with her fierce determination.

Unfortunately, Tang Rou’s conduct had many people viewing her in a different manner. They were all more willing to point out her flaws and magnify them, using them to make her seem unskilled.

Of course, Tang Rou’s performance wasn’t flawless, and under such nitpicking, people could find flaws everywhere. After these flaws were magnified, Tang Rou was nothing more than a pretty face who couldn’t do accomplish anything, according to some. 　 Unfortunately for them, Tang Rou’s performance clearly rebuked that. Even if they had ignored her strengths, her victories were recorded and noted.

Tang Rou had broken through Rookie’s Block without faltering.

This was a spectacular achievement for a rookie, yet those nitpickers completely neglected to consider it.

In these ten years since the alliance had been created, only two people had managed to break through Rookie’s Block before without faltering: Wang Jiexi and Sun Xiang. Both were top Gods now. After that, last season’s Tyranny’s rookie, Qin Muyun had managed to play a stable hand through his debuting season. However, in Tyranny’s team, the four gods had drawn a lot of attention and snatched a lot of data. Qin Muyun’s statistical data wasn’t all that impressive, low profile to the point where people didn’t even think any fluctuations in his data were noteworthy. In addition to his rather wallflower like presence, he escaped most people’s attention.

This was to the point where, when the alliance was writing up the report on their choice of Best Rookie, they only mentioned Wang Jiexi and Sun Xiang for players who had broken through Rookie’s Block and completely ignored Qin Muyun.

However, this was enough to prove how impressive Tang Rou’s performance had been this season.

Because of this impressive performance, the Alliance couldn’t not give Tang Rou this award for something like “conduct”. From a competitive perspective, this definitely wouldn’t be fair. 　 Best Rookie: Happy’s Tang Rou.

That was the Alliance’s final decision, and they weren’t surprised by the uproar that it created. However, Tang Rou’s powerful performance gave them the confidence that she’d live up to the award she was given.

Compared to this Best Rookie, the other awards had some objections, but it wasn’t nearly as intense.

Best Sixth Player went to Blue Rain’s Song Xiao.

Most Improved was Hundred Blossom’s Zou Yuan.

Best Partners, in the end, was given to Team Samsara’s new striking duo, Zhou Zekai and Sun Xiang.

MVP, Happy’s Ye Xiu.

With the unspecialized character Lord Grim and his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, he had managed a spectacular thirty-seven consecutive individual competition wins and led a new team like Happy to the playoffs.

Ye Xiu’s return to the Alliance had brought yet another never before seen record.

Samsara’s strength, after two consecutive championships, was something everyone was used to now. In contrast, the lack of it would be uncharacteristic and disappointing. Naturally, everyone’s expectations rose. As for Happy, a new team like them reaching such heights was downright weird. What did one mean by “valuable”? This was valuable. It was because of his existence that Happy reached such heights. This display of value was the best explanation for the choice of MVP.

A fourth time!

That was when people realized that Ye Xiu had broken yet another record with this award.

Three-time MVP was a record belonging to Ye Xiu. No one would’ve guessed that after so many years, he would win it again.

Four-time MVP, and the Glory Pro League had only had ten seasons so far.

Behind Ye Xiu, it was the Season 8 and Season 9 MVP Zhou Zekai.

Then, there was Season 7’s Wang Jiexi, Season 6’s Huang Shaotian, Season 5’s Zhang Jiale and Season 4’s Han Wenqing. These names, at the top of Glory, had only gained such an achievement once each. The four of them added together was equal to one of Ye Xiu. 　 The true king has returned!

This was what many thought, seeing the number of this greatest regular season award that Ye Xiu had won.

In the prep time for the playoffs, the regular season achievements had caused a small uproar, but this was something everyone was used to already. The regular season awards were distributed at around this time every year, and every year, there would be objections.

However, such an intense argument over a rookie was something completely new. The Alliance had been prepared, clearly stating the reasons for Tang Rou’s award in an interview, but many still wouldn’t accept it and continued to argue over it. However, they couldn’t do much except argue, because they couldn’t change the Alliance’s decision.

The award winners would all be personally informed by the Alliance. Chen Guo was exceptionally excited over Ye Xiu’s and Tang Rou’s awards, while in the face of the other awards, Chen Guo became an irrational nitpicker.

For example, for Best Sixth Player, Chen Guo thought Tang Rou performanced well and was often fielded as sixth player, so she was definitely worthy of this award.

For example, Most Improved, Chen Guo didn’t care that Qiao Yifan only began playing official matches this year, saying that he had shown great improvement since he was in Tiny Herb, so he should get the award. Fang Rui had successfully switched classes, which was an improvement as well, so he should get the award as well.

For example, for Best Partners, Chen Guo had only ever and would only ever accept Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng as best, no debate.

“It should all be ours!” In the end, Chen Guo was very unsatisfied with the Alliance’s choices.

Chapter 1384 - Too Close

Happy responded to Chen Guo’s complaints with a grin.

Naturally, winning these awards were a cause for celebration, but Team Happy didn’t have the time for a celebration yet. They still had plenty to do in preparations for the playoffs, especially getting used to their new equipment.

Forty pieces of Pseudo Silver equipment!

In this last week, Happy’s R&D worked overtime and managed to finish the last three Silver equipment right after the end of the thirty-eighth round, giving Happy a total of forty pieces of Pseudo Silver equipment.

Compared to proper Silver equipment, Pseudo Silver equipment was disposable, a temporary fix for Happy’s lack of proper equipment, but they didn’t have any room for improvement. This expenditure pained Chen Guo, but she understood Happy’s current situation. Without special methods, it was impossible to improve their hardware so quickly. The other teams had managed to get to where they were through years of cumulative effort. No matter how talented Happy was, they couldn’t catch up to the powerhouses in these one to two years of time. So, right now, Happy could only use these short-term solutions.

It was just good that this solution didn’t use up too many valuable materials, so it didn’t conflict much with Happy’s development of proper Silver equipment.

The only proper piece of Level 80 Silver equipment was the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. 　 For it to be equipped, the umbrella needed a five level reduction to its level requirement. They had finally managed to create this stat and apply it every form of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. As a result, each form’s base stats were clearly a cut above level 75 Silver equipment, and the bonus stats had gained small improvements as well.

At level fifty, when the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had been fully developed, it had shield, spear, rifle, taichi, scythe, staff, ninjato, tonfa and estoc forms, as well as having the abilities of a Mechanic’s mechanical box.

All the further improvements had maintained these forms. And this time, Guan Rongfei successfully added new forms in the jump from level 70 directly to level 80. 　 Using the tonfa form as a base, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could now become Nightwalker’s dual swords.

The umbrella ribs that held up the umbrella while opened could now be detached and equipped to the wrists to form a Fighter’s claws.

With the umbrella closed, The canopy could open horizontally above the shaft of the umbrella, forming a weird shape like a poleaxe, but this was actually the Swordsman’s greatsword. . In addition to the nine old forms of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, there were now a total of twelve forms.

To use all low level skills, all they needed was a form for each superclass (Mage, Swordsman, Priest, Gunner, Fighter, Nightwalker). However, more forms meant more variety, and would allow the unspecialized style to become even more unpredictable and complex. Plus, considering how it was possible to set a different skill on each form, three more forms meant three more non-unspecialized, non-awakening class skills.

In the end, of the twelve forms, there were two Swordsman, one Gunner, two Fighter, three Priest, two Mage and two Nightwalker. It was pretty evenly distributed.

Everyone, including Ye Xiu, were doing their best to familiarize themselves with the new equipment in this limited time given. Esports Home’s reporter, Chang Xian, called or came to visit the Internet cafe every now and then. After all, he was a reporter, and his primary work was to gather intel. Though he knew that no team liked to be bothered at a time like this, Chang Xian still had to try and get something out of them.

However, no matter when he came, Chang Xian didn’t see anyone except Boss Chen Guo.

The only person he managed to meet in the team was the boss; this was a clear display of Happy’s grassroots status. No team’s boss was like a receptionist like Happy’s Chen Guo, easier to find than any of the team members even. If it was any other reporter trying to interview a team, then they’d probably die of happiness at such a situation.

However, Happy was the exception. Chang Xian snuck into Happy again, only to see Chen Guo looking at him with a smile. He smiled weakly, feeling a little helpless. “Sister Chen…”

“What? Not happy to see me?” Chen Guo asked. She was only just starting to learn how to interact with the media, but the reporter she had the most exposure to was Chang Xian, also a newbie in his field. He was honest and principled individual, not nearly as sly as veteran reporters. Against him, Chen Guo had no problems.

“No no, of course not,” Chang Xian hurriedly replied. He didn’t dare offend Chen Guo! Though she was almost like a receptionist in how easy it was to a get a hold of her, she was still the boss of a team.

“Sister Chen, seeing that I’ve come over so many times, could you give me some insider info?” Chang Xian was practically begging.

“There really isn’t anything to give. It’s just that they don’t want to be disturbed, so they went into closed-door training for the championships!” Chen Guo said cheerfully.

Chang Xian had heard these words many times already, but he couldn’t believe them. Although he was new to the industry, these few years had honed his observational skills. In addition, Chen Guo wasn’t someone who was adept at hiding her thoughts.Her cheerful manner of addressing Chang Xian clearly told him that she was hiding something from him.

“Ai, sister Chen, can you let me see brother Ye and the others and ask them about how they feel about the first round?” Chang Xian was close to tears. It might’ve been plain as day that there were things going on in the team that Chen Guo was hiding, but the problem was that she was hiding them, and hiding them well. Chang Xian didn’t have any way of getting her to spill. She was clearly enjoying the feeling of knowing something that he didn’t!

“They’re pretty busy recently, why don’t you wait a couple days?” Chen Guo answered, sounding completely serious.

“Then, sister Chen, what do you think of the first round?” Chang Xian could only make do with Chen Guo. 　 Yes, make do!

For any other team, getting an interview from the boss was no small feat, but over here with Happy, it was “making do”, because it was way too easy to get to see Chen Guo. Chang Xian had seen Chen Guo who knows how many times while eating noodles at the food stall on the street corner. They were familiar with each other like kin, and there was no sense of mystery to it at all. Thus, Chang Xian knew that Chen Guo was a rather unorthodox boss, and it sometimes felt like she was just one in name. Happy’s biggest decision maker wasn’t her. Of course, on the Alliance’s database and Happy’s registration forms, as well as the sponsorship forms, Chen Guo was the sole owner of Happy’s assets, the biggest boss of Happy.

This boss… was a bit of a puppet, but she was more than happy to play the part. If Chang Xian had to describe it, then he’d call her a One True Fan!

Yes, a One True Fan*!

Compared to that young master Xia Zhongtian from Chien Tea Green, she was way more of a true fan. Xia Zhongtian had far greater control of New Excellent Era than Chen Guo had of Happy, and he acted like a typical team club boss. As a City H reporter, Chang Xian had naturally gone to see the current Excellent Era.

Chang Xian really wasn’t sure how to deal with a boss like Chen Guo.

They were friends and that was great, of course. However, as an interviewee, though she had such a high position, her value was low and just thinking of it was frustrating him. He often saw Happy’s boss, but he couldn’t get any information about what was happening with Happy. He’d be considered a joke if word got out!

“The first round? We’ll defeat Blue Rain, of course,” Chen Guo said.

Chang Xian sobbed inside. There was no substance to that! He had been expecting it though, so he hadn’t even bothered to record it.

“Do you have any special strategies planned?” Chang Xian asked.

“That’s a secret, I can’t say.” Chen Guo smiled.

What secret? You don’t even know, do you? Chang Xian felt the mental tears pour.

“Will boss Wei play in the match against Blue Rain? He has history with Blue Rain, after all!” Chang Xian then asked.

“That’ll depend on our strategic needs. We won’t arrange anything for the drama,” Chen Guo informed him seriously.

Damnit, what’s with that serious attitude. That guy told you to say that, didn’t he? Chang Xian looked around subconsciously, as if someone in the Internet cafe had somehow sent her a telepathic message.

“Little Chang, sit for a while and make yourself comfortable. I have to go out to get some supplies,” Chen Guo then said.

Chang Xian nodded helplessly. See! That was Happy’s boss. She never acted like a bigshot or anything. Chang Xian watched as Chen Guo left the Internet cafe and then went into a random tobacco shop, coming out with a carton of cigarettes not long later. 　　 So she was getting cigarettes for Ye Xiu and Wei Chen! Chang Xian was familiar enough with Happy to immediately come to the conclusion.

“Little Chang, sorry to have to ask you to wait a little longer. I have to take this up!” Chen Guo returned, waving the cigarettes at him and then going upstairs.

They were too familiar!

Chang Xian’s mental tears were like a relentless waterfall. They were so familiar with each other that they didn’t think of him as an outsider anymore. Originally, this would be a great relationship to have, getting so friendly with a team would be a great convenience for any team reporter! However, Chang Xian knew that he was too close with Happy now. They were close to the point where he felt rather ashamed to pry into their preparations, like he was desecrating the shrine of their friendship!

He… really hadn’t been very good at drawing the line between professionalism and friendship! It was a little too late now for him to realize this. After a moment, Chen Guo came back down and began chatting casually with Chang Xian as she went through the bookkeeping for the Internet cafe.

Happy’s boss believed that all the regular season awards should belong to Happy…

This was what Chang Xian got from their chat. However… was this something he could write into an article? Was it??? This was just teasing between friends! Of course it wasn’t something he could write.

What was he to do?

The weekly esports issue was going to be a special on the Glory League playoffs. This issue before the matches began was meant to be about the preparations for each team. How was he going to write up an article on Happy?

Nomyummi TLNote Joui*: In China, fan culture is diverse, and people have gone as far as to label different fans. For example, I’ve used One True Fan for 真爱粉 (literally, true love fan), taking inspiration from “OTP/3” One True Pair/Threesome/etc. to mean a fan that feels sincere loyalty and love for their team/idol and is willing to follow them and help them, but generally keeps a clear head. You also have rabid/brainless fans 脑残粉 which has come up before in the novel.

Chapter 1385 - Playoffs Special Issue

Chang Xian was worrying over the fact that he might not be able to complete his assigned task. Professionally speaking, the blame was partly on Happy for not being reliable. Other teams, for example Blue Rain, were also in closed training, and weren’t taking interviews, but they had their own public relations team working to provide their reporters with something to report, allowing them to deal with their own work responsibilities. As for Happy? In a single year, they had the core of the team down, but they didn’t have a club system that could deal with all their issues like Blue Rain did!

Public relations?

Happy didn’t have anything of the sort. Chen Guo didn’t have enough experience, while Ye Xiu put everything he had into overseeing his team members’ growth, their strategic arrangements, improvement of their equipment, accumulation of stored materials. However, he didn’t care about things like dealing with the media that had no direct influence of their team’s strength. The others wouldn’t notice this sort of thing either, so Team Happy really had no understanding of this whatsoever.

Chang Xian once again returned empty-handed. Some of Happy’s regulars were now looking at him weirdly. He had heard them mumbling once and almost coughed blood. With him running over to Happy so often and constantly hanging around Chen Guo, he no longer seemed so innocent. In the eyes of outsiders, he seemed like a shameless pretty boy who refused to stop clinging to Chen Guo.

Chang Xian felt like crying himself to death. When he went back and checked their Esports Home reporters’ group chat, the other team reporters responsible for the playoffs issue had plenty of material to go on, and even the City G reporter responsible for Blue Rain had a draft that Blue Rain had provided. All he had to do was add some of his own opinions and then he’d be good to go for Blue Rain.

As for him?

This time, he’d better not think of distinguishing himself from everyone else. If he could even get anything in, he’d be content.

Chang Xian could feel his anxiety rising, he pulled on his hair, he couldn’t sleep!

He didn’t bother hoping for an article draft like Blue Rain had given because he knew very clearly that Happy didn’t have anyone to deal with that sort of thing. He couldn’t place his hopes on the players, they didn’t have the time. Apart from that? Boss Chen? Chang Xian felt cold sweat on his head just thinking about it. His impression of Chen Guo was the furthest it could be from writing this sort of thing.

There was nothing for it. He could only rely on himself. He’ll just make it up! He’ll show it to them afterwards to make sure it was okay.

Helpless, Chang Xian could only write up draft himself. After struggling over it for two days, he went back to Happy, with a slight hope that he might be able to meet one of their players, only be be crushed when he saw Chen Guo downstairs again.

“Sister Chen,” Chang Xian greeted.

“Back again!” Chen Guo greeted him, but why did that ‘again’ sound so piercing? Looking around the Internet cafe, there were quite a few looks of disdain directed at him that were quickly retracted and fixated to computer screens when they noticed Chang Xian looking over.

“I drafted this article on Happy for the playoffs issue. Have a look, how is it?” Chang Xian weakly handed over his substanceless article draft, which had no sources but himself to take from.

“Oh? Alright!” Chen Guo accepted it and looked through it carefully, which made Chang Xian feel marginally better.

“Little Chang! This article is just full of slogans. There’s no substance to it!” Chen Guo said.

Chang Xian felt the tears start again.

Of course there wasn’t any substance! You always block me at the Internet cafe and never let me interview the players or leak any information to me. Where would I get any substance from?

Chag Xian felt chagrined, to the point of speechlessness. Seeing this, Chen Guo wasn’t completely clueless as to why.

“Er… just now I was just speaking from the point of a reader. It’s actually pretty good, go ahead and publish it!” Chen Guo said.

“Sister Chen, can’t you give me something to write about?” Chang Xian asked.

“There really isn’t much I can give you. We Happy only have so much to our name, you know that! And because of this, we have to fully utilize all the time we’re given and improve as much as possible in this week,” Chen Guo replied.

“Stop trying to fool me, Sister Chen, I know you guys have a trick up your sleeves. I can tell,” Chang Xian said.

“Haha. Of course we have something, but we can’t say anything about it! Otherwise, how are we going to surprise everyone?” Chen Guo said.

“Alright!” Chang Xian nodded. Chen Guo had personally admitted that they had an ace up the sleeve and that could probably count as something with substance he could write about. As for not knowing the specifics to their ace up the sleeve, that was reasonable! If a team really revealed all the tricks and strategies they were going to use to deal with their opponents, then everyone would probably be suspicious that they were doing it on purpose to fuck with their opponents. Chang Xian was pretty skilled at his job, and upon hearing of this information, the gears were already turning in his head, figuring out how he could use this.

Soon enough, the weekly esports special playoffs issue started publishing. The pre-match articles were, naturally, about predictions and hopes for each team in the playoffs. Apart from articles from the assigned reporters of each team, Esports Home had also invited renowned Glory analysts to write about their views of the playoffs.

For example, famous guest commentator Li Yibo. His special column was of the same style as his commentating this season, careful and cautious, not daring to make predictions. Li Yibo’s section was like a replay. He brought up all the most spectacular moments of the regular season; of course, he had been a commentator for all these matches, and his rehash of the events were lifelike and clear. Then, he went on to explain what strengths and flaws each team had, in his opinions, before bringing his article to a close with best wishes to all the teams.

Renown analyst Cha Xiaoxia had announced that he was a brainless fan of Happy’s long ago, and had supported Happy plenty throughout the season. However, Cha Xiaoxia’s brainless fan comment was just a simple joke. He merely looked more highly upon Happy and thought them more interesting. He merely spent more effort on uncovering Happy’s strengths. His praises for Happy were methodical and logical, unlike those Happy haters with Ruan Cheng at their head. They were really brainless crazies and pretty much beyond saving with their delusional talk.

In Cha Xiaoxia’s column, he had continued to express his love for Happy, and in his analysis for the eight playoffs teams, Happy took up 70 percent while the other seven teams took up the other thirty.

The editorial department had mixed opinions on if they should invite Zuo Chenrui to write a section or not because this guy was a real brainless maniac when it came to what he loved and what he hated. It would be natural that anything he wrote would lack objectivity. In the end, the editorial department decided to try and get Zuo Chenrui to write a piece not about Blue Rain and Tiny Herb. In the end, they were resolutely rejected by Zuo Chenrui.

Others, like Ruan Cheng, only wrote for Esports Times, so even Esports Home wanted them, they wouldn’t be able to invite them.

They had gotten plenty of long and eloquent pieces. Apart from these renowned analysts, they also had a few by pro players, some retired, some still going. The players of the eight playoffs teams naturally didn’t have any time for it, but the players of other teams were already on summer break. The media usually invited renowned gods to write for them. This time, they had managed to invite Void’s Li Xuan, Misty Rain’s Chu Yunxiu and Royal Style’s Tian Sen.

The three had more or less recovered from their disappointment of this season, and had their popcorn prepared for the show ahead. They each had different views on how the playoffs would go.

Li Xuan had his bets set on Samsara. This was the most mainstream opinion; there wasn’t much more to it.

Chu Yunxiu, on the other hand, was rooting for Happy, and she directly admitted that the main reason was because her good friend was in Happy. Of course, afterwards, she also went and discussed Happy’s strengths and flaws from a competitive perspective.

As for Tian Sen, he had his eyes set on Tyranny. He thought that, after holding back for a season, they would meet the playoffs with explosive force. Royal Style, once at the top, was heading towards ruin, and Tian Sen deeply felt that forlorn feeling of feeling himself wither away. Tyranny’s veterans were, no doubt, currently experiencing this stage of life. Though Tian Sen was in his prime as a pro player, he had the same feeling as he watched them. His hopes in them was more like well wishes.

The esports weekly issue was comprised of these contents. Afterwards, the reporters they had sent provided more into each of the eight teams. Apart from Blue Rain and Happy, the other six had managed to interview the team players and had plenty of material. Blue Rain’s club had provided a draft, and the reporter had, naturally, built off of that. Happy’s was a little worse. Chang Xian had more or less written a draft for Happy and then used what little he had gotten from Chen Guo to expand.

Yet, in the end, the six that had managed to interview the team players all seemed rather plain and boring. The severe atmosphere of the playoffs seemed to have already enveloped them. Though they had personally faced the media, the players of those six teams had barely said anything of substance. Blue Rain had provided a draft, so that was even worse. In the end, it was Chang Xian’s piece on Happy that was most authentic, stating how boss Chen Guo herself had personally admitted that Happy had an ace up the sleeve for the playoffs.

What was this ace up the sleeve?

This was what Chang Xian had focused on.

Chang Xian’s guesses weren’t important. After all, anyone could try and guess! Thus, what ace up the sleeve Happy had became the biggest discussion of the issue. Some guessed that it was a new strategy, some guessed that it was a new and never before seen team formation, and some guessed that it was secret weapon in the form of equipment. Either way, there was a limited amount that could be talked about and all sorts of guesses were flying around.

“What do you think?”

Team Blue Rain, Huang Shaotian asked Yu Wenzhou as he set down his newspaper. They were going to be Happy’s opponents soon, so they were naturally rather concerned about this. After he asked, Huang Shaotian didn’t bother waiting for Yu Wenzhou to answer, immediately expressing his own opinion, “With that guy present, I bet that this is just a smokescreen.”

“Really? I don’t think so.” Yu Wenzhou held a newspaper in hand, too. His gaze didn’t leave the page as he listened to Huang Shaotian talk.

“They probably have some sort of trick or ace. If they didn’t have anything, then this smokescreen would be rather pointless. Happy’s members aren’t that immature,” Yu Wenzhou continued.

“Then what is it?” Huang Shaotian was confused.

“Don’t think. If you think about it, then you’ll have fallen for the trap,” Yu Wenzhou set the newspaper down as he spoke. “Just pretend you haven’t seen it!”

“I’ll do my best…” Huang Shaotian didn’t sound very confident.

Chapter 1386 - Complementary

Was this a smokescreen of Happy's or not? The players were curious and the debate raged on. However, apart from Blue Rain, the other teams didn't concern themselves with it. What tricks did Happy have up their sleeve? Either way, Blue Rain was their lab rat. Once they fought with Blue Rain, then everything would be revealed. It wasn't like the other teams were gonna meet Happy first round, so why should they care?

All the teams were working hard to prepare to take down their respective opponents. On the dawn of the war, everything was quiet. There was no more news or rumors flying about, just each team silently preparing for that fateful moment.

June 14th, the opening match of much anticipated playoffs began.

City K, at Hundred Blossom's home stadium, Hundred Blossom's captain Yu Feng had arrived, alone and too early. He stood in the middle of the field. Here, was exactly here the projections would be, where the characters would tear at one another for victory.

Yu Feng looked up, gazing at the high end projection technology.

Here he was, once more...

Yu Feng looked around the venue.

It had been two years since he had came to Hundred Blossoms, and this was the second time he had stood on the stage of Hundred Blossoms' playoffs journey. Last year, their opponent had been Tyranny and he had personally seen the attitude Hundred Blossoms' fans had towards Zhang Jiale. It looked like hate, but was this hate not born from love? In the end, it was because Zhang Jiale was important to them. Yu Feng hoped to gain such importance, so he always did his best at Hundred Blossoms, and he hoped to bring Hundred Blossoms something they had never had before.

The championship!

Yu Feng had won the championships before, and this made him far more fortunate than many of the other players in their circle. However, that championship bore too many marks from other people. He wasn't primary in that championship. Yu Feng hoped to have a championship that, when people thought of it, they would immediately think of his name.

That was why he stood here, and mercilessly abandoned the team he once loved so deeply, Blue Rain. Because of that, that brainless fan of Blue Rain's, Zuo Chenrui, had dragged his name through the mud and stomped on it, but Yu Feng merely smiled and dismissed it.

In the face of what he pursued, none of this was important. The world was fair. If he wanted to gain something, then he would have to lose something. This was, more or less, the basis of the principle of equivalent exchange. This was what he had done, and wasn't this also what Hundred Blossoms' ex-captain Zhang Jiale had done?

Of course, him and Blue Rain weren't like Zhang Jiale and Hundred Blossoms, and this was one of the reasons he had come to Hundred Blossoms. Yu Feng had even, embarrassingly enough, had a dream where after he left Blue Rain and joined Hundred Blossoms, Blue Rains fans treated him the same way Hundred Blossoms had treated Zhang Jiale. That wasn't any sort of great situation to be in, and Zhang Jiale's pain was plain to see, but Yu Feng envied him. That was exactly what he sought, after all: to be seen as important!

He knew that his position in their hearts couldn't compare to Zhang Jiale, and probably even fell short of their previous Berserker Sun Zheping, but Yu Feng had confidence because he was already completely a part of Hundred Blossoms. He believed that his efforts would be seen by Hundred Blossoms' fans, and now, what he had to do, was charge through this first stage.

Samsara!

The strongest team, in the eyes of countless. In this matchup, the online polls had 81 percent of people with their bets on Samsara, an overwhelming advantage.

But what was funny was, that in the regular season when the two teams faced off, Hundred Blossoms had won 7 to 3 once, and then lost 4 to 6 last time. If you added the scores, Hundred Blossoms was in the lead 11 to 9! From this, it could be seen that sometimes, statistics really meant nothing. Who would think that they were stronger than Samsara just from the advantage from these two matches between them? None, practically none at all. The 19 percent support that Hundred Blossoms had probably wasn't because anyone thought them stronger, but just that they could win.

Strong and weak, victory and defeat, there was never any certainty in it. Being stronger would increase your chances, but it was never 100 percent. And so long as it wasn't 100 percent, then there would always be a chance for a different ending. Even if it was one in a million, it was still a possibility.

Right now, it seemed, that the general populace believed that Hundred Blossoms only had a 19 percent of victory.

Then let this 19 percent become reality! Yu Feng took a deep breath and glanced at the time. It was still early, nowhere near 8:30 PM. After taking a walk across the competition stage, he decided to leave, but that was when he saw Zou Yuan. This teammate of his had also come to the stadium and was ascending the stairs to the stage.

"You came, too?" Yu Feng asked. Though the two were rather far away from each other, there was no one in the stadium, making it completely silent. Yu Feng barely had to raise his voice to hear it echo throughout the stadium.

"Yeah, I came to get a feel for the atmosphere ahead of time," Zou Yuan replied.

"Get a feel? How?" Yu Feng looked behind him. There was not a single person in the stadium. It was dead silent.

"I'm going to put my imagination to the test, as exaggerated as possible. That way, when the time comes, I'll just think to myself 'Ha, so that's it?' Then, I won't feel the pressure anymore," Zou Yuan said.

Yu Feng laughed. The pressure the team had suddenly piled on top of his teammate had nearly driven his teammate crazy. He was probably thinking of that time as a way to alleviate the match pressure!

He looked towards Zou Yuan, who stood at the edge of the stage staring at the empty spectator seats. Suddenly, Zou Yuan shut his eyes and opened his arms, focusing on his method of relieving the pressure he felt. Yu Feng didn't utter a sound. He simply watched him quietly, not even taking a step.

A short while later, he saw Zou Yuan retract his arms, open his eyes, look at him, and chuckle.

"Done?"

"Done. Would you like to try?" Zou Yuan asked.

"Me? Nah! It doesn't suit me. If the crowd isn't is as spirited as I imagine, I'd probably be disappointed," Yu Feng said.

"Haha, true. You're different than me!" Zou Yuan sighed.

Yes, the two were different, not alike in the slightest.

The pressure that Zou Yuan had nearly gone mad from was exactly what Yu Feng had always hoped to have.

Zou Yuan feared that pressure, but Yu Feng enjoyed it.

When Yu Feng came to Hundred Blossoms, Zou Yuan didn't hesitate to hand over his responsibilities as the core player and the captain to Yu Feng. After the pressure onto him lessened, Zou Yuan worked hard to learn those responsibilities, to seize the good fortune that had been forced onto him. His efforts gradually paid off, but he didn't regret his decision of giving up his core position. In the end, he couldn't change his personality. The roles with the most pressure, captain and core player, were far more suited for Yu Feng, who would certainly do better at them than he could.

How fun!

Zou Yuan couldn't help but think to himself sometimes. The two of them were opposites, yet they had ended up becoming teammates and partners. Was it because they were different that it was easy for them to complement each other? In this season's evaluations for Best Partners, the two had earned high marks.

Is it the revival of Blood and Blossoms?

Zou Yuan remembered the target the Club had initially given the two of them. Now it looked like they would just have to make do. Blood and Blossoms required a quick connected playstyle. It wasn't as simple as just having the technical portions down. The personalities of the players mattered too. Unfortunately, Yu Feng was no Sun Zheping, and he was no Zhang Jiale. The two were unable to recreate the former Blood and Blossoms. In the end, they created a style that belonged to only them, a different partnership between Berserker and Spitfire.

This was the so-called passing of time.

The past wast the past. Trying to force a recreation would always lack a certain flavor. What people reminisced wasn't really Blood and Blossoms, but rather the feelings they first felt seeing Blood and Blossoms. Those feelings could never be replicated because a first was a first. The next time would never be the first, but the second.

Our own style!

Zou Yuan thought to himself. In the beginning, when Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Blossoms had been left with him, he had been terrified. The team called for him to succeed Zhang Jiale's position, so he studied Zhang Jiale like his life depended on it to the point that he had almost started copying Zhang Jiale's habits. But what was the result? He wasn't able to do it as well as the real Zhang Jiale. He couldn't bear the pressure. That season, Hundred Blossoms had relied on the rising Tang Hao to carry them, while he as the core studied and copied Zhang Jiale, throwing the team out of the season.

Afterwards, he knew that he couldn't continue on like this. He needed to find a path that would let him survive. As a result, he was very grateful the moment Yu Feng joined the team. Yu Feng had taken that burden off his shoulders, letting him find his own path without any pressure.

Sure enough, they were a good pair! Zou Yuan recalled the idea of being complementary that he had just thought of.

Then next on the list is winning together!

Zou Yuan was just about to say something, when he heard a loud commotion. He and Yu Feng turned their heads towards the other side of the stadium, where a group of people were pouring into the stadium.

Samsara!

It was Team Samsara!

Team Samsara's members were all present. As soon as they entered, they saw Yu Feng and Zou Yuan standing on the stage. Their footsteps didn't stop because of this though as they walked onto the stage. Yu Feng checked the time and knew that Samsara was here to warm up too. The away team would often come ahead of time to familiarize themselves with the new environment. It was the playoffs right now. Samsara definitely wasn't going to miss even the slightest detail that could give them an advantage.

"It's Hundred Blossom's two leaders!" As everyone knew, Samsara's captain Zhou Zekai rarely took the initiative to greet others. The one to greet Yu Feng and Zou Yuan was Samsara's vice-captain, Jiang Botao.

'Yup, you guys are here to warm up?" Yu Feng responded. He wasn't a stranger to Jiang Botao. Their generation of players had an intimacy from growing up as rookies together. Team Samsara had been formed from Season 5, Season 6, and Season 7 players. Many of them were of the same generation as Yu Feng. For example, the All-Stars Jiang Botao and Lu Boyuan had debuted in Season 6 just like him. Yu Feng had undoubtedly been the most eye-catching. That season, he had won both the title Best Rookie and the championship title with Team Blue Rain. Yu Feng's rookie season had been perfect. The only other one to have garnered such achievements in his first year in the Alliance was Team Tyranny's Zhang Xinjie.

Even so, it didn't change one point: their group of Season 6 rookies had all played supporting roles in their respective teams.

The one to break through that fate was Yu Feng. He had joined Blue Rain and came to Hundred Blossoms, becoming the first among the Season 6 rookies to assume a core position.

Chapter 1387 - First Match

There were four players who debuted in Season 6 and went onto becoming All-Stars: Yu Feng, Xu Bin, Lu Boyuan, and Jiang Botao. Apart from Yu Feng, the other three were not core members of their respective team. If even these All-Stars were like so, then the other rookies of that generation were even less important.

The Season 4 rookies were nicknamed the Golden Generation. On the other hand, these Season 6 rookies were nicknamed the “Helper Squad” because of these coincidental happenings. The name pointed at how the Season 6 rookies all held support roles in their respective teams.

The title was just for fun. No one would actually take these words to heart. But still, now that Yu Feng had become the core of Hundred Blossoms, the name “Helper Squad” no longer had the same impact as before. The Season 6 players all joked that Yu Feng had let them down.

They were joking, of course.

Even if Yu Feng became his team’s core player, so what?

Jiang Botao and Lu Boyuan were still members of the “Helper Squad”, but they stood besides Zhou Zekai, forming the formidable Team Samsara. The “Helper Squad” had helped win the team two championships back-to-back.

Yu Feng didn’t envy them though.

Champions? He had already become the champion once. What he wanted was to win the championships not just with the status of a “Helper Squad” member.

That was his personal goal. He didn’t care about denying being a part of the “Helper Squad”.

“We’re not bothering you guys, are we?” Jiang Botao continued to chat with him. This social player could make friends with anyone, even when the two parties were irreconcilable adversaries. But for old players, though their attitudes on stage were very professional, none of them ever showed anger to each other off the stage.

“No problem, you guys go ahead. We’ll stop bothering you,” Yu Feng said.

Even though both sides could maintain professional relationships on stage, in this sort of life and death battle, they were unlikely to happily chat around under such a tense atmosphere.

“Take care,” Jiang Botao said as he watched Yu Feng and Zou Yuan leave the stage together. Samsara’s other players didn’t regard their encounter as anything serious, and the everyone quickly started warming up.

At 8 PM, no seats in the stadium were empty. For the playoffs, each match was crucial. Thus, playoff matches were much more watched than regular season matches. The stadium had seats specifically for the away-game fans as usual, and Samsara’s loyal fans already had their slogan hanging down. The words two-time champions were the most important. After all, three-time champions had yet to happen, and it wouldn’t be good to call it too early as their slogan. It could be something that they could yell as a good-luck blessing throughout the entire tournament though.

The two teams finally entered the stadium.

The entrance ceremony wasn’t any different than the ones in the regular season. As Hundred Blossom’s home stadium, the cheers and claps for them were louder. Although Samsara was the defending champions and the current most popular team, it was still their playoff opponent’s home stadium. The fate of the noise from Samsara fans could only be obliteration. Any team that made it to the playoffs were inevitably popular teams.

The broadcast wasn’t going to miss out on any playoffs match. The commentators were once again Pan Lin and Li Yibo, the signature duo. The broadcast team had originally wanted it to be a tri-cast like the Happy versus Tiny Herb match. In that match, the program had invited a guest commentator, and since many players wouldn’t be participating in the playoffs, the program wanted to invite a well-known player.

For this match, the program had thought of a brilliant figure.

Sun Zheping!

He was a former Hundred Blossoms player, and he would certainly have a lot of things to say as a guest commentator.

But when the program sent an invitation to Sun Zheping, they didn’t think he would actually refuse. As soon as they approached him, the door was shut. Their morale had dropped considerably. During that time, they failed to find any other suitable players. In the end, it was still Pan Lin and Li Yibo duo-casting for the first match of playoffs.

After introducing the players on both sides, the two looked for things to say as they waited for the match to officially start.

“These two teams encountered each other in the final round of the regular season. Just another week later and they’re back at it again.” Pan Lin said.

“With it being a back-to-back match, these two teams must have a deep understanding of each other by now. In this situation, none of them have any secrets. The winner will be decided by how each team is able to execute their plans and adapt to their opponent’s plays.” Li Yibo said.

“From the regular season records, Hundred Blossoms actually has an 11-9 advantage. However, in the online poll before the playoffs, 81% of players thought Samsara would win!” Pan Lin said.

“It looks like Samsara’s outstanding performance this season has helped them earn quite a bit of support and confidence from players!” Li Yibo said.

“I wonder how this match will turn out?” Pan Lin wondered expectantly.

“Hey hey! You guys aren’t going to watch the match?”

At Team Happy’s meeting room, Chen Guo was keeping the TV under her watch. She saw that the match was about to begin, yet no one was coming over. She rushed out of the meeting room baffled and found everyone focusing on their own computers.

“Of course we will, but not now,” Ye Xiu said.

“Then when?” Chen Guo was puzzled.

“We’ll watch the VODs,” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo understood now. Ye Xiu and the others wouldn’t be watching to see who would win, or for fun. They would be watching it for the information, so a live broadcast wouldn’t be as helpful to them as a VOD.

Since no one would be watching, Chen Guo found it boring to watch it alone. Normally, the playoffs was a time when even players who weren’t fans of the participating teams would watch excitedly. However, the current Chen Guo was no longer a pure Glory fan. She needed to consider Team Happy as her first priority for most things. As a result, after hearing Ye Xiu’s explanation, she realized that this match wasn’t just a brilliant show, but precious information. Thus, watching the VODs would be better.

A bout of shouting could occasionally be heard from the first floor of the Internet cafe. Happy Internet Cafe’s match broadcasting tradition never went away. The playoff matches would obviously be played. Chen Guo gently closed the door to the practice room, so Ye Xiu and the other could continue practicing in peace.

Bang!

Just when she closed the door, she heard a loud noise from behind her. She turned around and saw that it was their guild department’s Wu Chen.

He looked towards the meeting room. From the not-yet-closed door, he could see the match playing on the projection screen. However, there didn’t seem to be anyone there, and Chen Guo had just gently closed the door.

“They’re not going to watch?” Wu Chen said.

“They’ll be watching the VOD,” Chen Guo said.

“Oh!” The former pro-player Wu Chen immediately understood.

“Everyone’s really working hard!” Wu Chen sighed.

“Yup!” Chen Guo nodded her head. At this moment, another shout came from down below. Chen Guo couldn’t help but look towards the meeting room.

“Boss, you’re not going to watch either?” Wu Chen asked.

“I… I’ll be watching!” Chen Guo nodded her head. In the end, she was still curious. Samsara, Hundred Blossoms, who would win? Who would be Happy’s next opponent? If they wanted a better chance to win the championships, then it would be better if Samsara was eliminated early, no?

Chen Guo and Wu Chen went into the meeting room together. The players on both sides had entered the stage. The climax before the match had ended, and the floor downstairs had quieted down. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were still chattering non-stop. There clearly wasn’t going to be any high points until the match finally started.

Thump.

Chen Guo heard a noise from behind her. When she looked back, it was Guan Rongfei. He had somehow sneaked in without a sound and found a seat to sit at.

So I’ll be watching the match together with these two today? Chen Guo smiled. It had never happened before!

When the match finally began, Chen Guo, Wu Chen, and Guan Rongfei quietly watched the match.

“Who won?”

Happy had a good work-rest schedule down, and it could not be broken in such a crucial moment like playoffs. When it was around 10 PM, everyone came out of the practice room and watched the broadcast of the match that had ended not too long ago. They went over and asked about it.

“Samsara,” Chen Guo told them the results. She had hoped Hundred Blossoms would make the upset. Because she had wanted it, the match had been more stressful all the way until the end. In their home game, Hundred Blossoms ahd lost the group arena and team competition to Samsara.

“Points?” Ye Xiu asked.

“11-7.” Chen Guo said.

The playoffs tournament format was based on headcount. Samsara had won the group arena and team competition, so they won the full 11 points. Hundred Blossoms had lasted until the last matchup in the group arena, so they took 4 points. However, they suffered a large defeat in the team competition, only taking down three of Samsara’s players, ending with 7 points total.

“Oh,” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

It seemed to only be a 4 point difference, but from the competitive format, it could be considered a crushing defeat. Lasting until the last matchup of the group arena meant they were equally matched in that area, but losing the team competition with a 3 person deficit was a huge loss.

“Let’s analyze the match tomorrow!” Ye Xiu said.

Hundred Blossoms home stadium.

The audience members had left. The post-match press conference had ended too. Only the janitors were left in the stadium.

Yu Feng once again returned to the stadium onto the stage.

We lost…

They had tried their hardest, yet they still lost.

In the regular season, Samsara had been so fierce and aggressive, but in the playoffs, they became calm and steady to the extent that they couldn’t tell that they were an aggressive team at all.

After winning two championships, this team had been thoroughly refined. In their away game, in such a tense playoffs match, they could still play so calmly. Hundred Blossoms had chosen to be aggressive this match, hoping to show off their power in their home game. But facing Samsara’s calm display, their aggressiveness was like throwing rocks into the sea, silently stifled by their opponents.

Lost!

The loss wasn’t regretful or resentful; the loss was so… proper. It was as if it were inevitable.

This sort of feeling terrified Yu Feng.

Had his fighting spirit been worn away during this match? Had his unconscious already determined that Hundred Blossoms could not win against Samsara?

Yu Feng clenched his fist. I cannot waver. In times like these, I definitely cannot waver!

Chapter 1388 - Each Making Their Own Preparations

After the end of the first playoffs match, there was an outpouring of reviews praising Samsara’s champion-like performance. As for Hundred Blossoms, they hadn’t made any major mistakes worthy of criticism, but it was exactly for that reason that Samsara seemed all the greater.

In the blink of an eye, it was the next day. The first match hadn’t even been fully digested when the second match of the playoffs had arrived. Team 301 was playing their home game against Team Tyranny. Tyranny had conserved their energy all through the regular season, so how would they explode now in the playoffs? Because so many were curious about this question, this match received extra attention.

But Happy needed to pay attention to this match for a bigger reason than mere curiosity. According to the playoffs bracket, if Happy eliminated Blue Rain and advanced to the semifinals, then their opponent would be the victor of 301 vs Tyranny. If everything went smoothly, then Happy would be facing one of these two teams.

But on this night, Team Happy hadn’t gathered together to watch the match. They weren’t watching this match, nor had they watched recordings of the previous playoffs match.

The next day was Happy’s match, and throughout this entire day Happy’s training had been focused on small adjustments and regulation. After dinner, everyone was free to do whatever they wanted. They could each use their own methods to reduce the pressure of this upcoming life-or-death match.

In the meeting room, Chen Guo once again set up the projection screen to watch the match, and like before, the two who came by were Wu Chen and Guan Rongfei.

The players came onstage, the match was about to begin, but Chen Guo couldn’t focus.

What was everyone else doing?

Chen Guo really wanted to know. After dinner, everyone had split up without talking about what they were all going to do, and although she was curious, she ultimately hadn’t bothered them. But to be honest, she still had some small hope that one of the players would stay with her, because she was very nervous too! She wished that she could do something with someone who was going to play the match tomorrow.

“Has it started?” At this moment, she suddenly heard Ye Xiu’s voice.

“Huh?” Chen Guo turned her head to see Ye Xiu walking through the door.

“You want to watch?” she asked, surprised.

“Yeah, I have nothing to do, so I’ll watch,” he said, casually finding a seat and sitting down.

Chen Guo looked at him and realized, that’s right! This guy didn’t need to do anything to relieve pre-match pressure, right? To him, wasn’t this all as natural as eating and sleeping? He would just do it however he was supposed to.

“It’s just about to start,” Chen Guo said. Ye Xiu might not feel any pressure, but Chen Guo was extremely nervous. Still, once Ye Xiu arrived to watch this match with her, she suddenly felt that her heart relaxed quite a bit.

“These guys actually know how to conserve strength,” Ye Xiu mused. “I do want to see what kind of match they can play now.”

“Mm…” Chen Guo of course knew to whom Ye Xiu was referring with “these guys.”

The match began.

Tyranny’s first player: Lin Jingyan; 301 sent up Li Yihui.

A face-off between two Fighter class players. The final winner was Li Yihui, with a small advantage.

And then Tyranny sent up their second player, the rookie Song Qiying. After defeating Li Yihui, who’d only had a small amount of health remaining, he also defeated 301’s second player Gao Jie.

“This kid has a bright future,” Ye Xiu said, giving his judgment of Song Qiying. Even though he lost the Best Rookie award to Tang Rou, that was largely because he was in a well-established team like Tyranny, and as a rookie he hadn’t had as many chances to play in real matches like Tang Rou had. If not for Tyranny’s three old generals rotating out this season, Song Qiying might have had even fewer chances onstage.

If Song Qiying had had the same chances as Tang Rou, or if he had been used by Tyranny like Lu Hanwen last season, maybe he would have posed a threat to Tang Rou in the contest for Best Rookie. With a personality very similar to that of Zhang Xinjie, even though he was young, he gave people the impression of being extremely reliable.

But after defeating Gao Jie, Song Qiying was very quickly sent off by 301’s third player Qian Wenju. Then, Tyranny’s Zhang Jiale went in and defeated Qian Wenju. 301’s Yang Cong came up, but in the end he too died in Zhang Jiale’s brilliant Hundred Blossoms display.

“These guys are in pretty good condition today!” Ye Xiu said. Qian Wenju had dealt a good amount of health when Zhang Jiale took him down, and then Zhang Jiale had continued on to defeat Yang Cong’s full-health Scene Killer. It was practically a 1v2. After that, however, 301’s group arena anchor Bai Shu came onstage. By this point, Tyranny still had three players left, so their advantage was clear. Zhang Jiale played a very relaxed match, and although he didn’t complete a 1v3, he still did his job in whittling down Bai Shu for the next player. Tyranny’s fourth player was their captain Han Wenqing, and in the end Bai Shu’s Tide fell to Desert Dust.

“They all have a lot of spirit!” Ye Xiu exclaimed, after seeing Tyranny take the lead in the group arena, 5 to 3.

Next was the team competition. Tyranny finally revealed how their rhythm was different from what it had been during the regular season. In the regular season, even towards the end when they stopped rotation and come onstage together like this, the focus had still been on maintaining condition for the playoffs. There had always been worries that such rotations that prevented all three from being onstage together would cause their cooperation to become rusty.

Reality proved that for these generals, such concerns were unnecessary. For these experienced players, it was like riding a bicycle – once you learned, then no matter how long you went without riding one, you would be able to pick it up again very quickly.

Three out of the four Tyranny old generals appeared in a match during the regular season, but when they started making their adjustments for the playoffs, they swiftly readapted to working together, and didn’t need much time to get used to each other again.

They continued to repress their excitement and save their strength. They were waiting to unleash it at the playoffs.

And now, it was here.

They’d restrained themselves for this season, they’d heard all sorts of comments like “these guys can’t keep up anymore.” But at last, Tyranny entered the playoffs, and they didn’t need to save their strength any longer. They’d endured this kind of talk, and could now launch their powerful counterattack. Of course, however, they weren’t doing this because of the talk. This was the rhythm that Tyranny had prepared for this season, since the very beginning.

6 to 2.

In the end, they won a crushing victory. 301’s strategy had only been refined through half a season. Now that it had lost some of its newness, it couldn’t stand up to this most experienced team in the Alliance.

The final score was 11 to 5, quite a large difference, and this had been 301’s home game…

Hundred Blossoms, 301, they had barely clawed their way into the playoffs, only to lose their home games in the very first round.

Some were delighted, some were crying; this was how all competitions were destined to end.

“It looks like Tyranny will win,” said Ye Xiu. 11 to 5, this was a large advantage. Not many people would favor 301, who would have to make a comeback on Tyranny’s home field.

“Alright, let’s head back and rest!” Ye Xiu stood up and announced, as though he were about to go onto a battlefield right now. In his mind, probably, tonight’s rest was a very important part of preparing for tomorrow’s match.

One after another, they exited the meeting room, only to see that there was still a light on in the training room. Ye Xiu casually pushed the door open, and found that Mo Fan was still inside.

“What are you doing?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Video.” Now, finally, Mo Fan wouldn’t completely ignore people when they spoke to him. When it was a question, he would at least answer it.

“Oh?” Ye Xiu walked up, followed by Chen Guo. The two of them stood behind him and saw…

“These are all videos of Blue Rain’s players!” Ye Xiu realized that Mo Fan was watching the performances of Blue Rain’s players in the group arena. Happy of course had all of these match recordings, and they had organized them. Matches that were particularly worthwhile were picked out to serve as final summary data of Blue Rain. Mo Fan was watching all of Blue Rain’s 1v1 battles from the regular season.

And tomorrow, Mo Fan would be appearing in the group arena. Ye Xiu didn’t have the habit of waiting until right before the match to announce the roster; typically he’d announce it the day before the match.

The roster they were using against Blue Rain had been announced that morning. This round, Mo Fan would be the second player in the group arena. Now, it was already the night before the match and everyone was relaxing and adjusting their condition. Mo Fan, however, was still stubbornly studying the data on the Blue Rain players.

“Don’t stay up too late!” Chen Guo, feeling moved, gave him a heartfelt reminder.

Mo Fan didn’t answer, he just nodded his head and continued watching the video intently. The few of them realized that there was no possibility of chatting with Mo Fan, so they didn’t say anything else and merely left.

Downstairs, the match had ended, and people should have been dispersing after watching the broadcast in Happy Internet Cafe. But right now, it seemed even more lively than it had been during the match. From the top of the stairs, Ye Xiu and the others looked down and saw that their three players, Qiao Yifan, Luo Ji, and An Wenyi, had been enthusiastically surrounded.

“What’s going on?” Chen Guo immediately ran downstairs to ask the manager.

It turned out that these three youngsters had sneakily joined this crowd of gamers to enjoy the match with everyone else, but when the crowd was dispersing, they were accidentally discovered and recognized. Gamers who came to Happy Internet Cafe, did their attitude toward Team Happy even need to be mentioned? They swiftly surrounded them and sent their well-wishes toward these three young players.

“Hey hey!!” Chen Guo directly rushed for the PA system at the front desk of the cafe and shouted to get everyone’s attention.

“Let our players rest!” she shouted.

“Ye Xiu!!” In the end, everyone hollered even louder than Chen Guo. Ye Xiu hadn’t taken the back door, instead walking down the steps through the Internet cafe. Chen Guo’s shout had attracted everyone’s attention, and instantly everyone discovered this even more exciting presence.

“Calm down!” Ye Xiu decisively made his way to the front desk and plucked the microphone from Chen Guo’s hand.

“Everyone calm down! If you want to cheer us on, everyone is welcome at the stadium live tomorrow!” Ye Xiu shouted.

“Go Happy! Go!” Everyone chanted enthusiastically. They were all fairly in control, actually, because everyone knew that tomorrow was Happy’s match, and no one dared harass them too much at this time. If someone was being particularly difficult, then the other gamers wouldn’t accept it and would take care of the problem themselves. So, Ye Xiu’s simple two shouts were enough to let everyone understand and settle down. The three youngsters extricated themselves, thanked everyone for the support, and left with Ye Xiu.

Halfway back to their residence, they saw two familiar silhouettes squatting on the curb. One had cigarette smoke curling all around him, while the other was playing with what looked like a bicycle chain in his hands.

The group quietly approached, and heard Wei Chen telling Steamed Bun all about his glory years.

“In those days, I was Blue Rain’s soul and backbone, a person they could never be without!” Wei Chen was saying, his face full of sadness from reflecting on the past.

Chapter 1389 - Everyone’s Preparations

After uttering this pensive sentence, Wei Chen actually didn’t say anything else. Everyone thought for a moment, and realized that he had already spoken of the details, and this was just the concluding sentence. They’d been watching the match for over an hour now, and hadn’t seen Wei Chen or Steamed Bun during that whole time. Perhaps the two of them had just been sitting here beside the road, with Wei Chen describing the shining days of his youth?

“Soul, what soul? It was just two years!” Ye Xiu came up and mercilessly exposed him.

“Bullshit!” Wei Chen spun around, but when he saw it was Ye Xiu, he was actually quite calm. “Without me, would there even be a Blue Rain?”

Wei Chen wasn’t exaggerating here. He, like Ye Xiu, entered the Glory circle when the professional Glory Alliance still hadn’t existed yet! In the beginning, they were all simply ordinary gamers. The only way to make a living through gaming was through some transactions in-game. At the time, Ye Xiu’s guild was Excellent Dynasty, but he hadn’t been the one to create that guild. The person who’d created the guild at the time probably had no idea that it would lay the foundation for Club Excellent Era to establish a dynasty.

At the start, Guild Excellent Dynasty was like any other in-game guild, created by an ordinary player who’d pulled together some in-game friends to make a fun group that would allow them to play together. As they played, some groups became larger and larger, and after the Glory Alliance was first established, a few of these guilds became the in-game foundation for clubs and teams. Excellent Dynasty was like this, Blue Brook Guild was like this too. What was different was that the founder of the guild Excellent Dynasty, Tao Xuan, went on to become the boss of the club it formed the basis of. For Blue Rain, there were other investors, but the foundational guild had truly been established by their first captain Wei Chen, when he still played in-game. Without him, there would be no Blue Rain – this statement wasn’t an exaggeration.

“Tomorrow, if you guys can’t even beat my juniors, that would be too embarrassing,” Wei Chen said, glaring at the Happy players.

To leave behind his old team and then have to fight them – for most people, this was a rather sad thing. But Wei Chen had taken eight whole years to complete this process!

Eight years. What feelings did he still have toward Blue Rain?

Even though most of his talk about his glorious days in Blue Rain was nothing more than shameless boasting, everyone could tell from the old guy’s voice how he missed the past.

Did he miss his youth? Or did he miss Blue Rain?

No one asked further, because everyone knew, no matter what attitude Wei Chen had toward the past, he was now a member of Happy, and he stood clearly on Happy’s side.

“Tomorrow, let’s play well,” Ye Xiu said.

“Let’s go!” Together at the side of the road, the youths cheered and hollered.

“Where’s Fang Rui?” After everyone calmed down a bit, Ye Xiu casually asked.

“Haven’t seen that guy,” Wei Chen said.

Everyone had their own ways of preparing for the match, so what was this master of playing dirty doing? Everyone was curious, but no one would bother him simply out of curiosity.

Upper Forest Park neighborhood.

It was already somewhat late, but there were still a number of people out and about, walking dogs or simply enjoying the night air. Su Mucheng and Tang Rou sat together on a stone bench beside the road, tilting their heads to look at the sky.

“The weather today was really nice, how come there aren’t any stars at night?” Su Mucheng said.

“The stars are always there, but sadly, there’s just too much air pollution. It’s not that there aren’t any, it’s just that we can’t see them. Or it might be because the starlight is too faint, and the lights from the cities are hiding their light!” Tang Rou said.

“Yeah, it’s really a shame!” Su Mucheng sighed.

“By the way,” Tang Rou suddenly said, “the first time you played in the playoffs, how did you feel?”

“The first time? I was very nervous, very worried. Worried that I couldn’t do well enough, worried that I couldn’t help him,” said Su Mucheng.

“Then what about later?” Tang Rou didn’t ask who the “him” was, it was very obvious.

“Later… It was true, I didn’t do well. If I’d done better, then that year Excellent Era probably would’ve been champions again… Han Wenqing lost to Ye Xiu three times in three playoffs. But that time he won, because he gained a good helper at his side. And Ye Xiu didn’t…” Su Mucheng’s expression became somewhat saddened.

Tang Rou suddenly regretted her words; she’d forgotten that Su Mucheng had won second place the first time she’d participated in the playoffs. This seemed to be a very good result, so close to the championship, but in reality it was extremely painful. That feeling of missing success by just one step, it was enough to make anyone collapse. Regret, self-blame, no result could provoke these feelings as much as a second-place, almost-success could.

“I’m sorry,” said Tang Rou.

“Don’t worry, it’s a long time ago now,” said Su Mucheng.

Was it a long time… Tang Rou couldn’t help but wonder. That time, the championship had just barely slipped out of Excellent Era’s grasp in the finals, and after that, Excellent Era had never entered the finals again. Wouldn’t Su Mucheng’s sense of guilt only intensify through the years? Had she always felt that she hadn’t helped Ye Xiu enough?

“This time we’ll win for sure!” Tang Rou said.

“Aren’t you nervous?” Su Mucheng asked her with a smile.

“I thought that I wouldn’t get nervous, but now, I’m realizing that’s not the case,” Tang Rou said. Nervousness? What was that? Up until now, the things that made most people nervous would only make Tang Rou more excited, more determined. But this time? Excitement, determination, these were all there, but they weren’t enough to completely dispel the nervousness. Tang Rou discovered that her heart still held a sense of fear, and she admitted this.

“Really?” Su Mucheng continued to smile. “Then that might be a good thing! You know, I always thought that you were too lacking in nervousness. Of course, it’s not good to be too nervous, but to not feel nervous at all, that doesn’t seem very good either!”

“Even Ye Xiu gets nervous?” Tang Rou said.

“Of course he’s nervous. In fact, he’s been extremely nervous this whole season. If not, then how could he work so hard and put his full effort into everything?” Su Mucheng said.

“I sure couldn’t tell,” Tang Rou murmured.

“Nervousness can be turned into action! As for you, you should enjoy this rare feeling of nervousness. For you, this isn’t an obstacle at all, this is nourishment,” said Su Mucheng.

“This is the method of reducing the stress of playoffs? Change your nervousness into medicine, and eat it?” Tang Rou said.

“Is this not a good method?” Su Mucheng said.

“It looks like that’s the only way,” Tang Rou said. She essentially understood Su Mucheng’s meaning.

“Oh, you two were here this whole time!” At that moment, Ye Xiu with the group of old and youth had also returned to the neighborhood. As they walked along the road, they saw the two people sitting on the stone bench.

“Yup!” Su Mucheng and Tang Rou stood up, also prepared to return home.

Now, almost all of Happy had gathered here. They were just missing Mo Fan, who was still watching videos in the training room, and Fang Rui, who they still hadn’t seen around.

“Where in the world did that Fang Rui run off to?” Ye Xiu once again wondered.

“Him? He went to sleep!” Su Mucheng said.

“Huh?”

“He came back a bit after eight, and then went to sleep,” said Su Mucheng.

“He slept at eight?” Everyone exchanged glances.

At eight, Ye Xiu, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, and Luo Ji had been watching tonight’s match; Wei Chen and Steamed Bun had been sitting beside the road and exchanging bragging stories; Su Mucheng and Tang Rou had been strolling through this neighborhood and chatting. And Fang Rui at that time had apparently already gone to bed.

“Sleeping at eight, how long is that guy planning to sleep?” Wei Chen exclaimed.

“Is this how he’s dealing with the pressure?” everyone wondered.

“Or maybe he’s scared that he’ll be too nervous to sleep, so that’s why he went to bed so early, to have more time to grow tired,” they continued to discuss.

However, no one was so curious that they would check on whether Fang Rui was actually sleeping. This was the pattern of this night before the competition, everyone dispersing before coming back together in the end.

The next morning, when Ye Xiu awoke and came downstairs, he saw none other than Fang Rui. As expected of someone who’d gone to bed at eight, he was full of energy in the living room as he read the newspaper.

“301 lost pretty badly!” Seeing Ye Xiu come downstairs, Fang Rui greeted him and then made this comment. In his hands was today’s edition of Esports Weekly, which he had already gone out to buy this morning. Now that it was playoffs season, the amount of available copies of this newspaper was rather tight, especially since they were near the area of the old Club Excellent Era. If you didn’t go extremely early, you might not even be able to buy a copy.

“Yeah, I saw the match,” Ye Xiu said.

“Those old guys from Tyranny are still working hard?” Fang Rui said.

“Well, of course, how could they not?” said Ye Xiu.

“But the report said that they played kind of defensively,” Fang Rui said.

“Their strategy has a few changes. It’s no longer the fiercely fighting and charging Tyranny of before,” said Ye Xiu.

“They’re going slower?” Fang Rui said.

Ye Xiu nodded.

“They might be our next opponents. It’ll be a hard fight,” Fang Rui said.

Two top-level players didn’t need to say much. A few simple sentences was enough to understand the situation.

Because Tyranny had many old veterans, from an outsider’s perspective it would seem that they weren’t suited for a fast tempo. Old veterans were more suited for a steady fight to maximize usage of their experience and patience as they dealt with their opponent. But Tyranny had never used such a style before. They had fiercely fought and charged for ten years. Yet in the playoffs of this season, they slowed their pace as a whole.

Tyranny hadn’t just been rotating its old veterans to let them preserve their strength! They’d adjusted their strategies from the very foundation, building a new path that suited them better instead of relying on the rhythm they’d always had.

“Those old guys aren’t the only ones becoming more fearsome,” said Ye Xiu.

“Oh?”

“There’s also Zhang Xinjie,” said Ye Xiu.

“Him?”

“His style always suited this sort of slow rhythm better. Just looking at playstyle, he and Tyranny don’t fit at all, but because of his personality, he could force himself to adapt to tactics that didn’t suit him. But now, Tyranny’s style is developing in the direction of his true strength!”

Chapter 1390 - Team Protection

In the end, Happy only had a chance of facing Tyranny if they made it through this round; it was a little too early to worry about them now. More urgently, Happy needed to focus on playing well in their match against Blue Rain.

In this week, apart from familiarizing themselves with their new equipment, Happy actively prepared to face off against Blue Rain. They didn’t think about anything else, preparing themselves with only Blue Rain in mind. And now, it was time to bring all of this onto the battlefield.

During the regular season, Happy had twice met Blue Rain and lost rather miserably, 1 to 9 and 2 to 8. This time, what would Happy use to try and defeat Blue Rain? Today’s edition of the Esports Weekly analyzed this question. Esports Weekly, which had become daily issue after the start of playoffs, had its content divided into two topics. One part would focus on the match that had just ended the day before, while the other part would analyze the upcoming match that night. The content was detailed and substantial, and the gamers loved it, but these were busy days for the media workers.

From online polls, it seemed that Blue Rain was much more favored to win. About 73% of voters supported them, while only 27% were for Happy.

But Happy wouldn’t shrink back from such numbers. When they faced Excellent Era in the Challenger League, their support rate had been even more pathetic than this, but so what? If votes determined final results, then there wouldn’t be any need for the match at all, just give the prize after voting finished.

On the day of the match, there wouldn’t be any more heavy training, but the players still had to touch the computers a bit. There was no way they’d wait until the match began to start warming up, after all.

That afternoon, Happy’s players all arrived at Happy’s training room, each sitting down in front of a computer and opening Glory. Some played rather seriously, while others were more casual and relaxed. They no longer needed Ye Xiu to teach them. Warming up before a match, this was something they all had to do during the regular season, too. After going through this season, everyone knew what methods they liked to use to warm up, and so they each did their own thing.

And as they steadily adjusted their condition, they watched the minutes and seconds tick by.

When it was five o’clock, Chen Guo came over to call everyone to dinner. On match days, they generally ate earlier than usual. Right now, only three hours were left before the beginning of the match, and the atmosphere was incredibly heavy. Chen Guo only ate a few bites before feeling full, struggling to continue the act. In comparison, the players seemed somewhat more relaxed than her.

After they ate, they dispersed to do their own thing, until coming back together at seven o’clock, when it was time to go to the stadium.

Leave Happy Internet Cafe through the back door, cross the road, enter the stadium through the player passageways…

Happy had walked this route for an entire season now, but never as seriously as they did now. It was as though every step they took now would affect the final result of this match.

The preparation room was already ready, the air conditioning already running to bring it to a comfortable temperature. After everyone entered, they found a seat and sat down, and then they were silent.

Too stifling!

Chen Guo deeply felt the pressure in the air. At a time like this, she should really say something! Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu, looked at Wei Chen. These two seniors among seniors would normally take great care in adjusting the team’s attitude and atmosphere, so why weren’t they saying anything now? Was it because they were also feeling suppressed by this atmosphere?

Should I say something?

What do I say?

Good luck? Relax?

There was no point in repeatedly emphasizing these sort of mottos! She should have prepared some jokes. Maybe those would have some effect right now.

Chen Guo thought and thought, but she still didn’t know what she should say. But at last, Ye Xiu began to speak.

“Everyone remembers the strategies? Do I need to go over them again?” Ye Xiu said.

Everyone exchanged glances and silently shook their heads. No one spoke.

“Mm, the key is just spontaneous changes, we have a large advantage there. In terms of typing, I’m sure I can leave Yu Wenzhou behind in the dust.”

There were a few dry chuckles.

“Yu Wenzhou, as a pro player, has a completely insufficient handspeed,” Ye Xiu said. “But he was still able to become an All-Star level player. Do you know why?”

Everyone shook their heads. To be honest, they weren’t much in the mood for guessing things like this right now.

“He plays to his strengths and avoids his weaknesses,” said Ye Xiu.

“Silly, right?” Ye Xiu laughed. “But this is the truth. In this Alliance, there is no one better than him at doing this. This is Yu Wenzhou’s style, and this is the strategic style of Team Blue Rain as a whole. Ever since their soul, the person they could never be without, their previous captain Wei Chen retired, Blue Rain has been on the rise…”

“Fuck off!” Wei Chen had to interject.

Everyone laughed again, and this time it wasn’t as strained as before.

“Since our opponent this round is Blue Rain, I advise you all to learn from our comrade Yu Wenzhou. Avoid your weaknesses and use your strengths. Every one of you, fiercely place your strengths onto this battlefield for all to see. If you can do this, then you won’t have a single regret left in your heart. Don’t worry if it’s not enough. Everyone has their lacking areas, and that’s why we’re a team. Where one person lacks, the other four come to bolster. This is what it is to be a team.

“Everyone protects their teammates’ backs, and so everyone has someone at their back protecting them. So, rest assured, and charge forward boldly!”

“Happy, it’s time to go onstage.”

Just as Ye Xiu finished speaking, a worker knocked at the door of Happy’s prep room, calling them onstage.

“Let’s go!” Ye Xiu called, and everyone stood up and walked out of the prep room. Across the hallway, Blue Rain’s players were also walking out of their room.

The two teams each lined up in the passageway, with the two captains standing at the very front. Because the speech that Ye Xiu had just given had begun with Yu Wenzhou, Happy’s members couldn’t help but take extra glances at this Blue Rain captain whose handspeed wasn’t up to par.

“Did you guess what ace we have up our sleeve?” Ye Xiu, standing at the front of the line, asked Yu Wenzhou.

“We did not,” Yu Wenzhou smiled. He hadn’t even bothered to try and guess.

“I don’t mind telling you now,” said Ye Xiu.

“I’ve been waiting for this moment as well,” said Yu Wenzhou.

“It’s equipment,” said Ye Xiu.

“Oh, your Myriad Manifestations Umbrella isn’t dragging everyone else down anymore?” Yu Wenzhou said. Lord Grim’s umbrella had been Level 70 for the entire season. Right now, never mind the core characters, any character with a Silver weapon would definitely have their weapon upgraded first, so essentially all of them were now at Level 75. For weapons, 70 was practically an extinct number.

“Hehe, I should say that you guys will be dragging me down,” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Would it kill you to stop bragging?” At last, the person standing behind Yu Wenzhou could restrain himself no longer.

“Whoa, how many sentences did we say to each other just now? He actually lasted until now without opening his mouth! Must have been very difficult, huh?” Ye Xiu said to Yu Wenzhou with extreme surprise.

“Haha…” Yu Wenzhou could only laugh. What else could he say!

“Later, when you see it, try not to cry with fear,” Ye Xiu turned and said to Huang Shaotian.

“Try not to cry when you lose, too,” Huang Shaotian retorted.

“How could I lose?” Ye Xiu said loftily.

“Have some shame! You already lost twice.” Huang Shaotian was referring to the regular season.

“I didn’t lose.” At this time, Ye Xiu abandoned the “team” he was always talking about. If just talking about himself, he indeed hadn’t lost. He had thirty-seven consecutive wins!

“That was luck.” Of course, Huang Shaotian stubbornly had to continue.

“How about you get lucky for me to see? I only won thirty-seven in a row. I purposefully left one out. The record’s just begging to be broken!”

“…” No matter how stubborn Huang Shaotian was, he didn’t dare take up that challenge. Fortunately, right then, the workers signaled to the two teams to begin entering.

“Let’s go.” The away team entered first, but Yu Wenzhou didn’t forget to acknowledge Ye Xiu as he left, before stepping into the stadium proper.

For a stadium that wasn’t their home stadium, getting polite applause was good enough. Cheers and whatnot, even if their own fans had followed them here, would definitely be suppressed by the home stadium fans. How would the home fans tolerate the visitors going wild on their turf?

The stadium lit up with a projection of Swoksaar, who did some random movements. The chance to act cool or whatever of course wouldn’t be given to the away team characters; it was good enough that they didn’t bash them. The live announcer gave some cursory introduction for Yu Wenzhou, before calling up the next onstage.

Huang Shaotian immediately came up, and his treatment was about the same as what Yu Wenzhou received. This sort of thing was commonplace, and it happened at everyone’s home stadiums. Blue Rain’s players had seen the world, so of course this wouldn’t bother them. One by one the players came out and up onto the stage. And then when it was time for Happy, the sound was immediately different. The moment that Ye Xiu walked out of the passageway, the shouting and cheering instantly filled the entire stadium.

In the projection, Lord Grim displayed the many changes of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, while Ye Xiu waved to the audience members on all sides. Even the amount of time that was given was different from what Blue Rain got. As for the introduction, they only wished they could describe all of his glorious accomplishments in the most extravagant way possible.

One by one, Happy’s players walked onto the stage, and then they shook hands, and parted. Two people were left, undoubtedly the first players of the group arena, too lazy to leave and then come back.

“Ye Xiu, it’s Ye Xiu!” Commentator Pan Lin was already shouting excitedly.

Ye Xiu was actually Happy’s first player in the group arena. It was already the playoffs, and he still wanted to go on first? Before the match, practically no one had predicted this arrangement. With Ye Xiu’s unparalleled 1v1 ability, everyone logically expected that he would be fourth in the lineup.

But now, he was the first one!

As for Blue Rain, the first one up was the Qi Master Song Xiao! Their Mister Clutch was thrown into first slot in the group arena. What sort of plans and hopes were behind that choice?

After greeting each other, the two headed to their own competitor booths.

“Happy actually sent Ye Xiu as the first player in the group arena,” Pan Lin marveled. “This is completely unexpected. Coach Li, what do you think about this?”

“Um, I would think that this is mostly to boost Happy’s morale! Happy has a lot of rookies, after all, and this is their first time in the playoffs. The pressure is definitely high. If Ye Xiu goes first, he can get a win and raise their spirits, as well as lessen the responsibility of those after him. I think that’s Happy’s plan,” Li Yibo said, doing his best to speculate.

Chapter 1391 - Level 80!

The two players entered their booths and their characters loaded in. The match was about to begin.

That was when some sort of uproar erupted amongst the in-stadium audience, and then, the live broadcast commentator Pan Lin also suddenly yelled, “No way!!!”

“What?” Li Yibo was puzzled. The character loading was always the same, so he didn’t pay attention.

“…” Pan Lin hesitated. Just now, in the character loading screen, when it reached Lord Grim, his equipment flashed by and Pan Lin thought that he had seen an 80 in the Level section. However, it had just been flash, and he wasn’t sure what he had seen exactly. The character loading screen was a fixed shot, there wouldn’t be any special shots. Thus, Pan Lin didn’t say anything, just hurriedly asking the cameraman to display Lord Grim’s equipment as soon as they entered the match.

The uproar that had briefly occurred at Happy’s home stadium was also because some people had seen Level 80 on Lord Grim’s equipment. Just one or two people, then it might just be that they misread, but then those people who thought they misread realized that quite a few people were misreading today!

The characters loaded in quickly and before the audience had figured out what was going on, it had finished and the characters spawned on the map, symbolizing the start of the match. The live broadcast immediately displayed Lord Grim’s equipment.

Boom!! 　 The audience exploded. This time, the entire audience could clear see it: Equipment Level: Level 80. And it wasn’t just for one piece of equipment either.

Weapon: Myriad Manifestations Umbrella;

Top: Dissonant Soul Armor;

Shoes: Cloud Breaker Boots;

Belt: Chain Lightning Belt;

Cape: Civil Dawn;

Badge: Sky-Splitter;

Right ring: Hurricane.

Of Lord Grim’s equipment, these seven pieces of Silver equipment were Level 80.

“Lord Grim has… Level 80 equipment equipped. What’s going on?” This time, Pan Lin could see it clearly, and didn’t have to suspect that he had gotten it wrong, meaning that he was free to yell about it.

Li Yibo was also completely struck dumb. Level 80 equipment? What the hell?

There was no need to even mention the audience. The stadium was naturally a cacophony of confusion. Everyone was first shocked into speechlessness, then they exploded into discussion.

Even the referee wasn’t spared. When he saw the Level 80 equipment, his brain practically short circuited. Then, his first thought after that was to wonder if something had gone wrong with the system. Did they need to pause the match?

Then, Blue Rain’s players were also stunned upon seeing the Level 80 equipment.

“Level 80 equipment? What’s going on?” Huang Shaotian expressed his bewilderment. Though it wasn’t to the point where he would cry from fear, he had to admit that the Ye Xiu had truly managed to shock them this time.

Yu Wenzhou clearly hadn’t been expecting that improvements to their equipment would be a Level increase to eighty. However, after a moment of shock, he began to organize his thoughts.

“Is it a system error?” The other members of Blue Rain all wondered.

However, Yu Wenzhou didn’t think so. The equipment and system would all be checked before the match, to make sure that the match would go smoothly. It wasn’t like there hadn’t been small errors with the hardware before, but errors in data hadn’t occurred once since the start of the Alliance, so why now?

“The characters are Level 75, that’s for certain.” Yu Wenzhou took his mind off of those incidents and began to analyze this logically.

“For Level 75 characters to equip Level 80 equipment, then there must be a ‘Level requirement minus five’ stat on the equipment.” Yu Wenzhou swiftly thought of this.

“However, how they created these pieces of Level 80 equipment is a complete mystery.” Of course, Yu Wenzhou wouldn’t know. If he did, then Blue Rain would have Level 80 equipment, too.

“Happy’s R&D is that skilled?” Huang Shaotian exclaimed in shock. Level 80 equipment was enough to leave all the powerhouses in the dust.

Discussion had erupted everywhere. After Yu Wenzhou, commentators Pan Lin and Li Yibo soon figured out that these pieces of Level 80 equipment had a “Level requirement minus five” stat, making them usable, which was relatively obvious. However, after that, no one could say how Happy managed to create Level 80 equipment under a Level 75 Level limit. 　 “So this is the ace that Happy had prepared for the playoffs!” Pan Lin exclaimed in the broadcast.

“Level 80 equipment? How?”

The match continued. After confirming that nothing had gone wrong with the software or hardware, he didn’t have a reason to pause it. Currently, Song Xiao, on the field, had also found out that his opponent had Level 80 equipment and was naturally shocked.

“Afraid yet?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Even so, it doesn’t mean that I can back down!” Song Xiao replied.

As expected of the most renowned clutch player of the alliance, Mister Clutch. Against Ye Xiu, who had won thirty-seven consecutive individual matches this season, against this shocking reveal of Level 80 equipment, Song Xiao expressed his shock, but soon calmed. Afraid? Back down? He was just joking around. In reality, he was treating this like any other match, focused on taking victory.

“Let’s go then!” Ye Xiu called out and then the two charged forwards.

The group arena map choice naturally couldn’t only consider Ye Xiu’s needs. A clean, simple map would be great for him and Tang Rou, but for those like Fang Rui who relied on dirty play, then it would be a huge trouble.

Thus, the group arena map had to make sure to take care of everyone’s needs, so it’d usually contain a variety of terrains.

However, it didn’t seem like either of the two participants had any intentions to use the terrain, the two were heading directly for the center.

Just as they were about to meet, with everyone eagerly anticipating how this Level 80 equipment would perform spectacularly, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim suddenly swerved.

Ye Xiu, having maintained a straightforward and brute force style for thirty-seven rounds, suddenly decided to switch to being strategic in the first one on one match of the playoffs.

“Ye Xiu has decided against a frontal contronfation,” Pan Lin noted.

“A wise choice,” Li Yibo commented, “The group arena is different from individual matches. One must defeat their opponent with minimal cost to oneself, so, if possible, it’s better to use the environment and play strategically. Brute force styles aren’t actually the most suited to group arenas. In individual matches, their victories will be victories no matter if they take down an opponent with great cost or if they manage to take down an opponent without losing a drop of health. However, in the group arena, these two results are completely different.”

“But many teams still have brute force style players in their group arena lineup! It doesn’t seem like anyone avoids having them play in the group arena,” Pan Lin brought up.

“Brute force is a style that players use, but it’s not set in stone. In the group arena, brute force style players can play a little more wisely. Like Ye Xiu, for the individual competitions, he kept a brute force style, but now with the group arena, he’s decided to be a little more flexible,” Li Yibo said.

“But some players seem to stick with using brute force even in the group arena,” Pan Lin argued.

“Yep! After all, everything has its exceptions! Different situations will require different attitudes,” Li Yibo said.

The two stopped their conversation there. Currently, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had swerved left, heading towards Song Xiao’s right flank. However, since Ye Xiu only swerved after the two had seen each other, Song Xiao knew exactly where Lord Grim had gone and was already keeping an eye on that side.

Ye Xiu didn’t act like many dirty play pros did, hiding away and waiting for a chance. From an opening on that side, Lord Grim peeked around the corner and, boom boom boom, three Anti-Tank Missiles came blasting over.

Song Xiao had his eyes on that side and he saw Lord Grim just as he peeked out. The three Anti-Tank Missiles couldn’t even count as a sneak attack, yet…

Boom! 　 Receding Tides actually got hit by one of the missiles. The force of the explosion threw him back a few steps, but Receding Tides soon stabilized himself.

“He did it on purpose!” Li Yibo immediately realized. 　 “Oh?”

“He’s testing Lord Grim’s attack power,” Li Yibo explained. Too many pieces of equipment had been changed, causing a huge shift in stats. Though the base four stats could still be seen, they needed experience to get an understanding of Lord Grim’s attack power. Song Xiao had a good grasp on the consequences of getting hit by this attack, and at the same time, he was giving the rest of Blue Rain information. In the future, they’ll continue to face Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, so they had to hurry and collect data.

“Hm, Lord Grim’s switched out several pieces of equipment at once, very effective. All the data that the teams collected on him during the regular season is pretty much useless now. Everything will have to start from scratch,” Pan Lin mentioned.

“What’s even more troublesome is that the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella clearly has different stats depending on the form,” Li Yibo added.

“Happy really has dropped quite the bomb!” Pan Lin said.

“Right now, we just don’t know if only Lord Grim has seen such improvements or if all the characters in Happy have,” Li Yibo continued.

“We’ll know soon enough.” Pan Lin seemed rather excited.

“Hm… After Ye Xiu let Lord Grim attack, he hid again.” Li Yibo returned to the match.

“Song Xiao isn’t rushing either. Is he trying to figure out Lord Grim’s attack power? Advisor Li, what do you think of this attack?” Pan Lin asked.

“Ah… the attack’s damage has clearly gone up,” Li Yibo said. This season made him feel more and more that he was falling behind. He was preparing to do some revision and further study. Actually, it was very hard to get much from a single attack. This was something decided by both the attack power of the attacker and the defense of the target. 　 Li Yibo was like the audience, he didn’t know the actual stats of the characters, so it would be impossible to ask him to deduce much from a single strike. Team Blue Rain’s members at least knew their teammates’ character’s defense, and they could derive the attack from the damage taken. As for the other spectators? In their eyes, there would be a hundred different damage calculations from Lord Grim fighting a hundred different opponents. It would be extremely difficult to figure out Lord Grim’s actual attack power. 　 Though Li Yibo was studying up, he couldn’t figure out something so difficult in such a short time, unless a team was willing to provide their stats.

Unfortunately, that wasn’t possible. So, he could only say that Lord Grim’s damage had increased, which was clearly unnecessary. If his attack power hadn’t changed, then what would the point of switching in all that Level 80 equipment?

Chapter 1392 - Counterattack

“Neither side has made any moves!” Pan Lin shouted. This would usually be boring, but Pan Lin was excited. He was looking forward to what Level 80 equipment could do.

Li Yibo found Lord Grim’s info and compared the stats before and after. The four main stats were clearly displayed, so Li Yibo hoped to quickly find something he could analyze.

“Lord Grim is moving deep. Could he be looking for better angle of attack? But the area he’s in should be within Song Xiao’s line of sight. There doesn’t seem to be any location which he can mount a sneak attack from though. Is he going to venture even farther in?” Pan Lin continued to comment. Usually, if it wasn’t a deciding moment, these remarks would rarely be said. However, right now, it looked as if Pan Lin would even analyze Lord Grim’s thumb movements.

“Just as I thought! Lord Grim is going even deeper. He’s planning on making a big turn!”

“Ah, Song Xiao has also moved!”

“Receding Tides is moving forward. Song Xiao truly deserves to be called Mister Clutch, he has exceptional mental fortitude! It’s quite bold of him to push forward. Lord Grim’s already moved away though, so cutting in won’t be dangerous. In fact, he might be able to see through Ye Xiu’s intentions this way.”

“What…” Pan Lin muttered to himself. For a moment, he wasn’t able to continue. He had been too ambitious in guessing Ye Xiu’s intentions. Ye Xiu didn’t move according to his analysis and instead moved in the opposite direction of what he had expected. This surprise caught him at a loss for words.

However, with Song Xiao’s Receding Tides moving away, there were now no traces of Lord Grim.

“He calculated everything that precisely?” Pan Lin was shocked. Although it was just small play, being able to read someone so thoroughly was truly frightening.

At this moment, the broadcast cut into a slow-motion replay.

“Oh…” Pan Lin suddenly understood. It wasn’t a calculation. There had been an angle from Lord Grim’s previous position where he could see Receding Tides.

“As expected of Ye Xiu!” Li Yibo returned to the match, “He’s extremely proficient at this map, a trait very few young players possess. Young players lack an attention to detail towards maps, which is a huge advantage for the home team.”

“Happy’s Qiao Yifan is quite good in this area too!” Pan Lin mentioned his name.

“He’s got a good mentor beside him!” Li Yibo sighed.

Pan Lin subconsciously thought of other players on Happy who weren’t particularly strong in this area. For example, Steamed Bun and Tang Rou weren’t thorough enough in their utilization of the map. Saying all that would tear Li Yibo’s praise apart though, so he restrained himself.

Song Xiao didn’t see Lord Grim, so instead of having Receding Tides continue moving straight, he circled around in reverse.

“Song Xiao’s very experienced,” Li Yibo said, “Even though he doesn’t see his opponent, from the distance he’s traveled, he has a rough idea of Lord Grim’s possible positions. If Lord Grim wasn’t in those areas, he wouldn’t have been able to disappear from the map so quickly.”

“Oh, the two sides are…” On the bottom right corner of the broadcast, a bird’s eye view of the map appeared. The positions of the two characters were represented as dots as they moved. The camera constantly switched back and forth between the two characters, giving a feeling of tension.

Closer, closer…

The two sides neared each other. At the next intersection, the two would meet. Everyone held their breaths. Suddenly, Lord Grim jumped.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s ninjato stuck into the wall. The wall that originally couldn’t be jumped was instantly climbed through the usage of the Ninja class’s special skill.

That’s cheating!!!

That was what Pan Lin wanted to shout. The surprises from the unspecialized still gave off a feeling of cheating even after an entire regular season. Everyone’s thought process was different from Ye Xiu’s. They needed to spend a certain amount of time and effort to understand what an unspecialized could do. As a result, when they saw Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim in a match, they would constantly think “why didn’t I think of that?”

The cameraman was also in a fluster. He wasn’t sure which first-person perspective he should look at to best display this suddenness. Should he use Ye Xiu’s hunter-like view to show his sharpness? Or should he use Song Xiao’s confused-prey view to show helplessness?

There was no time to think carefully. The camera instinctively shifted to a viewpoint.

Song Xiao’s perspective.

Receding Tides was moving.

Then, a grenade suddenly appeared from above and dropped in front of him.

Too awesome!

The cameraman cried out in his heart. Song Xiao’s perspective had given this grenade highlight clip. From above to below, the image of the grenade grew larger as Receding Tides moved. Everything was quiet as the grenade fell. It was as if the scene was static.

If only it could be in slo-mo… the cameraman was still obsessed with the shot.

Bang!

The grenade exploded, and Lord Grim dropped from the sky.

Roll, roll, roll.

Song Xiao’s Receding Tides rolled backwards three times and then shot a Qi Bullet.

The spectators all felt frightened seeing this sudden ambush. However, Song Xiao himself was as calm as ever. He did reacted promptly and appropriately.

Three rolls backwards pull the distance between Receding Tides and Lord Grim, and then a Qi Bullet at the slightest opening.

“Beautiful!” Pan Lin cried out.

Ye Xiu’s ambush had been beautiful, but Song Xiao’s response was too. This level of play was truly deserving of the playoffs. It was just the first exchange, and Pan Lin felt like it was worthy of the ticket price. Unfortunately, he didn’t have time to praise this moment because there was still a battle underway.

The Qi Bullet flew out.

Lord Grim didn’t dodge it though, and tanked the hit to stay on the offense.

“Even if it’s the group arena, sometimes it’s necessary to show a tough display!” Li Yibo praised.

By tanking the hit, Ye Xiu maintained the initiative. But because of Song Xiao’s calm response, the ambush didn’t deal too much harm. The battle had suddenly shifted to a direct confrontation.

“An ambush doesn’t seem to be a good choice against a player with strong mental fortitude like Song Xiao,” Pan Lin said.

“Ye Xiu was at least able to gain the initiative through it,” Li Yibo said.

No one would have any objections to that. In a direction confrontation, Lord Grim would be attacking 70% of the time.

“But it can’t be said that Song Xiao is at a disadvantage,” Pan Lin said.

Song Xiao was 70% defending, 30% attacking. Yes, he seemed to be a bit on the backfoot, but his rhythm was steady.

“Such a steady defensive counterattack playstyle is Blue Rain’s style,” Li Yibo said.

The healer character exemplified the team’s style to a certain extent. Of the eight playoff teams, Samsara, Tyranny, Happy, Thunderclap, and Hundred Blossoms all had Clerics as their healers, a show of their overall offense-oriented playstyles. As for the other three teams, Tiny Herb had two healers, an exception. Then, there was Blue Rain and 301, who had Paladins as healers. And these two teams leaned towards defense.

Especially Blue Rain.

Team Blue Rain was a paragon of a defensive counterattack team.

Defend while waiting for mistakes and capitalizing on them.

This was their team’s playstyle, which eventually became many of the styles of the players on the team. To be a part of Blue Rain’s main roster, not having beautiful defensive play was extremely difficult.

As a defense-heavy style, being on the passive side was normal because you were intentionally giving the the opponents space. As a result, while it looked like Song Xiao’s offense looked rather weak, Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn’t think it was mark of him being at a disadvantage. It was just how he played.

So they waited.

Defensive counterattack. The high point was the counterattack. Opportunities were fleeting. Once grasped, it couldn’t be let go. That instant required explosiveness and efficiency. For a defensive counterattack playstyle, defense needed to be steady and slow, while the counterattack needed to be fast and fierce.

Everyone stared at the screen. The Happy fans listening to the commentators were held in suspense.

Song Xiao wasn’t a stand-out existence during the regular season. His numbers were so-so, but everyone knew he was formidable during playoffs. He wasn’t an easy opponent. As a result, even if Ye Xiu was the King of Duels in the regular season, everyone still felt worried.

Straight Punch, Knock Back, Grenade, Shining Cut, Double Stab, Ghost Slash, Floating Bullet…

Skills after skill was released through Lord Grim’s ever-changing Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. His speed was so fast that the viewers couldn’t even clearly distinguish what forms his umbrella were in. A skill came out, and then the umbrella transformed into a different form.

Without a pause.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella never stayed in the same form for more than two seconds.

Bang!

A falling Flower Palm suddenly struck Receding Tides, sending him flying backwards.

“Ah!” Pan Lin cried out in astonishment. The equilibrium had been been broken by the palm.

“Ye Xiu’s broken through Song Xiao’s defense!” Li Yibo shouted.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella continued transforming non-stop, but this time, the rate of hits landing on Receding Tides had increased.

“In the end, Song Xiao isn’t able to hold on. Let’s see if he can turn this around,” Pan Lin said.

They still had confidence in Song Xiao because no matter what, this player wouldn’t panic. He had the mental fortitude necessary to make a comeback.

So they waited.

Before, it had been a defensive counterattack style. Now, it had turned into a get-beat-up counterattack style.

But Lord Grim’s offense continued to pour out relentlessly.

As a result, Receding Tides took even heavier beatings.

The expressions of those waiting for a reversal gradually started to turn strange.

“This… is he going to get taken out in one combo?” Pan Lin started questioning. Their hopes for Song Xiao seemed to have disappeared.

“Ambush to start, suppression with attacks, offense breaking defense, one combo kill,” Li Yibo summed up the battle with twelve words.

The so-called defensive counterattack playstyle. So we’ve seen the defense and the get-beat-up part, where’s the counterattack?

“Is he not able to find an opening to counterattack?” Pan Lin was still thinking about it.

Chapter 1393 - Eyes Are Blurry

Everyone held hope for Song Xiao because he never panicked, because he always performed spectacularly during critical moments.

But this time? Ever since Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim pierced through his defenses, Song Xiao failed to successfully get them back up. If it was said that he had deliberately left openings in his defense looking for a counterattack, then right now he was purely focused on resisting his opponent’s attacks; he was playing on the defensive to survive.

However, even in this sort of situation, players proficient in defense could still find ways to break through the opponent’s offense and seize opportunities to turn the tides.

Song Xiao was a calm player and was also exceptional at defense, which was why unlike other players who were overwhelmed by the Unspecialized Blitz during the regular season, people felt like he definitely wouldn’t lose like them.

But from the looks of it, they shouldn’t hold any such expectations. Song Xiao was being suppressed just like every other player. Receding Tides was in dire straits. As for Song Xiao’s current state of mind, no one knew.

“He only has 10% health left,” Pan Lin hadn’t given up. He hoped to see a sudden reversal at the final moment. But then he looked at Lord Grim’s health and despaired.

73%.

Lord Grim still had so much health left. Song Xiao’s playoffs opening was starting off unlucky. As soon as he left the door, he met a brick wall.

It’s not going to just end like this, is it? Some were muttering in their hearts. In particular, the Team Blue Rain fans had confidence in Song Xiao, because Song Xiao never let them down at the crucial moments.

But… there’s a first time for everything. In the end, Song Xiao had his first failed performance when it mattered.

Loss.

70%. Lord Grim’s health halted here when Song Xiao’s Receding Tides fell.

The stadium applauded to Ye Xiu, of course. Some brave young fellows were even so bold to shout “1v5!”

Song Xiao walked out from the player booth on stage. The broadcast zoomed in on his face, but there didn’t really seem to be any particular expression on it.

“Song Xiao’s performance today is a bit disappointing!” Pan Lin sighed.

“Or perhaps our expectations for him were too high,” Li Yibo said, “Song Xiao’s technical skill isn’t considered anything outstanding, but rather it’s because of his exceptional mental fortitude that he’s able to perform beyond his usual skill level during key moments like the playoffs. On the other hand, other players get nervous and might become too cautious, leading to a decrease in their level of play. One side plays worse, while the other side plays better. As a result, it’s not hard to understand why Song Xiao always seems to play spectacularly in the playoffs. Unfortunately, his opponent this time was…”

“Saying Ye Xiu gets nervous in a playoffs match sounds more like a joke, doesn’t it?” Li Yibo said.

“Yeah,” Pan Lin confirmed.

“So Ye Xiu dominating him isn’t anything unexpected. If Song Xiao’s opponent had been a Happy rookie, perhaps things may have turned out differently,” Li Yibo said.

“It looks like Blue Rain didn’t expect Ye Xiu to appear first even in the playoffs. Their original idea was probably not to have Song Xiao encounter Ye Xiu,” Pan Lin analyzed.

“Yeah, let’s see who Blue Rain’s second player is,” Li Yibo started paying attention to the big screen. The playoffs was set up to always be suspenseful. It wasn’t like the regular season’s group arena, where the two team’s lineup would be listed all at once before the three players went onto the stage. The playoff’s five-player group arena was done one at a time. Before it was time, no one besides the player’s respective team would know who would be up next.

Lu Hanwen, Blade Master, Flowing Cloud.

Finally, the big screen displayed the name of Team Blue Rain’s next player.

“Uh, this…” Li Yibo wanted to say something but then hesitated. Lu Hanwen was still the Alliance’s youngest player, but he had already been a part of the main roster for two years, entering All-Stars both years. In his first season at just fourteen years of age, it was because of his mistake that the team lost.

Team Blue Rain’s method of training Lu Hanwen was too unrestrained. Nowadays, no team would throw their rookie out onto the battlefield to play around and figure out things for himself. Everyone trained their rookies methodically step by step. Quite a few people expressed their worries for how Team Blue Rain was treating Lu Hanwen.

When rookies first entered the Alliance, they needed time to get used to the intensity and pace of the professional circle. Many talented youths were able to immediately adapt and shine as soon as they stepped onto the stage, with all sorts of awards suddenly being thrown at them.

But what rookies never knew was that what they were facing wasn’t the true professional scene. Because they were a newcomer, neither they nor the pro scene was familiar with them. And once they started shining, the pro scene would notice them, and the other opposing teams would make preparations to target them. It was only at this moment would the rookies truly be facing the pro scene; teams would use anything at their disposal for the sake of winning.

Countless rookies crashed into this iron wall, leaving their heads broken and bloody. And this was the so-called Rookie’s Block. Many of the current Gods had hit this wall before.

They had broken past it, but numerous talented players disappeared into nothing after hitting this wall. The more massive the blow, the greater the pressure, the more unfavorable it was for the rookie’s growth.

In many people’s eyes, Blue Rain’s Lu Hanwen had fallen into such a predicament. And to no one’s surprise, once the teams started familiarizing themselves with him, his performance dwindled. However, Lu Hanwen never fell into low spirits. He continued to work hard. It was as if he had just entered the Alliance. He continued to preserve that endless reserve of energy.

Dwindling performance? A mistake dragging down the rest of the team?

Lu Hanwen had experienced and suffered through them all. However, his enthusiasm never wavered. He was true youth filled with boundless spirit. His heart was filled with sunshine without a single bit of haze.

Blue Rain had used the method most suitable for him. He didn’t need to be protected. He could face setbacks and crash to the ground heavily, but he would always quickly climb back up, stumbling until the day he flew.

“Coach Li, what are your thoughts on this matchup?” Pan Lin saw that Li Yibo seemed to want to say something and switched the conversation to him.

“Ye Xiu is experienced. Lu Hanwen is driven. It’s going to be an exciting match,” Li Yibo smiled.

Pan Lin guessed that this wasn’t what Li Yibo had originally wanted to say, but it wouldn’t be good to press him on air. He could only continue with a brief introduction of Lu Hanwen’s situation as he watched the young player get up from his seat and head to the stage.

“This Lu Hanwen has a big heart!” Pan Lin suddenly said, when he saw Lu Hanwen cross Song Xiao.

“Yes, compared to skill, the heart is much more difficult to train. Lu Hanwen is only a young kid. How rare,” Li Yibo said.

“Blue Rain’s two players are talking with each other. Is Song Xiao passing on the experience he had just gained from this match?” Pan Lin guessed.

“Blue Rain should have that knowledge way beforehand!” Li Yibo remarked. After all, Blue Rain and Happy had fought against each other twice in the regular season already.

“Perhaps a new discovery?” As Pan Lin said these words, Song Xiao and Lu Hanwen parted. Lu Hanwen went onto the stage, while Song Xiao returned to his seat.

“Is he really hard to fight?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“My eyes went blurry,” Song Xiao got to his seat and shut his eyes.

“Blurry?”

“That umbrella changes forms again and again and again non-stop. I really can’t bear it,” Song Xiao said.

Everyone in Blue Rain looked at each other. When they prepped for this match against Happy, Ye Xiu and his unspecialized were obviously a huge focus, but they hadn’t prepared for something like this.

“What is this?” Blue Rain’s Spitfire, Zeng Xuan, sighed. Spitfires could be considered as the best at interfering with the opponent’s line of sight. Others might not be able to reach the apex and emulate Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms style, but it had become a commonly utilized Spitfire technique.

Ye Xiu’s technique was different from theirs though. They simply used visual effects, but Ye Xiu directly made visual attacks! Making someone’s eyes go blurry, that was the effect of Flash Bullet!

“What did you say to Lu Hanwen?” Yu Wezhou asked Song Xiao.

“I told him to try to cut in from the side or circle to the back. Try not to fight face to face. Doing so is truly too disgusting. Truly. You guys should try when you have the chance,” Song Xiao said.

Yu Wenzhou didn’t ask any further and watched as Lu Hanwen went into Blue Rain’s player booth. Then, the characters loaded in. Flowing Cloud and Lord Grim entered the map.

Lu Hanwen obviously wasn’t the type to go around in circles. Flowing Cloud went directly towards the center. As for Ye Xiu? He once again took a roundabout path, a different route than last time too. Previously, he had Lord Grim go to the left, this time he changed it to the right.

“Playing dirty again!” Huang Shaotian ground his teeth. He was a bit nervous too. He knew of Lu Hanwen’s style better than others. Lu Hanwen wasn’t good at dealing with dirty play. An ordinary level of dirty wasn’t a big deal, but Ye Xiu’s dirtiness, on the other hand, was on another level.

“Lu Hanwen is taking the straight path, while Ye Xiu is taking a roundabout route,” Pan Lin explained the opening.

“Ye Xiu seems to be taking it at a medium pace! It doesn’t seem like he plans on rushing for a position,” Li Yibo commented on Lord Grim’s movement speed.

“Where is he planning to mount a sneak attack from this time?” Pan Lin said. Ye Xiu’s strategic movement wasn’t completely dirty. He didn’t hide, attack, retreat, harass, retreat, harass, and annoy his opponents to death. Most of the time, he would launch a sneak attack to gain the initiative and then keep fighting face to face. However, this was the group arena. The less health lost the better. Under these circumstances, it wasn’t impossible that he would play completely dirty. The Glory Textbook. No one believed that there was no style Ye Xiu could not play.

Would he play dirty?

Everyone stared at Lord Grim’s unhurried movement and thought quietly to themselves.

Chapter 1394 - Ineffective to Effective

Lord Grim and Flowing Cloud took their own paths. Neither side was facing each other but from the omniscient view of the spectators, it could be seen that the two characters were closing in on each other, even if there was stuff between them.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud moved in a straight line and reached the center of the map first. Seeing that his opponent wasn’t within sight, he didn’t hesitate and continued charging forward.

“Wow, Lu Hanwen is very decisive!” Pan Lin was pleasantly surprised.

“Oh, this way Ye Xiu won’t be able to find a place in the center of the map to mount a sneak attack. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud has already left!” Li Yibo said.

“Is this the advice Song Xiao gave? It’s simple, but effective!” Pan Lin said.

With just these few words, Flowing Cloud had already crossed through the center of the map towards Lord Grim’s spawn point.

“But what’s Lu Hanwen going to do next? He’s not hoping that he’ll find Lord Grim at the spawn point, is he?” Pan Lin questioned.

“Lu Hanwen should have a better understanding of this map from the first fight. I’m guessing his plans are based on this understanding. Or perhaps, someone gave him some pointers,” Li Yibo said.

“Song Xiao?” Pan Lin looked at Flowing Cloud’s movements.

“Song Xiao may have played on this map, but his understanding might not be better than the players off-stage,” Li Yibo said.

“Yu Wenzhou!” Pan Lin realized. Why would the off-stage players have an easier time grasping the map? Because they had spectator control, allowing them to get a full view of the map or cut to different perspectives. This control gave them a much more complete picture than what the broadcast could give. Song Xiao had never traversed to Lord Grim’s spawn point, however, those off-stage could see the terrain Lord Grim passed through and his spawn point via their spectator view.

Team Blue Rain obviously wasn’t very familiar with the map chosen by Team Happy, but a tactics expert like Yu Wenzhou could easily find numerous strategical points from the map in this amount of time. What areas should be avoided, what areas could be utilized, the following Blue Rain players could already start reflecting on how to take advantage of these points. Perhaps Lu Hanwen had been given a suggestion by Yu Wenzhou.

“Let’s see what he’ll do!” Pan Lin suddenly became excited. But at this moment, Lord Grim suddenly changed directions.

Because he was taking a roundabout route, Lord Grim hadn’t reached the center yet. Even so, he suddenly turned left, making his way towards the path to the center.

“This is!” Pan Lin yelled. For a moment, he couldn’t figure out Lord Grim’s goal. Li Yibo was also thinking about Lord Grim’s decision. After awhile, it looked like he was planning on charging out from the right flank to meet with Flowing Cloud.

“No way! Switch to Ye Xiu’s perspective!” Li Yibo shouted.

The camera immediately switched views. The scenery was rapidly changing. Lord Grim was moving very fast, traversing through the map with great familiarity. Not far from his position, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was following the main central path towards the south.

Slide Kick!

Lord Grim suddenly did a Slide Kick, not as an attack but as a way to move at a low height. He slid across the ground through the gaps of several thick tree branches.

Jumping over the tree branches or circling around them were possible options, but Ye Xiu choosing to use a skill instead wasn’t just to look cool.

Lord Grim and Flowing Cloud were very close. Everyone felt like the two would soon be within each other’s sights.

But after the Slide Kick, Lord Grim immediately hugged the ground.

The camera reacted quickly this time. With a snap, the perspectives of both players were shown simultaneously on the big screen.

Lord Grim hugged the ground as he moved, while from Lu Hanwen’s perspective, there was no one in sight.

He’s hidden himself!

Everyone gasped in surprise. Then, they saw Lord Grim roll, without standing up, to behind a shrub.

Nothing abnormal could be seen from Lu Hanwen’s perspective, but Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had quietly approached him.

There was no time to reflect on this scene though.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud continued to dash forward. From the bush Lord Grim was hiding behind, the sound of footsteps could be heard. Everyone in the stadium could hear it, let alone Ye Xiu.

Just as Flowing Cloud passed by the bush, Lord Grim jumped out.

Lord Grim hopped over the bush instead of leaping through so that he wouldn’t be heard.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella also jumped out, transforming into a spear.

Dragon Tooth!

A back attack against Flowing Cloud.

Whoosh! Tap!

Two sounds rang out simultatenously.

The sound effect that came with Dragon Tooth could not be eliminated by player control, but when Lord Grim let out the Dragon Tooth, the sound effect coincided with the Flowing Cloud’s footstep.

Was it a coincidence?

Or was it skill?

There was no time to analyze it. The two sounds were different, neither was covering up the other. But because of the mix between footstep and skill, Lu Hanwen reacted a beat slow.

Pu!

This sound was incomparably clear. Flowing Cloud’s back had been pierced through by Lord Grim’s spear.

Dragon Tooth inflicted a Stun. A follow-up combo didn’t need to be said. After being struck in the back, Flowing Cloud’s health rapidly fell.

“Lord Grim’s attack power must have been improved,” Li Yibo didn’t make this comment for nothing. Even though he couldn’t see the exact numbers, he was confident in what he had said.

Pan Lin didn’t follow up. Li Yibo had said these words before! Why would you repeat yourself? His equipment are all Level 80. It would be weird if his attack power didn’t improve, can’t you say anything meaningful?

“Lu Hanwen’s on the defensive!” Pan Lin described the state of the fight.

“Who would have thought Ye Xiu would do something like that? Could he have seen through Lu Hanwen’s intentions?” Li Yibo said. The two sides had started fighting. There was no way to switch perspectives to analyze Ye Xiu’s previous string of movements.

“It’s not going to be a one hit to death, is it…” The combo had only just started, and Pan Lin was worried. Although Lu Hanwen had been voted into All-Stars twice, which made it seem like he was better than Song Xiao, in terms of emotional control in a match, how could this young player compare to Song Xiao, the player nicknamed Mister Clutch?

Even Song Xiao had been crushed in a direct confrontation by Ye Xiu, now that Lu Hanwen had been attacked from the back, turning the situation around would probably be even more difficult, no?

In the blink of an eye, 15% of Flowing Cloud’s health had been taken away. A back attack increased the damage by a considerable 20%. Assassins had a class advancement skill “Art of Assassination” buff, which buffed that number to 40%. Unfortunately, class advancement and awakening skills could not be attached to a weapon.

“I hope Lu Hanwen can stay calm and search for opportunities to fight back,” Pan Lin continued.

Fast!

This was the impression Lu Hanwen got from the fight. From the first Dragon Tooth to now, he had lost 15% of his health. The unspecialized didn’t have class proficiency or armor proficiency, so their stats couldn’t compare to real class. Plus, their skills were low-level, so their damage wasn’t high. That was the objective opinion towards the unspecialized. But Flowing Cloud had just lost 15% of his health in an instant, low damage? Then use speed to make up for it! Lu Hanwen could tell how closely linked the attacks were. He didn’t know how an unspecialized could attack so fast. Did his attacks not have start-up and end animations? Was it his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was transforming again again and again?

Lu Hanwen couldn’t tell. He was trying his hardest, but Ye Xiu was more experienced. He kept adjusting his position, so Lord Grim was behind him.

It wasn’t Vanishing Step, but it was the same reason.

But in this case, he didn’t need to be troubled over his eyes blurring.

This energetic and hopeful youth could still find good points in this situation. Even if these good points had no value, it still made him feel gratified.

Now, he needed to find a way to break out of this predicament.

Lu Hanwen didn’t panic, although he wasn’t that calm either. He had courage though, the courage to try. Failure after failure, he would scratch his head and then try again!

Bang bang bang!

Flowing Cloud was using his sword too, but some of his attacks looked pretty poor from the lens of an expert. It was as if he was panicking without any thought behind his attacks, hoping to luck his way out.

“This sort of recklessness probably isn’t going to work on Ye Xiu, is it?” Li Yibo said.

You can do it!

Many people were cheering for Lu Hanwen, especially Blue Rain’s fans.

Although it looked like he was just randomly doing things, it wasn’t necessarily that there was no thought behind his attacks. Lu Hanwen was at the very least never doing the same thing twice. In other words, what looked brainless wasn’t actually brainless. He was testing different methods. He couldn’t think of any certain-success methods, so he could only gamble on the probable ones.

If one didn’t work, he would try again. If that didn’t work, then a different one. Another failure? Again…

Bang bang bang bang…

The “brainless” Lu Hanwen continued to struggle, sword light dancing randomly.

“Good child!” Huang Shaotian praised.

Yu Wenzhou chuckled, but didn’t say anything.

The percepting Blue Rain players could see it. Lu Hanwen’s attempts might have carried a lot of energy, but none of them succeeded. However, his constant attempts may have failed again and again, but they were taking a toll on Ye Xiu. And this effect, through Lu Hanwen’s brave tries, was slowly accumulating and expanding.

Ye Xiu was trying hard to get rid of it, but Huang Shaotian and Yu Wenzhou could see that he wasn’t able to completely eliminate it.

Having Lord Grim keep up this insanely fast offense was extremely difficult in itself. It required extraordinary precision. Lu Hanwen’s ineffective methods were converging into a whole, transforming into what could be an effective solution.

Chapter 1395 - There’s Still a Gap

Bang!

Flowing Cloud’s Silver weapon, the greatsword Flame Shadow, clashed against the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella with a dull sound.

Meteor Form!

The fastest of the powerful Level 75 skills was as quick as lightning, even when used by Flowing Cloud, who had a slow attack speed. Still, Lord Grim managed to parry the attack.

“Oh, what a shame. If Flowing Cloud were using a tachi or a lightsaber instead of a greatsword, that attack definitely would have hit,” Li Yibo sighed. But to his surprise, after this attack, although Lord Grim managed to parry it with his umbrella, his body was still pushed backward. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was actually jolted to the side.

“This…” Li Yibo was shocked. Even though Meteor Form was a Level 75 skill, this skill prioritized speed and involved the blade moving light and fast. In terms of attack priority, it wasn’t very strong. Lord Grim might not have high-level skills, but he should have still been able to parry it. But Lord Grim’s movement right now made it look like he hadn’t been able to withstand the impact of this attack at all.

Purposefully faking an opening?

Just as this thought flashed through Li Yibo’s mind, he saw Flowing Cloud unleash another Headwind Strike. The sword tip swung in a circle, and Lord Grim’s chest spurted blood.

“Beautiful!” Pan Lin was already shouting. Lu Hanwen finally broke through Ye Xiu’s crazy attacks and successfully counterattacked within the span of one move.

Sword attacks came out one after another, whistling through the air. Li Yibo watched a few attacks, and suddenly reached a realization.

“Even though Flowing Cloud doesn’t have a high attack speed, the greatsword gives his skills greater impact. That Meteor Form just now, if he’d been using a tachi or a lightsaber then Lord Grim might have been able to parry it, but because it’s a greatsword, his skill priority wasn’t high enough, so it was directly knocked aside,” said Li Yibo.

“This is a very good opportunity! Hopefully Lu Hanwen can take advantage of it,” Pan Lin shouted.

In an instant, the attacker and defender had switched roles. But Flowing Cloud’s combo had only reached the sixth attack, an Upwards Slash, when Lord Grim jumped into the air. He took the Upwards Slash and flew even higher, then raised the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella over his head. Pa pa pa, the umbrella folded and lengthened, the flaps beginning to hum and spin. Instantly, Lord Grim was pulled to the side.

Rising Dragon Slash!

Lu Hanwen hurriedly controlled Flowing Cloud to use an attack that would hit Lord Grim in the air, but he was too slow. The sword light flashed right by Lord Grim’s body. But Lu Hanwen barely had time to feel regret when the humming noise from Lord Grim’s umbrella suddenly stopped, and Lord Grim was already extending his right leg…

Eagle Stamp!

Bam bam bam bam.

Four consecutive kicks mercilessly fell upon Flowing Cloud’s body, and the priority of his Rising Dragon Slash had long since expired. He’d originally wanted to use a Falling Light Blade to get away, but he was still too slow, and Lord Grim stamped down upon him.

Shing! Lord Grim pulled out the tachi from his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, Falling Light Blade! Lu Hanwen hadn’t been fast enough to use it, but Ye Xiu now very leisurely used it. The tip of the sword pressed against Flowing Cloud’s throat, and they continued to fall.

The entire audience was stunned.

This reaction, this combo…

Lu Hanwen had only just broken through and begun a counterattack! The Happy fans live at the stadium hadn’t even had time to begin worrying about Ye Xiu when this guy recovered the situation. In comparison, Blue Rain’s players only made their fans worry more.

Bang…

Because of the Falling Light Blade, Flowing Cloud was stuck and couldn’t escape. Just like that, he was crushed against the ground, sending up a cloud of dust. Punisher, Earthquake Sword, Lord Grim used another flurry of ground attacks against the already-fallen Flowing Cloud. Lu Hanwen was once again at the disadvantage.

“Aw, Hanwen didn’t grasp it well!” Huang Shaotian sighed. He was also a Blade Master player, so he had quite a right to speak about the judgments made in that moment. He felt that that opportunity had been created extremely well, and if it had been him, there was no way he would let the opponent get away after only six attacks in a combo.

“His attack was a bit slow,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Mm… The equipment would have a bit of effect on that, but the greatsword should have been enough to deal with that situation. Hanwen didn’t have good control, the timing wasn’t accurate enough,” said Huang Shaotian.

“Or you could say, Ye Xiu’s timing was simply too accurate,” said Yu Wenzhou.

Huang Shaotian paused and realized, indeed, that was the case. The attack rhythm of the unspecialized Lord Grim was extremely rapid, and Ye Xiu’s controls were still so accurate. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was a greatsword Blade Master. It was hard enough for slow to keep up with fast rhythm, and because the opponent was Ye Xiu, the difficulty was only greater.

“Find another opportunity, kid! Don’t give that guy another chance to show off!” Huang Shaotian said, grinding his teeth.

Ah, too bad!

Lu Hanwen had only managed six attacks before Ye Xiu took back the initiative, so of course he was disappointed. He was positive, he was optimistic, but he wouldn’t forget scars instantly. As a pro player, he couldn’t afford to forget scars so easily, because every scar was a lesson, something that led to growth. Lu Hanwen’s personality didn’t help him forget scars; it allowed him to actively face his scars, never fleeing.

Maybe I could’ve done this or that instead, and it would’ve turned out better…

Lu Hanwen, just like this, grew up through these “ifs” and “maybes.” From mistakes and failures, he accumulated experience nonstop. But this kind of growth didn’t happen overnight; making a mistake once didn’t guarantee that it could immediately be avoided next time. After all, with Lu Hanwen’s current skill level, the mistakes he made wouldn’t be those particularly obvious kinds of mistakes. Sometimes, it would be a problem of small, inadvertent habits, and it would require a lot of time to pick them out and fix them.

Over these two years, Lu Hanwen’s growth had been clear to see. He had grown so much since he entered the Alliance, but the opponent in front of him now…

Lu Hanwen sighed deeply.

By the time he’d entered the Alliance, this God in front of him had already become a legend. He never would have thought that he’d have the chance to meet him in-game. That summer, Lu Hanwen had followed Blue Brook Guild to train in-game, and that summer he had accumulated numerous painful failures.

An extremely difficult opponent, possibly even more difficult than Senior Shaotian.

At that time, Lu Hanwen had already felt it, and that had only been in-game, where the two of them hadn’t had too many face-to-face exchanges. At first, he’d only heard from Blue River, the guild worker bringing him along, about how this person stirred up storms and reaped the profits. Afterwards, the exchanges in-game had only verified Blue River’s words. Lu Hanwen clearly remembered how even he, someone who had clearly come to support Blue Brook Guild and fight Lord Grim, had ultimately become that guy’s helper in the process of stealing the Boss.

He’s too good!

Lu Hanwen could only think this. In terms of skill and technique, he could still work hard to improve, but those things like strategic layout and maneuvering? It was like their captain Yu Wenzhou.

Lu Hanwen could could view Huang Shaotian as the goal he was chasing after, even the target that he wanted to surpass, but Captain Yu Wenzhou… forget it! How could he ever match that kind of guy? Lu Hanwen never believed that he had that kind of mind.

Their in-game struggles allowed Lu Hanwen to learn Ye Xiu’s skill in this area, and this alone was already breathtaking. And then Happy entered the Alliance, this legendary God returned to the professional stage, and then, 37 consecutive individual wins.

How could this kind of person be beaten?

Whether in terms of strategy or technique, he still just couldn’t compare?

Compared to Ye Xiu, Lu Hanwen could only draw this sad conclusion. He was brave, he was fearless, but he could recognize skill. Yet even when recognizing this huge gap between himself and Ye Xiu, he could still battle courageously.

There’s still a gap!

Lu Hanwen was very clear on this point. As for whether or not he could close this gap, Lu Hanwen didn’t think about it too hard. Victory wasn’t simply determined by such a gap. Lu Hanwen, as well as most of those who were raised in Blue Rain, held this belief in his heart: A gap isn’t scary. A gap doesn’t determine everything!

Because they had a captain called Yu Wenzhou. Because their captain had a weakness that was fatal for most pro players.

But Yu Wenzhou frequently used his situation to tell Blue Rain’s team members and Blue Rain’s trainees who dreamed of becoming pro players: A gap isn’t scary. What’s scary is giving up because of a gap.

“Even someone like me hasn’t given up – what reason do you have?”

Even now, Lu Hanwen still remembered the words that Yu Wenzhou had once said to the trainees at training camp. Although he was very young, he could understand this relatively straightforward point. And Yu Wenzhou’s experience of walking through Blue Rain’s training camp was even more of a real, living motivation for all of them.

In the training camp, they wouldn’t give up on their dreams; on the battlefield, they wouldn’t give up on victory.

They saw the gap, but they wouldn’t shrink from the gap.

Continue on like this!

Facing a gap, Lu Hanwen doubled down on his determination. Win or lose, he wouldn’t think about the outcome too much. He just knew that he had to put his full effort in to do everything he could.

These efforts weren’t meaningless, because this was the group arena. This was a team project. Whatever health and mana of Lord Grim’s that he could deplete, the next Blue Rain player would feel the benefits. This would become the basis of their victory.

So, fight hard!

“Lu Hanwen really has a great attitude. Even though Ye Xiu has completely suppressed him, he isn’t retreating or getting discouraged at all,” Li Yibo praised.

“He definitely has a bright future ahead of him,” Pan Lin said, moved.

Although the two praised him freely, the fact that they were talking about his future made it clear that right now, they didn’t think Lu Hanwen would win.

44%!

When Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud fell, this was how much health Lord Grim had left. Blue Rain had already sent up two players, but they had only knocked away a little more than half of Ye Xiu’s health.

“Happy is already in a two-point lead,” Pan Lin announced.

“1v2, and in the playoffs… Ye Xiu really deserves the title of King of Dueling this season. Just this kind of performance should be enough to silence the doubts that he only won so many consecutive victories because he hadn’t met strong opponents. Ye Xiu had the ability to achieve victory at lesser cost to himself, but he didn’t need to do so in individual battles,” said Li Yibo.

“But if he wants to 1v3 right now, it looks like it’ll be a bit difficult. Lord Grim lost a lot more mana than health,” said Pan Lin.

“There’s still 11%,” said Li Yibo, after checking.

“Uh… this time, at least, he shouldn’t be carrying mana-boosting equipment, right?” Pan Lin still clearly remembered the events of last year’s Challenger League.

Chapter 1396 - The Talkative Rhythm

Getting a useful amount of mana recovery wasn’t something that could be accomplished with just one or two pieces of equipment. With the current stats of equipment, as limited by the maximum equipment level, a set of many pieces of equipment was needed. Lord Grim right now had many pieces of Level 80 Silver equipment, whose stats weren’t visible, but for stats like mana or health recovery that had a visible effect over time, it could be directly seen whether or not they were present. On Lord Grim’s body now, there didn’t seem to be any such equipment.

And carrying an extra set of equipment into a match was something that hadn’t been done for a long time. A set of equipment increased weight, which became a large burden on this high-level professional stage, especially since this was now the highest-level playoffs competition.

But Li Yibo didn’t dare use common principles to draw conclusions.

Ye Xiu leading Team Happy to return to the professional scene, this was already so far out of everyone’s expectations. Anything contrary to common expectations was possible. Perhaps the weight added by this set of equipment could be erased somehow by Ye Xiu’s unspecialized Lord Grim?

Li Yibo didn’t say anything. Everyone was waiting to see.

Lu Hanwen came offstage and returned to Blue Rain’s player area.

In the first battle, Song Xiao had knocked away 30% of Lord Grim’s health. In the second battle, based on his onstage performance, it had seemed that Lu Hanwen was doing better, but in the end he had only taken down 26% of Lord Grim’s health, which was a little inferior to Song Xiao’s performance.

From this it could be seen that the scene onstage and the actual numbers were two different things. It had looked like Song Xiao was taking a beating throughout the entire match, and he had ultimately fallen in a one-wave rush. But during this process, he had relied on his tenacious defense to wear away Ye Xiu by a significant amount. On the other hand, Lu Hanwen’s aggressiveness was more apparent, and he’d actually found an opportunity to successfully counterattack, but ultimately, he hadn’t worn down Ye Xiu as much as Song Xiao had.

However, Blue Rain’s players didn’t fuss over this point.

“You played well,” said Captain Yu Wenzhou.

Lu Hanwen nodded, taking this simple sentence to heart. He knew that their captain never threw around these polite words just to comfort his teammates. Whether success or failure, victory or defeat, he would always be gentle and sincere. He wouldn’t criticize harshly, nor would he protect them excessively.

So, even though he hadn’t won, his performance was correct, was worthy of recognition. When he thought about this, Lu Hanwen’s courage was suddenly refilled, and he almost felt like charging back to play another match against Ye Xiu.

“Of course this was impossible. All Lu Hanwen could do was turn toward Blue Rain’s third player, who was already walking onstage, and holler: “Go Huang Shao!!”

Huang Shaotian heard it, but he didn’t turn around. He simply waved his right hand, his index and middle fingers raised in the shape of “V” for victory.

“Ah, Team Blue Rain is already sending out Huang Shaotian as their third player!” Pan Lin said.

In the five-player group arena of the playoffs, simply winning the final victory wasn’t enough. The key was to win more points by having more players left standing. So up until now, a common strategy was to place the ace player in the third or fourth spot, because if a victory was achieved then, that would guarantee two or three points. If, on the other hand, the ace player was fifth, then even if they won the final victory, they would only have one point. One point had much too small of an impact on the team round. The team competition was rarely fought until only one player remained.

“But the current situation can be seen as fairly unfavorable toward Blue Rain,” said Li Yibo. The fact that he spoke so carefully, even though Happy was so far in the lead after completing a 1v2, only showed how cautious he was now.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim still had 44% health, but only 11% mana remaining. This little mana definitely wasn’t enough to kill an opponent like Huang Shaotian, so what would Ye Xiu do? Did he bring equipment, or would he use Wish Prayer?

But even if he did have Wish Prayer, it would only be at Level 1. With Lord Grim’s Intelligence stat, he would probably only be able to recover around 10%. 21% mana, this still might not be enough to deal with Huang Shaotian, would it?

Still, Ye Xiu had already knocked down two opponents. At this point, everyone was already quite satisfied with his performance. For this round, any amount of Huang Shaotian’s health that he managed to knock away would be considered a victory.

Huang Shaotian came onstage and entered the player booth. His character loaded in, and very soon, the third battle of the group arena began.

“I’m surprised you’re up so soon. Fighting me, the pressure’s pretty high, huh?” The moment the match began, Ye Xiu began to talk in the channel. The audience members watched as Lord Grim lifted his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, surrounding himself with glowing blue light and chaotically-flying chanted runes. Indeed, he was using Wish Prayer. But ultimately, the mana-recovering equipment didn’t make an appearance. It appeared that in the rhythm of a playoffs match, even Ye Xiu couldn’t carry such a burden.

“I don’t have much mana left, it should be easy for you to pick up this wallet!” Ye Xiu continued to speak.

“How come you’re not talking? Since I saw it was you, I made extra sure to talk a bit more. What’s wrong with you, did you get muted? Or are you so scared that you’re all choked up?” Ye Xiu was still talking. But Ye Xiu was already on his third message sent, which everyone found strange. What was going on? Huang Shaotian wasn’t saying anything, while Ye Xiu was blathering on. Had these two switched bodies or something?

“Holy f*ck you’re so annoying!”

Just as everyone was growing confused, Huang Shaotian finally exploded.

“Who wants to talk to you? We’re enemies right now, enemies! Understand?”

“You were so arrogant just now, defeating two of our people! Right now, are you getting mana-recovery equipment or doing some Wish Prayer or whatever? Whatever dirty tricks you have, bring it!”

In an instant, Huang Shaotian had already sent three messages in reply. Indeed, his rhythm here had surpassed Ye Xiu’s.

“Oh, that’s more like it. If you don’t yell a few sentences, the whole atmosphere feels wrong,” said Ye Xiu.

“Screw your atmosphere! Even if you want to do anything you don’t have much mana left, so stop wasting time and hurry up and come out and die!”

“Be patient. As you wish, I’m recovering mana!” Ye Xiu said.

“As expected, dirty and shameless,” said Huang Shaotian.

“Hehe, you’re just jealous,” Ye Xiu replied.

The cast time for Wish Prayer was long, as was the skill’s duration, so Ye Xiu activated the skill at the very beginning. Huang Shaotian had essentially guessed that Ye Xiu would do this, so as soon as the match began, he had Troubling Rain fearlessly charge forward.

Even as the two people were playing seriously, they were also chatting away in the channel. The audience didn’t know what to think. This was the high-stakes playoffs! In the two previous battles, who was in the mood for chatting? As expected of the super-God Ye Xiu, what a calm attitude for him to be able to chat with Huang Shaotian like this…

As everyone quietly reflected, those two were still going at it. Even though Wish Prayer was slow, it was still faster than Troubling Rain making his way toward Lord Grim. Happy hadn’t chosen a small map for this group arena, perhaps for this reason exactly.

Finally, Wish Prayer was complete, and Lord Grim recovered 11% mana, putting him at 22%. With this one-fifth mana, Ye Xiu could probably casually wipe out two or three ordinary players. But against a pro player, then the outcome would depend. Huang Shaotian was a strong player, so almost no one had any hopes for Ye Xiu. Happy’s supporters just hoped that he could chip away as much of Troubling Rain’s health as he could. When Ye Xiu defeated Blue Rain’s first player Song Xiao, someone had actually shouted for a 1v5, but right now, there weren’t even people yelling for 1v3.

A yell for a 1v5 was immediately obvious as a joke, so no one would pay much attention upon hearing it. But to shout for a 1v3 right now? In theory, 22% mana was enough to defeat a character. But the opponent was Huang Shaotian! Shouting for a 1v3 now would just seem ignorant. The passionate fans now suddenly became very rational, and they didn’t pull out unsuitable cheers.

After finishing Wish Prayer, Ye Xiu didn’t control Lord Grim to walk directly forward. Like last round, he took the path to the right. This didn’t surprise anyone. When starting a match at a disadvantage, especially when the opponent was such a strong player, it made sense to use more tactical thinking.

While Troubling Rain continued to charge, Lord Grim circled around to the right, and soon began to head directly toward the center road. When the audience saw this, they realized, this was an exact repeat of last round! Once again, Ye Xiu wanted to sneak directly behind the opponent and ambush them!

As expected.

This time, Ye Xiu had accurately calculated Troubling Rain’s movement speed. When Lord Grim circled to the right and then cut back to the center, his rhythm was completely synced with Troubling Rain’s footsteps. Of course, it wasn’t so coincidental that he used the same bush as last time, but like before, there were plenty of places for Lord Grim to hide and wait to ambush.

Roll, Slide Kick, again with these low-movement skills. Soon, Lord Grim had made his way right next to the path.

However, the audience members could see from the live display screens that Huang Shaotian’s camera view was currently locked onto the exact spot where Lord Grim was hidden.

The televised broadcast was a bit slower, but soon enough, they also displayed a split-screen featuring Huang Shaotian’s camera view.

“Ah, Ye Xiu’s ambush position has been discovered!” Pan Lin shouted.

“Blue Rain has enough understanding of the map now. Plus, Ye Xiu is repeating his strategy of last battle,” said Li Yibo.

“Will he directly attack?” Pan Lin shouted. As soon as he said this, Troubling Rain halted in his steps.

Silence.

A sudden silence.

Earlier, Troubling Rain’s footsteps had been pounding on the ground, and Ye Xiu was using that sound to anticipate his movement position. If Lord Grim poked his head up now, he would certainly be seen by Huang Shaotian.

But Huang Shaotian suddenly had his Troubling Rain to stop…

He’s found me!

Ye Xiu immediately realized. Right now, he could pretty much judge where Troubling Rain’s final step had taken him, but it was possible Huang Shaotian was already controlling Troubling Rain to small hop, roll, slow walk, or other such silent movements.

If he wasn’t accurate in his judgment of position, then if he acted now, he would only lose the initiative. This wasn’t what Ye Xiu wanted.

After Ye Xiu instantly and clearly organized his thoughts, his actions were extremely decisive.

Slide Kick!

Lord Grim moved low to the ground, and then rolled twice to the right. Ye Xiu was actually controlling Lord Grim to turn and move away.

Chapter 1397 - Blue Rain’s God

Silence, complete silence.

Neither player knew what the other was doing. Even listening carefully, there wasn’t a whisper to hint at the other’s presence.

Only the omniscient audience knew that both of their characters were moving.

Lord Grim rolled twice after a Slide Kick, swiftly leaving his hiding spot for another. As for Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain? As Ye Xiu expected, he had merely slowed and rolled into a crouch, carefully approaching where Lord Grim had been hiding before.

Without any hesitation, sword light flashed, cutting through Lord Grim’s previous hiding place.

Whoosh!

Lord Grim had originally settled next to a meter high mud wall. Troubling Rain had attacked with a Piercing Form.

This skill had very high priority, and sword light shot into the mud wall, tearing through it like paper and exposing the upper half of the blade on this side.

A miss. Huang Shaotian made a swift judgement. He immediately had Troubling Rain tug his sword out, but Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had already flashed out from the other side, sending a Laser Rifle his way.

Lord Grim couldn’t get that far with a Slide Kick and it barely took Laser Rifle a blink to arrive. However, Huang Shaotian was facing his way, so he could clearly see Lord Grim’s actions. No matter what, he couldn’t leave his sword behind though, so Troubling Rain fell into a crouch.

Boom!

Half the Laser Rifle smacked into the wall, taking off a small chunk, and the other half shot directly over the wall, brushing right over Troubling Rain’s head.

Laser Rifle didn’t have the same force that Piercing Form did, and Lord Grim’s Laser Rifle was only rank one. Being able to take off a small chunk of the wall was good enough.

Fwip!

Troubling Rain had already yanked out his Silver weapon Ice Rain by now and was hiding behind the wall.

Slide Kick!

On Ye Xiu’s side, Lord Grim saw Troubling Rain crouch after he released the Laser Rifle, so he resolutely charged out. However, this was when the audience once again saw an important opportunity on the big screen.

On the screen showing Huang Shaotian’s screen, after Ice Rain was pulled out of the wall, his view immediately went towards the small hole that Ice Rain and made. The hole was too small, so it was impossible to see anything clearly, but the moving shadows were clear enough.

Apart from Troubling Rain, wasn’t the only other thing that can move Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim?

Lord Grim executed another silent Slide Kick, but this time, Huang Shaotian caught the movement through the tiny hole he had made.

They were very close. Huang Shaotian didn’t hesitate. Troubling Rain rolled to a stand at once, rolling right off the meter tall wall. Ice Rain’s deep blue sword light stabbed down towards the bottom of the wall, but on this side of the wall, Lord Grim, Slide Kicking over, had raised his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. The tip opened up, revealing the dark gun muzzle. As the deep blue sword light came down, light flashed from the muzzle and a bullet shot out.

Two strikes, a little out of synch. For a moment, it was impossible to figure out who’s attack had hit first. Blood splashed from Lord Grim’s shoulder, while a bullet found its home in Troubling Rain’s side as he rolled sideways across the wall.

Lord Grim’s Slide Kick had yet to finish, but that was when he suddenly stopped. He was already pressed to the ground, but after that strike, he became even more intimate with the ground.

Falling Blossom Form! A Level 75 knockdown skill.

It was an excellent follow up from Troubling Rain, but at this time, Troubling Rain had already been thrown into the air.

Floating Bullet! A Level 1 knock-up skill.

One was a Blade Master high-level skill, the other was a Spitfire novice skill. In that moment, the two executed a trade. In terms of damage, Falling Blossoms Form was far stronger than Floating Bullet, but the final result was that one character was flat on the ground while the other flew into the air. It seemed like neither could do anything to the other in that moment.

However, it only looked like that.

Because Lord Grim wasn’t Troubling Rain. He had ranged attacks.

Bang!

Lord Grim, still on the ground fired, another shot. From this perspective, the strike from Troubling Rain that pinned Lord Grim to the ground had given the latter to perfect angle to shoot from. If his Slide Kick had continued for another step or two, then it probably wouldn’t be nearly as comfortable.

Another bullet flew.

Troubling Rain hadn’t been tossed too high by the Floating Bullet. At this distance, for a ranged attack, it was far too close. At such a distance, the travel speed of their skills didn’t even matter anymore, even if the skill Lord Grim was using was the relatively slow Stun Bullet.

Huang Shaotian adjusted Troubling Rain’s position in the air, but in the end, he still failed to dodge this close ranged attack. His character froze in mid air, his adjustments futile. Three booms of cannonfire from down below, too close to dodge, not to mention that he was stunned right now, and three anti-tank missiles erupted against Troubling Rain one after the other. Flames and smoke bloomed in the sky, suspending Troubling Rain in mid air. By now, Lord Grim’s knockdown debuff had worn off and a chain of bullets erupted from the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s muzzle.

Gatling Gun! Ye Xiu attempted to continue juggling Troubling Rain in the air, and with Lord Grim back on his feet, he was free to chain even more attacks after closing in.

However, Ye Xiu’s opponent was Huang Shaotian.

His character bore the title of Sword Saint, and his strength was recognized as one of the top in Glory.

As soon as the stun effect of the Stun Bullet passed, Troubling Rain moved.

Falling Light Blade!

Troubling Rain made himself plummet from the sky and Ye Xiu hurriedly adjusted Lord Grim’s angle, bullets chasing after the Blade Master. Unfortunately, as soon as Troubling Rain readjusted his pose, he immediately switched to a different skill.

Guard!

Plink! Plink! Plink! Plink!

Silver weapon Ice Rain swept down horizontally in front of him, guarding against the hail of bullets. Bullets! It needn’t be said what precise mechanics this required. However, Ye Xiu wasn’t dead. After several bullets were blocked, he once again readjusted Lord Grim’s angle. With a shift in sword light, his attack glanced away from Ice Rain’s blade, but Ice Rain was already sweeping out, slicing a circle through the air.

Headwind Strike!

Troubling Rain’s body spun like a drill, parallel to the ground, his sword stabbing through the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s bullet rain, straight into Lord Grim.

Blood splattered, forming a circle in the air. Lord Grim’s Gatling Gun stopped.

“Spectacular! Absolutely spectacular! As expected of Huang Shaotian! As expected of the Sword Saint!” Pan Lin cheered without a care in the world.

From a mere wall between the two, to their exchange, in this short period of time, they had unleashed a flurry of changing skills. In the end, Huang Shaotian’s skilled bladework broke through Ye Xiu’s close ranged bullet rain with a Headwind Strike!

Last round, Lu Hanwen had broken through Ye Xiu’s offensive and successfully counterattacked using Headwind Strike. This time, Huang Shaotian had managed to overcome his passive stance and take the initiative with a Headwind Strike as well.

Then, Huang Shaotian displayed his array of Blade Master skills, more precise and experienced than Lu Hanwen.

Troubling Rain, still spinning in the air, didn’t even bother landing. His bent legs kicked out, pushing off the mud wall behind him.

Meteor Form!

This was the fastest trick in a Blade Master’s repertoire, and with the boost Troubling Rain gave himself from kicking off the wall, his body seemed to transform into a shooting star.

The deep blue sword light flashed at the front, drawing a blue streak that darted forth. Then, in the path that the blue light took, a dark red replaced it, blooming and spreading. It was the blood that this strike had drawn from Lord Grim.

“That’s damn cool!” Pan Lin yelled. The bloody line that the blue light had drawn, the scene of it erupting in the air, it was so cool he was almost crying. Secretly, he promised himself that he would go back and replay this moment in slow motion a hundred times after the match.

“As expected of Huang Shaotian!” Li Yibo could only find this one sentence to express himself and display his shock in that moment.

The timing, the use of the environment, the mechanics, all of it, the top of the top.

This was Glory’s top player.

And this match was a battle between two of the very top players of Glory.

After Ye Xiu successively took down two of Blue Rain’s players, the atmosphere finally peaked again.

Though those two matches had Song Xiao’s steady defense and Lu Hanwen’s never-give-up enthusiasm, Ye Xiu’s victory still seemed ever so matter of fact. It didn’t create the tense atmosphere one expected from a playoffs match at all. Or at least, it seemed that way.

Yet now, Ye Xiu versus Huang Shaotian, Lord Grim versus Troubling Rain, this fast paced offense, the beautiful and dazzling action. This! This was a true battle between gods!

However, currently, it was Huang Shaotian who was performing beautifully, who had the advantage. This match was on Happy’s grounds, so the atmosphere had its limits. It was Blue Rain’s fans on the away team spectator stands that were cheering wildly.

Changing Spring, Blue River, Chilling Nightfall, Flying Brushstroke, Bound Boat, etc etc.

These were those responsible for managing Blue Brook guild. In the last steps of the season, they had come with their team to the battlefield. This was the benefits of the job, but at the same time, they were the ones who were responsible for leading the Blue Rain fans in their cheering.

“Huang Shao!!!” Blue Rain’s fans bellowed under their lead. Changing Spring personally held the flag embroidered with Blue Rain’s team logo, waving it swiftly through the air above their heads.

Blue River next to him was also very excited. He wasn’t very loud, but his class ingame was the Blade Master. This was the class he loved, and Huang Shaotian was also his favorite player.

Right now, Huang Shaotian’s opponent was Ye Xiu, the Lord Grim that had so much interaction with them ingame, that had tormented them until they coughed blood so many times.

Blue Brook Guild’s members had been eager to see their team’s pro players beat the other up for them. In the regular season, Blue Rain had won twice against Happy, which was great, but unfortunately, Ye Xiu hadn’t lost a single round against them in the individual competition.

Then, in the playoffs, he destroyed two of their players upon coming up.

Changing Spring, Blue River and co had sat depressed in the stands. Could it be that not even their pro players could do anything about this guy?

But now, their core, their God Huang Shaotian was on the field. Although Blue Rain was two players down and Ye Xiu had wiped out two people in succession and was at a health disadvantage from the beginning of the third round, Huang Shaotian’s spectacular performance had them vibrating with excitement and pride.

See that!? That’s Blue Rain’s God. That’s our God! Blue River thought proudly.

Chapter 1398 - This Feeling

It had already been a year and a half since the new Level 75 skills had been implemented. They were no longer in the experimental stage of last season. By now, the pro players had already completely mastered these skills.

The four Level 75 Blade Master skills: Falling Blossom Form, Meteor Form, Piercing Form and Curving Wind Form had already become core skills in their offensives, influencing the entire system of their class playstyles.

The Level 75 mass update had given Happy many opportunities. For example, all those materials won in the battle for Level 75 Wild Bosses, using Orange equipment from the new update to close the gap in equipment quality between them and Excellent Era…

However, for Ye Xiu as an individual, the Level 75 mass update was a disadvantage.

Ye Xiu was known as the Glory Textbook, a master of all the classes. His experience was incomparably comprehensive. However, the update naturally would influence Glory’s metagame. In a time like this, if one wanted to continue being a master of all, then they would need to carry out far more and far deeper research on the new material than others.

Ye Xiu had never gone out of his way to achieve this. His title was from the accumulation of his experience and skill throughout all these years, naturally allowing him to achieve this title.This had to do with a lot of factors, including how he was a part of the very first batch of Glory players, how he was always at the head of the development of techniques and styles in Glory, and how Glory had stopped at Level 70 for so long.

The Level 75 update unbalanced this situation.

Although with Ye Xiu’s experience and knowledge he could easily come up with all sorts of ideas upon seeing the new Level 75 skills, he hadn’t looked into it like pro players would with their preferred class. So, when this mass update occurred, a textbook like Ye Xiu would need some time to patch for the update.

That unmatchable master of all would naturally crack a little during these patches.

However, this actually existed for all pro players. In building and refining their new combat system, each person would be met with all sorts of accidents and mistakes on the field.

This was because each person had to update their own Glory schema and this progress might not always be the same for each person, especially since players prioritized their own classes. As for the other classes, they merely had to observe the results of the research of others.

In the earliest times, all the experts would gather to discuss all manner of things and they would manage to bring a scientific air to the game. Since Ye Xiu had many creative and foundational ideas and achievements in all the classes, his Textbook title was set from then on.

However, as the Glory pro scene developed into the competitive scene it was now, there was less and less of a chance for these top players of Glory to sit down and simply chat about the update.

In these times, most people would prefer that what they managed to find out would never be known by any other, forever stay a secret weapon for the field.

Everything had become information that, if used well, could be the code needed to claim victory.

This competition had Glory’s technique development growing ever the fiercer and more varied.

In the past, all the experts would come together to discuss, select, experiment, and come up with rather unified answers.

However, everyone walked their own path now, and tested each other’s hypotheses in real battle. In the end, the techniques that resulted from this varied. As Blade Masters, Huang Shaotian’s use of the Level 75 skills would be different from Tiny herb’s Liu Xiaobie, or Samsara’s Du Ming, or 301 Degrees’ Gao Jie.

Everyone had their own ideas and techniques. A standardized path slowly ceased to exist.

Under these circumstances, it was naturally far harder to be a master of all classes.

Though Ye Xiu may not have aimed to and pursued such an advantage, under these circumstances, being a master of all classes didn’t yield as much benefit as it could’ve.

Especially with the Level 75 skills morphing the entire system of skills.

Now, what he was facing was a class that had experienced a relatively large shift in the paradigm due to a whole four Level 75 sword forms being added. in addition, his opponent was the one with the title of Sword Saint.

Even though Ye Xiu wouldn’t neglect to keep an eye on Huang Shaotian, wouldn’t be completely clueless as to how he used the four sword forms, but in the end, knowing was different from experiencing it firsthand.

“What do you think? This feeling’s not bad, huh?”

After Meteor Form brought Troubling Rain past Lord Grim, drawing forth a stream of blood, he immediately turned. Huang Shaotian even took the time to type out a sentence as he did this, and then, Immortal Guides the Way!

If this stab attack with a powerful blowback effect was used in a combo of attacks and blew its target too far, then it would naturally cause the combo to break. However, at this time, Troubling Rain had already used Meteor Form to switch positions with Lord Grim. This attack blew Lord Grim back, but soon enough, Lord Grim slammed into the meter tall mud wall. Instead of being sent out too far, the powerful blowback effect slammed Lord Grim into the wall, dealing another round of damage as well as a stun.

Troubling Rain’s offensive continued!

However, the audience was still pondering over what Huang Shaotian had meant by what he typed just now.

“This feeling? What feeling?” Pan Lin wondered aloud.

“Er…” Li Yibo wasn’t sure either.

Shockingly enough, something Huang Shaotian had typed had managed to elicit everyone’s deep contemplation. What a rare sight! Usually, everyone would be doing their utmost to try and ignore everything that the typed into the chat. However, in this match, against a strong opponent like Ye Xiu, Huang Shaotian didn’t have much energy to spare on flooding the chat. Under such a circumstance, everyone believed that Huang Shaotian would only spare energy on typing something truly meaningful, and not waste it on bullshit like usual.

What feeling?

The feeling of being suppressed? Huang Shaotian was probably mocking Ye Xiu, taking revenge for the two that were wiped out by Ye Xiu, right?

That was what most people thought. The only ones who could truly understand the essence of the trash talk that was compressed into this one sentence was Blue Rain and Happy’s players.

“He’s probably talking about the slight slip in rhythm due to an unfamiliarity with a new system, right?”

Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou and Happy’s Fang Rui practically gave the explanation for Huang Shaotian’s “this feeling” simultaneously.

“It’s definitely payback!” Fang Rui continued with certainty, “Because everyone got bullied pretty badly by Ye Xiu’s unspecialized.”

That’s right. In regards to having trouble adapting, how could the changes brought on by the Level 75 skills compare to Ye Xiu bringing back a completely discarded ancient playstyle?

To everyone, that was truly a completely unfamiliar system. No experience, no ideas, no one had Ye Xiu’s comprehensive knowledge either. For the unspecialized Lord Grim, from the original discovery, to officially engaging in the pro scene, it had been two years if your rounded up. However, this unfamiliarity had yet to disappear. No matter who was met with the unspecialized Lord Grim, they were overwhelmed.

Thirty-seven consecutive victories in the individual competitions, then wiping out two people at the very beginning of the playoffs. This intimidating record of Ye Xiu’s had at least some ties with the advantages that his unspecialized class brought him.

But now, Huang Shaotian was using this unfamiliarity against Ye Xiu, so his triumphant jeer was understandable.

Troubling Rain had Lord Grim completely pinned on that meter tall wall. What Ye Xiu had originally used to conceal himself was now exactly what was cutting off his escape. Sword light splattered blood onto the wall again and again, slowly dying it crimson.

Ye Xiu’s defeat of his two previous opponents meant that he had already beautifully accomplished his mission in this group arena. Even if he was killed by Huang Shaotian here, it wouldn’t matter. But, they weren’t satisfied with just that!

None of Happy’s members were satisfied. Maybe they were too greedy, but just seeing Ye Xiu on the field, they felt that he wouldn’t be defeated without doing something shocking.

Losing was normal, but being completely suppressed like Song Xiao, like Lu Hanwen? Even if the opponent was Huang Shaotian. It was completely incomprehensible to Happy’s members.

Impossible!

Happy’s players thought. This feeling in their hearts was far more intense than even the most loyal fans of Happy.

The support of the fans was sometimes completely irrational, blinded by emotions.

But they weren’t like that. Happy’s members were clear headed and yet this sharp feeling came from their utmost confidence in Ye Xiu. How could that guy, who started from nothing, who took an Internet cafe team through the vicious competition of the Challengers League into the cruelest stage of Glory, the playoffs, be suppressed like this? This was unacceptable!

“Stop pretending! Hurry up and use your ace!!” Fang Rui suddenly cupped his hands around his mouth and roared at the stage.

Ye Xiu couldn’t hear his voice. The two characters fighting in the projection wouldn’t be able to react at all. Instead, it was Blue Rain’s members on the other bench that heard him.

“Ace? What ace?” They wondered aloud, nervously watching the match.

“What ace does he have?” Chen Guo also asked nervously.

“How the hell would I know? Either way, he definitely has one!” Fang Rui replied.

“Definitely!” Su Mucheng determinedly expressed her support.

“Then hurry up!” Wei Chen slapped his leg.

“He’s going to use it soon, right?” Tang Rou said.

“What will it be?” The others all wondered in eager anticipation. Though they had no idea what it was, they were certain it existed. Happy’s members seemed almost like a bunch of cult members, all blindly believing.

“Die!!” On the field, Huang Shaotian once again sent a message. By now, Lord Grim only had 7 percent of his health left and this message was almost like a death sentence.

Whoosh!

But then, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella suddenly opened. The sword light that Troubling Rain had gathered, preparing to unleash the last strike to Formless Phantom Blade, hit the surface of the umbrella.

Not good!

Huang Shaotian felt his heart leap.

If it was just holding up a shield trying to endure the hit, he wouldn’t be so nervous, but the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was so damn massive when opened. Lord Grim was hidden behind it and Ye Xiu was definitely trying to play some sort of trick.

“Not saying the right thing at the right time is your greatest flaw!” Ye Xiu’s message popped up on the screen.

Did he leave an opening by typing that one word? Huang Shaotian subconsciously wondered. If Ye Xiu had the time to chat with him, then the other had probably already prepared his trick.

Experience, awareness, everything sparked and burned. Huang Shaotian resolutely canceled Formless Phantom Blade.

Sword’s Divine Judgement!

The Blade Master Awakening skill, activate!

Chapter 1399 - A Bite Back

Sword’s Divine Judgement, the Blade Master Awakening skill. The user’s attack speed and attack power would increase sharply, and at the moment of execution, sword qi would fly out in a fairly large 360 degree circle.

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain suddenly used this skill as a defensive option rather than an offensive option. The sword qi swept up the surrounding earth, an attack as defense, and without any blind spots either. When Ye Xiu had Lord Grim hid behind his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, Huang Shaotian had guessed that there was an eighty percent chance that Lord Grim would try to close the distance with a movement skill. But whether it was a frontal charge or a Shadow Clone Technique to flicker behind him, his Sword’s Divine Judgement covered all possible options. The instant he used this skill, Huang Shaotian fixed his gaze onto Lord Grim. He wanted to see what sort of tricks Ye Xiu had planned on using.

The sword qi circled around Troubling Rain as he turned slightly to the right. Huang Shaotian thought it was more likely that Ye Xiu would have Lord Grim use a Shadow Clone Technique or a Teleport to attack him directly from behind. This was a technique Ye Xiu frequently used. In critical moments, players would always subconsciously seek comfort and choose the option they were most familiar with.

But no…

The spectators could see better than Huang Shaotian. Lord Grim, who was hiding behind his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, didn’t see the seals required for a Shadow Clone Technique nor the flow of mana for a Teleport.

Lord Grim simply kept the umbrella in its shield form to protect against incoming strikes and then stepped to the right diagonally.

It was a very simple movement, one even a normal player or even someone didn’t know how to play Glory could do.

However, it caught Huang Shaotian off guard.

His Troubling Rain turned right. Lord Grim stepped to the right.

Both sides moved to the right from their perspective, and as a result, they happened to move in opposite directions.

In that instant, Lord Grim suddenly disappeared from Huang Shaotian’s view through just this simple step to the right.

Any player could get their character to take a step to the right, but they definitely wouldn’t be able to make the prediction and calculations required to achieve such a precise outcome.

The distance, the position, the angle, the timing, the speed, etc.

If any one part was slightly off, the vanishing effect would not happen.

It looked to be a simple step, but the skill required to pull it off was the accumulation of ten years of effort.

Huang Shaotian instantly recognized that the situation wasn’t good. Troubling Rain immediately snapped back to where Lord Grim had still been in his sights, but now, Lord Grim was directly in front of him.

Even though Troubling Rain had swung his sword as he turned around, Lord Grim’s attack came faster. After all, his movement skills were attack skills to begin with.

The blood that filled the air was in part due to his own fault.

Fuck!

Huang Shaotian was extremely annoyed. Despite his skill, he couldn’t figure out where he had gone wrong.

Was using Sword’s Divine Judgement a mistake?

Or was it because I was too confident Ye Xiu would move behind me?

These all seemed to be reasons, but also weren’t.

And this sort of feeling was common when playing against Ye Xiu. You had no idea where he saw through you.

It was truly the most disgusting feeling possible!

Could you at least let me know where I made a mistake?

Even Huang Shaotian felt helpless and discouraged at this feeling. It was terrible for one’s morale and fighting spirit.

“DON’T BE TOO ARROGANT!!!” Huang Shaotian typed in chat. Rather than trash talking his opponent, it was more of a reminder to himself. Many people knew that Huang Shaotian’s famed trash talk was often a way for him to focus.

Huang Shaotian had absolute confidence in winning. He had originally been crushing Ye Xiu in every area, yet Ye Xiu had been able to find an opening, a layered strike to both his technique and his mind. So at this moment, Huang Shaotian needed to remind himself not to become lax.

He needed to continue to focus and maintain his calm.

It was just a tiny bite back. All I need to do is keep steady.

Huang Shaotian’s message made him appear flustered and exasperated, but in reality, he was reminding himself to not be like that. He handled the situation very maturely and calmly. He successfully suppressed his urges, and this was the willpower of a true Assassin, of Glory’s number one opportunist.

Even Ye Xiu wanted to praise him.

At this moment, calmly resetting the fight was far more reliable than urgently trying to take back the upper hand. The opportunity Ye Xiu had obtained after machine-like calculations had been calmly dissolved by Huang Shaotian.

“I thought I’d be able to take away at least a quarter of your health. Forget it, it’s my loss!” Ye Xiu sighed in the chat.

“What do you mean ‘it’s my loss’! It was going to be your loss anyways!” Huang Shaotian grinded his teeth. He didn’t seem calm, but at this moment, his Silver weapon Ice Rain pierced through Lord Grim’s heart, striking the fatal blow.

16%.

That was the amount of damage Ye Xiu had been able to deal against Troubling Rain through his counterattack.

It was already quite an impressive number. The spectators felt a bit disappointed at Huang Shaotian. Quite a few people felt like Huang Shaotian’s performance was rather poor. If he had been a bit tougher and directly traded, he definitely wouldn’t have lost that much health.

But the true experts knew better. No one could have handled it better than Huang Shaotian did.

Ye Xiu’s final words weren’t meaningless trash talk. If Huang Shaotian had been a fierce and relentless warrior that traded, perhaps the amount of damage he would have taken would have been above Ye Xiu’s expected number.

The opponent was Ye Xiu!

Those who thought Huang Shaotian could have done better were all blabbering armchair experts.

As Ye Xiu came down from the stage, the stadium was filled with applause.

His Lord Grim had started off with 44% health, and in the end, he was only able to trade it for 20% of his opponent’s health. It looked like a loss, but Glory was never about pure numbers.

Ye Xiu hadn’t disappointed anyone. He had been suppressed to the point of suffocation, yet he had still been able to beautifully bare his fangs and fiercely bite his opponent back. If it had been anyone else facing Huang Shaotian’s dominating play, they would have most likely given up.

What’s more, Ye Xiu had already taken down two of the opposing side’s players. Huang Shaotian had been his third opponent.

Applause. His performance was absolutely deserving of such fervent applause.

That was what every Happy fan thought. As they clapped, they were afraid that they weren’t loud enough and continued to clap louder. As Ye Xiu walked back to his seat, the applause crescendoed, becoming louder and more resonant.

“Good work!” All of Happy’s players stood up and welcomed Ye Xiu.

“The rest is up to you guys,” Ye Xiu said.

“No pressure!” Fang Rui grinned. Happy’s second player appeared on the big screen.

Mo Fan, Deception.

“No pressure, right? Little Mo!” Fang Rui hollered. Mo Fan had already left. He didn’t even look back.

“It’s the playoffs, and he’s still gotta act like that!” Fang Rui mumbled.

Chen Guo wasn’t feeling as playful as Fang Rui.

Mo Fan. He was the first of Happy’s rookies to stand on the playoffs stage.

How will he perform?

Will he be nervous?

Will he make mistakes?

His first opponent is Huang Shaotian. Such a large step won’t be too challenging, right?

Chen Guo stared at Mo Fan’s back. Because Mo Fan practically never talked, she had no idea what he was thinking. She could only worry more.

“Happy’s second player is Mo Fan,” Pan Lin introduced, “He’s a very patient but also very explosive player.”

Patience came from Mo Fan’s incomparable patience in seeking opportunities. Explosiveness came from the mere three ways he knew how to attack.

“Speaking of which, Mo Fan and Huang Shaotian are similar players!” Li Yibo said.

“Uh… I guess so!” Pan Lin said, “There’s a clear difference between them though.”

“Yes. Both are adept at seeking opportunities. But in comparison, Mo Fan is better at waiting while Huang Shaotian is more proactive,” Li Yibo said.

“Of course, if the team competition came and all he did was wait, how could he do well?” Pan Lin said.

“In the end, they come from different places. The habits that Mo Fan acquired aren’t easily eliminated,” Li Yibo said.

Mo Fan’s background was no secret. Anyone who played fairly often in the Heavenly Domain knew of the infamous scrap picker, Deception.

“Then let’s see how this match will turn out!” Pan Lin said, showing his interest in the match.

The new match began.

Troubling Rain had 80% of his health. With Huang Shaotian’s identity as a God against a rookie, this 20% disadvantage was nothing.

The vast majority of people favored Huang Shaotian to win this match.

But Mo Fan couldn’t be underestimated. After all, he had the glory of defeating a God like Sun Xiang. No one could ignore the possibility of an upset.

A scrap picker from the game! And now he was standing on the playoffs stage. Many spectators had complicated feelings. No one had any good feelings towards scrap pickers. However, it had been awhile since they had seen someone walk out from the game and make it to the biggest stage in the pro scene.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun and all the other rookies had obviously started off in the game, but none of them had the fame that Deception had when he joined the pro scene.

Once a player’s fame reached a certain level, the Club guilds would immediately notice and recruit them. These players would most likely step onto the professional stage before being able to achieve much of a reputation in the game. But Mo Fan was different. He had ignored countless offers and accumulated enormous fame before being pulled into the pro scene by Ye Xiu.

A legendary scrap picker wasn’t a good reputation though. If not for this point, Mo Fan would have perhaps been an incomparably popular player, because he was someone who had truly been born from them. He would have been a symbol of the grassroots community!

Chapter 1400 - Mo Fan's Plan

The match officially began.

The map was chosen by Team Happy, so Mo Fan was no stranger to it. He immediately chose to take a roundabout route through the right path just like Ye Xiu did last match.

Huang Shaotian did the same as last match too, taking the direct path to the center. The only difference was that this time, Huang Shaotian wasn’t nearly as quiet as last match. As soon as his charactered loaded in, he began cheerfully chatting away with Mo Fan. Swoosh swoosh swoosh, words filled the screen, but not a single response came from Mo Fan, not even a punctuation mark or an emoji.

“Wow, so quiet! You’re not saying anything? Kid, don’t be nervous. Think of this as a normal match. Chatting is a way to relax!” Huang Shaotian was like a benevolent senior, kindly lecturing his junior. However, Troubling Rain’s Ice Rain told a different story as it glimmered from time to time. On the big screen, Huang Shaotian’s viewpoint was constantly shifting, carefully taking note of the sides of the road. No one had any doubts that the moment he met Mo Fan’s Deception, any sort of kindness would disappear.

After several of Happy’s matches, everyone had a certain understanding of the maps that Happy liked to choose.

The map layout was usually rather simple. There would be a wide path through the center, directly connecting the spawn points on both sides. It also served as a dividing line for the map. As for the left and right, or the east and west ends, consisted of two types of terrain. The north and sound usually had a certain symmetry to it.

For example, Huang Shaotian had chosen the middle path directly to the center, and there were numerous ambush spots along the road. Ye Xiu always took advantage of these spots, and Mo Fan took advantage of these as well.

“The two sides are getting close!” Pan Lin said. In these situations, a bird’s eye view of the map was usually displayed so that the viewers could see the two characters closing in.

“Which ambush spot is Mo Fan going to choose? To tell you the truth, I feel like Huang Shaotian has pretty much understood this map. No matter which side Mo Fan chooses to ambush from, it’s going to be difficult to surprise Huang Shaotian,” Pan Lin said.

“Yes, Huang Shaotian has chosen the central path like before, probably for this reason. He has a good understanding of the left and right side of this path. If he chose to directly fight from the east or west wings, there are probably gaps in his knowledge of the terrain there. As a result, it’s better to choose to fight in the places he’s most familiar with,” Li Yibo said..

“From what you’re saying, Mo Fan, who’s trying to ambush Huang Shaotian, is the one at the disadvantage?” Pan Lin said.

“If he insists on his current plans… but he should be aware of it. Even if he doesn’t have enough experience as a rooke, I believe the others in Happy would have reminded him,” Li Yibo said.

No one knew of Mo Fan’s personality other than those in Team Happy. From the matches, people could see that he didn’t like to talk, but how could they know that he was more quiet than even Zhou Zekai. It was like he was determined not to communicate.

As for what Li Yibo just said, Happy had obviously reminded him. Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, and so on all tried. In the end, they only got one word out of Mo Fan: Okay.

But as soon as Mo Fan started the match, he still chose to take a roundabout route and look for a spot to ambush Huang Shaotian. Happy’s Fang Rui had jumped to his feet when he saw it happen.

“This punk only knows how to act cold. He didn’t listen to anything I said!” Fang Rui shouted.

“He probably has his own plans!” Su Mucheng said. Mo Fan’s dislike for talking wasn’t fake, but he didn’t reject other people’s opinions. At first, he had been at heads with Ye Xiu, but his attitude towards him slowly changed. The others didn’t need to be said. If he didn’t want to listen to her and Fang Rui, then he would have just left instead of staying to listen. Even if all they got was an “Okay”, he definitely took their words seriously. Was Mo Fan the type of person who would elaborate?

“That punk, I wonder what he’s got in mind,” Fang Rui said.

The two sides grew nearer and nearer, but Mo Fan still hadn’t picked a spot yet.

“What’s wrong? Is Mo Fan not able to find the right spot because he’s nervous?” Pan Lin said.

“I feel like it should be because he’s not in a hurry to find a spot?” Li Yibo said, “It looks like he knows that his opponent has seen through the ambush spots along the central road, so he doesn’t plan on doing this sort of ambush.”

“Then why’d he bother taking the roundabout route?” Pan Lin said.

“He at least won’t get into a direct confrontation that way!” Li Yibo said.

“Okay… let’s keep watching,” Pan Lin said.

Five seconds later, Pan Lin suddenly thought of something: “Hey! Right, let’s take a look at Mo Fan’s equipment!”

“Of course!” Li Yibo slapped his forehead. He had forgotten too. Everyone had been completely absorbed into Ye Xiu’s pace that they forgot that Happy had upgraded their equipment. Quite a few of Lord Grim’s equipment had changed, what about Mo Fan’s Deception? When the characters loaded into the map, they forgot to check.

“Level 80!” The cameraman cut to a list of Deception’s equipment.

Silver equipment didn’t need to be clicked on. After all, the stats were all hidden. Only the name and the level were shown on the list.

The weapon was the most important, so it was listed first.

Ninja Blade: Sixteen Leaves.

“Sixteen Leaves, what a strange name!” Pan Lin mumbled. The Glory system automatically came up with the name for Silver equipment. Sometimes it would match the stats or the characteristics of the piece of equipment, and sometimes the meaning was more implicit and required more thought to understand the logic. All in all, the name didn’t mean much. However, it was unquestionably another piece of Level 80 equipment.

Deception’s Boots, Emblem, and Cape were also Level 80 equipment. He had fewer than Lord Grim, but it wasn’t anything strange for the core character to have more.

“Speaking of which, we haven’t really felt a difference in Lord Grim’s equipment!” Pan Lin suddenly thought. In the beginning, everyone wanted to know how much stronger Lord Grim would be with his set of Level 80 equipment, but after fighting three rounds, they didn’t see it giving Ye Xiu a huge advantage. Everyone felt like if Lord Grim didn’t have the upgraded equipment, the outcome still would have been similar.

“Lord Grim’s increase in attack power is very obvious. The minute changes in his other stats don’t seem as obvious right now. The bonus stats on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s various forms isn’t clear either. As for the added-on skills, we’ve so far seen the Laser Beam from the Gun form and the Priest’s Wish Prayer.

“Ye Xiu… isn’t holding back, is he?” Pan Lin suddenly had a feeling, “The high-level skills tacked onto the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella make up the core of how he does battle. I believe that Team Blue Rain definitely wants to find out which high-level skills the current Myriad Manifestations Umbrella has, but in the end, Ye Xiu’s only used two. There’s too many that haven’t been used. Blue Rain can only be wary of them in the team competition,” Pan Lin said.

“That’s right,” Li Yibo nodded his head, “Ye Xiu won beautifully in the group arena, but the information he gave out was rather small. I wonder how much Blue Rain’s gotten out of it. But the skills added onto the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s various forms must be a headache for them.”

“Ah! Right now, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain and Mo Fan’s Deception have passed by each other. Sure enough, Mo Fan decide to ambush Huang Shaotian,” Pan Lin returned to the match.

“Troubling Rain’s movements have become more careful. It looks like Huang Shaotian is very clear as to what possible ambush spots there are in his surroundings. Hm? Coach Li, if that’s the case, then when they first started, for a length of time, it wasn’t possible for him to ambushed, yet if I remember correctly, Huang Shaotian had still been carefully taking precautions!” Pan Lin suddenly became doubtful.

“That wasn’t taking precautions. That was him giving his teammates more information on the map!” Li Yibo said.

“Oh, so that’s what it was. It really makes you feel like they’re a very attentive team!” Pan Lin sighed.

“Yes,” Li Yibo said.

On the battlefield, Troubling Rain had rushed past Deception’s coordinates and continued to push forward. As for Deception, he began quietly heading to the edges of the central road as if he wanted to choose an ambush spot.

“Is he planning on acting out when Huang Shaotian retraces his steps after not finding anyone?” Pan Lin guessed.

Li Yibo shook his head but didn’t say anything. He had no idea what Mo Fan was planning.

“What exactly is this punk thinking?” Let alone Li Yibo, even Mo Fan’s teammates, who had a better understanding of Mo Fan, were wondering the same thing!

But then afterwards, Mo Fan still didn’t choose a spot. It was just that after moving along the edges of the central road, he began running towards Troubling Rain.

“Is he trying to do a back attack?” Pan Lin wondered.

The back was the biggest dead angle. It also came with bonus damage, so circling around to the back to mount a sneak attack was the most advantageous option. But because of this, pro player would always be on guard for their rear, especially in 1v1s without any teammates to rely on and when no information was known on the opponent’s position.

“I hope he’s not just planning on sneaking up from behind… Huang Shaotian is on guard against it,” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes, when he looks left and right, he can also see behind him out of the corner of his eye. Even though he’s not looking carefully, it’s more than enough as a precaution against back attacks,” Fang Rui said.

Hearing their worries, Chen Guo suddenly became nervous. Seeing Deception catching up to Troubling Rain, she really wanted to jump over there and yell in his ears “Be careful! Don’t go up like that.”

“You punk, where are you hiding? You’re so patient! You’re still not going to show up?” Huang Shaotian said.

“It’s been so long already. Do you want a yellow card? Referee, give him a yellow card!” Huang Shaotian continued to type.

The yellow card immediately appeared. To Huang Shaotian.

“Uh…” Huang Shaotian didn’t retort and defend himself. He already knew why he had been given the yellow card.

This was the playoffs, not the All Stars. Even if the referee knew that he was just joking around, trying to lead the referee to make a call was absolutely an offense. As long as it was attempted, the player would definitely be penalized.

“Look, I ate a yellow card for you. Why don’t you hurry up and come out?” Huang Shaotian didn’t dare mention the referee again and started typing madly towards Mo Fan.

Chapter 1401 - Blind Spot Operation

Instantly, another textwall.

The referee’s eyes were hurting. To be honest, for Glory matches, there wasn’t much that the referee had to supervise. After so many years, the main reason why people got carded was for trash or otherwise inappropriate talk. It could only be imagined how much of a burden a Huang Shaotian match was on the referee. The opponent could ignore his screens of text, but the referee couldn’t!

All messages sent during a match were recorded, and the Alliance would review them after the match. If they discovered something inappropriate that the referee had failed to catch at the time, then that would be the fault of the referee.

Against Ye Xiu last round, Huang Shaotian’s trash talk was unusually scarce, which the referee greatly appreciated. But this round against a rookie, Huang Shaotian’s chatterbox status was on full display. Especially since Huang Shaotian had already earned a yellow card, the referee was quite motivated to find another fault so that he could give a second yellow card and directly end the pain to his eyes.

But, there wasn’t anything…

If it were really that easy to find a flaw in Huang Shaotian’s trash talk, then it wouldn’t be so hated. Instead, the various teams would love watching the phenomenon.

No one would need to do anything, he’d just talk himself off the stage. How fortunate would that be?

But right now, everyone could only quietly mourn for Happy’s rookie.

This sky full of trash talk, there was no way he’d experienced it before, right? What kind of mood was he in right now? Is he already irritated beyond belief?

Pan Lin also wanted to find something interesting in Huang Shaotian’s trash talk to talk about, but Huang Shaotian’s trash talk always emphasized quantity over quality. He muddled his way through half a screen without finding a single thing worth reading, and eventually the broadcast just maximized the chat window to let the audience experience it for themselves.

The two characters were still moving on the map, yet the televised broadcast was showing the nonstop jumping of text messages.

“As expected of Huang Shaotian!” The audience understood that this chat channel close-up was very rare to see outside of a Huang Shaotian match!

“Mo Fan’s Deception still hasn’t made a move, he’s still trailing along. He wouldn’t be paying so much attention to the chat that he forgot about the battle, would he?” Pan Lin chuckled.

“Probably not…?” Li Yibo was a bit hesitant. The pro players all knew Huang Shaotian’s style, but Mo Fan was a rookie. If he couldn’t adjust to this, then maybe he really would become distracted.

Finally, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain arrived at Happy’s spawn point. Of course, he didn’t discover Deception over here, and Deception still did not reveal himself.

“You want to test my patience? Then let me tell you, you’re done for,” said Huang Shaotian.

“I’m a patience expert, I can watch all of my teammates slaughtered one by one and still endure without moving!”

“Damn you, is that example worth bragging about? You’re completely missing the point!” The crowd immediately started discussing this. This sentence didn’t demonstrate how frightening his patience was, it just became another example of why his trash talk was of insufficient quality.

“The longer you make me endure, the scarier I become,” Huang Shaotian continued.

“So in other words, if you still want that sliver of a chance at victory, then if you come out now, it might not be too late.”

“You don’t have much time, I’ll give you 12 seconds.”

“Why 12 seconds? Because this is the limit of my patience right now. It’s very precise, isn’t it?”

“The timer begins now, don’t lose count.”

Message after message after message…

But a few audience members really couldn’t help but look at the clock and begin to count the so-called twelve seconds.

Was Mo Fan counting?

No one knew, but indeed, he wasn’t just sitting around. Deception had arrived at the revival point and quietly hidden in a corner.

Ninjutsu: Disappearing Body Technique!

Mo Fan’s Deception activated this skill. Climbing, hanging upside down, he used all sorts of movements he couldn’t normally use to quietly advance, swiftly approaching Troubling Rain.

“Is he making his move?” Pan Lin shouted. “But it hasn’t been twelve seconds yet!”

Li Yibo gave him a look. Twelve seconds, you took that seriously?

“Huang Shaotian is still studying the area around here. Is he still sending a report to his teammates?” Pan Lin said.

“So that’s what it is! Mo Fan’s about to attack!” Li Yibo suddenly reacted.

“What?” Pan Lin was caught off-guard.

“Blue Rain has already walked this path three times, so they already have an understanding of the ambush points to the left and right. But right here is Happy’s spawn point. Up until now no Blue Rain player’s character has arrived here, and Ye Xiu immediately took the roundabout path in all three of his rounds. Blue Rain hasn’t gotten the chance to actually study what this area is like walking straight forward!” Li Yibo called out excitedly. As he watched Deception’s movements on screen, he grew more and more confident.

That’s right, this was definitely it!

The path that Deception used Disappearing Body Technique to take was the path that Ye Xiu hadn’t taken in any of his three battles. Huang Shaotian shouldn’t have an impression of this area in his mind.

In other words, this was a blind spot in Blue Rain’s understanding of the ambush points on this map! And Mo Fan would definitely attack immediately, because with Huang Shaotian’s experience, even if he didn’t have prior knowledge of this area, if he studied it long enough, he would quickly discover that there was an ambush point here.

“Is that so?” As soon as Pan Lin spoke, Deception was already flashing forward.

The status from Disappearing Body Technique was still active, and unlike the Thief’s Stealth skill, it wouldn’t lower the movement speed of the character. In fact, under this condition, the Ninja could use any skill, and whether it was movement or attack, it would be silent.

Mo Fan timed it precisely, and Deception silently rushed out, silently approached, silently began forming seals.

Huang Shaotian wasn’t an actual God. He didn’t see it, and there was no sound, so he truly had no idea that this attack was coming. He was constantly rotating his camera view left and right to observe the surroundings, but when his view discovered Deception’s silhouette, the attack was already beginning.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh whoosh…

Numerous Deceptions seemed to simultaneously leap into his view.

Ninjutsu: Shadow Dance!

Mo Fan started off with a powerful skill. Instantly, dozens of shadow clones surrounded Troubling Rain.

The attack began.

“A cheap trick!” Huang Shaotian shouted, without panicking. Troubling Rain’s sword flashed with light, warding off the encirclement’s attack. He himself, meanwhile, was calmly observing all of the Deceptions before him, and he swiftly determined which Deception was the heart of the Shadow Dance.

This one!

Huang Shaotian zeroed in on his target. The light of Troubling Rain’s sword condensed in an instant, and pierced forward.

Puff!

The Deception burst into a cloud of smoke.

“Pretty fast reactions!” Huang Shaotian shouted. He was extremely confident in his judgment, and he believed that he hadn’t seen incorrectly. He hadn’t been able to break the skill only because Mo Fan’s reaction and controls weren’t slow either. Before Troubling Rain’s attack landed, he had already switched the heart of Shadow Dance to another Deception.

But because Troubling Rain had approached so close, the Shadow Dance attack was greatly disrupted.

Puff puff puff!

In an instant, Troubling Rain broke another three shadow clones.

“Watch me!” Huang Shaotian’s messages were still nonstop. From this, it could clearly be seen just how different his showdown against Ye Xiu last round was. At the same time, it caused people to once again ponder the tragic, age-old question: if this guy could always be that focused, instead of getting distracted by typing and chatting, then just how frightening would he be?

But those who would think this clearly didn’t understand that for Huang Shaotian, sometimes, his chatting and typing was his way of focusing all of his attention on the match.

Shadow Steps!

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain activated a skill that was somewhat similar to Shadow Dance.

Instantly, seven false images of Troubling Rain spread out. Unlike shadow clones, the images created by Shadow Steps were truly false. They couldn’t be attacked, nor could they take damage. From the explanation of the skill, these were afterimages left behind by the high movement speed of the Blade Master combined with the light of his blade.

So, unlike Shadow Dance, Shadow Steps needed constant controls to maintain the images after they appeared. On the other hand, if no more controls were given after using Shadow Dance, the clones would simply remain inactive, but they wouldn’t disappear. Furthermore, even if one didn’t control them individually, they could be given to the system to be automatically controlled.

The Shadow Steps needed controls, but controls meant that as long as the skill’s duration hadn’t run out, it could change at any time.

Seven Troubling Rains spread out, but in the blink of an eye, they became four, and then five again.

The battlefield was a blurry mess. The referee, who had already gotten dizzy just from Huang Shaotian’s messages, now felt like he wanted to throw up.

This was really so difficult!

A few members of the audience also pulled out eyedrops.

Just like this, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain, in the midst of these illusory afterimages, defeated Deception’s clones one after another.

“So strong!” Pan Lin was shocked. The player who had silently ambushed his opponent would just be broken and taken care of like this?

“There’s only two left now, so which is it?” Huang Shaotian laughed. His Shadow Steps had ended, and there were now only two Deceptions left on the field.

Whoosh!

As soon as his message sent, one vanished by itself. The Shadow Dance skill had run out of time as well.

The audience once again looked at the health bars of both sides. Deception’s heart in the Shadow Dance had never been caught, so he hadn’t taken any damage. Troubling Rain had taken a bit of damage, but only 4%. For a successful ambush with the powerful Shadow Dance move to only deal this much damage, it was somewhat depressing.

“Tell me, what use was there in ambushing me?” Huang Shaotian shouted. Troubling Rain charged forward!

Whoosh!

Another cloud of smoke.

What?

Huang Shaotian was stunned. This was also a shadow clone? He actually hadn’t discovered this or expected this at all.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Deception flew up from the ground. The flash of a ninjato was never particularly bright, but its sharpness didn’t lose to any weapon.

Blood flew from Troubling Rain’s neck.

4%!

The Shadow Dance that he’d worked so hard for had only taken 4% of Troubling Rain’s health, but now, an Underground Tunneling Technique attack was successful, directly taking 4%.

When Mo Fan exploded, he didn’t just use one attack. His flurry rush was generally at least five combos long.

The attack was continuing!

Chapter 1402 - Fight on the Tree

A sneak attack via Underground Tunneling Technique was a common technique of Mo Fan’s. In the battle prep against Happy, Blue Rain wouldn’t neglect him just because he was a rookie. They made sure to look deep into each of Happy’s players, including Luo Ji, who only fought in the last few rounds, and their first captain as well as the first guild leader of Blue Brook Guild, Wei Chen.

However, knowing was one thing, actually being able to use this knowledge on the field was another.

If knowing could solve all problems, then that would make competitions far too easy.

Mo Fan had used Shadow Dance to open up this exchange, and the mass of shadow clones distracted Huang Shaotian. This was a very clever opening move and Huang Shaotian had been completely tricked by it. He hadn’t thought for a moment that this SHadow Dance was a mere distraction.

By the time the strike from the Underground Tunneling Technique slashed at Troubling Rain’s throat, it was too late for Huang Shaotian to react.

Bird Fall, Flame Cut, Neck Bind Technique, Flickering Charge!

Four consecutive Ninja skills, the first three flawlessly executed in midair, the speed making the audience watch on in awe. By the time applause rose from the audience, Deception had already completed all four skills. Their eyes could barely keep up with the movements and Troubling Rain was completely helpless against it, all the skills hitting solidly.

Who would spare a thought for caring about how Deception was a scrap-picker now? The audience roared their excitement; this was a rookie! And right now, God Huang Shaotian was completely helpless against this rookie! What skill!

After Flickering Charge, there was a slight pause in the offensive. It seemed that Mo Fan had hesitated for a moment, but upon seeing Troubling Rain still struggling to orient himself, he immediately charged forwards with another attack.

Ninja Arts: Cicada Shell Double Slash!

Deception chopped both hands towards Troubling Rain’s staggering form, but didn’t expect a sword to flash out at him.

Sword light swept right into Mo Fan’s line of sight.

Hit!

Blood splashed out and this time it was Mo Fan who didn’t have time to dodge. Troubling Rain was still staggering, trying to orient himself after those attacks. He might not be steady, but his sword was. What terrifying adaptability and control!

At the same time, Huang Shaotian’s typing was also very steady.

“Heh, you’re stretching yourself a little too thin.” Huang Shaotian said even as Troubling Rain continued to steady himself and unleashed another attack.

Blade Storm!

Even under the current circumstances, the skill Huang Shaotian had managed to unleash was the powerful Level 65 Blade Master skill. The relentless stabs had blades sweep at Deception like a storm.

Substitution Technique!

Mo Fan resolutely gave up on resisting, using an escape skill.

The straw man that was substituted in was instantly torn asunder by Blade Storm. Mo Fan didn’t dare have the escaping Deception launch another attack, aiming for a large tree behind him and leaping up into it with a few swings on his ninjato, looking down at Troubling Rain from up high.

Has he seen through me? That was what Mo Fan was thinking to himself then.

“Blue Rain’s seen through it,” Ye Xiu, on the bench, had already come to this conclusion.

You’re stretching yourself a little too thin.

The audience probably hadn’t thought anything of Huang Shaotian’s words. Even the commentators were discussing the moment of hesitation after Flickering Charge and before Cicada Shell Double Slash.

“He shouldn’t have hesitated!” Li Yibo said.

“He is a rookie, after all. He lacks experience!” Pan Lin sighed.

The two had noticed Mo Fan’s hesitation, but didn’t know the true reason behind it.

Mo Fan’s hesitation was because he knew that he couldn’t execute the following attack flawlessly. After that Flickering Charge, he could feel his focus slipping. It was just that it seemed like a great chance, so after hesitating for a moment, he went for it.

However, as reality had proved, Huang Shaotian wasn’t an easy opponent to take on when he wasn’t at his peak state. Even with his character stumbling around for balance, the Sword Draw Troubling Rain had used had still accurately struck Deception.

So, Mo Fan gave up trying. No matter what Huang Shaotian followed up with, he already had his Substitution Technique at the ready, fleeing first and thinking later.

“Huh?” Seeing Mo Fan’s Deception dart up a tree, Pan Lin and Li Yibo were completely befuddled.

“That was a great chance for an attack! How come he didn’t take it?” Li Yibo mumbled. This Happy! He could never manage to figure out what they were thinking! What was this strategy now? Just now, after he had used the Substitution Technique to escape Blades Storm, Deception had landed in a prime position to counterattack! Yet Mo Fan had Deception run all the way up a tree to escape. Was this Substitution Technique really just for an escape?

“Mo Fan’s being very cautious!” Pan Lin tried to be optimistic about it.

“Yeah…” Li Yibo agreed noncommittally. This was one explanation, but his intuition told him that there was another reason behind it.

Blade Storm ended up hitting a straw substitute and Huang Shaotian naturally cancelled the skill as soon as he could. He looked around, immediately finding Deception.

“You climbed so high? Trying to capitalize on the fact that I can’t climb trees?” Huang Shaotian sent a sneer emote and Troubling Rain charged.

Blade Masters didn’t have the ability to climb with ninjatos like Ninjas. Troubling Rain darted to the base of the tree, sword light flashing, aimed right at the trunk of the tree.

It was all normal attacks, but slice, slash, cut, swipe, the sword light slid around the trunk and instantly carved out a path in the bark. Then, over and over again, sword light cut into the bark, splintering it and sending wood shavings everywhere.

“Is Huang Shaotian trying to cut the tree down?” Pan Lin stared in shock.

“So fast!” Li Yibo exclaimed over Huang Shaotian’s mechanics. In just a few moments, the cut around the trunk had deepened greatly. Mo Fan didn’t even manage to react before Troubling Rain suddenly jumped back twice, Ice Rain hanging to his left before being swung out.

Sword Draw!

Dark blue sword light arced out beautifully, but soon enough, the middle of the arc dimed and died. This part of the arc had sunk into the deep cut on the tree.

Rumble!

This Sword Draw had the tree finally succumbing to it’s injuries and gravity, splintering and swaying before tilting to one side.

It really did get cut down!

Everyone stared in shock. That tree wasn’t thin at all. A character definitely wouldn’t be able to put their arms all the way around it. Yet, in these few short moments, Huang Shaotian had gotten Troubling Rain to cut it down.

“Huang Shao so fierce!!!” On the spectator stands, Blue Brook guild’s leaders led the fans into cheering.

Huang Shaotian didn’t stop to gloat, retracting his sword quickly. He didn’t even bother to pose before he leaped onto the tree and ran up the angle at which the tree was still falling.

Triple Slash!

Sword light opened up his path, and with the tree slowly falling and the angle becoming lower and lower, Troubling Rain was swiftly heading towards Deception, who was steadily losing his height advantage.

Shuriken!

Mo Fan was no sitting duck either, sending out a shuriken under the cover of the leaves.

Clink!

Triple Slash just so happened to collide with this Shuriken, knocking it aside. Troubling Rain’s speed didn’t slow in the slightest.

On this steadily falling tree, both characters moved rapidly.

Troubling Rain was charging forwards and Deception was retreating.

The tilting tree had created a lot more cover for the characters.

Hundred Streams!

Troubling Rain continued to charge, when suddenly several streams of water erupted from a nearby patch of leaves.

Rising Dragon Slash!

Huang Shaotian’s reaction speed was nothing to laugh at. Troubling Rain ascended into the sky. The streams arrived, rising up and weaving into a prison, yet Troubling Rain had used this Rising Dragon Slash to escape from above, clearing the attack in a jump.

Falling Light Blade!

Then, Troubling Rain once again plummeted onto the tree. Huang Shaotian had already caught sight of Deception.

Collapsing Mountain!

Troubling Rain leaped up again upon touching the ground, slashing down towards Deception.

Deception hurriedly jumped away.

This Huang Shaotian, he’d somehow managed to twist in the air, changing Collapsing Mountain’s angle and sending his Collapsing Mountain after Deception.

Mo Fan had no choice but to have Deception parry, bringing his ninjato up to meet the sword.

Clank!

The weapons clashed. Collapsing Mountain had very high priority. Just raising a ninjato to meet it wouldn’t be able to deal with it at all. Deception spat blood. This represented that he had taken damage from the strike and he fell back against the tree from the force, but with a quick roll, he was back on his feet.

The two danced their deadly dance of skills along the fallen tree, their skilled mechanics sending the stadium into awe.

But that was when, in the chat, two shocked words popped up under Huang Shaotian’s name, “Holy crap!!!!!!”

What?

Everyone blinked in confusion for a moment before they saw Troubling Rain disappear into the foliage of the tree with rustle.

Boom!

Soon after, the tree finally crashed fully against the ground, everything that was squashed under the tree roared with rage, dust and rocks flying up and engulfing the area like the aftermath of an explosion.

The entire scene was plunged into a cloud of dust.

Where’d Huang Shaotian go? Where was Troubling Rain? What happened?

Everyone noticed then, with shock, that Troubling Rain’s health had plummeted in that moment by 50 percent. In addition to Deception’s previous attacks, he only had 10 percent remaining, already at red blood.

It was lucky it was a TV broadcast, allowing them to replay a close up of what just happened. Then, everyone realized, that after Troubling Rain’s Collapsing Mountain, he had stepped down to land, only to miss the tree and fall through the foliage. He had landed on the ground first, and then, the tree landed on him…

The replay was wound back a little first and then everyone realized what had actually happened.

Before, it was Deception at that position, so Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain attacked. However, back then, Deception had stabbed his ninjato horizontally into the tree and stood on his ninjato. When he jumped away, dodging, he had taking his ninjato. The area he was perched on, hidden by the leaves, was actually devoid of branches, so there wasn’t actually anything to land on there.

God Huang Shaotian had ended up falling for such a simple trap, causing his character to misstep in battle.

Even the experienced and skilled commentator pair Pan Lin and Li Yibo were lost for words in the face of this scene.

Jouissance: And thus this is why we call Huang Shaotian “Master of Fighting Trees” (战树大师 zhàn shù dà shī), which has the same pronunciation as Master Tactician in Chinese (战术大师) and only one character difference, except instead of “fighting tactics”, it’s “fighting trees”

Chapter 1403 - Disparity

The battlefield was silent. The stadium was silent. The computers and TVs tuning into the match were silent.

The Glory competitive scene had ten years of history. It was quite common for players to damage the surrounding terrain in certain special maps, but it was the first time anyone had ever seen someone personally chop down a tree and squish their character underneath it like Huang Shaotian did.

He truly is Huang Shaotian! The viewers thought to themselves. It was the playoffs, yet he still had the guts to pull off such a hilarious scene.

At the stadium, after a moment of stunned silence, applause erupted. Another high point of the group arena had unexpectedly come. It was just that this high point came with lots of laughter too.

Clap clap clap clap clap.

Ha ha ha ha ha!

“Huang Shao! Huang Shao!” The Happy fans imitated what the Blue Rain fans shouted when Huang Shaotian executed a brilliant play. They shouted these words again and again in rhythm. This sort of opponent was just too likeable. Happy’s fans didn’t mind clapping and cheering for him.

The pro players on both teams looked at one another. Whether it was Blue Rain or Happy, neither team had expected such a play. Even the experienced experts had only realized what had happened from the replay.

“Nice job, Mo Fan!” A smile spread across Chen Guo’s face.

The others experts such as Ye Xiu were all sweating. They put themselves in Huang Shaotian’s shoes and felt like such a scene could have happened to any of them.

“Huang Shaotian’s mistake really… uh… makes a deep impression!” Pan Lin took awhile to organize his thoughts before finally saying these words. The viewers watching the match heard the comment and started laughing. Yeah! Apart from “deep impression”, what else could be a better description?

“How surprising!” Not to be outdone, Li Yibo immediately followed with another fitting reaction.

“Troubling Rain still has 10% of his health left,” Pan Lin didn’t forget that the match was still underway.

“Deception has…” Li Yibo checked Deception’s health and choked.

When the two exchanged blows, Mo Fan had opened with a sneak attack, and the following combo brought away 20% of Troubling Rain’s health. Then, Huang Shaotian chased after him aggressively before finally being squashed by a tree.

During this chase, Huang Shaotian hadn’t been able to deal continuous steady damage, taking away only 6% of Deception’s health.

94%.

Deception had 94% of his health left.

A 6% vs a 70% trade.

A rookie against the Sword Saint, Huang Shaotian.

If they hadn’t seen it personally, who would believe it? In terms of numbers, Huang Shaotian had been crushed by Mo Fan. Only those who actually watched the match would know how Huang Shaotian had been wronged.

A tree fell, and 50% of his health disappeared…

Pan Lin’s and Li Yibo’s update on their health bars brought everyone back to the match.

Dust filled the air from where the tree fell, and the tree leaves quivered from the violent crash to the ground.

As for the two characters?

Everyone hastily looked for them.

The camera quickly locked onto the two characters.

Troubling Rain’s blood-drenched body showed just how much damage he took from the falling tree.

Troubling Rain struggled unable to move. He was clearly stuck under the tree. Swordlight flickered as Troubling Rain twisted his body and cut behind him.

Rumble!

The tree trunk on top of him suddenly lurched, but Troubling Rain had already rolled away.

The viewers took note of the chat. Was Huang Shaotian going to say something?

Actually paying attention to Huang Shaotian’s trash talk was truly a rare scene.

But Huang Shaotian disappointed them. When everyone was annoyed, he wouldn’t stop talking. When everyone wanted him to talk, he shut his mouth.

Fine! The viewers understood. They may be laughing at how Huang Shaotian lost 50% of his health, but for Huang Shaotian, he was probably so furious he was going crazy, no? This was even more of a tragedy for the entire Blue Rain. Their ace player had inexplicably lost 50% of his health. This group arena was looking more and more unfavorable for them.

Troubling Rain’s movements became more cautious. He only had 10% of his health left, but he wasn’t willing to give up just yet. Troubling Rain still had plenty of mana, and his fighting strength was normal. He needed to carefully protect this 10% health.

Where’s my opponent?

Huang Shaotian looked around in search of Deception.

Where’s Deception?

It wasn’t just Huang Shaotian, everyone was looking. Despite having an omniscient view, they unexpectedly weren’t able to find him. The camera cut to Mo Fan’s point of view. His screen was filled with branches and leaves. There was only a small sliver that he could see out of.

Mo Fan wanted to take advantage of this opportunity, but Troubling Rain had escaped from the trap faster than he thought. He wasn’t able to find the right opportunity to act, so he used the dust as cover to roll to the fallen tree, and hid behind the dense leaves and branches.

Huang Shaotian’s situation was so tragic already, but he didn’t show any mercy, carefully preparing for another sneak attack.

Through the help of the broadcast, the viewers quickly locked onto Deception’s position. Troubling Rain didn’t dare make any rash moves. He simply stood in place, observing his surroundings cautiously.

Finally, the dust settled, and the leaves stopped shaking. Troubling Rain jumped onto the tree trunk and slowly turned, examining everything in his surroundings.

Pop!

A gentle sound rang. Huang Shaotian nimbly turned his viewpoint and had Troubling Rain dash towards the source of the sound.

Purple smoke instantly expanded from beneath the leaves.

Ninja Tool – Smoke Bomb!

With only 10% of his health left, Huang Shaotian could not charge in. Seeing that he wouldn’t be able to get anything out of this situation, he chose to retreat far away to outside of Smoke Bomb’s range and waited patiently for the purple smoke to dissipate. Only then did he start moving forward again, his gaze locked onto a certain spot.

While he waited on the side, Huang Shaotian didn’t just wait there doing nothing. He carefully observed the flow of the purple smoke and grasped Deception’s movements from it, because he knew Mo Fan would definitely borrow the purple smoke as cover to move about. From these small details, he had been able to locate Deception’s current hiding spot.

Quite hidden.

Huang Shaotian thought to himself as he looked at the dense bunch of leaves. Even though he didn’t see Deception, he had determined that he was over there.

Troubling Rain continued to be cautious, taking each step slowly. He didn’t make any moves in a single clear direction. He didn’t want Mo Fan to know that he had already found him.

And just like this, Troubling Rain walked into Deception’s attack range.

Still not moving?

Huang Shaotian had kept watch on that location. Troubling Rain had walked into a position that gave Deception plenty of opportunities. Still not satisfied?

Too greedy!

Huang Shaotian was helpless. He also knew the patience that a hunter had because he was that type of person too.

He was giving out openings that would let him make a counterattack, but it clearly wasn’t enough to move his opponent.

Fine! Let’s see just how patient you can be. Huang Shaotian thought to himself as Troubling Rain made another step closer.

Still no movements.

Another step, nothing.

Huang Shaotian felt his head hurt.

He had experienced Mo Fan’s skills. His instant bursts were incredible. Although he couldn’t keep it up for long, Troubling Rain only had 10% of his health. A short burst from Mo Fan was more than enough.

If he got any closer and let the opponent initiate, he might not be able to counterattack.

“He can’t keep delivering himself over!” Li Yibo shouted. Through their omniscient spectator view, they could clearly see the situation on both sides and had a clear grasp at Huang Shaotian’s intentions. From the analysis he had given previously, everyone agreed with Li Yibo: he can’t keep delivering himself over.

But Huang Shaotian still had Troubling Rain take a step forward.

This was perseverance, bravery, and more importantly, confidence.

The situation was unfavorable for him, yet he still had the confidence that he could turn it around.

Deception rushed out!

For him, it was the best opportunity he was going to get. The previous opportunities were indeed quite good, but he wasn’t tempted by them. He patiently waited until the golden one appeared.

The patience trained from being a scrap picker wouldn’t lose to anyone.

“Good!” At this crucial moment, Huang Shaotian first typed out a message.

Storm Shuriken!

Numerous shurikens flew out. Under this cover, Deception quickly formed a seal, Shadow Clone Technique!

Troubling Rain, Sword’s Divine Judgement!

Huang Shaotian didn’t hesitate even though this skill had gotten him into a bad situation last match. When it was time to use it, he was still confident in his judgement and used it with no second thoughts.

Sword qi flew out in every direction. Deception, who had used Shadow Clone Technique to get behind him, was swept away by the sword qi.

Stun!

The damage from Sword’s Divine Judgement wasn’t great, but the Stun effect was remarkable.

Troubling Rain turned around with a Rising Dragon Slash.

Deception was launched into the air. Rising Dragon Slash into Falling Phoenix Slash was a very common combo, but Huang Shaotian decided to go more complex. He used a Headwind Strike in the air into an Immortal Guides the Way. Before Deception was blown away, he immediately followed with a Falling Phoenix Slash.

The sword pressed down on Deception as he fell. Although this combo dealt more damage, the difficult execution meant that a slight flaw in the chaining of skills could lead to Deception breaking free from it.

But everyone could also see why Huang Shaotian took the risk. By chaining these skills together, his character fell slightly slower, allowing him to dodge all of Deception’s Storm Shurikens.

Huang SHaotian would not let himself waste the 10% health he had left.

Chapter 1404 - Technique

Boom!

Falling Phoenix Slash’s knockdown priority was very high. Deception crashed down against the ground, even forming a small crater upon impact, but the flashing sword light had already caught up.

Falling Light Blade!

Almost as if flying on his sword, Troubling Rain and Ice Rain arrived in front of Deception in the blink of an eye.

Deception was rapidly forming hand seals with his hands.

Substitution Technique!

Huang Shaotian could predict this. This was one of the most disgusting things about fighting Ninjas. They had numerous escape techniques that could brutally murder their opponent’s attack combo.

Luckily, most Ninja techniques required hand seals, which was their form of casting. Even though a Ninja’s casting speed was decided by affective APM, it still gave their opponents the chance to interrupt.

His mechanics were very fast, but, it wasn’t fast enough!

Huang Shaotian’s calculations were very precise. He had executed his offensive with Mo Fan’s escape techniques in mind, aiming to make sure the other didn’t have a chance to use them. The time between the short stun after Deception crashed into the ground from Falling Phoenix Slash and Troubling Rain’s Falling Light Blade hitting wasn’t enough for Mo Fan to use the Substitution Technique. These detailed calculations were one of the many factors that differentiated top Gods from rookies. No matter how talented a rookie was, their lack of experience meant that they wouldn’t be able to make such detailed and accurate estimations.

Hit!

Ice Rain swung down, and Huang Shaotian already had his next moves all planned out.

But in that moment, he noticed the hand seals Deception was making.

This wasn’t the Substitution Technique!

Huang Shaotian’s eyes were sharp, able to capture the tiny and rapid hand movements Deception was making.

This… was the Underground Tunneling Technique!

Mo Fan had actually decided to choose to counterattack at a time like this. This was shocking to Huang Shaotian. He hadn’t predicted such a possibility because when they had been prepping for their battle against Happy, they had found two clear and fundamental traits to Mo Fan’s style.

Patience that wasn’t second to anyone’s, and an absolute aversion to risk-taking.

Considering this player’s background, it wasn’t hard to understand this style.

Thus, this Underground Tunneling Technique completely contradicted his style. This was a risky move, and Huang Shaotian hadn’t expected Mo Fan would consider such a decision at all.

But, he could probably interrupt it, right?

The hand seals required by the Underground Tunneling Technique were more complex than the Substitution Technique!

That’s what Huang Shaotian told himself, but he still had a bad feeling about this.

Different techniques had different complexities, but players also had different levels of familiarity and mastery for different techniques. For rookies, this was more evident. It was completely possible that the more complex Underground Tunneling Technique would be faster than the Substitution Technique.

Hit!

In the end, Falling Light Blade struck Deception, but had it interrupted the hand seals?

There was only a slight difference in timing, so miniscule that not even Huang Shaotian could make a judgement. All he saw was Deception thrown back by this Falling Light Blade and then suddenly disappearing into the ground.

He had completed the hand seals!

Huang Shaotian’s reaction was immediate. Troubling Rain, having just landed on the ground, once again jumped up without hesitation and slashed down.

But… it hit air.

Deception hadn’t jumped out to attack him. Now, he was once again displaying that disgusting patience of his.

What an annoying opponent!

Huang Shaotian cursed under his breath. Actually, god knows how many times his opponents had cursed him with the very same words. Partially because of his trash talking, partially because of his battle style. It was extraordinary, and extra annoying*.

Huang Shaotian didn’t know when Mo Fan planned on attacking. The moment he landed would be the most dangerous, so he accompanied his landing with another strike downwards.

Deception still hadn’t struck, and Huang Shaotian felt that it was quite the shame. Though his patience was admirable, but in Huang Shaotian’s eyes, the other’s decision wasn’t the best. The optimal moment to strike with Underground Tunneling Technique was the moment it was activated. In that moment, Huang Shaotian had been a bit of a mess. However, now, he had oriented himself and was prepared, quietly awaiting the moment the attack was launched. Did Mo Fan really think he could succeed in a sneak attack now? Not unless Huang Shaotian disconnected.

“What a shame!” Thus, Huang Shaotian began spamming the chat again. Even underground, Mo Fan could still see the chat channel.

“You missed your best opportunity,” Huang Shaotian continued.

“Now I can even have my character easily walk out of your Underground Tunneling Technique’s range,” Huang Shaotian finally said.

Range?

After he typed down this word, Huang Shaotian startled.

And then Deception’s Underground Tunneling Technique activated.

Not under Troubling Rain’s feet, but in the farthest corner of the skill’s range from Troubling Rain. Just like that, Deception jumped out of the ground to face Troubling Rain.

Holy shit!

Huang Shaotian realized that he had made a mistake.

This Underground Tunneling Technique wasn’t about offense at all. In that moment, it was used as an escape skill. And now, hadn’t it successfully interrupted his offensive? The two of them, facing off directly? With Troubling Rain’s 10 percent health, a few skills exchanged was enough to kill him.

Seeing Deception’s emotionless avatar face, Huang Shaotian felt like he was looking directly at Mo Fan’s expression. While he was rambling away, the other was probably emotionless like this, not even sparing his words a glance!

Deception turned, and escaped, once again using the environment to hide himself. His opponent only had 10 percent health left, yet he didn’t directly attack.

However, this time, he was very active. While hiding, he would often throw a shuriken or something to harass Troubling Rain, baiting his opponent into coming closer.

Huang Shaotian didn’t know if he should cry or laugh. He, a God, was now… being played around with by a rookie?

However, he didn’t have any way to deal with. This rookie was no joke, and his own character only had 10 percent of his health left, and so he was set in a very awkward circumstance.

After patiently tormenting him for a good while, Mo Fan finally found an opening he was satisfied with. Deception charged out, unhesitantly showing an air of ‘yes, that’s right, I’m taking advantage of the fact that you barely have any health left’.

What a damn bastard!

When Troubling Rain finally fell, Huang Shaotian was so angry he couldn’t even type anything anymore, only slam the desk and curse.

Mo Fan won!

Though everyone had expected this result when 50 percent of Troubling Rain’s health was smashed by a tree, when the victory actually occurred, it still sent the audience into an uproar.

Counterattack of the grassroots?

This was it!

This wasn’t the first time Mo Fan had achieved something like this before. Last time, he had defeated Sun Xiang in the regular season, no?

However, that time, he had the clear advantage from the beginning of the match. This time, 100 percent versus 80 percent, rookie versus God, how many people would even consider that 20 percent advantage? From the beginning, everyone was expecting Huang Shaotian to win.

Though this match included a hilarious catastrophe of getting 50 percent of his health smashed by a tree, making Huang Shaotian’s situation look like an unfortunate accident, this situation was artificially created, and they couldn’t neglect to consider the role Mo Fan’s skill played. Plus, in their head on exchanges, Mo Fan hadn’t been completely suppressed by Huang Shaotian. Compared to the last round where Ye Xiu had 30 percent of his health knocked off in one go by Huang Shaotian, Mo Fan had yet to fall into such an ugly situation. On the contrary, he had started off with a successful ambush, taking out 20 percent of Troubling Rain’s health in one.

“What a glorious victory!” Pan Lin exclaimed in the live broadcast, purposefully reminding everyone to not overlook this victory because of that lost 50 percent.

“After all, it was Huang Shaotian who cut down that tree…” Saying this, Pan Lin had to stifle his laughter. No matter how he described it, it would sound hilarious.

Huang Shaotian left the stage amidst laughter; some were mocking, some sympathetic, some just cheerful, all sorts of different emotions accompanied by applause and people yelling “Huang Shao, Huang Shao”. He didn’t know how to feel.

After returning to Blue Rain’s player bench, his teammates all came up to shake his hand, or pat his shoulder and whatnot to comfort him.

“What the hell? What the hell you think you’re all doing, huh??? If you want to laugh, just laugh!!” Huang Shaotian exploded. These assholes! He could tell they wanted to laugh, but all came over pretending to comfort him. They were terrible actors, none of them seemed sincere at all.

“True, it’s too hard not to laugh!” Song Xiao was the first to burst into laughter.

“We’re already lagging way behind! Be more serious!” Huang Shaotian warned everyone with a serious expression. In the group arena, three of Blue Rain’s players had been beaten already, including their ace player Huang Shaotian, while Happy was only at their second player. Plus, Deception still had 64 percent of his health left.

“Yes. We’re at a huge disadvantage. We need to be more cautious.” Captain Yu Wenzhou directed his words at the next player in line.

“Yes sir!” Li Yuan saluted his captain.

Li Yuan was a season eight debutee, playing a Summoner. Unlike other newbies who were usually careful and docile upon joining the team, Li Yuan was very lively, enthusiastic no matter who he was faced with, and quickly became familiar with Blue Rain’s players and other staff.

Though Li Yuan had amicable relationships with other people, Li Yuan wasn’t the kind of rookie who made waves. He hadn’t appeared at all in the Season Eight Best Rookie nominations because he hadn’t had many chances to play that season. Then, in Season Nine, Lu Hanwen, the youngest player in history, debuted in Blue Rain, directly taking over the position Yu Feng had left and completely outshining their second year player Li Yuan.

However, Li Yuan hadn’t let this bring him down, andhe wasn’t at all jealous of this rookie that had outshone him so much. He treated Lu Hanwen like everyone else, taking care of the other. Finally, in the past year, Li Yuan gained more chances to play and cemented his position in the team.

Then in this season, Thief player Lin Feng transferred to Wind Howl and Li Yuan stepped forward once more, becoming a permanent core member of the team and gaining more chances to perform in the individual competition, group arenas and team competitions. His performance was admirable. Now, on the final stage of the playoffs, he was fielded.

Chapter 1405 - Search

Li Yuan…

Happy looked at Blue Rain’s next player. He wasn’t a particularly talented player, yet he was a player no team could lack. Talented players also needed accompanying leaves to serve as contrast for them. No team consisted of only Gods. There were only so many Gods!

Li Yuan wasn’t a God, but anyone who could be a part of a powerhouse like Team Blue Rain certainly had to have the skill to back it up. To be allowed to participate on such an important stage, how could he be underestimated?

Li Yuan. Summoner, Eight Notes.

Three of Blue Rain’s players had been eliminated. By now, Blue Rain had a fairly good understanding of this originally unfamiliar map. Li Yuan did the same as his three previous teammates and had his Eight Notes boldly take the central path.

This time, Mo Fan unexpectedly did not have Deception take a roundabout route, instead choosing the central path as well.

“Is he planning on a direct confrontation?” Pan Lin said in surprise.

Mo Fan’s patience and caution had left a deep impression on everyone. Even when his opponent only had 10% of his health left, he still stuck with his usual strategy of searching for an opportunity to make a sneak attack. His scrap picking habit of always prioritizing his safety first was truly suitable for the group arena!

So why did he suddenly want a direct confrontation?

Pan Lin wondered as the two characters quickly came into each other’s view.

Li Yuan’s Eight Notes immediately stopped and started summoning creatures. As for Mo Fan’s Deception? With a sudden stride to the side, he scurried into a bush and disappeared…

He still intended on launching a sneak attack. Everyone let out a sigh of relief. They weren’t used to seeing Mo Fan’s character charge forward fiercely. Hiding was more like it.

Li Yuan noticed that Deception had hidden himself, but he didn’t care. He was a Summoner. He wasn’t too afraid of an ambush. He continued to summon creatures, soon letting the viewers know his playstyle.

Spirit Style!

Creating an enormous army was easy for Spirit Style summoners. Little Spirits could be stacked up to a total of eight for each element. Every two same element Little Spirits could merge to form a Big Spirit. Four Big Spirits of different elements could merge to form a Spirit King.

A maxed out Spirit army could have a total of eight Little Spirits, four Big Spirits, and a Spirit King. Compared to the four beasts of the Four Sacred Beasts, the number of summons was far greater.

But because the higher staged spirits required lower stage spirits to be formed, finding a balance between them was the difficult part. Let’s say a Spirit King was suddenly killed in a battle. To make it up, two more Big Spirits were needed. To make these two Big Spirits, the Little Spirits needed to be merged. Performing these many spells to merge them together wasn’t easy to do quickly. As a result, for the Spirit Style, replenishing one’s summons was crucial. Waiting for one’s Spirits to be killed before summoning more wouldn’t work. And because of the complications involved in maintaining a Spirit army, Spirit summons had a fairly long durations. Little Spirits could stay on the field for a minute, Big Spirits two minutes, and Spirit Kings four minutes.

Four minutes was a long time. In 1v1s, Ye Xiu and the others on Happy could crush noobs in tens of seconds.

Li Yuan didn’t panic. When he saw that Deception had gone into hiding, he sent out a Little Fire Spirit to chase after him, while Eight Notes continued to summon. Other classes needed to worry about not being ambushed when pursuing their opponent, but Spirit Style Summoners had plenty of Spirits to protect them, so there was nothing to fear.

The Little Fire Spirit looked like a small fireball. Not long after it reached the grass, the grass began to wilt because of the heat. The Little Fire Spirit had a bit of burning power, but when a Big Fire Spirit came over, it was like moving lava. The brushes started to smolder and smoke spread through the air.

By now, Li Yuan’s Eight Notes had summoned four Big Spirits, six Little Spirits, a grand crowd. He boldly stepped into the previous area to the side of the central road that Song Xiao, Lu Hanwen, and Huang Shaotian had avoided due to their unfamiliarity with the map.

“Where’d you go?” With the Spirits protecting him, Li Yuan appeared completely calm and had time to type. Even though he didn’t talk non-stop like Huang Shaotian, he was clearly the type who liked to say a few words when there was time to.

Mo Fan could even ignore Huang Shaotian’s map attacks. How could he be bothered by Li Yuan’s simple words?

For a moment, Li Yuan wasn’t able to find Deception. He found a spot and planted a Devil World Flower. Because Devil World Flowers were rooted to a location, they weren’t suited as the core of a style, but no Summoner style would let go of such a powerful summon.

For example, the Devil World Flower didn’t rely on sight or sound to search for a target. It would automatically detect any target within its range and attack the target with its vines.

But when the Devil World Flower was planted, there were no movements from it, meaning this surrounding area was safe.

“You ran quite far away!” Li Yuan muttered again. Eight Notes immediately waved his wand, sending out a command with each wave. The summons started spreading out to search the surroundings. All of the summons were set to auto-attack. As soon as a target was discovered, the summon would automatically attack and Li Yuan would immediately know.

“Playing hide-and-seek with a Summoner isn’t a good idea!” Pan Lin said. The spectators had an omniscient view, so they obviously knew of Deception’s current location. The previous Devil World Flower had worried them. Fortunately, Deception had moved away. However, now that Eight Notes had started conducting a wide area search, Deception’s constant movements to escape Li Yuan’ s notice gave them even more anxiety.

“He’s up against a Spirit Style Summoner, after all!” Li Yibo sighed. Eight Notes had maxed out his Big Spirits. He now had four Big Spirits and eight Little Spirits searching the area. As soon as a fight broke out, a Spirit King would inevitably be summoned. The Spirit King was the most powerful Spirit and could use the skills Elemental Cut, an Elemental Split, and an Elemental Explosion, each skill stronger than the other.

“Perhaps finding a way to escape would be the wisest decision,” Pan Lin thought.

But Mo Fan clearly thought differently. He had Deception stay there and play hide-and-seek with the summoned spirits.

Happy’s fans were on their edge of their seats for Mo Fan, while the neutral spectators and Blue Rain’s fans felt like this time, Blue Rain had this match in the bag. Mo Fan’s sneaky playstyle had met his nemesis!

But after watching for a bit, they noticed that something wasn’t quite right.

Again and again, just when it looked like the spirits would find him, Mo Fan would immediately have Deception evade them.

“Wow… how incredible!” Pan Lin stuttered. Mo Fan’s ability had once again exceeded his expectations.

“Yes, this is the skill trained from scrap picking.” Li Yibo said.

Anyone who had experienced with Glory immediately thought of a scene: in a dusty battlefield covered in countless blade and bullet marks, a cold ninja nimbly wandered through the battlefield, carefully dodging any attacks and avoiding attention. Afterwards, he filled his bag with all sorts of precious equipment and materials until it was full before disappearing into the fringes of the battle…

Compared to that environment, twenty enemy spirits was nothing!

The viewers sighed. As for Li Yuan? His spirits still hadn’t uncovered Deception. He was starting to lose his patience.

While the spirits were searching, he wasn’t staying idle. Eight Notes stood within the Devil World Flower’s protection range, while he carefully observed his surroundings. His spirits weren’t wandering around aimlessly. They were moving towards his dead angles according to the terrain. Even so, Deception was still nowhere to be found. Could he have already run far away?

It was hard not to be suspicious. In reality, the spectators with an omniscient view all knew that Deception had uncovered himself before. Unfortunately, Li Yuan couldn’t see 360 degrees, otherwise he would have noticed Deception not just once or twice.

Unable to find Deception in any direction, Li Yuan wasn’t sure what to do. His search had lost focus. He couldn’t just keep spreading out his search forever, could he?

Li Xuan carefully observed in a circle. After reflecting on his search plan, he felt like there weren’t any holes, so he had his spirits increase the radius of the search area another step.

Not good!

Everyone saw this scene and shouted in their hearts.

Deception hadn’t run far! And by increasing his search radius, Deception was now inside the circle, giving Mo Fan an opportunity. Had he insisted on staying, anticipating this sort of opportunity would appear?

Sure enough, Deception started approaching. However, Eight Notes still had a troublesome Devil World Flower. Li Xuan was still a pro player. He wasn’t so naive as to wait for his Devil World Flower to disappear before planting another one.

As a result, Mo Fan didn’t keep waiting. He watched as the spirits spread out further, and after seeing Li Yuan summon another Devil World Flower to replace his current one, he rushed out.

Whoosh!

Devil World Flower’s vines suddenly climbed out of the ground towards Deception. Mo Fan had predicted this move. The Ninja’s biggest advantage was that he could form his seals while moving or while in any position.

Ninjutsu – Explosive Flame Dragon!

Another Ninja Level 75 skill. After forming the seals, Deception held up his two fingers and formed a triangle, putting it in front of his mouth. A light purple flame flew out from his mouth. As soon as it touched the air, it immediately started exploding wildly creating a chain of flames towards the Devil World Flower.

Fire attacks dealt additional damage to Devil World Flowers. With just this one move, the Devil World Flower turned pitch-black. The extending vine instantly turned lifeless and dispersed into ash.

At this moment, Li Yuan’s Eight Notes had lost his only protection.

Chapter 1406 - Restricted

Fighting a close-ranged battle?

Honestly speaking, the Summoner’s common weapon of choice, the Wand, had a very high attack speed, usually having a rating of around 9 to 10. Because of this, there had even been some Wand users among Battle Mage players, focusing their playstyle on their magic abilities. When it came to Summoners, their close-ranged fighting power was pretty much close to zero. If they relied on themselves to fight in close quarters, they could only use some superficial skills that any class had access to, and if they really had to, they could use Lash, which was normally used to buff their minions. Evidently, these few skills weren’t enough.

As such, some Summoners would opt to learn some of the Battle Mage’s initial skills, like Dragon Tooth, Falling Flower Palm, Circle Swing, all of which were very popular. This would let the Summoner have at least some capability of defending themselves in an unexpected close-ranged battle.

However, skill points were precious, and learning these skills wasted too many points, making many Summoners very reluctant to use this method. As such, there was now another more sketchy method of dealing with the problem: putting a skill on their weapon.

Teleport!

This high level skill from the Elementalist class was undoubtedly a strong option for escaping, and Li Yuan’s Summoner, Eight Notes, had chosen this path. The moment he saw Deception charging towards him and instantly dispatching the Devil World Flower, he cast Teleport without hesitating.

Teleport was an instant cast spell. It wasn’t impossible to interrupt, but the window of opportunity for doing so was extremely short, making it very difficult to interrupt. Deception had yet to properly latch on to his opponent, and in such a scenario, interrupting the spell was pretty much impossible.

Zap……

A sound like an electric current sounded out, and Eight Notes had already been teleported several units away from his original position, leaving only a trace of magic power behind.

But then, Flame Cut!

The flames frantically swept towards Eight Notes. Li Yuan looked over, and Deception was clearly still back there, but then how was the attack already so close to Eight Notes?

Shadow Clone Technique……

Running into a Ninja was Li Yuan’s misfortune. Using Teleportation could indeed instantly create some distance between the characters, but the Ninja could use Shadow Clone Technique in this way to immediately close the distance. A Summoner’s Teleportation could only be level 1 at best, meaning that the distance travelled was the shortest possible.

Li Yuan hadn’t overlooked the fact that Deception was a Ninja, but he had no other options. His usage of Teleportation was just an attempt, trying to see if Mo Fan’s reactions were fast enough to catch up. Unfortunately, Mo Fan did catch up. He wasn’t just an expert in escaping, but also in pursuing his target.

The distance moved by Shadow Clone Technique wasn’t enough to let Deception completely close in on Eight Notes, but Flame Cut, a skill with some range on it, was already enough to reach Eight Notes.

Eight Notes turned over and rolled.

Summoners were only lacking close-range skills, but these basic movements were obviously something that every character possessed. Some Summoners with excessive self-confidence would choose to use their basic movements to dodge attacks, a method even more economical than putting Teleportation on their weapon.

However, within the professional scene, no Summoner would choose to use this ‘economical’ method. Simply put, there were no noobs for them to bully in the Alliance, so purely relying on sidestepping attacks wasn’t going to cut it against an offensive from any pro player.

Shining Cut!

Mo Fan used a low-level Assassin skill, and in a flash, Deception had completely latched on to Eight Notes.

Ninja Arts: Cicada Shell Double Slash!

With this skill, after the Ninjato was unsheathed, both the blade and the scabbard would attack together, crossing and attacking enemies to the left and right of the character. But Glory’s mechanics allowed for a great deal of freedom in controlling the character, and as such, when there was only one opponent, there was obviously no need to attack on both sides. When Deception used this Cicada Shell Double Slash, the Ninjato and scabbard both slashed towards Eight Notes.

Once one hit connected, the offensive immediately began. When fighting against a Summoner, Mo Fan didn’t need to attack too explosively. After just two or three moves, Eight Notes had already been thoroughly suppressed.

Even when a Summoner was under siege, the commands that they issued to their summons couldn’t be interrupted. But in order to control their summons, they still needed to be within the Summoner’s field of view in order for them to select the unit to control. At this time, Deception had already forced Eight Notes into a corner, cutting off part of his vision, and the attacks afterwards caused his camera to shake and sway non-stop. The broadcast cut to Li Yuan’s point-of-view, and it was really a tragic sight: the summons roaming around freely in the distance had become fragmented on his screen, intermittently cutting in and out of view. Under these circumstances, it was exceedingly difficult for Li Yuan to control his summons to come over and save him.

“Player Mo Fan seems to have a lot of experience in fighting against Summoners!” Li Yibo said surprisedly. He was just a rookie, and he hadn’t appeared much on stage in this season, but at this moment, he showed incredible adeptness at the techniques used to fight against Summoners.

At Happy’s player bench off-stage, upon seeing Li Yuan’s point-of-view, Luo Ji had a traumatized expression on his face.

Why was Mo Fan so used to fighting against Summoners? Because there was one in the team! When it came to their skill levels, there was quite a gap between Luo Ji and Mo Fan, but Mo Fan held nothing back when he played with opponents weaker than him. Mo Fan was earnest in every practice session, and as such, Luo Ji had been beaten into a pulp by Mo Fan hundreds or thousands of times. At one glance, the spectacle unfolding from Li Yuan’s point-of-view was just too familiar. When he fought individually against Mo Fan, he had similarly been forced into a corner and killed an untold number of times.

However, Luo Ji’s Concealed Light was a Elemental Beast Summoner, primarily making use of those four summons, but Li Yuan needed to control roughly ten spirits. United against a common enemy, Luo Ji involuntarily felt a sense of kinship with Li Yuan, unexpectedly feeling worried on his behalf.

Li Yuan was obviously suffering greatly. Now that he had been latched on to, there was definitely no room for him to finish a summoning spell. He had his back against the wall, and the summons in the distance were completely uncontrollable. At this time, seven of the spirits would flicker in and out of his view, but Mo Fan’s offensive tossed him from side to side, making commanding the spirits nigh impossible.

However, everyone could see that there were three spirits coming over in succession to protect him. Even under such restricting circumstances, Li Yuan had still managed to complete commands for three of his Spirits, showing off his significant caliber as a pro player.

But, only three of them……

Upon seeing the three Little Spirits charging over, the more knowledgeable viewers could only silently mourn. Spirit summons relied on creating an army of sheer numbers to achieve victory, so evidently, their individual attack power wasn’t too powerful. Whether it was in terms of Attack, Defense or Health, the spirits didn’t have particularly impressive stats. Spirits were more notable because their duration was long, and their attacks had a chance to proc elemental effects. But if it was just Little Spirits, they’d be easily dispatched in two or three hits by other players. Would the spirits charging over really be able to do anything, especially given that Li Yuan wasn’t able to arrange and deploy them properly?

Li Yuan was completely aware of this point, not taking Mo Fan as an opponent that could be easily harassed by a few Little Spirits. The three Little Spirits didn’t charge over and immediately attack, instead stopping and waiting at a point that Li Yuan had indicated earlier. This point was in a far more convenient location for Li Yuan to control the Spirits. Evidently, Li Yuan was arranging his Spirits against Mo Fan constantly tossing him from side to side.

“Not bad, Li Yuan is very prudent. Don’t think that he’s just taking a beating. His response to the situation clearly displays the defensive skills that players from Blue Rain possess,” Li Yibo exclaimed in admiration.

At Happy’s player bench, Luo Ji’s eyes flashed with understanding. He could see the wisdom in Li Yuan’s tempo. The three Little Spirits going up to attack was only a minor irritation, not serving any real purpose. But now that he had the three spirits stop at a convenient place, he had once again put himself in a good position relative to his spirits.

Mo Fan’s harassing attacks were mainly meant to disrupt the stability of Li Yuan’s field-of-view, but now, no matter how his vision was disrupted, Li Yuan would always have an option, and given his hand speed, as long as he had an option, it would be a cinch to grasp it. As expected, another Big Spirit was controlled from afar, beginning to move over and rescue him.

“It’s a Fire Spirit!” Pan Lin said.

“Mm… After all, Li Yuan doesn’t really have much of a choice. If he could choose, I think he would have prioritized the Ice Spirit or the Light Spirit,” Li Yibo replied. The Big Fire Spirit’s attack was Flame Blade, a close-ranged attack. On the other hand, the Ice Spirit’s Falling Ice and the Light Spirit’s Lightning were long-ranged attacks, and on top of that, there was a chance to freeze or paralyze the opponent with the attacks, something that would be of great help to Eight Notes. The Fire Spirit had high offensive power, but it needed to get close to attack. In the worst case scenario, Deception could easily beat it up along with Eight Notes.

“Let’s see what Li Yuan plans to do,” Li Yibo said.

“At this point, there isn’t much duration left on the Little Spirits either,” Pan Lin mentioned.

The broadcast immediately displayed the duration remaining on the Little Spirits, since there was a difference in when the spirits were summoned, and as such a difference in remaining duration. The spirits that were far away weren’t taken into account. Of the three that were close by, one had 9 seconds, while the other two had 14 seconds and 19 seconds.

The Big Spirit still had 2 minutes worth of duration, so at this point, there was no need to worry about it disappearing by itself. However, the Little Spirit with only 9 seconds left looked as if it wouldn’t be able to make any real contribution.

Li Yuan clearly understood this, and a convenient opportunity arrived to control the three Little Spirits, so he commanded the one with 9 seconds remaining to charge over. If it was going to disappear by itself anyways, it would be better to bring it over and cause some irritation for Deception.

This was a Little Ice Spirit. All the Little Spirits had to be close to the enemy to attack, and while they had a chance to inflict an effect on hit, the probability was much lower when compared to the Big Spirits. The Little Spirit floated over, but Mo Fan completely ignored it. When it was almost in range, he suddenly used Neck Bind Technique, and Eight Notes was flung over his shoulder, crashing into the Little Ice Spirit. Immediately afterwards, he used Flame Cut, slashing towards both the Little Spirit and Eight Notes in one swing, and the Little Spirit died. And Eight Notes? Li Yuan used this opportunity and continued to tenaciously control his Spirits. One Little Spirit had died, but two more rushed over to take its place. At the same time, one Big Spirit finally rushed over to surround him.

“Is this enough?” Pan Lin cried, betraying his concern. Everyone could clearly see that Mo Fan was an expert at dodging and escaping. With how little duration there was left for the Little Spirits, Mo Fan could just put in a little effort to contend with them, and they would disappear by themselves.

“There’s already no other options,” Li Yibo sighed. As time went on, the Summons’ duration was extremely disadvantageous, meaning that Li Yuan no longer had time to continue waiting.

One Big and four Small, five Spirits advanced, and Deception jumped out of the way.

“As expected!” Pan Lin shouted, Mo Fan was indeed planning to wait out the duration. The spirits that had encircled him hit nothing but air.

However…

“It’s a sacrifice! Spirit Sacrifice!” Li Yibo cried out.

Chapter 1407 - Scrap Picking Your Health

Spirit Sacrifice. A Level 75 Summoner ultimate skill. It wasn’t just for spirit users, but it was the skill with the highest attack power across all Summoner skills. After this skill came out, countless Summoners started calculating the damage this skill could do and, from the current tests, Spirit Sacrifice seemed to be the second skill after the Assassin’s Life-Risking Strike that could accomplish a One-Hit KO.

Of course, like Life-Risking Strike, wanting to successfully accomplish an OHKO was very troublesome.

For Life-Risking Strike, most of the time, one had to achieve the requirements for “Assassination Arts”, “Critical Strike” and other damage increasing bonuses. As for Spirit Sacrifice, it was even more troublesome. The skill damage had to do with the number of spirits, the remaining health of spirits, and the remaining time the spirits had. In theory, when all these numbers were at their max, that was when Spirit Sacrifice was at its strongest. However, this was only theoretical; it was impossible to accomplish ingame. Just with the remaining time, it was impossible to have all spirits at their maximum at once. There would always be differences between those summoned first and those summoned later.

All this was still in testing. In real combat, it would be even harder to find an opportune moment and conditions to activate a powerful Spirit Sacrifice. Plus, after Spirit Sacrifice was used, all spirits would disappear. For a Summoner, that was equal to losing all protection. If this strike missed, or failed to be fatal, then it would be a huge problem.

Right now, Deception wasn’t at full health, but a Spirit Sacrifice with one large and four small Spirits wasn’t enough to kill him. Li Yuan’s goal was merely to get himself out of his current situation. Clearly, he didn’t think that his five spirits could give Mo Fan much trouble while he wasn’t able to control them properly, with the other so good at escaping, so he resolutely decided to detonate the five spirits he had managed to gather.

The explosion didn’t make a huge noise like the cannon fire and explosions of Launchers and Spitfires. During Spirit Sacrifice, all that was heard was the sound of the spirits’ bodies shattering one after the other. The five spirits all unleashed the elemental power within them at once. Ice, fire, light and dark, the flash from the different elements erupted, striking everything within range.

This attack was an AoE, and Deception was clearly within its area of effect. This attack came too suddenly, and Mo Fan didn’t even have the time to execute a Substitution Technique before the light of the different elements enveloped him.

“It hit!!” Pan Lin yelled. Li Yuan took this time to get Eight Notes out of the way as he called the spirits that were still wandering about back to his side.

The small spirits were about to disappear, so Li Yuan didn’t place any hope in them. The three large spirits were more important, and then, a Devil World Flower was soon planted.

By now, the Spirit Sacrifice’s shockwaves were about done. This skill was all about the damage, and the shockwaves from the explosion of elemental power would continuously damage whoever was within range. Apart from damage, there weren’t any other effects. However, Devil World Flower’s attack had already arrived. Using the yet to disperse flash from the explosion, a vine silently shot out from the ground and grabbed Deception.

Storm Shuriken!

Escape arts were truly Mo Fan’s forte. He immediately countered when the vine came out, dozens of shurikens flying out like a storm, instantly cutting through the vine.

The skill that had KO’d Devil World Flower last time, Ninja Arts: Explosive Flame Dragon, was a very powerful skill, but it’s cooldown was long, and it hadn’t come off its cooldown yet. Deception didn’t have any way to wipe out Devil World Flower right now, and this was precisely what made it so annoying.

Hiding behind Devil World Flower, Eight Notes carefully began to summon again. The Big Spirits were on their way back, and the Little Spirits had mostly expired. He had to replenish his Little Spirits.

The offensive Deception had launched while trapping Eight Notes in the corner just now had taken out a full 61 percent of Eight Notes’s health. Summoners were a fragile cloth armor class, so they couldn’t take a close range ranged beating like that. As for Deception, that Spirit Sacrifice had blasted off 20 percent of his health. Though it wasn’t as spectacular as his own offensive, Deception wasn’t at full health to begin with, so he only had 44 percent left, in the lead against Eight Notes’s 39 percent.

“Happy’s Mo Fan really is a great player!” Pan Lin complimented.

“I feel that he really is a mature player already. From his playstyle, you rarely see the incompleteness belonging to newbie players,” Li Yibo added.

“However, he really is a rookie. I believe that there are many who know of this player. In his first match, he took two yellow cards and was disqualified,” Pan Lin said.

This event was truly surprising and unique. Even a newbie would have a hard time getting directly disqualified.

“But now, on the stage of the playoffs, we’re witnessing a Mo Fan that has matured so much,” Pna Lin exclaimed with a tone of “he grew up so fast”.

“But right now, Mo Fan isn’t in such a good position!” Li Yibo said.

With Devil World Flower on the field and no skill to kill it in one go, now was Mo Fan going to get his Ninja back on the offensive?

Run? Repeat what he had just done? Having had a taste of Mo Fan’s ability when it came to hiding, it was doubtful that Li Yuan would be caught off guard like that again. Right now, faced with the current defense, was probably the best chance Mo Fan would get.

However, this guy was extremely risk-averse. The current opportunity probably wasn’t enough for him to bet on.

Everyone was trying to guess what choice of action Mo Fan would take next, and Deception, while everyone was guessing, charged.

“Is he going on the offense?” Pan Lin cried out.

How many times had Mo Fan simply been feinting when they thought he was going to attack? What about this time? No matter what, the direction he had chosen didn’t seem like a plan to run.

Shuriken!

A shuriken flew out, interrupting Eight Notes’s casting. Then, Smoke Bomb!

Purple smoke erupted, enveloping the area, and the camera hurriedly closed in to catch the two characters within.

Deception was still moving.

Shadow Clone Technique!

He directly used this skill to send himself to Eight Notes’s side.

Devil World Flower attacked, the two small spirits Eight Notes had just summoned to his side attacked, and simultaneously, Deception attacked.

“He’s on the offensive! He’s going for it this time!” Pan Lin shouted. This time, it was clear. Mo Fan wasn’t hiding anymore, he wasn’t escaping, he was directly attacking his opponent, headstrong.

“He’s very good at judging the situation. If he left and then returned, it’s very likely that he’d be met with an even worse situation. This offensive is another style. Another style means another thing for the opponent to worry about. A playstyle that’s too focused and simple is easy to figure out.”

Mo Fan couldn’t hear what the commentator and guest commentator were talking about. He didn’t care about what these people thought because he knew that if he wanted to hear comments, he had someone to give him even better pointers right next to him.

Right now, he only wanted to do one thing: defeat his opponent!

Mo Fan had really changed.

In the game, he was focused on scrap picking. He would dart about the battlefield, be bathed in blood, but his attention was on the ground underfoot, searching for those valuable equipment and items. That was what he was passionate about obtaining. But now, his goal had changed. The opponent in front of him became what he coveted. Killing was never something in the foreground as a scrap picker, but now it was what he was fighting for.

However, Mo Fan was also the same in many ways.

While scrap picking, the only thing on his mind was equipment. All other obstacles he would dodge, avoid, that was what he did his best to achieve. Now, against a Summoner, his only target was the Summoner. Everything else, Devil World Flowers, Little Spirits, Big Spirits, all he had to do was avoid these obstacles.

Summoners seemed to counter Mo Fan’s ambush tactics, but a 1v1 fight against a Summoner really brought out Mo Fan’s talents. He had practised focusing on one target, with danger coming in from all sides during scrap picking, doing everything he could to scrap pick his target.

This was a battle, but because his opponent was a Summoner, it was also like scrap picking, and the target he was trying to scrap pick? Eight Notes’s health.

Everyone stared at this battle in shock.

With spirits harassing him, Mo Fan’s offensive wasn’t as one-sided as the previous one. Li Yuan’s Eight Notes would still have chances to cast summons, and with his wandering spirits coming back, he had more and more spirits. Yet, despite the growing number of spirits, Mo Fan had managed something. His Deception had managed to cling to Eight Notes. Perhaps Eight Notes could summon a few Little Spirits, but trying to run away from the center of the battle to focus on commanding his spirits? No way in hell. Even when he casted Teleportation upon coming off cooldown, Mo Fan had managed to interrupt it.

No one had seen someone fight against a Summoner like this: ignoring the summon creatures entirely and just going after the Summoner.

No one had seen someone execute this method so well either. Deception had been surrounded by quite a few summons already, but Deception still managed to dart between them, locked onto Eight Notes.

“Amazing! Absolutely amazing!” Pan Lin was yelling in shock. Meanwhile, Li Yibo had his eyes on the health of the two characters.

Mo Fan was doing well, but it was impossible for him to stay completely unharmed under the circumstances. The two characters’ health were both depleting at an even rate.

“If this continues…” Li Yibo seemed to see a certain future, a certain possibility. As the situation continued, this possibility became a reality.

Shlick! Deception’s ninjato buried itself in Eight Notes’s chest.

Whoosh! A chunk of ice slammed into Deception’s head.

The health of the two characters actually simultaneously struck zero.

Deception and Eight Notes, had perished together?

Chapter 1408 - Background

Glory!

That was when this word filled the screen.

Everyone was stunned. Glory, that word would only appear when announcing a victory, but wasn’t this match a tie? Glory shouldn’t have appeared then! Could it be…

Everyone scanned the field wildly and, as expected, amidst the light of Eight Note’s disappearing spirits, there stood Deception. Health, 0.7 percent.

He wasn’t dead yet?!

Everyone was shocked. It wasn’t until the broadcast replayed that moment in slow motion that everyone realized what had happened.

That’s right, Deception hadn’t died. In that last moment, he had completed a Shadow Clone Technique, and without their owner’s help, summon creatures couldn’t determine clones from real characters. So when Eight Note’s health hit zero, the Deception everyone had seen take a fatal blow was actually just Deception’s shadow clone.

This wasn’t a tie!

Happy’s home stadium supporters exploded. Though 0.7 percent was practically no different from a tie, victory and a tie were two different concepts. When everyone saw that Mo Fan had won and not tied, the morale in the stadium soared.

“Of course it’s not a tie.” Ye Xiu was smiling. There weren’t many people who had noticed that Deception hadn’t died, but Ye Xiu was doubtlessly one of them.

“He isn’t a killer, he’s a scrap picker,” Ye Xiu said.

That’s right!

Mo Fan wasn’t a killer. He didn’t have the mindset of a martyr. He was a scrap picker and, no matter when, his own life was the most important. A scrap picker, where only survival would make all his actions worthwhile.

“He’s practically made for the group arena,” Ye Xiu praised.

Everyone watched the close up of the victorious Deception. His expressionless face was brought up close for everyone’s scrutiny.

What sort of expression was the player behind this character wearing? Was he cheering? Jumping for joy? Everyone was curious, but they couldn’t tell right now. Since this wasn’t a tie, but Mo Fan’s victory, he had the right to continue, even with only 0.7 percent of his health left. Though some believed that there was no reason to continue with this much health left, even surrendering right now would be fine, Mo Fan didn’t do so.

Over at Blue Rain’s booth, Li Yuan had already gotten out.

In that moment, he had really thought it was a tie, giving him some degree of comfort. Though he hadn’t done excellently, he would have at least taken down someone. However, when Glory appeared on the screen, Li Yuan’s spirits plummeted.

He hadn’t died. It was the opponent’s victory.

This result was a huge blow to their morale.

Li Yuan walked off the stage in low spirits. Right now, the screen was filled with Deception’s most spectacular acts this battle, deepening his sense of defeat.

After he returned to the player bench, his teammates gazed at him, uncertain as to how to comfort him.

This result was rather comedic, but not a kind of comedic Blue Rain wanted to see.

“There’s no difference,” captain Yu Wenzhou spoke up then, “That much health isn’t a threat anymore. It’s the same as if he was dead.”

“Yes,” Li Yuan nodded. He knew that his captain hoped that he could look at this result logically, and try to not let it affect him too much emotionally.

“It’s all up to you,” Yu Wenzhou turned and spoke to another member of Blue Rain. It was the last player for them in the group arena, Spitfire Zheng Xuan.

“How stressful.” Zheng Xuan feigned wiping off sweat.

The predictions for this match had favored Blue Rain. No one had thought that Blue Rain would be in such a condition in just the first group arena.

Happy had only used two players to take down four of Blue Rain’s. If Blue Rain wanted to win, then they could only hope for Zheng Xuan to defeat three of Happy’s players. This clearly wasn’t very realistic. Being the group anchor wasn’t easy. For their opponents, they could see the match as an individual competition, because there wouldn’t be anymore opponents to defeat afterwards. So, against their opponent’s group anchor, they could fight it like an individual competition. They could be more daring, more direct. Meanwhile, the group anchor wouldn’t have the same privilege. They couldn’t be as daring, as free as they wanted. They had no one to clean up after them. They had to carefully preserve their health, doing their best against all the opposing team’s remaining characters.

Yu Wenzhou wouldn’t place such unrealistic expectations on his teammate’s shoulders, that was really giving them stress. Currently, they could pretty much ignore Mo Fan’s existence. After that, if Zheng Xuan could get them a point, allowing them to enter the team competition two points behind, that was enough. Of course, if he managed to defeat two players, leaving them at only a one point disadvantage, then that would be even better. At that point, Zheng Xuan’s performance would be perfect in Yu Wenzhou’s eyes. He wouldn’t consider the possibility of a one versus three.

“I’m off then!” Zheng Xuan got up and straightened his clothes.

“Good luck!” Everyone wished him.

“If I can’t get us a point, then let me be struck by lightning!” Zheng Xuan solemnly swore.

Blue Rain’s members were stunned for a moment before they realized that Mo Fan was also a point for them. A point with only 0.7 percent of his health left.

Everyone rolled their eyes, ignoring his joke.

“What! This is a point even Huang Shao and Li Yuan didn’t manage to win!” Zheng Xuan bemoaned.

“Just get the hell out already!!” Huang Shaotian growled. His mood clearly wasn’t the best; after all, he had left the stage amidst mocking laughter.

“Just watch me!” Zheng Xuan sounded confident.

No one was worried for him. Even if Mo Fan had a thousand tricks up his sleeve, and all sorts of unexpected tactics, health was the foundation of everything. A mere 0.7 percent of health wasn’t enough to execute any tricks. Perhaps he had the ability to combo his opponent without taking damage, but those circumstances and his current 0.7 percent health would have the opponent taking very different choices of action.

Match start.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn’t even bother saying anything. Actually, in most people’s eyes, It would be more acceptable for Mo Fan to surrender and leave. Continuing with 0.7 percent of his health seemed like a rather cheap move.

Zheng Xuan’s Spitfire character was called Bullet Rain, equipped with the Silver rifle, Drift. He was one of Blue Rain’s core players and was pretty famous in the scene.

Zheng Xuan was a player who debuted in the fourth season, becoming a pro player alongside Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian.

That was a bright, star-filled season, bringing about the circle of top players now known as the Golden Generation. Zheng Xuan debuted in the same season as the Golden Generation, and from then on, his signature phrase became “how stressful.”

Zheng Xuan was very talented, but back then, there was already a Spitfire player that shone like the sun, so newbies had a hard time taking the spotlight.

There were no Battle Mages, Strikers, Spitfires or Berserkers among the Golden Generation. Was this because no rookies debuted with these classes in the fourth season? Of course not. It was because, at that time, these classes were all occupied by the group of players standing at the top of the top. New rookies shoving these Gods from their positions? Not even in their dreams.

Zheng Xuan grew up beside the Golden Generation. Perhaps, in another generation, he would draw much attention, but next to the Golden Generation, he was but a drop in the ocean. Just in his own team, there were two eye-catching teammates that outshone him, not just in Glory, but also in their personal characteristics. One couldn’t shut up, and the other had crippled hands.

Zheng Xuan was rather speechless. Considering how normal he was, he could only lament over how geniuses always had their quirks.

How stressful!

Day by day, he matured amidst such complaints and became a reliable helper to his two Golden Generation teammates.

Over the summer between seasons seven and eight, the top Spitfire player Zhang Jiale suddenly retired. Hundred Blossoms flailed, trying to find a successor for Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, and the first name they thought of was actually Blue Rain’s Zheng Xuan.

The two came in contact, but they hadn’t even said much before Zheng Xuan rejected the offer.

The reason?

He was used to being in Blue Rain. Being the team’s ace? How stressful…

That was the reason Zheng Xuan gave for rejecting Hundred Blossoms’ offer.

Perhaps he was a bit of a coward. That’s what Zheng Xuan thought, but really, he was already used to it. From the beginning of the fourth season, under the halo of the Golden Generation, the other player from the same season all seemed negligible. In Blue Rain, he had debuted with Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian, but all everyone saw was the two of them. He had stood by their side for so many years, but when people remembered him, and recalled when he debuted, they were always startled. Hey! He’s also a season four debutee, from the same batch as the Golden Generation!

At first, Zheng Xuan could only reply with a strained smile, but soon enough, he really did get used to it. Whenever Blue Rain did poorly, he would see captain Yu Wenzhou and ace Huang Shaotian get grilled by reporters, sitting in the spotlight, and he would think to himself that his position was quite the blessing.

In a team like Blue Rain, he had an important, but not crucial position. Not as good as whoever was above, but far out of reach to those below. Stability was a realm of life, too!

Zheng Xuan was very satisfied with this realm he was in. He was prepared to maintain this, all the way until the end of his career. To be honest, he had no regrets and would be happy to end it here. He even had a championship.

Thus, Zheng Xuan unavoidably had some problems with motivation, even in the playoffs. However, that didn’t mean he would be bullied by someone with only 0.7 percent of his health left. Mo Fan’s Deception once again launched a sneak attack and was killed as soon as acted by a head-on trade of health.

He won a certain victory, but Zheng Xuan still felt his excitement rise. It was still a point! He was pretty good at cheering himself on.

Then, Happy’s third player was fielded.

Su Mucheng, Dancing Rain.

“Golden Generation, huh… How stressful,” Zheng Xuan mumbled.

Chapter 1409 - How Stressful

Su Mucheng, Zheng Xuan.

They had debuted the same season, so even though one was a true member of the Golden Generation and the other was a forgotten character behind their dazzling light, the two weren’t strangers to each other.

So when the match began, Su Mucheng already knew the first thing that Zheng Xuan would say in the chat.

“How stressful!” She beat him to saying it.

“What are you doing!” Zheng Xuan was unhappy. How could she steal his line like that!

“I’m saying it for you!” Su Mucheng replied.

“Tsk, even my line has been stolen, how stressful!” Zheng Xuan still said it in the end.

“The greater stress is yet to come!” As Su Mucheng spoke, Dancing Rain charged forward.

No circling, no hiding. A direct, head-on charge.

“Of course!” Pan Lin and Li Yibo both shouted.

During the player change, the two of them had already discussed how Blue Rain only had one player left. At this time, Happy didn’t need to be too careful. Boldly taking this round and then carrying the surging morale into the team round was undoubtedly the best choice. Right now, it looked like that was exactly what Su Mucheng planned to do.

“It won’t be like Mo Fan though, will it?” Right after his exclamation of “of course,” Pan Lin suddenly thought of another worry. Last round, Mo Fan had also controlled his Deception to charge forward like this, but then as soon as he met his opponent, he slipped away.

“Uh… probably not?” When he heard this, Li Yibo also began to have doubt. Logically, Su Mucheng wasn’t some stranger, and they were quite clear on her style. But after joining Happy, she now seemed to be surrounded by a blurred, opaque aura. Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, these old faces had changed classes, so it made sense that they would bring some surprises. But this Su Mucheng… Her class hadn’t changed, her style hadn’t changed, her play seemed to directly follow from what it’d been at Excellent Era. So why did she also feel different from before?

“Hm, let’s keep watching,” Li Yibo said calmly. He didn’t dare to make any careless judgments.

This time, Zheng Xuan’s Spitfire Bullet Rain was the one sneaking around as soon as the match began.

“Zheng Xuan wants to play dirty?” Pan Lin said. Playing dirty was a style, a school of thought, a choice that existed to be made in a battle. As a pro player, you liked it or you didn’t, you liked to use it or you didn’t, but if you said you didn’t know how, then you wouldn’t be a professional. Zheng Xuan was an old player now in his seventh year. Of course he knew how to play dirty.

“He’s the group anchor, of course he’ll have to face this carefully,” said Li Yibo.

Zheng Xuan, this group anchor, still had three opponents ahead of him.

Su Mucheng was the first, but who would be next? The dirtiest player of all, Fang Rui? That girl who was like a tiger, Tang Rou? That chaotic Brawler player? Or their old senior from Blue Rain, Wei Chen?

Zheng Xuan didn’t know Wei Chen. It was Season 3 when he’d arrived at Blue Rain’s training camp, and by that time Wei Chen had already retired and left. Zheng Xuan had heard a few stories about this old senior, though. He’d discovered and recruited Huang Shaotian from the game, he was the original owner of Yu Wenzhou’s inherited Swoksaar… No part of Blue Rain’s origin story could be separated from his name. Even their Blue Brook Guild, in the box labeled “Founder,” was forever marked with his name: Swoksaar.

Yes, Swoksaar.

Wei Chen’s Swoksaar, not Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar.

And then this old senior, after leaving for seven years, suddenly returned to this battlefield.

In the beginning, he’d drawn a lot of attention, but his return wasn’t like Ye Xiu’s. Wei Chen was not the protagonist of the stage, and his appearances were pitifully infrequent. Gradually, the discussion around him faded away.

Only Blue Rain would continue to pay attention to their old captain, their old senior.

Would he go onstage?

Zheng Xuan thought, and then suddenly jolted back to the present.

Damnit, got distracted again!

In such a critical battle, Zheng Xuan had actually gotten so lost in thought that Bullet Rain had subconsciously walked forward quite a bit. Now that he realized, he hurriedly studied his surroundings.

“This guy… He started daydreaming again, didn’t he?” Huang Shaotian said, watching Zheng Xuan’s match. He was all too familiar with this guy.

“A lack of fighting spirit remains his biggest problem,” Yu Wenzhou sighed.

“Even throwing him into the anchor position couldn’t help him focus completely,” said Huang Shaotian.

“If only he had Yu Feng’s drive,” said Yu Wenzhou.

“But if that was the case… he would have left long ago, wouldn’t he?” Huang Shaotian said. Everyone at Blue Rain knew that Hundred Blossoms had tried to recruit Zheng Xuan, that one summer.

“Yes… There’s really nothing that can be done.” Yu Wenzhou was helpless.

“If only he could be averaged out with Yu Feng,” said Huang Shaotian.

“Then what? Our team would develop a Blood and Blossoms?” Yu Wenzhou said. Blood and Blossoms had left a deep impression on the players of the Golden Generation, because Season 3 and Season 4 was when that style had been at its peak. The Golden Generation had all gone through Blood and Blossoms as a rite of passage.

“Who knows!” said Huang Shaotian.

These sort of meaningless hypotheticals always led to melancholy.

Because Yu Feng was too vigorous, too ambitious, too driven, he left them.

Zheng Xuan was too passive, too lacking in fighting spirit, and so he stayed. Staying was good, but his lack of spirit became the biggest limit to his strength. Zheng Xuan had talent, but because he lacked spirit and initiative, his talent was unable to shine.

He should have been able to accomplish more.

This was what many people had said of Zheng Xuan, and this guy had heard it all, but it still wasn’t enough to motivate him. Even in the playoffs, even as the group anchor, his mind would still wander. And this was Blue Rain – if this had been a team like Tiny Herb, with strict requirements, Zheng Xuan probably would have already been kicked out the door.

Blue Rain was a strange team, one that could accommodate all kinds of strange players. Huang Shaotian, this talkative opportunist; Yu Wenzhou, this master tactician with a slow handspeed; Song Xiao, the Mister Clutch who could only shine in the playoffs; Lu Hanwen, this surging youngster who was already so bold at fourteen years old. And even the ones who had already left: Yu Feng, who wasn’t happy even with a championship, a perfectionist who would only be satisfied with a championship he’d won as the core player; Lin Feng, who’d gone to Wind Howl, an unorthodox battle Thief player. And Zheng Xuan, a competitive player who… lacked competitiveness.

Blue Rain was such a collection of unique players, and every player had found his place here.

People had thought about this before.

If Huang Shaotian didn’t chat and instead focused his handspeed entirely on his controls.

If Yu Wenzhou’s handspeed met the standard, or even surpassed it.

If Song Xiao could perform as excellently in the regular season as he did in the playoffs.

If Yu Feng hadn’t left in pursuit of his ambitions.

If Zheng Xuan was a player with fighting spirit, who always put his full effort into everything.

How powerful would such a Blue Rain be?

Blue Rain was just this kind of team, filled with defective beauty. But on the professional stage, they would resolutely advance just like any other.

Right now, their lethargic Zheng Xuan was their critical group arena anchor. Awaiting him were three players, which could include two All-Stars, or this season’s Best Rookie, so on and so forth.

The road ahead was covered in thorns. Just like Zheng Xuan’s mantra, how stressful.

But even though he said this, when faced with this kind of pressure, he would still advance forward. He lacked fighting spirit, but he was still working himself up to fight.

Bullet Rain circled around the flank. By the time it was his turn to come onstage, Blue Rain had already thoroughly investigated the ambush points on both ends of the map. Zheng Xuan played like this was his familiar home game map, swiftly finding a suitable position from which to launch a sneak attack.

He gradually heard the sound of footsteps. Dancing Rain was beginning to approach.

And he thought about how after winning this round, there was another, and after winning that one, there would still be one more…

What a headache!

Zheng Xuan gritted his teeth.

“How stressful!” he said once more, and Bullet Rain began to attack!

“This is really so stressful!”

When Zheng Xuan said his mantra for the last time, his Bullet Rain had already fallen. The opponent he was facing was no longer Su Mucheng and her Dancing Rain, but Fang Rui and his Boundless Sea.

Zheng Xuan won one battle.

Putting in his full effort, he defeated Su Mucheng.

But after that, he was ultimately unable to defeat Fang Rui.

The group arena ended with Happy in the lead, 5-3. They were entering the team round with a two-point lead.

“1v2 really is my limit. There was just no way to go on.” After Zheng Xuan came offstage, he spread his hands helplessly and said this to his teammates.

“1v2…” Huang Shaotian’s mouth twitched. “You have the nerve to count Deception as one of your kills too?”

“It’s not me counting it, it’s the rules,” said Zheng Xuan, righteous.

“Alright, this kind of outcome isn’t entirely unacceptable,” Yu Wenzhou said calmly.

In the team competition, there wasn’t much difference between fighting until one person remained and fighting until two people remained. Normally, after both sides used up their sixth player, the side who next achieved the advantage of numbers would obtain the final victory in one swoop of determination. In the team competition, it was most common for there to be three or four players remaining at the end. Even battles with five players remaining were more common than those with only two. These were all conclusions drawn by experts analyzing the data gathered after the new playoffs format had been released.

But because this was now the established competition format, one thing that had to be considered was whether the opponent, with a two-point advantage, would use a playstyle that fully utilized this advantage.

This sort of strategic thinking had never been seen before. After the playoffs matches of last season, as of now, there were still no examples of this. Everyone could rely on experience and speculation.

And the current playoffs system gave a longer break between the group arena and the team competition. It seemed that this was to give the teams more time to strategize for the team battle, given the results of the group arena.

What was Happy going to do?

Yu Wenzhou looked over at Team Happy. Because they’d done well in the group arena, they appeared to be in high spirits.

Chapter 1410 - Swinging Balance

In the new playoffs format, the outcome of the group arena would cause the subsequent team round to be played differently. This was something particularly tricky about this new format. Both the losers and the winners of the group arena should think of ways to use this point advantage in the team round.

After working through all the emotions brought about by the group arena, both sides began anxiously preparing and making arrangements.

“Happy currently has a two-point lead. They’re doing much better than people expected.” Pan Lin and Li Yibo were also using this intermission to summarize the current situation.

“Speaking of which, Happy originally had the chance to win an even greater lead. If Su Mucheng had taken down Zheng Xuan, then they would’ve had a three point lead. An advantage that large is fairly uncommon in the group arena of the new format,” said Li Yibo.

“Yes, but unfortunately Zheng Xuan narrowly managed to win that battle. Too bad for Su Mucheng,” said Pan Lin.

“Team Blue Rain has been pretty unlucky today overall, but Zheng Xuan’s victory managed to let them recover a bit,” said Li Yibo.

“Happy’s Mo Fan was the highlight of today’s team round!” Pan Lin praised. “He completed a 1v2, and one of his opponents was Huang Shaotian. Truly a beautiful performance.”

“Yes, Mo Fan’s performance exceeded everyone’s expectations. This season, Mo Fan hasn’t appeared in enough matches to really be considered main roster, but his performance in this group arena was that of a core player,” said Li Yibo.

“Exactly. Even now, you can see lots of gamers commenting about how shocked they are at Mo Fan’s performance! Right here, I just saw a post from someone on Weibo named Hooked Mulberry, who was naming Mo Fan “the Godslayer.” It looks like they’re connecting his victory just now over Huang Shaotian with the time he defeated Sun Xiang,” said Pan Lin.

“Haha, two victories over top Gods, for a rookie that’s extremely worthy of praise. But to use such a title, we’ll have to continue to watch Mo Fan’s performance!” Li Yibo laughed.

“Right,” Pan Lin nodded, and he continued to scroll through the Weibo discussion of this match on his computer.

“Oh, this…” Pan Lin hesitated.

“What is it?” Li Yibo leaned over to look.

“Zuo Chenrui’s post,” Pan Lin said.

“Oh? What’d he say?” Li Yibo was delighted. Zuo Chenrui was a famous name in the circle. Because he was so opinionated in his writing, his commentary was often unexpected. And this match involved Blue Rain, the team closest to his heart, losing the group arena so unexpectedly. This guy definitely couldn’t sit still!

“Zuo Chenrui gave that tree a hundred million points.” That was all Pan Lin said. With Zuo Chenrui’s personality, his commentary was definitely filled with bitterness and outrage toward Happy, but Pan Lin couldn’t read that kind of content in their show.

“Hahahaha!” Li Yibo laughed. He knew Zuo Chenrui, and could completely imagine the look on that guy’s face as he watched Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain lose 50% of his health to that cut-down tree. Li Yibo suddenly wished that they could have invited Zuo Chenrui as a guest commentator for this match. That one exciting moment would make sharing this broadcast with another commentator completely worth it.

The two of them continued to look through the comments made by fans online and discuss the current situation, until at last, the team round was about to begin. The participating players on each side were summoned by the referee and began to walk onstage.

Team Blue Rain: Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian, Lu Hanwen, Zheng Xuan, and Xu Jingxi as the starting roster, with Song Xiao as sixth player.

Team Happy: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, and An Wenyi as starting roster, with sixth player Wei Chen.

“Ah! Happy’s sending Wei Chen onstage!” Pan Lin was surprised.

Wei Chen had history with Blue Rain, but because this history was so long ago, and because Wei Chen hadn’t had a very strong presence this season, there wasn’t much speculation or hype around this topic. And the playoffs wasn’t a place to arrange a roster for the sake of hype, anyway. The fact that Happy had chosen to send Wei Chen up now, regardless, was surprising to many people.

How useful could Wei Chen possibly be? This was an issue with a very large question mark. From his current abilities that could be seen from his scarce onstage appearances this season, it was hard to call him high-level. And his history with Blue Rain was so long ago, so in terms of knowing the enemy, he probably wouldn’t be any better than Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui, who had fought against Blue Rain for many years now. So why had Happy arranged for Wei Chen to go onstage this match? No one could guess.

On Blue Rain’s side, they were fairly calm.

Happy was a new team, and the greatest characteristic of a new team was that their strength developed with each battle they fought. On the other hand, teams like Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, Tyranny were all very mature and stable. They weren’t like new teams, who might change from day to day. Only a team that had just been created would be continuously changing and experimenting.

Happy had played through the entire regular season with this kind of rhythm, so many people might not have even noticed this point.

“Not having a mature style is usually the biggest weakness of a new team, but… Happy has turned this into their greatest strength.” This was Yu Wenzhou’s judgment of the team, prior to this match.

Because they weren’t mature, because they were always changing and experimenting, Happy became entirely unpredictable.

This was normally something that a mature team would work hard to try and avoid, but for a new team that didn’t have enough time to solve this kind of problem, they might as well just make the problem bigger.

Yu Wenzhou’s view was supported by data. From the research that they’d requested Blue Rain’s R&D to do, it was clear to see Happy’s rotating changes. As the team’s new players grew, Happy’s rotation of its players only increased, all the way until the end of the season, when even Wei Chen and Luo Ji joined the rotation as well.

This wasn’t an unexpected decision. From the statistics they’d gathered, these two players joining the rotation completely aligned with Happy’s trend of increasing variation. But because these two hadn’t joined until the very end, they had too much blank space at the beginning and relatively few appearances overall, so they seemed a little bit painful to the eyes.

Every one of Happy’s players was fully operational, all for the sake of the playoffs. Team Happy had been aiming for the playoffs since the very beginning.

Win the championships!

This wasn’t something Ye Xiu just casually said to mess with everyone. He had been completely sincere. From day one of the regular season, he had been planning, adjusting, training the whole team, all in pursuit of this goal.

Right now, Yu Wenzhou’s view of Happy was that no matter what roster they brought up, he wouldn’t be too surprised, because they had always been swinging and changing, unlike the mature and steady teams like Blue Rain. However, even has Happy was swinging, they manifested a sort of balance. They weren’t steady in an absolute sense, but they were in a relative sense.

Happy’s most fearsome person ultimately was still Ye Xiu. Not only was he sturdy in combat with a thirty-seven win streak, his control and deployment of the team as a whole was a completely easy and familiar task to him.

And right now…

“Just surrender now!” this person laughed as he shook Yu Wenzhou’s hand.

“Heh, it looks like that’s not necessary right now!” Yu Wenzhou smiled.

“Very soon it will be,” said Ye Xiu.

“You shut up!” Huang Shaotian interrupted.

“Remember to love the environment!” As Ye Xiu shook Huang Shaotian’s hand, his other hand patted the back of his hand in a friendly way.

“Oh fuck off!” Huang Shaotian shook his hand free. To the side, the referee could hardly bear to watch. Ye Xiu had really twisted the knife there!

The players walked past one by one, following the pre-match etiquette. They were also generally lined up in a fixed order; for example, the sixth person was generally lined up last. So, Wei Chen was the last person to walk in front of Yu Wenzhou.

“Captain Wei.” This was how Yu Wenzhou addressed him, when he shook his hand.

To the side, Huang Shaotian didn’t wait for him to come over, instead taking the initiative to approach.

“Captain Wei.” He used the same form of address, his tone completely respectful. Even Ye Xiu, who was also his senior and a pinnacle God who had already achieved the dazzling light of three consecutive championships before he’d even debuted, was someone he drove away with a “fuck off.”

Because this person in front of him now was different. If not for this person, Huang Shaotian might have treated Glory as no more than a frivolous pastime, where he’d run over to the game to cause a bit of trouble in his free time. He would have just continued living the life of an ordinary person, until he became so busy that even this pastime was forgotten, and Glory faded away from his life once and for all.

But he met Wei Chen.

It was this person who changed his attitude toward Glory. It was this person who sparked his interest in becoming a professional player. It was this person who ultimately brought him into Team Blue Rain. It was this person who helped him walk on his journey of growth.

And then he left, and Huang Shaotian earned a name for himself as a member of the Golden Generation, formally stepping into the professional circle. He took control of a character now called the Sword Sain, and charged through this battlefield. The whole world was open to him now, in a way that he never would have imagined, even in his wildest dreams.

And all of it was thanks to the person in front of him.

After he had left, they’d lost all contact. Huang Shaotian had wanted to meet him again, but he never imagined it would be like this. On the battlefield as opponents, and in the playoffs, where only one could survive. The bitterest of opponents.

But none of this could change Huang Shaotian’s feelings toward Wei Chen.

If he had to say which person in his life had the greatest influence upon him, his answer would only contain the name of this person.

“Surrender!” And then this was what he heard Wei Chen, this person who had the greatest influence on his life, this person whom he respected the most, say to him.

“How could we do that!” Yu Wenzhou smiled.

Huang Shaotian didn’t have too much of a reaction either, because it was entirely unsurprising for this person to say such a thing. Even though this was someone he held in great esteem, Wei Chen was indeed an extremely unscrupulous person.

“What a shame, I can hardly bear to beat you guys on the battlefield!” Wei Chen sighed.

“The same goes for us!” Yu Wenzhou said.

“But you’ve already beaten me,” said Wei Chen.

“It was just luck,” said Yu Wenzhou.

“It won’t happen this time,” said Wei Chen. “I’ll fight to my fullest.”

Chapter 1411 - Exploring The Map

The match began.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo went back to their usual program. After finding out what map the home team had chosen, they immediately searched up the relevant information and presented it to the viewers during the loading screen. For the unknowing audience members, the two commentators probably seemed omniscient, knowing the ins and outs of every map.

Map – Empty Sand Sea

The map was shaped like a rhombus. The two teams started on opposite sides of each other on the north and south ends of the map. The center of the map was an oasis. To the east of the oasis were ancient ruins, and a landscape of sand dunes were to the west of the oasis. The map had a variety of terrains, allowing for numerous viable tactics. It was a map that required adaptability.

While Pan Lin and Li Yibo hurried to finish their introductions, the two sides finished loading in. Each team had five players for a total of ten players on the north and south ends of the map.

The camera focused in on Team Happy. According to their experience in the regular season, Happy frequently played the sixth player switcharoo as soon as the match began to catch their opponents off guard. Happy had intentionally put Blue Rain’s old captain, Wei Chen, as their sixth player, as if he were their secret weapon. Even the program director wanted to know whether Wei Chen would be switched in immediately.

But Happy didn’t make any switches. After the five characters loaded into map, they immediately rushed out of the spawn point.

“Happy is looking very decisive. It seems like they already have a plan in mind! Blue Rain, on the other hand, appears to be a bit more hesitant,” Pan Lin said.

“Haha, it can’t really be said that they’re hesitant. Blue Rain has always been more reactive than proactive! This is their away game too,” Li Yibo said.

“Okay, Blue Rain is also on the move. They’re not charging straight towards the center, instead taking the left path. They should be heading towards the ancient ruins,” Pan Lin introduced.

The two teams played different openings. The home team went straight towards the center, while the away team took a more roundabout route. It’s almost like the roles have been reversed. The away team was usually unfamiliar with the map, so rashly trying to take advantage of the map can very easily go wrong. The away team often prefers a direct confrontation. Fighting in an open area was equivalent to erasing the opponent’s map advantage. How could the home team allow their opponents to do as they wished? In the individual competition and the group arena, perhaps there were people like Ye Xiu who picked simple maps and chose to fight it out in the open, but practically no home team did this during the team competition. It was easier to win if the map advantage was utilized well.

“Blue Rain isn’t moving very fast!” Pan Lin noticed that Blue Rain was moving towards the east quite slowly.

‘They seem to be studying the map,” Pan Lin commented on Blue Rain’s movements.

The match had just begun. It wasn’t like Happy could just suddenly descend upon them like gods, so Blue Rain’s formation was rather loose. There didn’t seem to be any strict tactical intent to it. Everyone looked to be moving freely. The camera cycled through the perspectives of each of Blue Rain’s players. It could clearly be seen that everyone was observing their surroundings. They were all moving in the same general direction, but the team was split into different zones. It was like they were in a race, each person in their own lane focused on their own task.

There was quite a bit of communication going on in Team Blue Rain’s chat, letting the viewers directly observe how Blue Rain was exploring the map.

“Blue Rain probably wants to establish an area that they’re familiar with and then lure Happy into fighting there to reduce Happy’s home field advantage,” Pan Lin said.

“Oh, isn’t this… what that team often does?” Pan Lin thought of something.

“Correct. Team Thunderclap frequently does this in their away games,” Li Yibo said.

“But it can’t be a random area, can it?” Pan Lin asked.

“Of course not, the home team obviously doesn’t want you to establish your own area, so figuring out which area to choose is a difficult decision!” Li Yibo said.

“Team Blue Rain seems to be speeding up,” Pan Lin suddenly discovered.

“It looks like they’re not satisfied with that area!” Li Yibo said.

There were messages in Team Blue Rain’s chat that stated this information, which was why Li Yibo was so confident in his judgement.

Dissatisfied with an area close to the spawn point, Team Blue Rain continued to push forward. And as time went on, the two sides were on the verge of encountering each other. As Blue Rain explored, they unknowingly went into a formation. It was only now did the viewers suddenly realize that the Team Blue Rain members were no longer as loosely scattered as before.

The change had gone unnoticed. From this, it could be seen just how fluid Team Blue Rain’s teamwork was.

The team continued along the northeast edge. The central oasis and the eastern ancient city ruins gradually came into view. Team Happy’s characters appeared in the oasis area.

“Try to stay under cover,” Yu Wenzhou said in the chat. Team Blue Rain quickly started moving stealthily. Flipping, turning, and climbing were frequently used. As they moved while staying hidden, they were still looking for opportunities to observe their opponents.

Blue Rain didn’t chase after Happy. Instead, they continued with their strategy and entered the ancient ruins.

Dilapidated walls covered the ancient ruins. There were all sorts of hiding places here.

“This will do,” Huang Shaotian looked around and then made a suggestion.

“Everyone, scan the area. Shaotian, watch that side,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“I might as well just say hi,” Huang Shaotian said.

“You’ve got a way to get close? If you’re going to go, Zheng Xuan, go with him!” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Fuck, that troublesome? Forget it!” Li Xuan immediately expressed that he didn’t feel like fighting.

“You can’t do it?” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Too stressful! But if you want me to go, I’ll go,” Zheng Xuan said.

Yu Wenzhou laughed. He knew Zheng Xuan was indicating that he had unconditional confidence in his captain. This guy was always like that. His fighting spirit was lacking, so he rarely took initiative. He basically needed someone to push him forward. For example, right now, he definitely wouldn’t volunteer like Huang Shaotian did, but if Yu Wenzhou gave him an order, he would try his hardest to complete it.

“Forget it, keep checking up on the terrain. Shaotian, watch that side. Try not to get discovered,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“I’m just afraid that they’ll give away a big opening, and I won’t be able to hold back,” Huang Shaotian rubbed his palms together as if it were some huge matter, when all he was doing was being on the lookout.

Happy’s chat didn’t have much content, while Blue Rain had quite a bit going on. The viewers had good understanding of their intentions. It was hard for the Happy fans not to worry. However, there was no way for them to tell this information to their players. They could only boo at the away game Blue Rain fans to vent.

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain temporarily separated from the team, leaving the ancient ruins. He continued the “flip, climb, roll” movements to approach Happy’s position, but before long, he saw Team Happy moving towards their location.

“They’re coming,” Huang Shaotian immediately typed, “I’ll stall them. You guys hurry up.”

“Got it,” the team replied.

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain stopped hiding and stood out in the open.

Boom boom boom!

Gunfire immediately headed his way.

“Fuck, Su Mucheng. You’re not even going to say hi?” Huang Shaotian called out.

He was on the edge of a Launcher’s range though, so the attacks didn’t pose any threat to him. Troubling Rain dodged the attacks easily.

“We didn’t even say hi and you’re already talking. If we said hi, wouldn’t you talk non-stop?” Ye Xiu replied. Team Happy suddenly sped up. Their slow Cleric was left behind as the others pounced towards him.

Huh?

Huang Shaotian’s eyes lit up. What a great opportunity! Those guys actually left their Cleric behind. Wouldn’t it be beautiful if he slipped past them and ambushed their Cleric?

Team Blue Rain had gone through this area, so Huang Shaotian had a grasp of it. He immediately had Troubling Rain dodge to the side and hide. To delay them, he could obviously just start fighting with Happy, but he would be stuck there too. The price for delaying them would be too high.

Delaying them had to be done from a strategic standpoint. He couldn’t let the opponents get a grasp on his intentions.

For example, like how Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain suddenly disappeared. Could Happy ignore him? Of course not. This opportunist might just suddenly bite at them when they let out an opening, and that little bite could be fatal too.

Huang Shaotian’s style was no secret. The opponents knew about it, so he would take advantage of it and have Happy divert more of their attention to his disappearance.

“Huang Shaotian, why’d you leave? Then, I won’t send you off!” Ye Xiu said in the public chat.

“Wait, I haven’t left yet! I’m following you guys!” Huang Shaotian said. He indeed wasn’t just having Troubling Rain sit there. Ye Xiu wasn’t so easy to deal with. If he didn’t pose a substantial threat, he wouldn’t be able to get his attention.

“Is that so? Then, you’d better follow us closely. It’d be bad if you got lost and then by the time you found us, your teammates were all dead!” Ye Xiu said.

“No way no way. I’ve played this map eight hundred times! I’m super familiar with it. I can close my eyes and still know the way. Do you know where I am right now? Hahaha!”

“Aren’t you right here?” Ye Xiu said as Lord Grim appeared in front of Troubling Rain.

“Eight hundred times? Super familiar?” Ye Xiu sent a sneering emoji.

Huang Shaotian knew the situation wasn’t looking good. The other side had seen through his intentions and even deduced his path. In that case, Ye Xiu definitely wasn’t here for a 1v1. He was planning on trapping him here!

But then again, that’s what I want!

If he didn’t leave such an opening, how could he lure Happy away? Huang Shaotian laughed coldly in his mind.

Chapter 1412 - Reverse Stalling

Blue Rain had just walked past this area, so Huang Shaotian had an understanding of it. This was why he intentionally had Troubling Rain make a sneak attack from this position. Happy could surround and attack him, but that would be exactly what he wanted. Huang Shaotian had chosen this location because he was confident that they could not hold him here.

However, he didn’t dare force his way through Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. If he got entangled by his unspecialized, he might truly be stuck.

As a result, when he saw Lord Grim appear in front of him and send a sneering emoji in the chat, Huang Shaotian quickly replied: “Oh no! I’ve been cut off by you!”

After saying these words, Troubling Rain turned around and ran away

“You think you can run?” Ye Xiu yelled. Lord Grim chased after him.

Everything was going according to plan. He just wasn’t sure what Happy’s other members would do though. This was a part of Huang Shaotian’s plans though. He needed to be in a truly dangerous situation. If his situation was too relaxed, it meant that trying to trap him would be without value. Why would the other side waste their time on him in that case?

Opportunity came hand in hand with danger. The greater the opportunity, the greater the danger. As the most famous opportunist in Glory, how could Huang Shaotian not know this?

Boom boom boom!

Artillery barrage suddenly came his way.

As soon as Huang Shaotian heard the noise, he dodged. He didn’t bother to see which direction the gunfire was coming from and had Troubling Rain roll twice. The explosions nearly scorched his back. The Void Sand Sea was covered in fine sand. When the missiles exploded, the fine sand splashed in all directions like water.

He dodged the attack with two rolls and also found Dancing Rain’s position.

Another one!

Huang Shaotian quietly imagined the positions of the two Happy characters and then made a decision.

Over here!

Troubling Rain switched directions and rushed towards the other end. From the time and the opposing character’s movement speed, he determined that this area should be an opening.

Huang Shaotian was experienced. At this moment, he was no longer bait. He truly needed to escape. If he made a mistake, he might really get caught by Happy and killed.

What he needed to respond to was the long-ranged pursuit from Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu’s highly mobile unspecialized. Huang Shaotian calculated in his head. But then at this moment, a message from Ye Xiu suddenly popped up: “You’re leaving? Then, I won’t send you off!”

What?

Huang Shaotian was surprised, but the sounds of gunfire could still be heard behind him. He could not stop. He could only keep moving as he turned.

From afar, Dancing Rain stood there with a cannon on her shoulders, her hair fluttering in the wind. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim didn’t give chase, but simply walked to Dancing Rain’s side.

Where was Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea?

Where was Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash?

Where was An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands?

Huang Shaotian checked where the locations from which they could surround him, but he didn’t see any signs of them.

Behind?

Impossible. The other side didn’t have the speed to intercept him from this direction.

So surrounding him was just a facade?

Then, where were Happy’s other three players? They couldn’t be fighting with their Blue Rain’s four players, could they? 3v4? Where’d they get that sort of confidence from? If that were his intention, then wouldn’t Ye Xiu have been saying too much? It would have given away his position?

Ye Xiu wouldn’t do that! This came from Huang Shaotian’s deep-rooted understanding of Ye Xiu. He had no time to slowly ponder over it. Huang Shaotian immediately made a decision from his intuition. So he’s letting me go freely? Fine, then I’ll go!

Huang Shaotian didn’t change Troubling Rain’s route and continued to rush out in this direction until he couldn’t see Lord Grim and Dancing Rain behind him. Then, he changed directions and picked a different route to come back.

“I knew you’d come back.” Not long afterwards, Lord Grim once again appeared, cutting in front of him.

A trap?

Huang Shaotian was extremely perceptive. He had been prepared for a trap. When he saw Lord Grim in front of him, he wasn’t thinking about facing just one opponent, but rather five!

When Troubling Rain made his first step, he had carefully considered his surroundings. He didn’t even blabber. He immediately had Troubling Rain choose a direction to rush out from.

This was the best direction to make a sudden break out from an encirclement from Happy.

“Don’t run! 1v1 me!” Ye Xiu called out.

“Who would believe you?” Huang Shaotian said, and had Troubling Rain run away.

But then, he didn’t come across any obstacles.

This isn’t right!

Even if this was the best direction to escape from, that didn’t mean he should be able to escape this easily. This meant one thing: there were no ambushes set up here. It really was just Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

Or could it be… that they intentionally didn’t ambush him to lure him back?

Huang Shaotian never tired of making these sort of guesses. Glory was never just about mechanics. Using your brain was also important. Someone who could instantly make these sorts of clear judgements was no less terrifying than someone with a crazy 500APM hand speed. Why was Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou a top Glory player despite his abysmal hand speed? Because despite his hand speed shortcoming, he was extremely intelligent and could instantly make correct and careful decisions.

If he went back, he might fall into their trap, but if he continued forward, he would achieve nothing.

So he went back. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain once again circled back, and tried to find another way to approach Happy and figure out their strategy.

“How’s it going?” At this moment, Yu Wenzhou asked about Huang Shaotian’s situation.

“There are three people who I haven’t seen any signs of,” Huang Shaotian knew that this match wasn’t just a game. It wasn’t the time to care about his reputation. He had yet to see Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, and An Wenyi. A 3v4 didn’t seem possible, but he should still remind the team to be careful. Blue Rain had no information on their whereabouts.

“Then, what’s the current situation?” Yu Wenzhou asked.

“I’m trying to find a way to investigate,” Huang Shaotian replied.

This area could already be considered as the border between Blue Rain’s spawn location in the north region and the ancient city ruins in the eastern region. The terrain of both sides could be seen. Traces of the ancient ruins were scattered around in a fairly sparse little forest. From Ye Xiu’s previous position, Huang Shaotian was able to guess his current movement direction. Troubling Rain traveled through the forest, checking his surroundings from time to time.

It looks like this time I need to have some actual contact with them.

Huang Shaotian thought to himself. His previous two actions had been on the cautious side because he hadn’t dared to be rash. As soon as he saw Ye Xiu, he ran away. As a result, he wasn’t able to figure out the opponent’s actual situation. After those two times, Huang Shaotian was starting to suspect that the other side was planning on surrounding him. He needed to verify this point. The most direct method was to place himself in an even more dangerous situation and trigger the opponent’s trap.

Huang Shaotian did his best to remember the details of his surroundings. These might be places which he could use to escape from a thorny situation.

Alright, that should be enough! Time to run into them!

Huang Shaotian had been visualizing the movements of Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim the entire time. He guessed that he should meet him around here unless Lord Grim had been chasing after Troubling Rain, which clearly wasn’t the case.

Over there!

A figure flashed. Huang Shaotian could tell that it was Lord Grim. He checked his surroundings and then had Troubling Rain quickly rush forward.

Triple Slash!

Troubling Rain moved diagonally, blue light flickering. With a flash, he reached Lord Grim.

Earthquake Sword!

Lord Grim immediately drew his sword from the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and attacks back. The two swords clashed, spinning wind around them. The ground of this little forest still had fine sand scattered about. The Earthquake Sword swept the sand up, forming exquisite ripples.

Huang Shaotian didn’t have the time to appreciate the beauty. He had forcefully cancelled his Triple Slash. With a stride, he blocked Lord Grim’s path and swung his sword with a Sword Draw.

Dong!

Lord Grim lifted his sword in front of him and blocked the attack using Guard.

Huang Shaotian didn’t hastily follow up.

He wasn’t here to win. His goal was to figure out Happy’s strategy. When he had blocked Lord Grim, he had been paying attention to his surroundings. Were Happy’s other characters rushing out to surround him?

No!

Even Su Mucheng, who had been with Ye Xiu, was nowhere to be seen.

4v4?

Were they planning on attacking the rest of Blue Rain in the ancient ruins?

Ignoring how Happy had figured out Blue Rain’s location, Huang Shaotian was about to remind his team, when Ye Xiu said: “You’re not running away this time?”

Have they surrounded me?

Huang Shaotian subconsciously looked to the left and right.

Bastard! Another bluff!

Huang Shaotian cursed inwardly and immediately messaged his teammates: “Happy might be coming over. Careful.”

On this side, Ye Xiu continued: “What are you looking around for? Did you think you’ve been surrounded? You’re too arrogant. You think we need to surround you to finish you off? Aren’t I alone enough?”

BOX-1?

Huang Shaotian thought to himself, but immediately disregarded it.

BOX-1 wasn’t suitable against Blue Rain because their Blue Rain’s ace player, Huang Shaotian, was different from other core players.

BOX-1’s intentions was to drag an important opponent away from the rest of the team. However, Huang Shaotian was already away from his team. Wasn’t trying to drag him away pointless?

On the contrary, if Ye Xiu was held onto by Huang Shaotian, that would be more harmful to Happy, no?

In a 4v4, Blue Rain wouldn’t lose to just anyone because they were too used to having one less Huang Shaotian in a fight. They would often be defending against five as four. A pure 4v4 would be even easier.

But how could Ye Xiu not understood such obvious logic?

What was Happy trying to do? Huang Shaotian discovered that his investigation was a complete failure.

Wait?

Complete failure?

Huang Shaotian suddenly noticed. Happy is stalling us! By stalling me, they’re giving away their movements.

Yes, that’s it! Huang Shaotian felt gloomy. He had been trying to stall the enemy, but in the end, it was the enemy who had stalled him.

Chapter 1413 - Pursuit

Huang Shaotian didn’t know whether to laugh or cry when he discovered the truth.

As it turned out, the whole situation had been very straightforward. He tried to stall Happy, but Happy obviously wasn’t going to let him. Happy ended up stalling him and prevented him from scouting.

This was just a regular action-reaction. Maybe there was an encirclement before, but not now. Happy definitely had their own strategy, but this strategy wasn’t tailored against Huang Shaotian; rather, they needed to hide it from him. Now, Happy has succeeded. Huang Shaotian did not manage to gain a single shred of information on Happy’s movement. His scouting resulted in complete failure.

“Keep your eyes peeled for Happy’s movements,” Huang Shaotian could only remind his teammates like this. Even though Happy’s Ye Xiu didn’t seem like a big threat now, if they dared to make this kind of arrangement, there must be a reason behind it.

“How about you?” The other side asked.

“I’m being annoyed by a fly,” replied Huang Shaotian.

Bang!

In the time it took him to send that message, Lord Grim’s attack arrived yet again. The Battle Mage’s Sky Strike came flying; the spear travelled in a graceful diagonal arc. If this was in the PvE portions of the game, Ye Xiu would never miss this strike. But Huang Shaotian wasn’t at the same level as a mob’s AI. The sword Ice Rain was propped accurately in the path of the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, and the two weapons clashed. The two both carried the air of elite pro players and smoothly transitioned into a backwards leap.

The distance between them widened. Again!

Collapsing Mountain!

Troubling Rain had only taken a small, half-step backwards when he immediately struck again with his sword.

However, Ye Xiu’s awareness and control didn’t lose out to Huang Shaotian’s. Lord Grim’s backward leap also consisted of a small half-step. As the Collapsing Mountain bore down on him, Lord Grim rolled to the side. Huang Shaotian wanted to forcefully change the sword’s attack angle, but he saw that Lord Grim has directly rolled out of range of what he could reach even if he altered his attack direction.

Ye Xiu wasn’t Mo Fan, after all. The two had an understanding of each other. Ye Xiu’s dodge even accounted for any variations that Huang Shaotian could produce.

Mid-roll and at half-crouch, Lord Grim pointed his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, which was already raised with the tip pointed outwards. The dark, hollow muzzle of the gun flashed with light, accompanied by the sound of a gunshot and a flying bullet.

Bang!

The bullet had hit a hard object, and sparks flew everywhere

Ice Rain was vibrating and ringing from the impact.

The whole stadium was in uproar. He blocked a shot from that distance? What kind of insane reaction and control was that?

“Not bad with your luck!” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s called skill!” Huang Shaotian retorted. Truthfully, he knew that previous block was quite fortuitous.

“Then what about this?”

Boom boom boom!

Anti-Tank Missiles. Three artillery shells shot out, one after the other.

The explosions dealt damage in an area. You would receive a faceful of ashes even if you blocked it. Thus, Huang Shaotian chose not to block, but instead had Troubling Rain directly use Formless Phantom Blade.

Intertwining swordlight instantly flickered out, followed by three flaming flashes. The Anti-Tank Missiles were unexpectedly hacked to pieces by Huang Shaotian’s use of a high-level skill. Even though there would be some splash damage, it would not hinder his advance. The swordlight was not impeded in the slightest by the explosions and had already criss-crossed towards Lord Grim.

Swish!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella instantly opened up. Ye Xiu had no way to dodge the countless strikes of this high-level skill, so he could only defend. The Umbrella’s shield form was light and had low resistance to knockback. Under the hurricane-like effects of Formless Phantom Blade, Lord Grim slid backwards, carving out two grooves in the sand with his feet.

For the final strike of Formless Phantom Blade, all the swordlight gathered into a bundle and struck out. Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s canopy looked like it was about to fold in on itself. This hit that had a powerful knock-up effect was transformed into backwards momentum by the shield’s resistance. Lord Grim looked like he was surfing on the sand. His two feet continued to send sand flying, as he rapidly slid backwards.

Formless Phantom Blade had long ending lag, so unfortunately Huang Shaotian couldn’t follow up and immediately pursue his target. By the time Troubling Rain could perform an action again, Lord Grim was also pretty much done sliding. The Umbrella’s canopy closed and bullets swept out from Gatling Gun.

Huang Shaotian spotted a half-wall next to him and immediately rolled behind it to take cover. The bullets sent rocky fragments flying wildly as they struck the wall. Huang Shaotian listened carefully to the rhythm of the bullets hitting the wall. If it sped up, that meant Lord Grim was getting closer. But right now, it sounded like the time between each shot hitting the wall was increasing. That meant Ye Xiu was probably controlling Lord Grim to retreat.

Charge!

Troubling Rain immediately jumped out from behind the wall. As expected, he saw Lord Grim retreating while shooting. When he saw Troubling Rain shoot out from his cover, he hastily adjusted his muzzle towards him. But Huang Shaotian didn’t stop controlling his character, who swiftly rushed forth, and left a string of bullets behind him.

Triple Slash!

BladeMasters’ most commonly used movement skill was used once again.

One, two, three slashes!

Three slashes, three changes in direction. Troubling Rain cut a beautiful arc and managed to arrive next to Lord Grim while dodging all his shots.

“Beautiful!” Even Ye Xiu praised him. Then, Lord Grim threw out a grenade while Troubling Rain performed the third slash of Triple Slash. The grenade grazed past the sword light, while Huang Shaotian rushed forward…

Boom!

The explosion completely engulfed the top half of Troubling Rain’s body.

However, grenades were a low-level Spitfire skill, and the knockback was mediocre. The explosion could only slow Troubling Rain down by a fraction as he moved forward with three sword slashes. Even though half of Troubling Rain’s body was still covered in dying flames and ashes, he still smartly completed the beautiful arced trajectory of his Triple Slash.

Just looking at damage alone, this grenade couldn’t even come close to the damage that Troubling Rain dealt by piling slashes onto the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s shield from Formless Phantom Blade. But comparing the visual effects of both attacks, Troubling Rain looked much worse. Anyone would say that Huang Shaotian would be feeling more frustrated in this situation.

However, Huang Shaotian did not have this third person view, so he was still upbeat. He was content when he saw that he had not received much damage and that his Triple Slash had not been interrupted. He didn’t care that the top half of his body might still be on fire, while Ice Rain slashed out again.

Lunge!

Troubling Rain slid forward one step, and two sword lights rapidly shot out.

Pop pop!

Their two swords crossed again, but Huang Shaotian immediately knew that something was wrong. Lord Grim was far too stiff, and the health drop after taking the hit was also off.

It was a shadow clone.

Huang Shaotian realized instantly. He quickly scanned around, and saw that Lord Grim was already a few units away. He was moving, while periodically looking back to check on Troubling Rain.

He really wanted to get away!

Huang Shaotian had Troubling Rain follow, while contemplating calculatively.

Lord Grin was charging towards the ancient ruins. Was he preparing to rendezvous with his team? Did that mean that whatever set up Happy had prepared was already in place?

“Found anything odd?” Huang Shaotian quickly asked.

“Nothing,” Yu Wenzhou replied.

“Ye Xiu is coming from my direction,” Huang Shaotian said.

“Oh? How’d the fight go?” Yu Wenzhou continued to reply. It seemed that side didn’t see any action, otherwise Yu Wenzhou would not have time to spare for typing.

“Unfortunately, I couldn’t discover what high-level skills he’s attached to his umbrella,” Huang Shaotian said.

His fight with Ye Xiu still had this kind of intention. In the group arena, Yu Xiu’s Lord Grim had only displayed gun form non-basic skills such as Laser Cannon. Blue Rain had no idea what else he was hiding, which was disadvantageous to them in the team competition. Huang Shaotian wanted to bait some high level skills out from the Umbrella if he could, given the rare opportunity of meeting one on one in the team competition. In the end, he didn’t know whether Ye Xiu held the skills back on purpose, but what mattered was that this exchange was worthless.

“Which area are you in now?” Huang Shaotian asked.

“The region at 89, 157,” Yu Wenzhou replied.

“Roger. I’ll try and herd Ye Xiu over. You guys get ready,” Huang Shaotian said.

“Be careful of the rest of Happy.”

“Will do.”

After completing this conversation, Huang Shaotian quickly switched to the global chat.

“Where do you think you’re going!” he yelled out. However, Huang Shaotian would not have an advantage if he really wanted to chase like this. Huang Shaotian talked big, but Ye Xiu had seemingly decided not to fight with him any longer. After some movement skills such as Shining Cut and Colliding Stab had been used, he turned a corner and vanished without a trace.

Fuck me! So direct?

Huang Shaotian was a bit confused.

He knew that no class could compete with the unspecialized Lord Grim in movement options. But he also said he would herd Ye Xiu towards Yu Wenzhou, precisely because he didn’t expect Ye Xiu to escape from him so directly. Ye Xiu’s dirty playstyle was in his mind, and he was obviously trying to lure him into some kind of trap or ambush. Huang Shaotian planned to observe carefully while chasing, in an attempted to lure his opponent in instead.

Ye Xiu ended up simply ignoring him and running away.

“Target lost temporarily,” Huang Shaotian could only report the truth to his team.

“What?”

“That guy ran away. You guys be careful, maybe they’re preparing to attack now,” Huang Shaotian said.

“You too, maybe they’ll use you as an opening,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“If only!” Huang Shaotian came to scout and did not get the attention he wanted. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng scared him together, and then only Ye Xiu stayed. He wished that Happy would treat him to a more grand welcome!

Huang Shaotian moved towards the wall that Lord Grim had disappeared behind. Huang Shaotian quickly approached and then slowed down when he got closer, keeping a safe distance. Then, he darted forward while slashing out.

The sword slashed empty air. There was no one behind the wall. Ye Xiu only used the wall as cover, and was now nowhere to be seen.

But he couldn’t have gotten too far.

Huang Shaotian looked around and observed possible locations that Ye Xiu could have run off to. To avoid being discovered by a pursuer, Lord Grim could only have gone in one direction.

Charge forward, leave a safe gap. Change direction, dash forth, slash.

He still slashed air, but this time, he got a grand welcome!

Qi Bullet!

The attack came from Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea. That slash hit nothing because Boundless Sea had dodged out of the way and immediately counter-attacked. No one was better than this kind of dirty play than Fang Rui.

Chapter 1414 - Double-Edged Bait

Roll!

Troubling Rain rolled towards the left, dodging the sneaky Qi Bullet from Boundless Sea. In the split second that he rolled, the front, back, left, and right were all quickly swept over by Huang Shaotian as he quickly adjusted his camera angle.

He’d already traversed the terrain before, so he had already visualized possible locations for an ambush, so now, Huang Shaotian only needed to confirm where the enemy was, and where he could break through from.

Of course, informing his teammates of his circumstances was also of utmost importance.

“Encounter!”

In the short time it took to complete one roll, Huang Shaotian had accomplished many objectives. However, his opponent, Fang Rui, didn’t drop the matter so quickly. Spiral Qi Kill!

Fang Rui’s Qi Master was always in a vulgar-looking half-squat posture, so the angle of his attacks was very different from traditional Qi Masters. Many of his skills were used in an underhanded manner, or from low angles. This time, before Troubling Rain had the chance to get up from his roll, he saw Boundless Sea brandish his fists, surrounded by clouds of twisting Qi, and directly began to attack him.

Roll again!

Huang Shaotian didn’t have any other option, and could only have Troubling Rain roll once more to dodge the attack. At the same moment, he launched his own counterattack.

Sword Draw!

The sword light flew out in the middle of Troubling Rain’s roll. This technique was easy to perform in theory, but if a normal player were to try, the attack would probably end up slashing into the ground eight times out of ten.

The sword light chopped out.

In the end, what everyone saw was Boundless Sea suddenly flat on the floor, resulting in the sword light harmlessly flying over his head. Afterwards, he raised his butt and thrust his hands forwards. Surprisingly, resplendent Qi suddenly gathered on his palms, and in this way, a Flash Burst was sent out.

It was truly unsightly!

Team Blue Rain was very inclusive, and as such, had many bizarre players. Huang Shaotian was calm in the face of such bizarre sights, especially since he wasn’t a particularly tasteful character either. But when it came to this fighting posture of Fang Rui’s Qi Master, he still had some difficulty looking straight at it.

This kind of a posture appearing from a Qi Master was truly too unfitting. It was no wonder that Fang Rui had been quickly tossed aside in this season’s All-Star voting.

The transfer of Boundless Sea was already a painful scar, but to top it off, the transformation of the character was so hideous, making it even more painful to look at!

Whether it was those who enjoyed Fang Rui’s dirty playstyle, or those who had some attachment to the Qi Master Boundless Sea, when they saw this kind of a fighting style, they would tremble uncontrollably, unable to cast such a vote!

But still, no matter how unsightly it was, dealing with it was still extremely troublesome!

Because this fighting style violated all common sense, gauging Fang Rui’s attacks proved to be more difficult. For instance, when he had suddenly went prone on the floor and then suddenly cast a Flash Burst just now, such a move had never been used before by any Qi Master in the ten years of Glory’s history. How could one guard against such a move? Huang Shaotian completely relied on his extraordinary reaction speed and inputs, forcing Troubling Rain to roll one more time to dodge the attack.

In the few moments that these characters had exchanged blows, after the first time that Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain rolled to dodge an attack, he unexpectedly not had another chance to stand up, and was stuck rolling on the floor. This kind of rolling left and right was something that Fang Rui was very familiar with, but other people weren’t! Huang Shaotian was suddenly forced into a passive position, and on top of that, Fang Rui wasn’t the only person in the area. What about Ye Xiu? Su Mucheng? Qiao Yifan? Just now, he hadn’t seen a single one of them, but that didn’t mean that they weren’t hiding in one corner or another!

What about behind this rock?

As he frantically rolled to dodge Boundless Sea’s attack, Huang Shaotian spotted a huge rock that Troubling Rain had brushed past, and his heart tightened. With their omniscient point of view, the spectators had an even better understanding of what was going on. In the stadium, Happy’s fans were already brimming with anticipation for the next scene, and their cheers had already been prepared, but…

Sword’s Divine Judgement!

Unexpectedly, in the same instant that Troubling Rain brushed past the rock, Huang Shaotian used the Blade Master’s Awakening skill.

Schwing!

A sound like a sword leaving its sheath rang out, and sword qi flew out in a circle around him.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was indeed hiding behind the rock, but Huang Shaotian’s willingness to burn a powerful Awakening skill to protect against a counterattack was beyond most people’s expectations. Any attack would be interrupted by the stun from the sword qi of Sword’s Divine Judgement, so Ye Xiu had no choice but to raise the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, using the shield form to receive the stun effect from the skill.

Immediately afterwards, Troubling Rain rolled again, unexpectedly heading towards Lord Grim, who was behind the rock. With this change of direction, he had actually managed to temporarily shake off Boundless Sea, who had been chasing and attacking him the whole way. Huang Shaotian finally had Troubling Rain stand up and straighten himself, but the mountain pass that stood in his way was not easy to get past.

Falling Flower Palm!

In the same instant that the umbrella was closed, Lord Grim sent a Falling Flower Palm towards his opponent.

In front was Lord Grim, behind was Boundless Sea.

Falling Flower Palm had a long range and significant knockback. If he wanted to dodge, there was no time, and whether he parried or blocked, he couldn’t prevent being knocked back. In this moment, almost everyone felt that Huang Shaotian really had no options left, and in the end……

Immortal Guides the Way!

The Blade Master skill, Immortal Guides the Way, had a strong knockback effect, and if one were to compare, it was significantly stronger than Falling Flower Palm’s effect. But with the distance between the two characters now, and with Falling Flower Palm already being used, could Immortal Guides the Way be fast enough?

It could!

In that tiny window of opportunity, Troubling Rain unexpectedly succeeded in performing Immortal Guides the Way, something that was inconceivable to many people. Even if Huang Shaotian’s hand speed had exploded, there was still the restriction of the character’s attributes and the skill’s properties. At this moment, this move shouldn’t have been completed on time, right?

“Sword’s Divine Judgement.”

At the end of the day, Li Yibo’s insight was still much stronger than that of the majority of people.

The reason why Immortal Guides the Way was completed in time, was because of the Sword’s Divine Judgement before it.

Sword’s Divine Judgement didn’t actually rely on that circle of sword qi to deal damage. Instead, it was a transformation skill, enhancing the state of the Blade Master’s sword skills.

Under normal circumstances, no matter how fast the hand speed, Immortal Guides the Way wouldn’t have completed in time, but with the support of the state from Sword’s Divine Judgement, everything had changed.

“So that’s what it is!” Pan Lin’s response was a little slower, only reacting after Li Yibo had finished his explanation, and in that moment, he felt heartfelt admiration. Admiration for Li Yibo realizing what had happened before him, and even greater admiration for Huang Shaotian, who had made such a precise judgement in that instant.

But no matter how precise the judgement, it was no match for sheer numbers.

Immortal Guides the Way had broken Lord Grim’s Falling Flower Palm, but immediately afterwards, Huang Shaotian found that the position Troubling Rain was in unexpectedly had Phantom Ghost power pulsing, with faint blue snowflakes falling, it was an Ice Boundary!

Triple Slash!

There wasn’t time to consider the situation more, so Huang Shaotian immediately had Troubling Rain use Triple Slash. The enhancement from Sword’s Divine Judgement also had an effect on Triple Slash, making the sword light sharper and faster than normal. Troubling Rain immediately withdrew from that spot, and as expected, an Ice Boundary took form, creating falling snow within its range. It looked beautiful, but Huang Shaotian had absolutely no intentions of letting Troubling Rain get anywhere close to it.

The Phantom Demon had already made his move, but what about the others?

His camera angle spun quickly, and he saw Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea already charging towards him again, but he couldn’t see where Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was.

What a pain.

Huang Shaotian hesitated a little, wondering whether or not to ask his teammates to rescue him.

Those four had painstakingly surveyed the battlefield, picked an area, and then finished deploying over there. According to Huang Shaotian’s original plan, he wanted to make himself the bait, and lure Happy over to that area, engaging in a decisive battle there. But now, as the bait, it seemed as if he might not be able to escape the net that Happy had prepared for him.

Not being able to find Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash meant that Happy could hide away and keep placing Ghost Boundaries, and eventually, Troubling Rain would be tied down by one of them, trapping him in the area. At that time, if he were to call for help, it would be even more troublesome. In order to help him escape, his team would definitely suffer great losses.

But even if he were to call for help now, what good would it do?

If they were to leave the area where they had set up, Blue Rain’s earlier deployment would have been wasted. On top of that, Happy also had the appropriate arrangements in their area. Trapping Troubling Rain was likely meant to force Blue Rain to show themselves, engaging in a decisive battle on Happy’s terms.

The crux of this game was to see who could lead the other team into their own territory.

Huang Shaotian was the bait, but he was the bait for both teams.

Happy wanted to trap him, thus forcing Blue Rain to move to them to engage in a decisive battle, while Blue Rain was counting on Huang Shaotian to be able to escape, instead leading Happy towards the area in which they had set up.

He couldn’t call for help, if he did, they’d be walking right into Happy’s trap!

But even if Huang Shaotian didn’t call for help, someone else had already done it for him.

“Everyone come and help! Huang Shaotian is going to get killed!!!”

Windward Formation? Wei Chen!

Huang Shaotian saw the name of the person who had sent the message, and could only stare blankly.

Was Happy using this tactic again? Swapping out their sixth player when no one was looking, without any way for the opponents to figure out who their last player was.

Lord Grim, Boundless Sea, One Inch Ash, Windward Formation.

They knew for a fact that Happy had these four characters in the battlefield.

Who was the last one? Was it Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain, or An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands?

Common sense dictated that it couldn’t be the Cleric that was switched out, especially in the playoffs, where cautiousness was of the utmost importance.

But still, Happy couldn’t be predicted using common sense. What tactics did they not dare to use? On top of that, Happy’s Cleric had always been viewed as their weakest link, and they often used him as bait, designing traps to protect their Cleric while killing off their opponents.

Swapping out their Cleric was a tactic that they were well-accustomed to using. What protection could be better than throwing their Cleric to the safety of the sixth player’s seat?

What on earth was their lineup?

He couldn’t tell just by looking, so Huang Shaotian could only charge forth, using this to determine Happy’s true team composition.

As for the support zone, it wasn’t close by, meaning that they couldn’t change their lineup whenever they wanted. If he could determine that Happy didn’t have a healer, disrupting their formation and having the whole team engage in a decisive battle there was certainly an option.

“What’s the situation like?” At this time, Yu Wenzhou sent a message in Blue Rain’s team chat, probably in response to Wei Chen’s cry for help on his behalf.

“Get ready to attack,” Huang Shaotian said, relaying his coordinates. “They may not have a healer in their current lineup.”

“No healer, they really have guts!” Yu Wenzhou sighed emotionally. As he had anticipated, if Happy wanted to have any real achievements in the playoffs, they couldn’t play by the book. If they really had to face against a team head-on in an open field, Yu Wenzhou believed that Happy might not be able to win against any team that had made it into the playoffs.

Any of these team’s tactics and coordination would be far more mature than that of Team Happy.

So Happy had to be extraordinary, and only then could they achieve victory.

So, what’s your extraordinary move? Yu Wenzhou had constantly been thinking about this question.